[
	{
		"unique_id": "010101", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRjp48UyVx39wvP2Jm7UQ3YZpj+TXa99ZHjgVauCb+P6iZZ1KlWHhEhv4HfSqrP1t1UagatP4IGRY2IMeMt7wNXJ8uXk0DFoPcJNm8BR65cPffpZjDuiZpTPKPsuyGeSNFGwczCwAS82MX8EERRQUtpMW0Y89iwA9Q==", 
		"answer": "24e9b4T/0A3j+YJgcx3mhfL5dTqHVDFTQ9hsNrEBfEud+jWE3rLSaw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHB1B7/+4Q0WxD1hdz8ISvfBSJA9CjQErR1YzH3XKKCaOTs2oMxNEiMnRtv833DreXy7hMbh60by5yWZCsQdstIx8aMxer6wX9Vc9JL2oN96o4Nc/gAzTOpNMbeJ+tiz3qFZ1H4Ynm8AnZ1nSPFynNQ6Jez8GeeVckjgDw8ko55reszMcee17HT4UP4rwiG1XrT5EXGkIUbjc3/iUZ12DBpWg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Regulating Act of 1773", 
		"option_b": "Pitt’s India Act of 1784", 
		"option_c": "Charter Act of 1813", 
		"option_d": "Charter Act of 1853", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010102", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV17RzfztIW7CQ0MStz+MVOMlKCKwFKrDfOa+3Z90Z1mHiRt09DbArLew41sKz41a+prfWSwHd4ov69+Ex+X53S4DCB78EjqUrk047oTjUoUrvw==", 
		"answer": "25yse9Hy0g3j4Yw0WxvhhfzsdWqQAG0crnqRUap1fDHhW6PbLMW75P7JtE+Ed1XaEuPq6UA=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ2Rj444AyEj/x0b3wMyuBWzFC43qNVqZwMGXrUefDbfn3355lLlmazVR9smLOpuXV9kAbz4FV7YeeMAEMc5tuxsnJ1ve3xTFCPMtJn5Jx7ZsTPPZPyCThNMDJIfB9yGGSKkz+YHm0EDB9miXZyn0WuJap8CuiFNszzRw8n5Rs/8koNcGama2d/ESsn0QP2XMwozvfA+KVoTyhPIr3", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Its legislative powers", 
		"option_b": "Its territorial possessions", 
		"option_c": "Its activities as a commercial body", 
		"option_d": "Its control over tea trade", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010103", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRjp48UpXArgyvnqNm7UQ2NRsHqTU7F1ZHSjWKLFZ/7yyIN4MVnJjlRu/HXPr+X7+VwYgeha+s6LeCdDV4VrwdGHl6zUwX9VIcdI08Be4Z0Wb/hB2DS7cZT4L+tgzWeMeAdvNdWaXzBZXcmZdtUZwlSL", 
		"answer": "25awaYPn1Auq1oY0EhH0haynYDiS+IL8eTv+MOPqbo7eR2jQmQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ2Rj444AyEj/x0b3wMyuBWzdC43qQRqJ2fHjwXKLGLuy+2pJhJk6ImV47/nPBqrb89kcGma0b6oGKfiEKcscvw96GwOq3xWIBJ85B2ql84JMecrQI7zijYMbaLLcu4muHLlb8Zi20EnU0tz7DhH9fpM/79z77R98nwQczgo526ogoNNLf1a2U4V60hxKLyn7RSbNgUVGBsM29/0qKpcI+oMOOpTvU+ue5lf6T5NYOIi9dqYNtbVSu2o8M9i8qUMTze1JI/vHeYl3hYugZfshck0p+LKMGV5bU8Lg=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Charter Act of 1853", 
		"option_b": "Charter Act of 1793", 
		"option_c": "Charter Act of 1813", 
		"option_d": "Charter Act of 1833", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010104", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV17i1/TyNHnJQ3IEsW+MQaY0f3ejQK/HLszzzJl1LlKOzXp45jbJpeWhoAtew+ha5Z2QMCkNcZxhiNGal/D/wTFgMNIElYYy158LaPhFwTijYIuZcXMbTdDQ3AY121/bXsXTZg==", 
		"answer": "24G3KIP20g3j8ZxgRhb3hfn6M27TF3FRrHnDRqtxMEPmU7LOb/n3x5AxBl+dzVR9sieR9Pay2WhgseKsP8UntWWVPt1ckQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHS3Bzk84wuVV7Txum/Om2QUjVJ8j+CW65xdDH3W+fQa+7qwJFoZ0iBiBto+nnUt6b/+loBiLsb5ojfZCoGPrlqz8WF1vD+ynYBEsVQ2o90pMtIK6cAziTtedXQKfBpjm+NIkv0ajyzEGM0lT/SynlOrY6r4S60Wsl30hA+l5N96YgoM5eL0a3T4liqjxWG1XiFQbJqUVuf9dqg7gO7r5Q9p8OCo3/88fr8iPnfsN8FZkhGt4M/UE6sha0E/WobXt2mfFDlcv8tnpD4CMVkNmkl469Z", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "To extend the trade monopoly of the Company", 
		"option_b": "To establish the Supreme Court", 
		"option_c": "To introduce a system of open competition", 
		"option_d": "To rectify the defects of the Regulating Act of 1773", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010105", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRjp48UlXw790vjtMG+QF2oU412MU7FwMH7lFITNYPnsxpsxM1PJnk5r92TQqrb1t1IBi+hf4JyaczZDboRjwcSA1OX7hHBHNcdNiJMy7ZRfXuZJ2DS+fJTLL+19y32TLkr+dHm0CjBdmjXfiyMUGpd6IfOv5bOON0BxztqEkw==", 
		"answer": "24WxfIWKwlnD+YEpU17Txum/Om2QUjVJ9z0ty25FhJimlc/PqtZhtKuR", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHD2A3+jpZgexD2zPy/FGjEQ20X4y7UCvc0dXzzW7DHfOj6iYN5Ihyrglpp9jbJpeXT+F0bnadXqZqQMC8CcIpozZCZ2Oj+0HhCMsoEm4Z05ZMNb7gAwyuoZsfeJfdgyS6DLlP5a3m8CnQ0mTjag2hXupr78iitUcg5zRA8gsd3/c0uPcOW1qaAqEy2gkaQ2W2URqhhUVmYodqt+VDcqYx4ocWI8RDJ/eDwifCT4NEYcQ1BrI9wbUj8nqZJ0SQ8WMn293o5kD8mjz7iOV2XrCRZng==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Charter Act of 1793", 
		"option_b": "Charter Act of 1813", 
		"option_c": "Charter Act of 1833", 
		"option_d": "Pitt’s India Act of 1784", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010106", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhz48sU0Whuy1vT4O2LWCmEQrWvDVKZ1ZGTxUbSCYeu+3Z90Z26Mik5382LPraKw1lAbz6ddqd/IJ3FcQoVTxvHEl6TU1nRAJ89KncBzpL0QavFSwjK/OfPeLvt8z2LAKEOwRTawBnFtqD/0xzxzu5e69yuyR9I+zhJyl8dL+NguOdqamYuc/V+sxg+MnFiQRL5xBUCYicCLpgPckJA3vcSPuCbe8LTqn+rF8dAfcUhducZ8bFaslqYQuCwqXsX0eABC5+XEZBT5MimnIjIT3Yaj5HFqyYUnVHM9+hgGkoxaa9R61Zno/DQlMc5+HDy0sARPwdRoVxLWV7K1wGnq+WkxSXQDap0tsSw7uE+TLhRqkm7cXzhQgIVm+94N2hcjemZWmXiggz2ElmDPdYCs6pL5xev/sqtm8bd4a8ArswIVMhpxQzvU6Bf5sN4=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxRH48oBihNe0hfegvQArXU1qVizr0A==", 
		"explanation": "25T4YYKz2Bfp+JcyVx3mhf/6NmrFEGdRkXqER691ZHjqWqCCb+7qiZh3Zw3e2gg79nPVqqL+9kcKi+hP4YvfVy0Ve5lhx8LJ2OK35nRPNMdI2oFhpI4XebQ46zK7ccbVL+wj6WuOIlfxa3myAjBWkT/Ri3Av6IK18We4Rt821BA21oZ2re0kOdSKzaGF7Q2biROM33KdCLJiUVKWoNzo5kaRoocqpo2ZvnLa5+fwiezv/tYCb0hmt4M/ZVKuhLxJ6z87WYiTZwRO4+rfc3PoLi2xJgJd7srwllhm1IZpamgm5hpIwqtXcdR62J/3gDxwA8NIVTqp40dP1YZ5XAPWdri70X335RV/XG5rdZhiqiQxpAvcLlts2n+USWxUh5Rq/NwQhgxueGFU3Hnmwj7Ls3Cfbpbu7sDfiv3itPli5uMEKE2DIEjMV7ESLeKXcDM7iuqUALZOOoxuGSWmMtsrvDrxKZOSnzMYw80pLHKn9SSd0tn9K2C/853thtFkVLUVMtbA+ve5jFLkISryYX6cdNnxWhywTXn70ht2slgM3GEA+m3QAYt24SgJ3mq4TAR3lzX2bXK1hf5T7MKad4tx8PrhzTMegbR+jZT6lBgyQAW8hHFE8o2RD11B1BTGDMQRxR0rTKATFZLUsmKE1XfTSHkda8f4BuiX0Slb3+3lnSFyrdAMR4WMKQqbjMwpxVelCfg5LWnsvI/vOO9sNmoQ9JYxw/7htMWpZ/anOCUoahm2TPxcs7xFKBFvAw7TAjBHZbarUt0KSeUP0XrEgxVHSz9GAxrY861Ifxajvs3bZir5bKcZHBDvZr0RU8HuS1WPIfmsiBPGC6+dm17+XV1lXD+MNLkf7An3Opj6IVOQnH127YHqNBF/TZESPzP8Znj57aSMHQMocSUrL8pFdUPMCx8i1CrLIrlEgqoQcRY0COizFhAEkwFAjSqSAVYFuVgNH7eoVlYpP6wJYFgY2z65XeAeUhiKizMGh0Kd0DusKPxNMEAxaCSagQzJlZZvnr2D9oE4FCMSEen/Zd5hM0E7", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "All four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010107", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQn4+JMpQRf9y+6/Im7CBiIYrWuRXadhc3TnFKXbLt333YM2NBygg19y8zbnoLGw+FVP3v8DvdGjfh4NX8Yv7Nmaw+35w2RIIM5NlIcy5p8La/FFwn2ue9nWJextx2+MZ0T+Y3mtC3x9gDjVi3AWrpa19jOyW9Qk/BsQ28dd/tw9PtuWyqCa5kr4h0al022UWrNrAxm+sMCt+UKQ4I0+9eSDtTvayPra17j04t8FdgFcuMZdcVKonrsBuA03R82mZh9O//CQYlvjNDqsKzIT3Yaj9WZsx5YgU2509V9hjZVTcM58xNXDuTw1LcxmVTy842ZPypZ9RiuYSLOQ33+k7VQxbDokY8p5tCh1shudPFFzn2WIAz8Rk4l9+95ZlAZsa2oAlWWvgy2OwGaAboHm6JSjx8TdvSZHZ0ylO3n62IPU8lY=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25T4YYKz0hb45YAjRl7wwP7+IHjVQ1IYt2v6QeNdfnXqVefjbfm+xpExdgvR2Rt/+2XSqqv34loch61fqYyaZDUGe4Uv3NiMl+f4yXxEIcVNm4wy5ZQbPORPwDS5fdfaLL5o22CDM0z/aSr9C3Y0gDnTyl9ZpZO6+z6HWuY541U7hcd54dszfNSQy7qW61n4hAOB3W6CTf1wGVHZtM28q1Sds8IrvMqDuDTS9/X3jrjV/8xLdh9d/5R6YkizmbtTuCwxQ9ugJFJf+eGQQlvgMCmtPncOud/mxGZg0o07VGwntBZIwqpYZslylo/hrjdwOcJ4VSeypgRGzoZvS1eCfbC9kGvl7Fk6cTo/bY8txA8nqBuVO1w+imSPXylCh4lk8MNZnAojVGFElXeZ2X+KjmHPb5bg5I74yajkqLwj0LEuPUiTPRz/WZsZd73NImlmiv6aHuZbOoliGWLyNdBu7yzpMpOZ2nkO39c0PXjrtCWPl9+1Gmq3o5P3l61lVL4GMNDM+9j3sVLDISr1Mj2SYsb9VwHjW275xwdquVgsxmE55mbRCcvBedfbU/uP1pyGHJVJvF8U", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "All four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010108", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0hHr+YIlQV72zPm/IWPVQ0EZom2XV7E0UXL3FKjELrymmMQxJU6Ag1w783TJtrGvy10zgYkWqc6+YzEGbJ9mxtfJ9fb+0HhSO4ZniI9l6t0MPOdP2ji/cd3cLup38mCiagWwRjWxC2d9mjaWqXREoZCv/Ca1FNc+0wY7mYl5/8E5L+uR+uXTqGS2khSN2G6SQbNjUViWts+kq1eduIMsvMKDjTz/ubTWiv3d+dAMIiFcu49+bRuohakN/WosXoiWehtf+PfYIVnoMiurJgAJ6omWEydH+P+B0mzwQIpU9xF2", 
		"answer": "25T0KLO/kTqq9oskEjqwwNsiClI665YbD0Io+R14+A==", 
		"explanation": "25T4YYKzxQv/8sUiVx3z0O76dSvzC2MDt3qREoJ3ZDHsUueTNrytiZZiNFmbmV5/smLOpuXj+EUKna1S7oCLaWIMeMt7wNXJ9fb+0HhSO4ZniI9l6toQavFSjCmlcZT4L/N+z2CZXlbMaS24FmJ9gD7Eg3lF6Iq1tQ61UNM2/BsOmKU45Nt8PduM1uiH+li9lUaA2XiQXa5hURTZnNro6k+Qr5U9sY2ZuTeb1/zrk+vH+d8FIgVbrJV2bFW9haEM62osXoi3Zx9OsfDfIX3jJCGiZwgS64v33nEp1pc7TWYn8V9JhMNTbMx60ZDwuTw5McoqATu/41RFyIRwWiuYSLObkGH3oFQzZnVrcZh4uW03pAydPUd72iu1WGxQgZRj8cIQhgFnPXtImTbMjTyKjCWoc4Xm+Y7xgObks/lq/OMOJ0WJNBzMWc0VaKPPNGIy3uiDCLUcPJEnByf0Ltog73nNKJONnzoCxdUkb3br5yXZgtj7MHay84bxi5RmEa0TOd/Wqc24ohzJbjehMXyKb8XzGRzxV3nr7wBZuTxlwTJQ/HDNDcl98C4Mi221CW1w0ibiY3CohbZZ7sKad4txx+ft2TdQlft2kIv42AR8SAL7mXdG8oeQQkxOw02WF8NH7QcqBbVBHZOdsnmekDb5RXgEfsC2FbqGxykIzeLiznV1rZ8ZW8yBPBzVysopiBa9Db1bR275oZXxffEQGGck+7xl2a2JuN2+Y/a2YCUje1q0VuFN+ptEbQY7BQPYRSlAbre+WZEHAe9JkmHCkkdLSHJZBFTVu6ceWBbqvtbJam+ear9cGhvjI7ILF47sXEbLMLG+wSTBRpyUnEm/HbM8btUkiq0BO6Z0k7Jf9nU=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A and D only", 
		"option_b": "A, C and D only", 
		"option_c": "A  and C only", 
		"option_d": "A, B, C and D", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010109", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhz48sU0WhuyzvjmdXvCDHQYsHaMXLA0f3ejQK/HLs72yIVlIk7JrFhvsnnA4/SopABQs6Zn56/SQycTf5lu3NmH0KT7wXZIIMpFjolk4doecvAAySWod8HPKehrjmiVKUbkbjazF0x6tnzzmWhXqo+y5i+yWt131B031qB3+80uMtiNlI+W5kiqhwrC033RYbNgGFWlu+3lq2aSpIs2so2ZuTeb1/v0ivnd6ZkYIgtdsot6cVi1lqRJ+SksWN69fBtO4tjeRRnELjyxKAoI+sLt0TRqz5QgUSkn8Q1Qi4BTIsN824jhqDskNsJkVTW1sQRpyZB1XhmFNgYpJipAOwMz86KxB4TYyrk=", 
		"answer": "25T0KLO/kTqq9oskEjqwwNsiClI665YbD0Io+R14+A==", 
		"explanation": "25T4YYKzxQv/8sUiVx3z0O76dUjYAnAFpm3Dc6BgMH7lFPaaPb6+xJZ1IhydhV471XnQprf++EFCqK1V7JyefGIMeMtNzd6O1ui3xWIBJ85B2qd98p8NcvtSgRqoetHJIfJSwGGGZ2z+YzC8RHF6kHHAj29CrYf7/Cn7XNM6gBQ+msd75N41MJee16zT5US0jxKDzmLRWLJzFEaK9fqg/lDQ4JYwsI2Msiab9+b8m+zW9JJLZAdA/5J3Zhu6nroa7GosWMWxJFJs/vLVc1rgJSa3ZwEbueLt0n1ohoooS2A6819Hl5debdJ6woGksyQ1LY1+HTb6pkpUzoZ5HwOTZq+xxGf26VQzNXs5YIstrCImsgqPO1F62mmFDDhZkcBJ7NkNnBdrPWZO3F/uhjaKwFmBQJ3Bq4nvxen8s7Yj5rEyLAGCMF/ZQ54ZJfPpMyd2z/mJBLBZN99zHyemGto4+Sv3L4TU0D9N8tYtLXb+tCuXlo3YOGGosoG5gdI2ALcFP8OF5c6wuU/LYDfoN3ivaNv7Tg3iXDzM2wslkBczzTMe53CVL4xx8D8Mkj6/TwRNnCPpbTy2l60c7YuYeoBx1u3v0ScDkeJ935fy0xQvSwWvhGlG8pSQWFld3hTQEd9H0AErTLEPAJ/D9y20h3/EQm8FP+f4BaGGgxhA36P9j3Zu/50PUYnOORffj8xm3B+0Qe1rUHHkp5Pqff0WHnds7bdjz62itsa3cPfkLXZqXR+wTONY55xeZhE3URzVDChKILSvQY5eTOFL1zXfmQNNVT9dDVPfx6YJXhDqvcHaayrdYr0QCxqiYqBFMs3sXXvBCf+KiDnaRr6Qhkj+S1YwS3qfJLMM8BT1OoXmZFO2nWxh/YHxOlQbRYADNTH6YGK8tuOMDUYudyllDYtUbgf8RRQtlX7gKPR3jKkZMBk+AannGl8bmxRdnDfTAhhHv0gHE+W6SFokIulHJVgQwDL1EOAPSQ7PiiNKj1KRyyzlOu5ZMF0qbWHTjUPkgtJPi7/5kIGXA9DnKf0P2owXaKJTQdr1EFYMm/39lvKgBWkrFGRjIerBW/GRuUG2K8bwq8Ka0llZzP4AM1M/ZTuSyZbNsEJkIeVbfWVZqTMfo9iSSg+5maVY31V7REygtWntUicpsxhhfdPqZNmcOY6m81VMBSvVRMB/lsB2+WztJp/QaAkwR3cnhALQdNfJxiGQOOy79KUMRTuq1ovfQJgtzUttjtO0gx0Y+Gg1jmj2DnvKduLpqApbYnV2X6aQHkheg1cjlSmozUftMM+lgeYGnrVPmLYc7BzytihihlGCD0zBcTP52/qbtHLPsUlhxqwjX2+1Un8t3Qk2UvEl5mouQSMlCbJgvaLwKPHQlmC7boiwyMwk61JdR6nZb66zssDwIePLILGs24XDK3fj8IF7AfHvI8wKLTbFazEbrbDzIoXKdEmDMGqH1/fYHS2ILCNernhgniKLWQhgInm+TsdJXiNclIdkY60ZoY7Hv0d1fWTZWJJsLTTpv/dK0ODQZ7e9l4o=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A, B, C and D", 
		"option_b": "A, C and D only", 
		"option_c": "A, B and D only", 
		"option_d": "B, C and D only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010110", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhz48sU0Whuyw/j+IX7CBnFRrHnDRqtxMFLrVbXWa/++6JRlZ1OPzQojpyWZn6vM+QJPvK1L6JyeZCsMcMtgzpCF0uP+131AJ89Sn8Bz6p5feexFzyi5fcLeYPh7wG2ULkr+dHmyAjBgnDSWrXNArZG1+jX2c985xQczmsBrrcszKdmc0KSv5h/4xi+M33eEW7RrHxSWs46k5ECdrMIqsN2ftCHe+uD4jvHc/p4CbEhGt4M/SlW4nqkHuAY9VsGnZBNf+PLVIXfiNSagLgIh95ij/3p91I0tSGog/RBIwoxQIsN/2YvhuHIzMMB6ECezt01PydR6UAXWd7Su2WSk81AtY3MoYMp/uS4ntAaIJVFwjleSGGwRsZh/+94KnAttPWBG3FXvjy+KjnzIb9Px/oz5xf/5tLEj8+M0OUSDPFrRU4lccbrNIid02OiWCJpSD5FPGDWmMNQg5Xn2JtaA1zxNw80hO3Lq8SSN3d61Pmystpy5j9Z5ArpAP8KK6Nmy8F/IczHkImnMJGsltzffIzN/mCmJnl4x570=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "2+T4YYKz0hb45YAjRl7wwP7+IHjVQ1YZpj+gWqJmZHTxFIbBeq3xz9cgfwnazUh+4nfUorH18xMbh60b5YuYeTEPf59m3tXJ1urzhHRZNsVRjolk4doZafpD2DSiesebL/gu2maFZ2L/cTyvCn9m2RbThHlEqY/85me4W885wxw+2sd9/tw9PtuWyqCa5kr4h0aR2WuQWrxwFBSVsMmh+E+dtIsusI2OvifV9/312vPd/8kFIglB/5J3ZhuVmawA+SR4GeuxZgZZ8OiZIXjoJyGwKw8J8N3mlldm04wqVGUI+iNI0MNfcYBy2ovr/DE/Ld9vFif6oUFDxoFvWleecf2Z03yk6VsrZ3UvcIlouG05rgydJBRsn3uOST9UmpRq6tkWm0Rqcy9UlHOgqzGPiWSBPL/m7Invienkqa9msoAoPE+DPFCYVJRcZKPQKG583uCVCuZaPIp1Vy/jMNcr7iq5JoSb0nkZ2NxgI3jk9SbZ2t3nNnOzvZHwj9g/VLgPINTX58ayvkjUISznYVCSYtn1SkSwbXP10Q98+1gHzS8X6W6USIhx8W0smWyxdUpYnHSgbXKl1uoc65CLP4c/0Pr+zzcTjLb7tIqUS0cI/DyvGV1XrfvJ", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "all Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010111", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV17i1/TyNHnJQ3AUomyMXONyf2OjUanDbfn3x5AxM1SMzXx05HPUraj1+UdPgK4bwICbeSNDX4h7iN+Pl7WvkSkecb83iP6cXjrZaGRNEoaS3PU=", 
		"answer": "24G3KIXh0Bf58YAyEg790vjtJivWEW0c42uLV+NRcWL3FI7MauT/ibR+KkyIg0I75nmGt631t3EdhrxS+obfUzAMaYUtGWUW/cOdC/vUoY/7D9UdWQ==", 
		"explanation": "25K3fpTh3xTv+ZFgXRiy7PP7PGqQImEF43CFEvIsJSmjFLDDfa37x5ZyM1mNzVJ1smLOpuXn9lgKz6ddqZqXdWIxe51gxMTJ2OK3lSkUZLVFlpN9pJERc+NOjDy+NMDTJb5Ix3yTMwXHZiv9C3Y0vT/Sj2xTpoe++yS+FNUlgAE6k8cA/s0sM87f1L2H4UOh/0a21H7RSb5wUV+Xutmmq0KP4JYwsI2ssiab8vvr2uzb9Z4sbQdW/6FwdV6umaUM9j54Xs70QRxP+OWcIVXvLySqNAYY/Yv33nEp44M6SSkd+htPg8N1bc1j15b98HIxMckqASG7rVdGwoZuWhPWYLW9kHjr91AtZjokY8pKszswswGRLVpq1iuIST5DnZRk7NkchkRic2sAjnP2hzGehXbPaJyj/4j5xcriqa1q4atnClOPIlKaJugNe4y0M+KXxZyKVF91Cw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Abolishing the Secretary of State for India", 
		"option_b": "To transfer powers from the East India Company to the British Crown", 
		"option_c": "Restoring the system of double Government", 
		"option_d": "Empowering the local rulers", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010112", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb7xyK8QdY21Bw8kcdZ7tx8M9HfiP/Euw20hw+GnG+ZTf1iHkGXsc+84kyS4IQ3p42OtDzP5vX12vnX/dcFaxtGrYdralSy16EHuAM2VcG1VBwLw+HRclvjYGCRblRdxcWj/2Apw5E9XGs4/QxOh4cWdsh2lojrrzskNsJkVTy842NP0ZFuURiEOZq93m324Vl/enxrR49juyw54Q6SLBR9iG6dWClV1IFlvvUBkAd2aWZWmTbDjSqFg2yDPIfsq4HvluHjtPlq/OMgJleFJ1LRWIpccbvFZ0Vgw/2SHq4cI5B0BCf1Ltwh8iq5KZjU9jcJ2dhi87EZjG/6v03lTyCCknPwZA==", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/IXnFBi5RoWqXErd8dTHxUabRYeO+wIQxIV2Fnl45oLDgcbBIQ1kx++Pbe7CGMA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHB1B7/+4Q0WxD1hdz8ISvfBSJA9CjQErR1YzHqWqPHa+m+yNdiLluHhF1y8XfIt+Xj41Yfz7xU/o+NdDFDfY5h3MKI26T2wHxIPc9XjpJz8JMQcrRJwn2EetDSIb5H2i6EIlb5YDe8EHVw1CXejzxxp5W+5ym0Rpo4xlUQk4l/7MR8PcTfzaCWqGq3kAOQ0nSDBZphH1GLtMLo5EXcgoc2ssyB8TPV8LT6iP3S5NsPIglc/6NnZlipg6Ef/WobXt26axtHsfDfIVX+MyGwM04V8Maj4nxg1cIkXHs/8RsGg8NVZ85nxJnotSgxK8RlG3O1pQRB0oB0UAWfYKT4xWbg5Ud/YXIuJa1iqignrwCOZXN7lG6OTSAWh8Bk+NYQlgEhFs+dFSVW8UsyOI325l96Lg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010113", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLs16z3qFKkD+c3mUXjBImgXejzxmoZevsjT7fdQzyRRyt4Rsrcc6fIbIgfzT7V6shwSO1WiZTbkkEBSKrN287k7cr4R4scKYsz7etPP2jP3B/tMObBwStog/QUm1g6Ea8GoRX8y9aS5FwvDRdVHgJSa3Zyc0o/ftlkBhw8IIXn108BZVlopYZdV6xZDhuHIyOtl9EDa041BIwtR/UBqbca+72WnooFQxcTo7aoZkqCQ2oAPcLkFwmX+VQyJC1I9tvsQRkERGfHxU3F/uhjaKwEaAcYPi5Zm8hOb04Lpx96IzLEXANBz6WYwOYfPPISdRxeePH6lQc4toVy/nM9Qp+XnpL5qdyzAO0dVgLnHh9SOLgfH7BWuNu5v6hpR5GrpAOdeF/cOy8FrIbS/uNnSdYYv9SkjzQG7q1g1x9xEriDMV+3LdC50/+itNina1CUVmnTHlLG+1l6pZ54eAa51ukcvKFLjSPrsmMPa2SQT6VRc=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz4g3r44AtVxDmiNS/NGXUQ1EFomuGX6Z6ZDzKfefDfOi+yphjNVmKmRt6/HKGkLHx41YCiqZPpKe2MCsQPp9nzZCK2PblwXJVc8Ncioxz6psLdftOjDuiZpToNP96y2OFKVG9Tnv85374Gzy7JCDE0gWedv89", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhf7wJ3nVAHZRoXqAU7ZndTH3XKKCXuTq3dBiZ3WHiVJ6slfFt+X/8RNe2PAPqYuMZCMBcoJ8wNWNl+W312hSJ8NJ2o90pJ4QafZMyX2qe8LeMvBjy2CUZ0z+JxuvDWR9hzmWo3JSoYKH+xu1Z8421BA/k4lsreEVfN6Mmamf5w27iRSQ2XiFCLxqFRSauty67kCI4IcgpcGMvzPP/fv3nLjc9p44dglGuot6bU/8vugL/Sk5RNuxKCZD+PeQQFf5YCGtMxwS/d7g03Apx8IqUWw15l9Ci5BCa85wwpHrsnIyOtl9EDa041BIwtR/UBqbca+72WnooFQxcTo7aoZkqCQ2oAPcLkFwmX+VQyJC1I9tvsQRkERGfHxU3F/uhjaKwEaAcYPi5Zm8hOb04Lpx96IzLEXANBzWU5pcZ7zEPidxy+WXCKIcJ5diVwDpPMcqvDb/YLWb0S0f39VgO3in+zycgN7wPCW7vZa5g9V4FbgFdsXN7Iunv1DOdSriIHHTZ83yWAHiXD4IybqDBiQDLuZjBu34BaSP", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_b": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is not the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_c": "Statement-I is correct but Statement-II is incorrect", 
		"option_d": "Statement-I is incorrect but\n Statement-II is correct", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010114", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3AHjrpP7JzfUSEXPoRpiIHRhre3y2FEPcNA2pVipI4XebRpwjmkddqbNOxvymvAM0qwZjWxRFJmnSXfmXQWpYap9i+6Ws4kjFU3joR9/dx8OtiNmbyB6Um9xg+MnG+USf1lH1DZose84wO/qIs2tPGDgiba4PH0n/bHsPciODRci456I3i0lrod/Th4cMugKB1NsbWIMAetISqsKwcO8c7nlmBhw8I9T2gw8V9LjY1Zcs9/z9jrunIkN8gqMDKptwRpyZB1Xle1e7Co0Wb9oFwxNVMlYYNsgCMJrziUIVd22mSaDDhZkcB46tENkAlmc3tT3HHplDqFwGSNc4Xmq4nvyunipflg/bE1LEKUdzmNVFBEZJE0AeM4XTUMexU=", 
		"answer": "25z4Z5//yFsMRG4z1CFI7DkSOmOoI7LK", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhentIG6cQ0sF436BXa99Y3nmUOfWZui+3YVwI1nJgFR1/WbJr7yw+FVPm6BeqY2QfTICcJIvwd7J/urzzXABOsMI2pR64do2cvBJzTPtYMbaJPsu2W+TZ1H4dTaqCjB7hDTYymhZ6IK3+WeZRtMjyQY61op9/8s0PdmLyui751q9kAOQkDuYXP1nHlqNvMC97kfctIo99cCCvz3L+/jg2vfVsMoDZ0hRsItvYlWl16cf/Th4Rdq1bBcL+OqQdVHsYCmtI04J68rn0zR+z5YhHUo8/RFHvo1qbPNn14zhsTc+K41DVTqp40JBy4d5HxWTd7ytw22k1F06NVkjZJh5uT91gAyIaFt42jrEHX8RkIlvvt4WgURif2BMlWXowiuDhSWKcofq+YW8kfrxpLwj/6wpJlGPOUWYWYtccbvFZ0Jz2f3bJKhYOp4nNC3rLdQg5XnwLta90T0E0YJiujt4MlP8/ZBV0kJY6VpS6Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010115", 
		"question": "24C2bJThkQ7i/oYoEhL3wvTsOWrECnQU436ARuNjcWKjQK/HLvn33Zt0Z1OPzU9z9zbHp6j5+Vocm7pa/YeJdWILe4priN+Pl8blzWVIIM4Es4527Ztff/xBwjqocJTdMvFjjimnKFP1dTeyFjBTkT/TmH1a6Iy9tQW+Wt02zFJygog4qu8zKtKN16eBqGq9iAOQ3XfRR7skOFqdvM/vtAHU28WiXYxNLIjTgGdR3De0", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHQ2Rj444AyEj/x0b3wMyuBWzFC4WILBG0FILuFrvjNDUEikT8=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ2Rj444AyEj/x0b3wMyuBWzFC+T+3WqpnMHDgQOfVb/6+yNdlMk6HhFV8smbJqqvkuRMmm+hY7ICLYiMPd5FqzJCd3+G3x35MI8dKg8dhpIgKcPEAxTPtXdrfKf8uzHfAIkv0bje6RGR8kXHFj2xXuoKv8Ge6UNc+zhwhgpV5+cEzMsTf1q7TykK1hAebnHqfTP1JEFCLtN3o6k2Y4IAqvMOKuDzctODxn/WT5dAPZxoSq456I1izmbwb9yZ4Xs70fBpOscPfd1H/LiexZykY987x13gpyYRpf2w68x5KzMNibYBh057ouTEkf9liHCD6oVZPxpB5TVeXYamw33rt9Ex/emwud8pssCF1rgncCkZ3jmKPRGx4moRi/5xZgQxmPXtJiHrlwiiKkyWObIPx5JDujOnkpbV6sqAvKE+HMFiYQoJcIpTPMWJgxOaJTYFZPZp1Fi6mMtNu1Tf9KZfTkXkh38skb0Du+CaQk8C1G2C0p5v3jd82A74TdsXN7IuxuU7UdWP1Lj2bacfwGRz4Rm+4xwdxux1rikR1VVNPskTN1+hFTfT9miQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "The Regulating Act", 
		"option_b": "The Charter Act of 1833", 
		"option_c": "The Pitt's India Act", 
		"option_d": "The Charter Act of 1793", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010116", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3ICiqZf4ICYMAMAastgzpDYgLymhHRZNstUjoV2pI4XebRnwyuoZtrUMrNJy2CFNUT8JzizADBgnDSWqXNDpoCy+We9RtU6gAE6k8dy+No1L9OW2rya50P4iQDCyHOUCI5xAUacuMvoyEyJspZ4s8Kf8SbT8f3r2vfV9tcIawle/4d8d1Kzmbs19hksUNyxZRdF5aT5SA7RLmiXLwtd2Mbm2HBgyIVpfGogtBBAwtIBOpEz04DnsCc0OskqATu/405V1Z1vWx6VYLS33ijr5hUrfX9rVp99rig4pE+/J0FsjiuIQ2xDkZZu8MUc1QliaXtFjmWggzGPwGiOaIfm+ZO8l+38oa1m9uMzJgGUPVmYVYIQabbDM259xKmUC+ZONoliGTfjAdsS8g7xKZWcnzYLkM0oKjf04CuNl8DwN3Gp85XwmNF4VL4COcfAqcKk/13VZGPiLm+BY8jgG81JE5uK+8wRXXq9Y3E4n+Y=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz+Fnr+YFgezewDbm4SXZFF7HmzNz7mUMRzw==", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhentIG6cQ1YZpj+iX6Z6dHjtU+fjbfm+xpExdgvR3Bty/HLDpqGw8ksKgrhP7IrfZCoGPqxg3tWb2evliVZEPcNWm4wy5ZQbPOBIyX2Oe8HVI/dijmiSKEiwczG4RHphhjjFjnVVvIq0+2e0UpojyBBypZJo/80xOZe81r2B/A2+iRTCyHOUQa8kHlKfvM2h6k/coYEsvMKDonLn+sj3u/zX+coCbQZTs4pmLxuPg6kd/Sc9X9z0QTsL+PeQYFj+L2i3NRsYud/r0zRIxZZpWHE3+ApCh4cWcMVl05bxuXI9Ptl+ECGp40VOw9RxXgOCca+rkHrh7FQrcH5rcYUtrigjpAGJLRR9lWeQSS9FnY9lvtYLmgkjaWdF3Hz1kDaYhGyMaJrs5cDzg6jkqLwjwbY3O0SNMBz7WZgOcfG1hahBQQEOFGdXY5ReBubK", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010117", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV17/xPfwJyvfFnYSrHKGEqxyMGXrUefrYOn3yJkxBFOcg1hy/mWGgqbkt1wJz/kCudfTMCMPbYQvw96GwOq3xWIBJ85B2q199pYaZbltxTO5e5TpJfhh3GOTeAeKdAGi4ktueuM2CLLgfgGu", 
		"answer": "27y2fIP81Qzp8oFgURH/yOjxNGeQEWcBsXqQV61gcWXqW6mCaOLsibpkNFCAgBts+2LO47b151IdjrxeqYuTdSEXbIRu3NXLFrB+tI1qNuxybBE/Ste63Q==", 
		"explanation": "25y2bJjy31nJ+JAuURf+1r3eNn+QDGRR8ibTC+N9fmXxW6PXbej6iZYxNEWamV52snnA46b/+l4agalXqZyaYDAGbY5h3NGd3uv5hHdOIYZpj5N+7ZcMPPZZjDyud9HLNPdgyS6UL0CwZDazB3VkgHHZjDwuu4ar9DW6QN93xRk3lZN3/8koOa7f7KaX7V/4kg6LzzfRXLVhUXmMpsKh5gORpY86sN+e8SXe5vG5jveT8ttLZwRXvJJ6ZxuzmaQQuCghEeWhex5C/KTGbkDoMjvjEwYI6oejwnxshqMqSSlM+BpBg49fccV3lpvrsT8lMcxmHCC32gRByZA8cxiEcP2V2Wbw7xU8dHcuJZ5i/C8w4QSSJ0Nw2mqPDDhZkcBN/8QRkBYjcmkAv3ntjyqFgWnPWZ/m6JTzl+nkpftItBoRkm1IKoMgndiLrR9I", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Bicameralism in provinces", 
		"option_b": "introduced communal representation for Muslim with separate electroate", 
		"option_c": "Extension of voting rights to all citizens", 
		"option_d": "Abolishment of the Legislative Assembly", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010118", 
		"question": "24GwbdHU3g/v5YstVxDmhfL5dULeB2sQ416ARuN7djGyDfSXLuTw3YV+I0mKiF875X7PoK2w+FVPm6BeqYiQfC4MaYJhz5CP0uXj0WNEIJkGVfI/ioK5zwHNm0MP0zfv6A==", 
		"answer": "25CrfJDx3RD5/4glXAqyyvu/NCvWBmYUsX6PErNhcn3qV+fRa//owJR0Z1+GgFZy4WXPrKuya9yMF0rxRtnsqCElDNZOow==", 
		"explanation": "25K3fpTh3xTv+ZFgXRiy7PP7PGqQImEF43CFEvItIySjRLXNeOT6zJMxIVObzU9z9zbDsLHx9V8GnKBW7ICLMC0FPoVg3JCG2ejuhHABFcNAn5Jz6NovafZMxT7tR9HJNvdtyy6jKEj9biquDX962HHUn2gWqY+o+me6FOolzwM7mIRx7MR8DMKd1aGQqH69lBCL337Ra7JpHF2Kpsen5QOdroZ4n8KEvyabxOH7lvHQsO0OcB5bvIM/QFSxmqEa6yM3X4iyZwAL5fPfIVv/YCWsNQtd6dnswH1nxYc6H7a0NwdzcBWa9vc7/tq3In0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Extension of communal representation", 
		"option_b": "Creation of separate electorates for depressed classes", 
		"option_c": "Establishment of a federal public service commission", 
		"option_d": "Granting power to the British monarch", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010119", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV17/xPTxdWTFF2EernrDXaU0ZHnmFI7MauT/x9dYKViMnV519nPIoKCw1lAbz6ddqd/GJHVcPN+yR1sY9Q/BaYNG+2mFqFY=", 
		"answer": "25ysKJLh1Bj+8oFgQRvixO/+IW6QB20cqnGKXa1nMHDwFI7MauT/iZZ/Ixy5jFBy4WLHredralusjzXH3VPd+xi42oEn", 
		"explanation": "25y2bJjy31nD+YElQhv8wfjxNm6QImEF43CFEvItJCajUanGa+m+3Z90Z36bhE9y4X6GsbD88hMGgehy54qWcWICcI8vzNWK2+XlwXUBGshAk4Ey5YlfffoAxTOpccTeLvprwHrAJkv0JyqyEnVmkTjRhDxFvIKv8Ge9RtU6gDQnkZJr+YhtaZvfiPHHvw34rxLCzGmeXrRgFFDZs8G6q1eUpcIotN+ZuCbS+/q5lf6T2dAPawkSvoh7I1iukqkd8SU2EceyKAZc/qTZb1DoMC2tIwsT7Yvn2XlgyIsmU3p0+xkGq41Sa8Ez15bg/AIxNMR5ATK041NJ05w8Sx+TNK+x12DwoEEwNWkuZo9puW0zswCRaEB2nyu+XiVFnZNjvvMWmAlsc3hFnXr0in3aO42dxzmci1+v/2Ce7Uaz", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "It abolished the office of the Viceroy", 
		"option_b": "It extended the British rule in India", 
		"option_c": "It established the Constituent Assembly", 
		"option_d": "It created separate dominions as India and Pakistan", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010120", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTjp48UtUwz5wPm/IWPVQ2cCt36BXqpneHzmWrOCYeu+y55yJlGMn1p3snrDpKzj+1Ibmrpe+s6WfmIQd5Mv2MKGwe35x3RSc89K2ql84JMeI7YlMNwCyumgZAkR5aLRMfoD", 
		"answer": "25K3fpTh3xTv+ZFgXRiy7PP7PGqQImEF43CFEvItISihi1E7Kj1BCWwfD1ocZB8ZZg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHU3g/v5YstVxDmhfL5dULeB2sQ416ARuN7djGyDfabLsTqiZ5/M06GiU5493KK46P/5RMbh60b74eNYzZDaoJizZzJ1e30xXxEIcdIk5N/pJsReLRExS+od8CbJfJrzXqJKEvjJzCzRGR8kXHVhWlYvJGitROzQcl7gAE6k8dR48w1Pdnf1a2U4V60hxKLyn7RS7JxH1eQuY6/6lDcsocoucyOtDab9u25m7jR+d0Kbw1Avoo/b167nrsF+T4tQ830ax1F4u3DdV3jJ2isIU4c94vWxmRs1MIBUnwn8V8OoYxDbMN62tjrunIDK8x+EHr6okpEh5U8cxiBca/4+Gfx81B/PVYuYoN+sCwhqBmZaHVtiW6RTiBI3cBf9tVZmAVpcn1JiG+gjTnLjWCCfpbx+MDzg6jyr61rsrcvLAGoOknLU55ccrbSIidxwuaICKgcMYYnEyv0ONY6vDz1JZWA1jYDkjku7+fBwYwW5O4vNk35620=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Government of India Act of 1858", 
		"option_b": "Indian Councils Act of 1861", 
		"option_c": "Government of India Act of 1919", 
		"option_d": "Indian Independence Act of 1947", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010121", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV17Vyuv6J2XdBmwF43CFEop6dHjiFIbBeq3xz9cgfwnRzV5o5nfEr6zj/wwzgZRVyMO+ci0Pd5hnzdTJw+zyhFNOMtRA2o90pLkQcuBSwzGRevaWBe16z2yMLlb4Yj39BTAlwXzbj3FUrZH79iiuWtk+zFU9kMdR48w1PeuR+uW25km9gkaG026TRLgkNluPsNym5kaStMIrrN6ZtD/n+tC0uerW8coOZkhT/4h6dBuzka4A+y90EfuxawBO5eXCeBTiJmiQMw8J/Ivl2WYp74wtVGh2Q7HrSD0mh7DpksRLModjGg==", 
		"answer": "25f0KLKz0Bfut6FgXRD+3L9WPYTbb80ksV7ApSQMzyFH", 
		"explanation": "25T4YYKz2Bfp+JcyVx3m+fPDO0mQCnFRoHCRQKZ3ZDHhUaTDe/77iddWKEqMn1V293jS46r2t3oBi6Faqa+cZGIMeMs+kIXRl+Hk0HBDP89XkoV2pJtfLaENwTigdtHJYP1h22CDLkmwaD/9LX5wnTCWnnMWqZCo/DSvFM4/xVUBk4Rq6Nw9Ls7f1q7T21m5kgPC2nSDCJRqFV2Y9fqg7gOfr5c2tsSB8SXa57T4lLjS9MgCcQdApsZ9bF+l15wB/WorVMumbQZK4/2QblKtMzyiMwtd7srwlnlowodpSWExtDxOg4pEb8F9lpfi/CY4Oo1pGia0oE1M+5pAUTTWfa7402f28lA8YTopYIlsqT4w4RuULRR/mX/cSSJVkYQr6tgc1Rd6bntFkTbvhH+Pj3CNcJajzI/qgPr+rbxt5uMlMAGBN1PUX54UbL3HZ3N6z6m5AqdON99oEWLFMts67jb1YJea23ku38wyOzfo8mq9m9/wOnG1oYHFgOh4MP8JJZHG5tmltV/TISHkInyGdc60TQD1D337x05mpR0k3CQUqGOYBoxotSILmHezTAgkoSLjfnm1l6xFqo2IP70l0uHpnTQfirRRkZ/+1VF8UQGomXpH8pOWW1QPzlvbDsEC0AxuDaEVHJnD+3mP1XfeTzwOcMDiE6eLgyNe3/Gxp295tpEAFY2KIRDVg80y2halCPJ3FVPlrcbqOP8HD3At6KsxxevhpN66YfbkO2Q5Lxv3VOpU8ZBDKA19UR/VAGRtcrG6X44WAcNO0HzEkhMIRnFNRU3N6OgaWBe6pcrbZ2jSZvEJAgrrbrIRFsLhDlPAdeWhzXDrFLaInFS2H3QkXDaUIL0I6xOyUNRX4yCyyG/VtwvmcxditQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "B, C and D only", 
		"option_b": "A and D only", 
		"option_c": "C and D only", 
		"option_d": "A, B and D only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010122", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV17hzPrxPG3ZAGMfoHrDXaU0ZHnmFI7MauT/x9dSKEmHjlJ34TbnoLGw+FVP3vANuNGjfh4NX8Zc3NGbw+HzhGNEI9RBiYV88JsLdeJFjDSjZ8DSNOt6x2GONHn+RXSUCnlgnTDCj3gWrIa48CmvRts7yQ8zgo534/QyH5rf8KaH+kK8kwWH2DuVQa9hEkDZsMKt6FeVr4wricOp/HL+5+D4mPTa49YOZkhBupZ+cVqokugM9C87RcemaQZO4tjeXVrFLz/jKg8T4Ivs0DR9zodpTn014BpLh41CLdMz0ZHyuTxwPs9lAzb6qlcPxoZ5HxSZZq+903y7olI2cNcQWbZOJ9foBJnhlg8=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25T4YYKz0hb45YAjRl7wwP7+IHjVQ0sfp3aCXONXf2TtV67Ofa3fyoMxKFrJ3AMtozbLoqH1t1JPja1c4ICReSwEPoRpiMSB0qTlwWFTNtVBlJRz8JMJebRJwi65fcDONPdhwH3AJVywZiquC3N9lSXfhHsWgY2//Ca1R5ogyQE61pNw6IgwPcDS1KmY4UO/xhaQ03iUW64kOEDV9dqg/lDQ4JIqutuEtTfftODxm+yT5NYOIj5bvINtbEL8hKAG7SY8Eca7ZRtF8PDVIUfiLS3jDgAZ8MrtxTRo1cInUmd5+xlAi4BfY8wz253pvjciLI1lE3OyqlcAwoxsXhmScbn402fx7lY2eUYlWYRP/CQm4Q6QO1s+mWSOXilSgMAr39MN1QtlPT4YyiegizGClGyOaJbnq5T0gKjgsrZg97A0aU6GdVjdVYgScaHBK25hy/2SAqgcMYYnBSf1Kdo89Tf+YIKc2nkB1d4pPHvm4COPl43lNnK/oYG5mts2ALcFdvPK5Mm2qRzGbyehDHyXdMrnGTjiSm/x1wtrtBEg22E5/C6YHIFq5mFNjHumTFZ3lyOgeHSk1r1Z5JacfoI4wPzi2nIEnfp8mpX0zV0oTwWvzWxXs5aLSlgPy0bZE40TzAxuPrEGAZrQ5mSYkjbxSGhNcMi2UP/QkGx01N//rSF8sZROccyPPhybg9AlxwWjBP5tFWXoq4fsLvlVHmwp6Lcx3eizsoq1erO3OWYiLwqlVvlQ4JxeZkBWBS0mMX1dqMAeYAROjjmK", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "all Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010123", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV17by/n2NGWQIG0ErXyKXrA0UXL3FKjELrymkMUxJl+KglZr/n/Vq/rM+W8BruVy542NdSMQe48vx9aP3uf+xX0BPsdOlZJ78IMjctYN6TC9e8PeMvtqjnqIIgXGbjq4Fn9t1CXZynVFu5a+tSipUNM5wRsxk5RE4+txfP6Rzbqc7Fi7gwLC0HKcQalhFRSYu8ro4k2YqZA9ttnN8TfX8fftk/fd4+IFRkVzs4pwdF64164G6mo9Xc23fBtE/6TfZxTjLybuKAgb8Mjq13gpy4ckX2wm5yNIvo1+bdcz25nqpXI/OY1+HTb6sFBB05FxWhmCO67412Hy5Vt/dHgkc48ttT56oB2ZaFdxiHmZTzgO1r0uxrIu4d0tBUelr3KH2Go=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "25T0KLOz0Bfut6FgUwz3hfTxNmTCEWcStz+/XJ96UzHqR+fBYf/szJRlZ16Mjlpu4XOGiqv0/lIBz4tU/ICceS4QPqps3JCG0aSmnCgTc8tFnoUy5doTdflJ2DipNNXVJL5nwGqJNUDzc3mtFn9inSLfhXIWroyptTOzUZoi0xBymYE46MQ5P8OW1qbT4UP4gA+O0HKfT/1xARSKusOtq0ya4JYwsI2DvjyW+/L/k/va8dJLcQ1Tq5U/YVSon+gA9mosWc30SxdF5fbRbRTsLizjNxwS78Lt1X1oysIlWG495xNHlopAZ4Bw2Y3qvzs8LI1eHTb6tEtSw9QAWhuTd6mx32aZoEI+ZjZrbYV6uTsws0PcJltq2n6PSSgRnY4r6tgc1SVgaS2z5erE3gA17WmvD1tWzhw1", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "all Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010124", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhz48sU0Whuyw/j+IX7CBnFRrHnDRqtxMFbsQqLQYOD7x4MxKFrJpFV/+3eGgqbkt1wJz/kCuNfATCw/cKoi4d6dxevz0XJEN4ZGk4Nz6Z8NffhJ3zCRevaWEOxh2GeEIkGwYTavRGNxhDDEi2hT6Ia38CSvW8g21BAhqolboOk+M9uWyqCW7A2sjgPC/3SERr5tHRSWs46B5UeVob42kYCoqSbe+vD8nrjQ/9MGdwZTs8ZtZkuukrsM9j45RcG7ZlDc1t1WwQRI7WYWCQVxJSlH", 
		"answer": "25T0KLOz0Bfut6FgXRD+3L+VKyEetn+YFiXslfQ8Kron", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHS0g2q5YAsUwb3wb38MGXEEWMd43yMXLdmf32vFK7Mev/xzYJyIljJiUJ64HXOuumw9l0Lz61I/Y+dfCsQdo5riNKA1OX6wWNAP89Xl8JfhvcCUeGYXy2mgIi6CGoM", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A, B and C only", 
		"option_b": "C and D only", 
		"option_c": "A, B and D only", 
		"option_d": "B and C only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010125", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb73Cm/Xds5gDY9g4l75MQvfPaczeic7g3p3lDTnHKfXK9rFUGasMro/0uZ4JIqus6IoiGb+/K5nv3Q9dAfcAletpx+d1KzmegA9moRX8y9aVx3/6TiZFX+LybjbzxUo4vf2DRdzodpfGogtBxUh4JCZ8Qz2p3jtSE8PtljAzb6oEtVyZd1UwTWcrKqkHj270M2e3kudsphtSYw4S2ZJlN/lifcYiNDgIgmydUKgQFxcy9wjnn2izGIhXbDPJLt78DMkOb6obsvsqQ1KE+UPFLfFpkUYL6AM293ivmUGqNOc4toVyPiOccr7yq5MYORzC0E39czb2PotD6Rl43wIWC5pobwmNE2FbEEdtXM+siio0+HYzblJniHdYW2ZdT+sTvK3/+eJ4AHRbrexQ==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFggCy7V6VK3AuNft1DyN5xBu0U", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+cUpQV7m1+j6dWnVAGMEsHrDZqtxMFjtUK7DYK3dxoJ/JFWFnhta8WKGrKOwpgtZ3uhf4IrfeSwHe45riNmHw/b4wGRCNoZQkoUy9IgQf/FT332icpTfJf1rwHqSJkn5fTipDX961DjYylVYrIq6u2eSQJZ31B0nhcs4/dozKt6b3KzT/EW5kkaW1H7RfrRnFEaWrI6740yJrIZ4u8KAuDza4PG5iffe9Z4ibAxbvohsI1qv16YG9mc3V869axtK/aTdZFnvJTqwZwEbucPqxTRs3pIoU20x8F9FjZZYYcl/mNjYsg4+DchrBjy0401Th5VwTBjWYK+t1Sjl7lF/cGI7aYtksm0hqQ6IaEB2k3jcXzhUhMBm/8ISkAAjaWdF3HTlhTaFjmyBe9Ps7cD4gOv1rq1x868uM0CUPFPWFo8FJaHFNHN92OCVCuZQNphuBC7nKdw4+XnpL4GRzSpNxNZgP2Xo4iOXkcjmeXavsJq5j8c2NroOMdDJpYuZv07TaW7WJG6HY9n6GTjiQGrx3Q1gpFRlyS8UqFLNBoN+92NNqna1WkEkgjXvenWvlbtPqpWLbYtx1Oft0yYVnLR0mpz+xxE9Uw2tiD9AvZGRTFVD3hTBF9kPhB0mCfQRG4HU4C2CmjbUQm8Oat3lQaqSxytNzvCxj295/5EKUZ6LPwqbm8sj2wO4DvNqFXPi6JLxOLwQEmEv76Z43Ojv9Rvp8GLuQc7OnLYlLv7fdS4=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion.", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion.", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false.", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true.", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010126", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3QAma1J54OafjZDcY0v4d6N3uW35XJVc8lC2tErtcNfdfpU3jKpYdfeJL56xmvAJEr+ZDytEDB7knHSk31Eq4uitS61FM4/xVUbmINx7MZ8LMWQz6Gd60irugixyHqFTbBhH0DZnOfy103chJs5p86FqHLS+uL2lu7W9J4Pax5bu49xZBushacf8SQ7WMm4KAFe8+7VYkD+YCGtMwFd7dni2Gdvw5A7WG109RFCwpFTccVhwJ3g/DExK8htGiGzpld8yahyaB+fd7X432bhoFo5NW4jYMprsyE5rhiVJlM+k3jcTyNDhoVo6pAQm0RxeHxQmXX0wjCNwHGHedPi6Y/qgKjjtLh3964iJ1WTah7zxZPlk8hDWWIsxRqco3Yb", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz4g3r44AtVxDmiNS/NGXUQ1EFomuGX6Z6ZDzKfefDfOi+yphjNVmKmRt6/HKGkLHx41YCiqZPpKe2MCsQPp9nzZCK2PblwXJVc8Ncioxz6psLdftOjDuiZpToNP96y2OFKVG9Tnv85374Gzy7JCDE0gWedv89", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhf7wJ3nVAHZRoXqAU7ZndTHXXKKCSeLozIV/KlmHmRt09DbvraH59hMujLwb5ojfIXtSJ8trwcaA0+HzhGVJNoZUiI9k7ZQcdfVMjC64dt7eI+p9jmeOM0qwcy6yRGB1hiXF+WhEqY2o8yKpRt8zgBQ8ksdq6Ns5LsGa3ZSd1EOLkgeW2XaURqkkOH3ZvN3o6k+Pr8I7ut+ftDHPtPX3nrjW6M4HYwFc/5J3Yk/8g6AMuD4qUManbhdZ4+HUIUf4IiKmJBoOudzmxHEp0o1pX2x09RtLi41fcdR2xJ3g/DApf9liEHOdrFJF1ZpzTVeBfamwkHzs5RU+fH5raowtkSQ7qByILUZt2nmZXzxempNi/Nwc1RBsPXtImTbshziCk2mOaJr17sD/iv3+o7BvspcvLAGSME/dRJsZYfPTMmV4z+qPHuocPJEnAyrjfdo69DzrYJ6V0T1BkM4lPXKn4CXZkMi1OGG3upzwncBzBroEdtPcqd+/tRzgbjXkM3OcdIv1VwywR3Xrkwt9shsw3CgG7SLbB5xx9iQB3mm5XUxrhzOgbnmomLkc+Iedb4E/wPzu0TdQjPs4i5PylBE5QA2ogX5Xu5KaD19A2FrVF8FH8AEnH/QFAZfdsn6VnXPdTjwCeY7xDr6C0SJJ1OD0znZ8rNAFW4OZIlnamZ5ezA6wE/5xTB6vTThw+KqHJMcgIbfEWBpgVA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_b": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is not the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_c": "Statement-I is correct but Statement-II is incorrect", 
		"option_d": "Statement-I is incorrect but\n Statement-II is correct", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010127", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3oBi6Fa5862fiYGbo5hzNWH1OG35XJVc8lC2tErsM1fcfVSxzipNMDTJb5rwGrAKEOwRSu0EHlnnHHEn3BT6Iq1tQ61UNM2gBQ8ksd86MswPcWa3ei65kmxh0aDzzuQRv1tH1Ccpcum70aStMI5u8nNoj3N8eb8k//dsM0fYxxXg4hMd1qokqUM9j54eOHuVBwLxezVIXXuNGinLhgU/c7nll1nwosoHWA64BAGlpRZIsl90p30uTw0OsN+VTe1rk1OzptyTFvWXbO82Wmk4Vs7NUoqboN+qCw77U+LIUB22n+USWxehJRi8d5ZgQsjbmpDmXLlwjmZj2jPaJvmq6LujPz5s7Ej0awqJE6OIlnZWpkUWb38KVB6w+qTTalac4tvEmL1KdQ6+TT8LoKHnz4Extwub3bl+zyc0sTmdmSottL6gcZkEbwUaZPQmiGR5ezzYR/jIcvqwxS/", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz+Fnr+YFgezewDbm4SXZFF7HmzNz7mUMRzw==", 
		"explanation": "26asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhentIG6QAWcSomqQV+NgeHSjdaTWLujwzZJ1Z36bhE9y4X6GsbD88hMGgehy54qWcWIMcMtO3decxPC3lSQNc5cdztc+pJsReLREyT6hdcbeJL5HwGqJJgXxdHm8CjB9mjXTmnlYrIa14We6Wt530xokk5V95M8yfMSL2LyWqHG2ugixyHqFTbBhH0DZnOfo4lDcoY4ruo2ZoyfetPb8mfnG49tLdgBX/6d8dxushacf8S49VYiyZwAL5ezVIUTsMjyqMwcS94vs0DRAyIYgXCk1+hsGlotTIsNh05nwtT0+f8JsVSetrARJyZB5TxKYcLi2xCjg71g2e3Mka5kh/AQ7pQadaFVwniusTSdYh5Rq8JxZgg13dS9UlHOgkDaMiHHPaJyj+IX/gOz14L9x/a5nPUmFdX7KX5kVdruABGh/x+aVGqNdP4tvVeDFQx5CoCBX9mTMZRLQRvo=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010128", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3oBi6Fa5868fzcNfYJj25Co1PC3y3cBYp4dyMB76pkNefVTyTntYNzeYPB7w2yFNQX/YXm8AHR9gDjZhH1a6I20+2q0Utw+wxwzmsd16MU+OcWMmaGdqFmwg0aB2XWFWrxoUVWXsY64+UyKqYw7vMyB8T7e8/3qlvnH+cgOIgtdqoh8alevq6Y67CssVMWxZgYL2M2KXVrZKC3jBg0JucLtwmZmwpcqWG109V9Vm5BCZ80z2Z6kuDsiOs5+VTa2pkdUzptyTFeQe6/40WTooFswezckY4xkvyQ0rU+RLVl8n3mPDCVf1JRj+5AVkANqbmNBiH/2h3+Ij3CBf5rv+LzyuebHqLBg+uMoLwGUPVmYRZkdcbbNImlm2amcBLBZPd9mFS3wOJUn73b4MpPU3DYfwtwjOzXPu/gXoXD4qShymfFEkyJh", 
		"answer": "25z4Z5//yFsMRG4z1CFI7DkSOmOoI7LK", 
		"explanation": "26asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhf7wJ3nVAHZRoXqCUaJhY3SjQK/HLsTwzZ5wKRyqgk518X/KsOXR9EdPgK4buNbGImITbIR5wdSM06Txy2MBJ85B2o596ZMRfeBJwzPte9KbM/Fjyy6OKEu9aD+7DXN9lT2Wh3lbqoap5me0UpojyBBy3oYxres5MsON2KTTxEi/jxWO3W+YXrgkMluMu82h5wOeucIsvcjNpzvY8eb2g7jc/p4fag0SrYN8bFaxkqYN+T4xXsb0ZxQL5ezVIUT/Lz6qKQ0U+Mej2nFuz5ElXH094hoGgYxDbMN62oukvTw0f9liEHOYpkpHxpg8fB+Xeb+9wijr5hUcencmYJhuuWF1oAGYaBx80yuIRC1F1I9tvsQRkERzb2BWlXjjiz6HwGmKe5rw54HojP714Lps560kIE2TdV7BFpkUYPPnKHF32OeUH7UcPJEnAyrjfccr/zb0LZOa2zgZ2dYub3jhtD6Rl43xMHauoZv6mpR0G74SMsKJqcaivlXEaDPgLXSHb87nFUjlQXXu1hx2vgwszTJcqHbKCY16tSwejXGzQEVwmyjufzDhjL9R44zDe48jwLXt0zZQm/x5kpnyxg4ASTi1nmtCpoGSSlJbjX3/XsQUhAAgD7sTBpPS5i2UkHfTSmkeeo7CCa3Hwi9cmu7wimQ9vtACXIGHOBzfyt8ozFe4D/lwR2LuvMbpL/MDA3cl9bwxzOKz996zcLOxP2BqYBz3XONc8IFYZww7GAWdAy1DbLGgUd0LUaBc3XjP1whOB2tBABrC9KZFUgKso8fBb2aecLQdGg2iYbwRG47xQAfbPfTp6zXHEq2dmQe/UUBlXiiSN7kD5g7xdsz+IRS6gGRl7cjzNxFYS5YZPy7/ZymOOxnmyfReFV+ObtHhx7IK", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010129", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sU0Vwz/1r32OyvzDG4ErnHDc+NjeWXrFLPKa+TsiZR+NU6Mjk879nPVoLf550cGgKZIqYeRMAEMcp5ixpCrlcq7iOpGjn+tMRlRlqBBp0M=", 
		"answer": "25K3fpTh3xTv+ZFgXRiy7PP7PGqQImEF43CFEvItIySufanWfOL63JR0IxydhV478XnIoKDg4xMAiehf8I+NcyoaPoJhiMCb2PL+ynJEIIoEs4527ZsRPNdP2TOufdjIYN9t2i6PIQWhPmnkSVVngDDUhnVFoIa/tSWyV9s6xQczmsd06M81L9uezb2B7V74jwjCz3KJCK12HkKQu82t+A/ciYw8vMyD8RvV8PHpn/bX9dAIZ0hzvJI/bF38xvFdr2cIQ8eiYRZO9aTWbkatNCCmZx4c69/qwn1myMImWykd+htPg8NXbMQz1YrhvSY5MMMqGjX6qkpEwoR5UROTeqn41Gfp6Vs2enQ4KcpKszswswGRLVpq2mSaDAVfkIlqvvEagURsey8RxSe5zxuClmyLeZej+4/rgPrj4Ltm5rQiLE/AIVTdFq4Za6fSIidzxO3bHbRTJZZpFCf1fcIn6DG5NJ6G2jxN3NAzO2Sly5S5qI3FpA+rVAQFwxX8tQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHU3g/v5YstVxDmhfL5dULeB2sQ416ARuN7djGyDfSXLuTw3YV+I0mKiF875n7D46b/+VAKn7wb5ojfdDsCbIhn0ZCA2aTjzHQBI9RLjIl8558MMLR0xDjtXdrfKf9gjk2PMkvzbjWuRFF3gHHZjDwH8dPitSKoQNs1zBwhnoJ8rco1P9aS3LqS5A20gwGLz3eQXKh2FEfZvMDo+EqE4JIqutuEvzHe57i5rvDWsPcFZgFTscZWbV+5h60H/C82Us30SRFfsevWIQW0dH/jNxwS78Ln03ApwI07HX088V9Wg5FCa9R62ZakszRwFsNuHDL643BIwtRbUAGTZrO11WbwoFo5NVMlYYNs/Aw2tU+TLhQvwzrFDChYgolv+9RZhQt0eH1T3HTlliiOhWvPaJvmq6P5i/zipfli/KdnOVOPI1XWVYgPJaTJM28y3uGJCKMcP5Z0AzG8ffMr+DzrIZrU8zAexJVgH2Xo4iOXkcT0NSWWuoHtwpR3GrtAFd7L6t6lolnJdWPNKG6HJMJ+BAEL4y6YrXhLaAc5zn0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Government of India Act of 1935,Introduced the concept of dyarchy in provinces", 
		"option_b": "Indian Independence Act of 1947,Provided for the partition of India and creation of independent dominions", 
		"option_c": "Government of India Act of 1919,Divided powers between the Centre and provinces with three lists", 
		"option_d": "Indian Councils Act of 1909,Established bicameral legislatures in six provinces", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010130", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sU0Vwz/1r32OyvzDG4ErnHDc+NjeWXrFLPKa+TsiZR+NU6Mjk879nPVoLf550cGgKZIqYeRMAEMcp5ixpCrlcq7iOpGjn+tMRlRlqBBp0M=", 
		"answer": "25y2bJjy31nJ+JAuURf+1r3eNn+QDGRR8ifVA+40WX/3RqjGe+77zddjIkybiEh+/GLHt6zm8hMGgbtP4JqKZCsMcJgvysnJ1vfky3JIMtJNlIcyzZQbdfVO3326fcDTYOpmyy6MJlK9aji2DX5z1CHEhX9Tu5D3tQC0Qt8lzhg3mJM44s58Fdmb0KnTyU6sxgmEnCrIGeQpUXCQo8es7kfcsJA3o8SDsjva+LTqj/rZ9d0fcUhbsZJwI0+ulqYa/i8qQ82wKBNF9aTCZEfoMj6mI04e+N/m0Xt7z4c6HWg68F9PjJdEbcRm1ZHqu3IgLcJ8HD25qkVMh5VpSxiYe7ChnCjN7lE2dHRrTIRpuT0wrwuZJld72kqfWGxeksA6p4RO2EROfH1LmXKgljeOwGCBeNPs7cDel+HkqaprsrEyJUTAPFKYf4MYbLKAJml2iu2eDqpdIZpjVwvoOdwvvDjqYJeanzAD1NwwKnnj8SSN0sz7PSWpvIT8nNF/E7FAJcXE/c778HXJZSrgLz2wad76WgH8XDzZ0BoluB5lmXlJui+YIYd85ygMjXu0CVBsl2fueXGjk6wc5YTOfoo12uHl0jwRlLR2kJW32xs6TgeyjHMDv4GSTVld3hTfEI0LwQ4nH7gAAJ/H9y2VmmPeSHUBbIy7C69IQ3HxRMGR+1flnwNB", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRHny/72OXiQImEF43CFEvIsJiCjXanWfOL63JR0IxybiEtp92XDrbHx41oZiuhS552LeTYWaoJgxsPJ1f23xX1NPNFNlIcy8JIaPMJJzzi/e82bNPEuwGGNLkvxczz9F395kXH/hHhfqY2otSaoFNQ4zlg9kIFx7sE9MJeS3KWR7V+rxgmEnG+ZTf1hCUSYu8qt7wOfr5c2tsSB/w7VwPz82t/c5tsZbAVXsZI/bF38vqYN8St4cMugKB1NsbWJMA2tJCG1LgoY/YvzxHt/z4wqVGg4tAxTgIlTYdRglpHqqD1wK99rGyC8plZSwpA8XhmSNK+9w2329lA7NXkqcY9qsz88pBzQaF1wjnmTSDlSnY5svsQRkERgcmFDmWb0wjCNwGGWfYHg45m8hOb04Klx/bUuJ0KJNFCYV5gIar3PKn489uevBaMcGpFjHiPoffwg+DzpJZiQ2jcO1ZkBLGOn+yzZw5ShbiW3soDyi9A2ALcFdtTL7Yu4thzlcyr1KG6bJtnhVQ2wRnK4+gBhvhllyS8UqGbdC4V+5ygJ3le+TU1l0ibzLH2v1rdS7oeeeoA11vv4nTMenLRrkI3yxhg1QAr7nmtCpoHRc1J7xVGWN8MDzQggTJcOAZjS+2GF1VfTXzwCeY6nWfHVgyVG2fH0j3J4u9AaXYnOIgzWiNs0iBi3Qfx9UW75oYn3PPBVBGsit713zOSivsu3Nf6hIWcvfQn3UOEZ/5BWYRF3EB/UEyEPY7e7WJ4XTfMP03vO1wJQU3pHAV/Iu7wAWA246sLdYGnKar4SHVKiYaYRU8fsDkPGMbGnxySJD7GIh0i6SkcgDj6UM7UO8Uf1donxMBq8nXsk/873clBXSMMZMym+e22/rKCKCgp6cikoKo9VaQmXJF//SQFPkIpmiq0EPSATfw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Government of India Act of 1919,Divided provincial subjects into transferred and reserved categories and introducing provincial autonomy", 
		"option_b": "Indian Councils Act of 1892,Increased the number of additional non official members in legislative councils", 
		"option_c": "Indian Councils Act of 1861,Introduced representative institutions by associating Indians with the law-making process", 
		"option_d": "Indian Independence Act of 1947,Marked the end of British rule in India and declared India as an independent and sovereign state", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010131", 
		"question": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRHny/72OXiQImEF43CFEvIsJiCjXanLeuT/3ZJ1Z0iBiBtr4HnFprbjt1wJz6xe6ouRZDACcoJ1ycSA2Oq3zX8BGshAk4Ey5oNfbvFT2DK/fdrcYOpmyy6MIkL5dDW8EHlikXHGhWtTupD74Sj7QNIygCoNqbhH0vcDA+ig5pes1w25iALC8XqVWrx3UWSLsN2h70aSo4s9po/Sd9t8Uj2VYY6pua0szkjo", 
		"answer": "25e3ZZPyyFstHNhHMxy6E5pcYbGfGZc3", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRHny/72OXiQImEF43CFEvIsJiCjXanWfOL63JR0IxydhV474mTJoKDj5BMAiehf7I2afjYRf4dm0tGd3uv5hHNYc9RBiZR99pMRe7RMyTqkZ9jaNPd4yy6QKFL1dSr9EH80gDnTyl5ZpYG67Ge6Wt537RQ2hIZrrfguOcSW3a2d60S9lUa21HKCCLxnBRSYvMOt7wOIr8I/p8yDpXLP/PHqn7jD4tEdawZRupU/Yhu4kq8b/S94Xs70exdH96nXbkLoMiaiKQ0Yucrt0jRlw4UgTmU14BZQh8NXd9R72YrtqCtyX7LS3C+HIy32Fdx5sBHIJw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Bo,mb,ay", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010132", 
		"question": "24GwbdH32Ar+5YwiRwr7yvO/Om2QE20Gpm2QEqFxZGbmUamCeuX7ibR0KUibiBt6/HKGt631t2Abjrxe+s6WfmIXdo4v4d6N3uX5hFJOPdVQk5Rn8JMQcrRJ332vdcfeJL5hwC6UL0CwRjqpRGBmmyffjnlS6Iq1tTOzUZoMkkVjxMc1vPV+BTL8o/hryee0WFFeeQKo4Q==", 
		"answer": "25K3fpTh3xTv+ZFgXRiy7PP7PGqQImEF7z/SC/AhMpAICpIBOJ85/n5oPLZdvug=", 
		"explanation": "25Gxe4Xh2Bv/44wvXF79w73vOnzVESITpmuUV6Z6MGXrUefha+Pq25IxJlKNzU9z9zb1t6Tk8kBPhqYb/YaaMAsNeoJuxpCq2Ork0HhVJtJNlY4y7YlffvVTyTnte9qbNPZrjkmPMUDiaTS4CmQ0mzeWo3JSoYL71CSvFItuk0BwBAHZUvtu727YMokZWR19tA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Morley-Minto Reforms, 1909", 
		"option_b": "Montagu-Chelmsford Act, 1919", 
		"option_c": "Government of India Act, 1935", 
		"option_d": "Indian Independence Act, 1947", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010133", 
		"question": "24KxfJmzwxzs8pclXB33henwdULeB2sQrT+rW7Bgf2P6GOfWZui+5JJ8JVmbnht09DbSq6Cw1FwBnLxS/ZuafjZDX5h8zd2L2/23wmNOPoZQkoUy1IgQav1Ozzi+NMPeMvsu9TzQdhawKmiARn8CP/oFuEGaN5l3tNfVteM=", 
		"answer": "27C0bZLn1B2q9ZxgRhb3hc3tOn3ZDWEYonPDfqZzeWLvVbPLeOi+6IRiIlGLgVJ+4TS1saCVA30jbhNXM1ZDkQCP", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH+1BTo8pczEhH0hen3MCvTDGwCt3aXR6Z6ZDHCR7THY+/y0Nd3NVOEzU9z9zbWsarm/l0Mirsb/ouNdWIKcI9m2tWKw+juhHRNNsVQn4Qy5oNfaPxFjDCoedbeMu0uwWjAM031JymvC2Z9mjLfi3AWqZCo8Cq5WNMy01lygY93rdw0OdqM3KSF7V74kQOQ2TuURLhnBVGd9cGmq0LcrIs1vNmItXLd5vX3mfDa49tJUda4g8sz6pAVgZ1ZBY3g1Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "directly elected by the people of those Provinces", 
		"option_b": "nominated by the Indian National Congress and the Muslim League", 
		"option_c": "elected by the Provincial Legislative Assemblies", 
		"option_d": "selected by the Government for their expertise in constitutional matters", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "010134", 
		"question": "25y2KIX71Fns8oElQB/mzPLxdW7DF2MTr3aQWqZwMHP6FJPKa63ZxoF0NVKEiFVvsnnI44z+81oOz4lY/c6QdmJSJ9g6iOKMxO3z0XBTKoZ0lZd39toIeeZFjDqkYtHVYOphjnqIIgWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVyrdUovJBxberdxH5TigyKySSViMcnvBQ8nA==", 
		"answer": "25K3fpTh3xb4t6IlXBvgxPG9jChK97tI0Gt9sf5ovG/ZhA==", 
		"explanation": "24e9e5j3xBj47sUwXQn31+6/Im7CBiIYrT+XWqY0eHDtULSCYeu+7phnIk6Hgkk71XPIprfx+xGm0z8FO5Gj7J5oJumtrQvt", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Historical Background", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Federal Legislature", 
		"option_b": "Governor General", 
		"option_c": "Provincial Legislature", 
		"option_d": "Provincial Governors", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020101", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb78SK2VdQzgBM9hMd5reszMsSL0LyG7UOsxieRz36cSrF9UV2X9eem70qd4JU5po2EvzvP/fX1luGT4MsfIg5drZF+cV/8lbFJ1QR4Y8etVBwLw+HRclvjYGCRblRdxcWj+1op9I0wHX41519HwpNfbc5204qkszRwK8VvVTC1rklVyZ1vS1ebe6u93W3q9BU2ezoCa45kvW00rwvcKVBolWidWClV1IZk7JAY1Sdsc3xUlWL1hzGfwEScb5bu6YzlxeH+4Og6ofdl6ClG7WO2+Dgs1o+Z1zqwZA==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFgjO8rPV+nXo8G+gZITEyovIU=", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdH61Rzrt4omEh+y5vLxJn/ZF3cUrWvDc7BndXzhWL6CaOLsib5/I1WIzUx64TbAqrfj4xMfnadL5p2adGIBZ8tC5pC72P23zX8BYp8XzsBfytotc+0MjDztZMbULfdgy2CUZ0P5YCyvATB9mnHCgnkWgY2//Ca1FNk4zRgnmI5r+YgxM8Ga1K2d/AH4kQeRnHKfTLhhFRSWu8vo5EXctIo99ciMoz7CtOTrlejc/tsFdhsSsIA/d1O516EN/St6tNExqP/PSGDYs2QumfiaGg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020102", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/aUabQLvn2zNdYCX/Jol19+3XPoqn87hMriqVa54qadGICPqhgxsOd3vDiwX9Vc+dXiYV/5pYGPK4A6SuoesDnLsJgnz/ZdBOwPXmbC2J5lSXfhXIWp4X7xjO6QN934hQ8ncd364gVMtOW2JSduhzh0lbChju+TrttEl2YuY6BxWDcpIc1tMOJ8TTU5rT42tvc/s0faxxHuohrI3qvhK0E+iYhbcbnOUsYqKSKIXboJyGtKQcT/ovs0DReyZAlWSkD9Q0Gq6pqbJQij8yz/GhwD8x4ATquqktOh5t6Hz6YcLS57GbM70J/eHslfMpium0hqQrcKVZxjG7cXC1YhpMr/8Ic1Qdsb31Fn2Lsm3+GgXGMdJbntMISSTd8OzSJlPIFWvhZlifY", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz/hfvtS2FTyUlprVQrGbvBLFVS5w=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgfB/mzPLxNGeQIG0fpG2GQbA0OFjNd+6CYev4wJR4JlCFlBt/93vHraH18xMOz4tU552LeTYWe4V7iPGaxOH6xn1Yc89K2tErsMpfSPxJ3326dcebJOt8x2CHZ1H4YnmOAXN7mjWWvXNEpIf7wiapGJogyBA81pNw6IgeLt6L0LubqFq9lAPC0HSeQ7RqFhSfutzowk2YqYM29d6YoSLU5uC5rvDWsPclQUhTuJR6Zl/8g6dJ6z8oQcemfFJf+eGQdlX/YC2lIQEP7Yvq0DR9zodpf3s94BZVisNXZdJ205ykqD1wON9rGyf6ikpEzpU8TBKacvC/337h8lsycHQ/JYtrqCgn4RuULRRpm3nceCRU1KJ598QQhgwjfGhSmXPkwiuEwHGHdYCj74XxhOb04LBtsrcvLAGhIFvNRZlcSrXGInUyxe/bXP8IY6NpKyzSNdBu8y3xJYTUyzEf1dxgP3bu5jnZk9/weWu1p9L6gcZkEbwUOsiF5Mqjs1TCZR/vHXOnbs60ahzxW3m48Q9rvFgqzmE55mbRCclo9D5NmHGiREFg0i7uLC34w+tg5LaGes4z1vLl0zwZlvM4kJ234xIuSwD7un5R8q22D0tO3hTfEI1WnVp3MLo1HJOR4myEgX/EQnMDP8HwQYGJxyVJmvTwnSF0sdBfDNjZbmA9sY4TWCNtfKet+lB9bp8=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only two", 
		"option_b": "Only One", 
		"option_c": "Only Three", 
		"option_d": "None of the Above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020103", 
		"question": "25y2KIX71Fnp+Is0VwbmhfL5dULeB2sQ5GzDQbdmZXbkWKKCaOLsiZ5/I1mZiFV/93jFpuXx+VdPm6BeqYiNcS8KcIwvx9bJ3vDkhFJOPdVQk5Rn8JMQcrgA2zWkd9ybMPFix3qJJET8JzW4BXRxhnHBi28WvIu+tSGyRskjgAE91pdq4tgzL9LfzaCWqES8gwfC033RSf1HHlqKoce8/kaStMIZpt6IvDDX7bT/leqT2dAPawke/4lqd1e1maEH/2osWc30ax1F8uHAdRTkLmiiZwwS9sCjxmFryos6VWwwtBZIwtIPMZQslCOj+v/V2p1Y1AsMfxvlJtM=", 
		"answer": "25iWKKP8yFvcOSG9u2MDE4BxsfdnVVhw", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH61Rzrt4omEh+y5vLxJn/ZF3cUrWvDc7BndXzhWL6CaOLsib5/I1WIzUx64TbAqrfj4xMfnadL5p2adGIKcMs+kYPdl+buhFxvc/RLg8wy5docc/lN2TOkZ8CbMvt4wWKVM0z/aTivHTB1mjWWmnNaoZey9ia3FM4/xRogn5RsrfozJZeI2LvT6Q21gwuA2WnRR7skBVyc9eem70qdrsIWtNmEvjza+LTalfbU4tsYcUQSvZNrI1O5178I62o9SdixZB5O9aTWc1vgYDyrIk4N+Nn3zzRgyMJ4BDtttBlJkMNea9MzxJngtTExM418HDatsARowtR/UBmCfbOt1Wyk9Fp/dH49aolsqCh1pwCOaFU+uWSSXzhYgJVu8MRZtBdweGJCkG+swj6FhCWHdYCj4oT5hPuwt7xx9+MiP0SOIUnZWoEFJbLEKHdmz+3bD78cJ5diVwvIHpcUwfX9ADzMvQY/JUs44uUP", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Jawaharlal Nehru", 
		"option_b": "MN Roy", 
		"option_c": "Mahatma Gandhi", 
		"option_d": "Subhas Chandra Bose", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020104", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV1790On8OmbVQ20X42uLV+NXYnjzRLSCXv/x2ZhiJlCazVJ1sief9/evtWnvp7HNPzd65lMAjTRR9ik=", 
		"answer": "24e9YpTwxRzut4c5Egr6wL3SIHjcCm9Rj3qCVbZxMozSEEvm5wMn8U4G1gz8xK0=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQwxD655ZgYgz91fLsNGfDQ3UUsXrDU+NndWWjW6GCfv/x2ZhiJlCazVZ69nOGobyw41sKz4pJ4JqWYypDeYR5zcKH2uH50DFVPIZQkoUyzZQbdfVOjC2ieN3PKf1vwi6MIkT0YiuuRHl61BzXmH9e6NLioXX7YNIygAUgmZd3/skwL5eQ366W+ki8xi+M2HKQCLlrHF2XvMGmq1CIoZYtpo2Mtybe5rTtkv2T598ZLkhFtpJ3I0+0kugb8S0wRYigZ1JY9OfVZVGtJjqsKk4J8c6j9GZg0os6VSkX+xJLjY1BZ8F/wpCkiDo1Jo1rGSC141RSyIRzTBKSNKmw1Sjh80E+d3YidoJguSMh4QCaaFU+uWSSXzhYgJVu8MRZtBdweGJCkG+gljDLhneOcZaj6sDygP+wo7Zt4bcuPVSUPFPWFosTd/PpKWN7y9WVMahoO5onOjf1MdwjvBX8IZGB2nkf1dMlLGPi8GqNmsi1Gnezo4LqzuRkG68PJdDJ+ou1tV/GdDDkYWmbY9K0XQH0D3L3x05ivg4giCQe53ffAMl44Cwfn3CkTEF30iHvfjy1nrsc+pCBa4syx/zj03IfnrRVioj73RB8TgqviG1GoZCMD2hHyBT6G8wA0QxuG7UPAJPVsmzWhnPASm4Ma8u2LL2UzyVFl+7whG5vtoQXFZ+aLQ3exp4nxhPxFfV8FXf/p5b2Lv0ZGSQo87YxxOK198W9c/a2bHEiZgn1nasGhJnFAui01+WYuxay3g==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Accepted by all parties", 
		"option_b": "Led to the formation of the Constituent Assembly", 
		"option_c": "Rejected by the Indian National Congress", 
		"option_d": "Rejected by the Muslim League", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020105", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t1cKgqlV7c6ZfzBDf8tMx96aw+3j0XRPJ4ZliZN36ZgTZbRXzS7tct3JM+ou3nuUZ0P/dS68FnQ0liiWp1IWmoyitS61FItuk0EOmLRs7Nw5MdKRzei6wReEiDKK2Tu4RrltEFrZm8+84kySoY54lsKDtiDe5+e5lf7V+d0CYwRepsZ7Zla9mawM/Go5Eeu7ZgFf+PDFZFr5YAmwNAsQ+8f6lnJm1MIvT2g5/RFBwpdeZ4BQ2Zb3qDskKtljGj36rEIA7pp4VhbWfbP4gTGwsGkxSXQ8bYNutG06p0+IIFE+iX+dWClckY5/7ZAenBJmcy9Bnnn2h3+CkyqObpaj6I/ul+3ztPtYPaEzqmAOcC63qppX2COU", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz+Fnr+YFgezewDbm4SXZFF7HmzNz7mUMRzw==", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhf7wJ3nVAHZRoXqAU7ZndTHOeufwYfSyiZYxJFOEgE51+2XS47f14VwDmrxS5oCeYjtDf4VriMCG2+3jzXJAP4ZQkoV99pMMaLgAyjS/Z8CbMOxh3mGTIkGwczG4RHlwkTCWhXoWqcOY+imoQNMj1RA8gsdZ/ts5MdWTwOiV51/4rwiG1XrRQbMkQA3K4Y6A7gOdsoUtsMnNpTra4LTtkv2T2dAPawlc/5Z6bEuwkuga8CUtXcz0YBNd9KTRIUfsOWiqKU4J8c7qxDRm0YxpW3wg4Q1DzsNXbMQzwpDlqHIxf+5lGyCuqlBVwppoHzaFZ7i10mT9oEI+Zjo/bY8tvigmtU+LKU0+jmTcTS9ZnYV9+5ANnQ1wQWF8kkX0gyuOjWCBaNPKwsD1lqjxrKpssqAoO1OFNkiYVIgfZKbTIidmwuzbJKhYOp5pVwznKdwh8jj1YLWb0T4f1cozbz/O2gnQ0sLzP2y5upP1gs02ELoNN9/B7M/3sRzkbi3yNXSHc876TUjRXG/93gxprlgjxzNQ7nDZBYBx8m0ZlnvwaktqgTPpeGm1n7FSqo2IP6c/1/ztnTse2KUhy8u34BU5By2Vrj9Us5ffW1RKjVjTH8kOyg5uHLsNHYLY8Wya1WbRWWgUP8f4QYGJxyVJmuLlznV1utAaXIGLYFnahNpmwQOiQfl8WGbjrMb/Mu5VCyQP9bxi3uS1os+1YbOFP3YvYhi7QK9O8oYRaUJ2EAHSF2RcdL2+FokRVuFd1maKvglMTn5HRVPC/60YWAqur8rLa1bQX78oBhuiSp0mVN24SkLCNP+tiDbGFP+d1WSxUVcxRy6IJL4ZpSbjaYn/Jh+q039l6oHkMVJeVJcSOGfxbSutrabDKRQzayU2IMpAdVHQWR4pkTDXZ/BpzbMIdVgMVK+yCkRWuRdJmiySAV4F4RVKD+WZSFZnCaZLM08Y2SKwH7RffQ/ZgzcIgk/c1SP/af9HNEo3fmDThkKgyssyyb/ojIrBB9H2bbsUwM0XILMbQpPEDE9cjvrp6qHpHywdA25yI/rNTKKA6RugQuHg4tfVylcL3bYNdn4oNjyGi5PAsC56IOVWanFYrj9ZqcbXdAOkmYVW20RgQxms9E/gAWIosRlna5blKtndM4jl5F8fEC3JVrVKgvk4ySThdfzeagkrDncghQ6feJLFwXSqM6jyweFJEhCr1JGLUot+rEl9wcymxkgApDU1pX3sHnfIe6e/vlIUcyUtG/bmEUsCClgh5zzlGBIv7ONG", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020106", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV17myun+OSvDF3AUrXiXWuN7djH3XKKCTeLw2oN4M0mMg08702XVpqjy+0pPjqtY5pybeSwEPp9giMSB0qTUxXNIPcNQ2q1794kWc/oA/DGseouZHDIi9Cs/IsfP5Awe0Sc3/A==", 
		"answer": "yu3hbW1FhmwWwoDm3ZzqsGKwTQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn3g3r+8UzRgz3y/rrPSvfBSIFq3rDcax6Y2XqQLLHYPm+6IRiIlGLgUI783XFrLf0/l0Iz7xUqZqXdWIgf4lmxtWdl8n+12JIPMgEqoxz6toIfecAn2X0NODTKe0u2W+TZ0H5cTC5AXQ0nT/ChTwE8dX75iK6QMl3xhog1qVq5Nw1L9/f8KaX4Uz4hwiGnCLCCK5hEECK9cin+QOIqId4pd+EvzHe+O25iezS5NsYXgZusbJ3ZhuflqoA9i8sEeW9ewFC/uqQUVjsLmi0Jh1d+Ivz2nVnhoQmTykg/BoGi41SZ9B22JzhsjE1f8JsVRq0p01Bh4B0XgPWY7yrkHj270UwZn8vJYh0/Dk9pE++Ol1qk3iUDCtegoV58N0cmxAjdGEAzS+01H+/iGDPbJ/i5cDrhPuwobpg97MzLEXAN0WYQoUZJZrOI25zxKm1DLJVPJFmG2LFMtsp7jzqM9aV0T1NxNElb1ry5yaQn43ZPGS9ppe1ztV4EP8JIpHJ7M/3pFOHdSvkYXucdMb1TQH/QTz31U5xvx1l6y4e+3bRHJx6+zlNv22jTElmnj6iSam99sfVSH5UNH5xdAtGWQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": 290, 
		"option_b": 296, 
		"option_c": 302, 
		"option_d": 389, 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020107", 
		"question": "2523f9Hk1Avvt5EoV17gwO3tMHjVDXYQt3aVV7A0f3ejQK/HLv3swJlyIlCQzUhv82LDsOXj4kMfgLte7c6Lf2IBe8tswN+a0uq3wn5Tc9JMn8BR65QMaP1U2TijYJT6M+1rw2yMPhqyKGp7onSybya0FHWY+osjeg==", 
		"answer": "25u3ZZj90A3v88UiS17mzfi/J37cBnAC43CFErd8dTHzRq7Mbejy0NdiM12diEg5PB7Q4g39bbdr3ZQNTUMpHg==", 
		"explanation": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7mzfi/FmrSCmwUtz+uW7BneX7tFJfOb+O+xpExdgXd2xc75n7D44b/+UAbhrxO7ICLMAMQbY5iytyQl/P21zFVPIZHlY5h7YkLPPtGjG71LZTWJfNsy3yTawX/YXmqDHl3nHGE0yoWv4ap8GevW5olxQUgk5R949x8HsWWzaGA4A2RiAKL3TfRSbNgUQ3K9dmt+UbctI14p8idozfI8frt2uzb9Z4bcAFcvINzehuvg6kd/Tl4bcaIZiZD9KTCZET/JTumKRoc7cL102cpwI07HX088V9WkIpYYcV/z9j3qDMkOt4qAjaopgROyIA8SxjWdrj41WTh40E6cTopcJ4tqygnpE+IJxR8nyuSQyFYmoF/+9RZlx0jaWdF3GT1jjqZkyWAetP344W8l+3jsLxg5qoxLAGTIV3MU55cUbvJNCdly/rbBKgcMJBpAzDnLsFu6Da5NJ6RnysIwMslPHLp4CuNm9vwKiW8oZ30zvZkHasJJdmFwMWzuV2LITTpLj2EY9nxGRz/D379kwdrsxE3zSIE5HuYDYV69jkImj6yUARplyriaW6y1rFaqpaGes4Bwfr61DwTkfV037fy0xQvSwWvhGlG8qWMXFlCz1jfG95H8AErTL0FEZeR5WyF1WLfC3sEacu2FaCCgz5d1ubjnSFyudAaXYnOPAvShN0jxA7xEul4QWL+6Ie5Lv0MSm0iuqZ5z62iuMSoYfqwOXEjYBT6VO5S+ptWKBJpHgjYFjcDILmtXZMRVuxK1nLDmQAIU3dMDEiM6K0FVEmrv9DHYGXTbKQPTg32YqcQAI75WgfbPfTp3DnEA/0bEZEaZK/M4OVhNIjR/XZo", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Directly elected by the people of the princely states", 
		"option_b": "Chosen by the provincial assemblies", 
		"option_c": "Nominated by the rulers of the princely states", 
		"option_d": "Nominated by the British Parliament", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020108", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YN7qyIN0KlmHmRZSqErIl631t3oBi6Fa586xcTYKcYVuxJCq2Orw1nRSIIZTlY4y8JIaPPlP3yntZ9HaNO0ux2DAM031JzyxAXNgnT7YmTxCp8Ov/SL7d9U50wE7gpJ949x8HcSM3KWR5FT4gAmQnG+ZTf1GA12NvN2gq2qSpIs5u429oz3N/fr6n+vv/uIFURxTq4NyZlWo2oEgohY2ZcCxKDNH/aT5b1DkIWiOMh0R8Maj+nFowZcsHWw58Q1Bh4cWY9MzwpDh/CIxLdlzVSSzt0wA05x5HxqZZ6n4w23l9EZ/fHRrcYJo/Cg5pAyIIVtwiSuIQ2xFnIUr3d8XhhBqaXpFkmKgoyyYhWiNcIqj7Y/uxfz4pflB4KozIFKIdXXWUoQda/PwNWhkw+eYCLVgPaNpICrvPt1u8zf8YJmSny0F1ZkmIHvr+z2QnMq1MHb6sJ3rnNF1AP8JOJHX7NintV/TISznYWmbY4v1WwfmSjzrxw9xshUgxjUDtyBfScqjhyiKKrnfkvbiYjKK", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz4g3r44AtVxDmiNS/PHiQAG0DsXqARuHrBbO1vXeQohI2XdGnhgvZ", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgfB/mzPLxNGeQIG0fpG2GQbA0Z37tFLPKa63zxoRlZ0+MjE9osn/I47H48hMKg61Y/YeQfjFDaoQv3NiMl8f4ymJVOtJRn45mpLsMb/FNzjG0NNLUMr56xmvABVf5czCuDDBdmjXfi3IWmJG04y61V98kjFUln5NwrZpsZJeM3KmH+w2MjgPC/XedCJRqFV2Y9eO9+E+VrcIUsMyKpDeb9/X0n7ja/p4YZwtdsYIzI0y1g6BJr3l4Qs21fAF3/9jeVVzoYC2vIg0J8MTtxTR+w5AsHWEx+BsGi40WSNV/z9XFqTUlLNkqRGru9QgAxpp4HwOecaT4x2325RU9dGkuYcpism0hqQrcC1V8k2WZWGx8nZN4998X1TRvfGEAk3Cg02bf1iW7dJaj+4z9i6j0qa9q9qYjaVWIMBzLU4wIdvPJKSdmwuzbLqlSIItuAzfjM8Fu3SrqJZuW0yBN2ddgP2Xo5CWLhsT6NyWuvNLthtE2BLAQI93E/cK4vhzIZ2P1KXjTdtn7TwH+THnrn05yvgwtiDIV+GPKCZ16tSgBm32kRlZlhiLzLHquhP5x/5GCdoMin7Xf1DkYi7g4npXzlBIoTwGpzXJKvIuNRkhGyEeWKsUC1gwoA6YEWNbi5myCkHvVRWhAVo7/EuiEzD5a3+DlwiF8sZROZpiPOBzWj9AyhT6YQfRqFW7jq4nrL/kWHiZVlxLZpb8Ot2PvnqXPXGEz", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct", 
		"option_b": "Only Statement-I is correct", 
		"option_c": "Only Statement-II is correct", 
		"option_d": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are incorrect", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020109", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t0cAm6lXqZ2LYicNeZ9niN+Pl/D/wTFiPMhXjolm8Z8RaLRh3y6oedbXOb55z33AI0DkYiuwDX5xkHHFhXBTpJr79z77QNIygAU9hpJ07Nw1M9nf1q7Tyl+xkg+R1Du4RrltEGiXhtqp/0aRpYws9eSk6w7VwPz82trB+coCcQASloh7alqy17gb9zwxX8uxe1Jc9PbVIVXhLCe3MwsZudjm12B6hosnHX088V9ljY1Fdslnw53qqHIRLN5vGDG2ugRCxod5W1eZev2s2G3t8hUvemo+aYt5tSI74Q6SLBR9lWaRWSJYgJkr7NUJhwFweGFUnWLpjTG3jlmBa5vq6Ii8iu6wtLFmsrAzKFWFOFnWQp5cYrrWImkyy+uUG6McOowoFjDjfdYh7iv8I4LLnYR0g5bV06k/CoRgFqN8Pis=", 
		"answer": "25yRKJ793QCoM596CAFrxx3aStwiPM62Ow==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn3g3r+8UzRgz3y/rrPSvfBSIFq3rDcax6Y2XqQLLHYPm+6IRiIlGLgUI75XfV46v/4xMLirxe+4OWficHPphgxNWFzqT13TFVO8MEio9i8ZYeaP1Pwn2icpT5Mvd6x32IZ2z+YzC8RER8kXH1i35fpoavtQqyR8k+zxtypot544gzOpfOgPzFpA2vjg+B1DuCTakkHkGN9dqg7gOIpZA1po2LviCb4Pz82vHd9NsbZwZWuoh8Zhuzkegg9i4xUIT0bBtd+ODVZRT5KC3jNAsc7dij33op0oosHUo7+gxSi5dDZ85nlrn3rzc9PcFzVTq041RSyIRzTQOfe7P4xGek9F06NWokdZ9hvTk8rgHcJ1I+jmOZDDxDm5Zi8NMchkgjamZUlDbzhy+KkmSbedPm54X/kefioa1m4eMhJlPAGEnLWoQRdv+AFG55wvrXTadSN99oAyrjL5Uj9Tf2Mp+A1jwe7NccIUPv/TnZn8j0N3b6p5r4mpRiHLpAFMPM/cKkuBzubyfoIHPTdtn7TwH+THnrkxlgpR1lyS0c53bMDY0/5igMim3wQEokhi/lLF+umK1I45abeoAlk9T/zjcdmvhh35n2xxg4Bwu1zWtLt42ND0xA3UHaH9kOywduDboFVJXe/2CDm3/EUjwfet7kBLuCzThJzur+gCFJt5VORZ6BOhDVids1iAC4FfU5VCfhqZT+OLw4H3cg878x2uKxosa6YfqrIiU9agiyGe5V/5pFfAd/UQbSFyEPc72vQo5eR+9dkljfhAtBSmwFRVvC/+gcVQHqutbHeGPQYLQPTgnrd7tFEo70T1XIMLGawTvBRq+ThVKyXlAsQTTdNrUf4EfxdoD9MAe2lyhp9tPgckJeRZcEfCH8ZiuKrKiLGERWdSodK1E8yKElS7EMCZUL", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020110", 
		"question": "24KwZ9H+3g/v88U0WhuyzfTsIWTCCmFR5FCBWKZ3ZHj1UbSCXOjtxptkM1WGgxw75n7Ht+Xj8kEZiqwb6J3fZCoGPox6wdSA2eO3wH5CJstBlJQy4pUNPOBIyX2EetDSIfAu7WGONFH5cyy4CmQ0tSLFj3FUpJrkt+WrvtDYMm2bMUc10TKLSds=", 
		"answer": "25+5f5D70Avm9olgfBv61+i9Xkkdi7xnekUXzCwwojS0Cg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdG0/hvg8oY0Wwj31r3NMHjfD3cFqnCNFeN9fjH3XKKCbeLw3ZJpMxyGixtS/HLPouXn9kBPgqdN7IrfcjtDVIp4ydiIxej2yDFvNs5Wj8B96to7efdFwT+oZpSKc7IunzfUcQXZc3mxBXlw1DXZnXIWvIu+tTK1UN8lzAw7mIA4/do1MtSWyaSW+w2sjgeWnHyEQblhFRSNvcvo71GdppYxu8rNvjSb4Pz82tvc/s0faxxHq49wbRuzkegg9i4xUIiHaQBP8PaQV1XhLCmhLwwV+MKj5nV9w45lHUsGtD5LgIZSacFhmtjlsjZwDcxgED2+sUUA94Z9TBaSNKq9wm2k4VksejogYJMtuiQytB2ZOxR3lCuIRCkRt49l7cQQgRFmc3sAvWXzhzKJjHzDPJH2/8D1kajnoaoj3KYvO1TAIlTXFoATc7bEZ3N6z6ncIqRWNpxzHjTjLpUc+Sr2LIOA1jYDl5kCHTfG+Siclsb0KyWtsoG5mtxzVJwIN9jX5Mq58FPBITfpJD23dMryTQH+SDzb3ANovgwxzSRcqGPWDMlN9CcIkHqiSARUgCbzbXjhgb9PqpaGes4BwfD/1DYVluA4kJ23wBU5Bye0g2xXu5CKSlJbjXXFDcgKxgU3QPQDAYKR/GifgX7VWTwAcNjzBeiTyykInczzhGR+q5kYUJ/OHhzIhdIz3B6+D7o5YW/ouoP/Mu4QRiQ48rcxyeKzpc+4YbOlInY9agj3UPwZ2ZRGaQp6AwfcCWRhZbC8Q997yUOILur2kmJ2dnstIDkw", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Mahatma Gandhi", 
		"option_b": "Sardar Patel", 
		"option_c": "Subhas Chandra Bose", 
		"option_d": "Jawaharlal Nehru", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020111", 
		"question": "24KwbZ+z1RDut5EoV17RyvPsIWLEFmcftz+iQbBxfXPvTefKYeH6iZ5lNByPhFV6/jbVprbj/lwB0Oo/ZklWqTrDzuE+6nWiBsYD", 
		"answer": "25+5ZoTywwCqpdFsEk+rkK295tyLT0lMgnLMlDqu8BJjKQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rxv80b3eJnjVDmAduj+MVONdfnXqVefKa+H6iZ5lNByPhFV6/jbVprbj/lwBz6dVqaSefjcCbJIvmoTFl7WukSEBB85B2qFh958SfvhZjCqsZ5TfKe19wWKWIkGwZj+pAWI0gDnTyl9ZppCv/DOuQNM4zlU9kMdR48w1PZec2KWWqES2kgnC2nSDS7gkHlrZocah+AOYoZsEu/GDhTretNXqif3e8tISIh9TrMZ8bFWvg6Ed7T49VYi7ZlJv9OfVbFboMmj6a05MoJ+1mjRoyIZpVH10/BpKhsNfdtMz0JH2ryZwMshvATq0pARPydRYWhSTeb+9wii1sRl/JCN/M8pZtCh1gByPLVl8lnLcWy1C1JRq7dsckUR0dHtI3HLygzmfiWuIPIfr7sDfiubjtLB357cuJk/AOlqYf4MYbLKMZ2Z8zqmSGeZYNp1mAyfifcEm+Xn9MpeSy3ku39czO37z4T6QncO1P2qo853vi8Y2AKgPdsjA6Nmk8GjPZGPlJH+Scs7nGR/1XXm43AhxshZlwCQR/GfcRMl94DlNina1UARzlzXlLH2thbEc6Y2AbJojxvb41CQV2MBwmtvWxw45Sga3lD9Os4CaD09K21HEH8FHxQQrArAMEZjF4S2CmjbEQ3lNe9z3B7zH4CNGyff4mnRptp8AGcyPIh2bg8pmzh6/APF1TCfsrInpKfkRSnAk//JSxeOyo8OvYOetI2tqYBT3d+BP9phTbRA7Q12RRXUWNOHs9NGRxCxhwSjyqb7PYI/IAw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "December 9, 1946", 
		"option_b": "June 3, 1947", 
		"option_c": "January 24, 1950", 
		"option_d": "April 28, 1947", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020112", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0hHr+YIlEhr7wb3rPW6QKmwVqn6NEop6dHTzUanGa+P9zNdQJEjJgl07oy+S9OXy5VoBiOhP5s6LeCdDXYRh28SAw/HyymUBEtVXn41w6INYb7RT2Dy5YceEYlb2jWUH1zKadbd1+kwdqzg=", 
		"answer": "25i5bJSz2A2q9sUmRxL+3L3sOn3VEWcYpHHDUKxwaTOqrP2TuUqsyhN/vlODFVg1", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgexD2wO36O2/VDWEU416ARuN7djGyDfOVLuD/zZIxM1SMzXh0/GXSqrHl8l0bz4lI+ouSci4aPoovzsWF2/23135XNtRBk4d8pJgQeO0MjDyheNvMKfBpjmeUZ1H/Jz+vBX1x1DDYkzx1p42o4S6vQc4+zxtyn5M4/cQ5PcSa3eoPIWEDALjUIYOM4lfLzD4Y", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Made it a fully sovereign body", 
		"option_b": "Reduced its membership", 
		"option_c": "Removed its legislative powers", 
		"option_d": "Dissolved it", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020113", 
		"question": "24KwZ9Hk0Aqq8oklUQr3wb3+JivEC2dRt3qOQqxmcWP6FJfQa/73zZJ/MxyGixtv+nOGgKr+5EcGm71e55rfUTEQe4ZtxMnWlSlIId7AA9+yo/BybvqsWvo=", 
		"answer": "25GqKKLy0hHp/4wkUxDzy/n+dVjZDWoQ4WOXgi9SluYITSpBu0Of6Zg=", 
		"explanation": "25GqKKLy0hHp/4wkUxDzy/n+dVjZDWoQ42iCQeNxfHTgQKLGLuztiYN5IhydiFZr/WTHsbywx0EKnKFf7ICLMC0FPp9nzZCq2Ork0HhVJsNKjsBT94kacfZM1X2FcZTMIe0u2maFZ0r8YzyuEDB5kTzUj24Wp4X74S++FPsk0xA/lIthoYg9MtPf0a3T/0yrxgOO2XiFTbkkBVvZocah+AOMr5ExocSCv3LU+rTdn/vW/dwOcEgL88YuOg/q14AMuDk9Q96xbFJC/6TEaV3+YCuiNw8e8N/6lmFn0oslHU0x9xpLgIZEIpEimti15WZmc419HTa042BSh6Z9VRKYcK+5kFj24UY+cTo8ZJktuSEwohuZLBR/iSuIRCkRhIV589EXkAp3PV9SmWXphjqFlCWAetP344W8pPvjpbRh/rplq/DC10vcTYz9DVGcBo5spA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Dr Rajendra Prasad", 
		"option_b": "Jawaharlal Nehru", 
		"option_c": "Dr Sachchidananda Sinha", 
		"option_d": "VT Krishnamachari", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020114", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV17/xPTxdW3FDWEFqnCNEqxyMGXrUefhYePt3Z5lMlmHmRta4WXDrqf87hNQzZKTFq+7j57DFXUHOtLFTJ8=", 
		"answer": "25i5Y5j91lnl8cU0Whuy5vLxJn/ZF3cFqnCNEqV7YjHlRqLHLsTwzZ5wZS7q6a8I/x3jDYZ61NjR5LE=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rxv80b3eJnjVDmAduj+UU7A0cTHhW6PbLuL4iZJ9Il+diF874HPWsaDj8l0bjrxS/4uMMDYLf58v39Gal/D213pEN4ZTk5R6pJ4NffJUxTOqNMDTJb59236SIkj1JzW8EzB7knHCgnkWpIK18WePXN934QYhk4p64dF8K9aMmauc5l6sjxKXyH6VCLJqUXCctsul6UaO4Nt09ZzU5WSXtPX3nrja5J4DZwRW/49rcBu6nroa7Go1VM2gYRxMseveIXDoIy2uJQsPuZqymjQ4n9Z/HV088V9nkZBTb8J/z9jzvSFwO8R5Bjy2tUFEh5tyHz2Xeqi5wnGksgFzNStyMNoh/CwztQqOaEB2nyu/QyJCgIl/68QQmgojam5T3HfkjS+fhWHNbXgpP06Bou5fF+dXvF7TfA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Enacting ordinary laws", 
		"option_b": "Representing princely states", 
		"option_c": "Ratifying international treaties", 
		"option_d": "Making of the Constitution for free India", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020115", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb72iWxUdkjyQM3hcdK6NszMMKL0KedqEC3kAOGnHmICJdlBlWRtNyk6k/cjocwp9jNvTPS8LT9le/dsMoDZ0hVqo97alW717gb8SQ7WNi4bQEL9+vCIUDlJWinNQ8b7cLt0TRmwMIAU2099VhVwqBZbNNn34zxqDs/MfFkVQG/oldPydQ0bV7MNIG2kFzs5RUQd3AuZp5kqigm4T2ZO1tyj3+VQyIRm5V/8tkXkAAjaWdF3HfzkjaZgXGGc53wq4/6xen+4LBt9qY3LE+EMFLMFp4Tc7bSIm51xKmyA6JVMt9mGSamOMY6/Tv1KYWc2j1NxNElb2fv/SaWgcLlMXz6vJS5idtgEa0ON9/G7Iu2vliHZzbvJXyeY8XgWASwX27x3Q1spxQg22EE4GPMSIBx8yEYm3CzTEAkhi/lLG+0lK1Z+5eLcZpxwOHt2jcD2Pt+35j42g4oThCumXZMvMmSTldGw1OUDco2Ta9uyg1JxrUqLdxC4Q==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFgjO8rPV+nXo8G+gZITEyovIU=", 
		"explanation": "25q6YpTwxRD88pZgYBvhyvHqIWLfDSIcrGmGVuN2aTHJVbDDZuzsxZZ9Z3KMhUlusnfIp+X540BPnKFc54eZeSECcIhqiNmHl/D/wTFRIclHn5NhpJUZPPdPwi65fcDONPdhwCONJk75aT79K3J+kTLCg2pTu8OJ8DS0WM8jyRo81op3+804fNWGmYKS/0ywhxSO3XfRZrhsA0HZtMCsq0qIs8IrvMqDuDTS9/X3mf2T+dBLdgBX/5ZtbFi5hLtJ9yx4Use6ewZC5fHEaFvjbSWiLAcT/okX0wKF6MFE1qUvaWO0Gt4X", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020116", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb71ii1R84+1AA3mJM4zNsvOdqd1bHT50v4rwiG1XrRQLxgUVXZsdup5wOOr4499cKL8TTJ9fnwlP+T5NYOIitdsZVrak+pg6EG9mo5X8z0bRxK8vDZb1OtLzqnLgAc69Kj2nV+1cIvUnt04BdDwoBZd85nxIHYsnICOsx5Gj3663YJndRAUVeifLj4+Wbg6VQxNVMlYY99uSMxpAGfLRRfmX/cQyoRxdk/qZAcmBRsampSmXKgljeOwEaAcoD34pTpgObk4Jhw4aYqK02ZdUjXFosJa7DULmh8iuiITaccNYprGzumLto4+Sv8KZGanzsC1MBgOH7z/GqNmsi1OHCuu53rh8BvVKsPdtzE4s73sVLeIQDuL26Hb9/hTQH/QTzxx05hsh0ozSVQ+3fRHIh9+ShNmHGiCW1qli7hLH2vkv5I5cKLcY8yx7XjzzYZlvVqhtv71QovBY5eaCsq6+VwlhW/4tsn8QQ=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFgjO8rPV+nXo8G+gZITEyovIU=", 
		"explanation": "25a3ZoLn2A3/8os0Ej/h1vjyN2fJQ20X41aNVqp1MHniUOfDLunryJsxNVOFiBt09DbAsaT9/l0Iz7xT7M68fywQaoJ73cSA2Oq3xX9Fc8NKm4Nm7ZQYPPtSyDSjdcbCYPJv2X3AIUriJy21ATB3myTYnm5P6Lez8GeSWt4+wRtyv4l86Ng5MtOa16uWqGy7kkaN2jvAEekzUVGUpcG/7lGZpMIsvcjNkj3V5+Dwju3W/spLQxtBuot9b0L8g6dJ/j82Uty9ZxwL8PeQYBTrNSSvPk4O9t3mxHFgwYxpX2Yw7VMGhZFXbNR62J+ktSZwK8VvVTKvt0xP1Z1oRleCe/210WPhoFQxbDoIaoR+qCQhtBuVJ1o+k3/cSClUmYVvvsMMnBBif2NF3HDvkH+ijmGGfdG6KlxsXW3NyZWoNOX4dkMG", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020117", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9geB/lxPX+J2fRDyI/pneRR+NjcWKjQK/HLs72yJ5jKl2HzVR9smLOpuXF+VoAgehr5pmaYjFDXYRixdmdw+HyhHhPc9JMn8BR65QMaP1U2TijYJT6M+1rw2yMPnn+WzePAXFnmz+MykhercOO+y60WpoHzwI3hJQ4zscxMd6Lza2WqFq5lUaQ2WiBR7N3GFaVsI6u5FHcr5csucSDuDzctODxn7jQ/9AYdgFGqpJ2bFW9m+gP6is1VN+7ehkL5ezRdRT6Lz2vI04a9t3mxHop0oosHXsx+B5Si4xYcch6xoukvjckKMhvG3Ouq0EA1IB9SxKFNLy21Cjw6FB/dn8lcZhssG0yrhmZOlpzn2WIDjoS+gu26WsjIAEgKPv0htw=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Ar58pc0WxH8hfzxMSviBmMCrHHDU7FxMGXxQaKOLu/r3ddlL1nJv1564XnI46zjt10Am+hP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB064hfaPxFjBy+Z9HJNPdhwCztAHk+T05ZrJM1o8cVgBgw", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHSwgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/IXnFBjlRiX6UU6t1Yn3iWOfsa+Xs3NdmJk/JhFV/93PC47H48hMsh6lS+4OefmIMeMt7wNXJ4ur+y38BA8lTn5JhpLkQcflJ2CmocZTSLr56xmvABEr+dC20EGVxmiWWq29FrY65+T77W9x36Rs2n4Y4xccrOcGay+TT/EW9xjSH3WieRv1tAhSXutro/0uZ4IE3p9+Isiab8ezplvnd8coCbQYSuYltI0+0kugo6zk9Q9y9ZxwLxezVIWHjKSetZz4S7s7xxTRKyY8kVH0g8RoGlYJFItJ2xYjrsiE5PcFvVTW1sQRF35VxVhmferr4xGDhoEc+e30uJYtjuG0wuRuZJkA+lW3cWCRU1JBk6dULhkR3dW5U3GXojSqHhCWNedP17pPogOywqbcj5qsiaXSOPFPWFsU/YL3UNWZ+g6mcArBZIZFqEizycZUg8y25JpmGnzYYxNUpIX7p82qNmsi1Omq0oIbwmsFiHbAON92F79m2vVnQbjHqYWmbZ9+0XgfmSm72wE5xvx1l2iQc6XbRB4ds/SQdjT6yTFBzlyLuLG+1l6pZ+cKPcYpxx/3pnTEVluBqnpe30xIqQha1gHpNpsSPSk4P3lGWKsUG0Ek8A7gEVIHQ4S2bmmTVC3gEbcv1FaSegz5N1uLli2U9q59OQYSLbA7UmNVmxxHxDulxUHWtq4n0MPUBHmEp6fJ9w+ak996zcLOXOGQ+agn3euBU/pxFfAd+UUPtFytZabatX5wSAcNA3GbenhNdU3ZGCxrv9KUFVBC+r8GBLmnWYrgOCxqiYapFIM/qSkbddceoxDzIBLeenUa3H3QkWj+RYYQF4BX1fIPgIV/zhGBt9cSlMF5PTMMDNCKzVXiqoLGXAgk0Py0rLMp1f0bGRB5klSzGZ+11mKJMMAwlROiVHFEFmR8Pli2SAFdR8FgWWuWuT0E1L6pRYF4J3Tu0H6ELVRPExjwFnBaIyiesCOlYNFs3cmudzYH+SQioTeasnFdrkmIAn2k=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both Assertion and Reason are true, and the Reason is the correct explanation for the Assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both Assertion and Reason are true, but the Reason is not the correct explanation for the Assertion", 
		"option_c": "Assertion is true, but the Reason is false", 
		"option_d": "Both Assertion and Reason are false", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020118", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRrl+ogpRgr3wL3oNHiQEWcCs3CNQap2fHSjUqjQLun7yJt4KVvJmlJv+jbgtqv09l4Kgbxa5c6teSULapgjiP2A2evlzWVINtUI2oF84Norbv1CzTHtVcbeIe0xjEx/BhpKQOBA13ZFHQ7+2fI=", 
		"answer": "25S8fpjg3gvzt6YvXxP70en6MCvfDSI3tnGHU65xfmXiWOfwZ+r23YQ9Z3GAg1Rp+2LPpraw9l0Lz5xJ4IyefGICcI8v7ciK2/HzwXUBEtRBm5MwCKrHi/2d8hcl0Mp1jm51vw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHS1Q/j5IoyS17RyvDyPH/EBmdRrHHDdLZ6dHDuUanWb+G++552L0iawRtW+3jJsazk/lYcz6lV7c6rYisBf4cvyd6Nl8Hvx31UN8NA2qFg4ZsMPONB332/ccfLL/B9x2yMIgX2aCv9AHV1mDjYjTxBoZeztTOzUckygBgzgpN9/9t8NdnfzaCWqGS2gg+D0juyR7N3BV2NoMum/wO9s5E9uM+BqHLy4LTum+uT89EFcRxbq5NrZl/8mKZJ0is2RMmmcVIZpaiQMA25d2TjJgAZucL3lmNo1cIhWGgw8RsGgJoWVMF/2pnmtDA4PsQqJTKupkgA85x5HxSZebCxxHzh5RU3dH5rN9stsSg4owqOOxg+jWOTDDtUhoUr+sIYggoje31PkTbkizmNhXeKcoej+YXwjO/5r6xwvuMrIE+HIFXLQoQfKfPBKWMyz/2TA69fc5h1GDf2Lpcc68yEy3ldUNGH5O4IP3An", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Union Constitution Committee", 
		"option_b": "Provincial Constitution Committee", 
		"option_c": "Drafting Committee", 
		"option_d": "Advisory Committee on Fundamental Rights, Minorities and Tribal and Excluded Areas", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020119", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sU0Vwz/1r32OyvzDG4ErnHDc+NjeWXrFLPKa+TsiZR+NU6Mjk879nPVoLf550cGgKZIqYeRMAEMcp5ixpCrmaacjJXvQNGro0UBtbyMYN0N", 
		"answer": "25awaZjh3Bjkt4omEjj7y/zxNm6QIG0crnaXRqZxPTHAGufwb+f/zphhJlCIjlN64H+K44b49lodgqlVqYGZMAYRf417wd6Ol8f4yXxIJ9JBn80ywIhRPNYO/nPtVdnZJfplz3zMZ2b4ZjCvCXF61D7QylpDpoe6+CK1QNs7gCc7kY9s/ogfM9qS0LyH7Uj1xjWDzn+QWv1SEFiVtMyg6UudqcIItNmIvX6bxOb8ifHX9dAfIgdU/6VwbUionrwc/SQsEemnexdG8+jJLBTfISKmKQoP+IvTxHV6x4ZrGrJ+gUq6ItQFSc70h+1+vQ==", 
		"explanation": "27a3eoP20g2q+oQ0URb7y/rsdWrCBiIXrHOPXbR9fna5aKnhZuz325pwKRyGixtd+3jHrab1t3AAgqVS/ZqadW9DXcUv+tGD1uP41HBNMsVMm5J7qNojctdIzTS/edXVYPFojkqSJkPkbje6RFN7mTzfnmhTrc770TX1FPh58ltyt4p66Mw3PcXTmZSdy0W5jxSP3XXRR7skN0GXsc+l7k2IoY54h8SKuSbItNf2l/Xa5MoOZ0USjIdtZ1qu154I9CY5U8C2YBNCsdTRdVHhbGifKT4P/Njq0nFn0sImWykX+xFVlopCd8V9wtjFryE1Ms9mDH76kUVKwpp4TRbWRK+5w2ngojnx71eoB6g6QQ21ZyuhRS4=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Chairman of Finance Committee,C. Rajagopalachari", 
		"option_b": "Chairman of Drafting Committee,Dr. B.R. Ambedkar", 
		"option_c": "Chairman of Fundamental Rights Committee,Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel", 
		"option_d": "President of Constituent Assembly,Rajendra Prasad", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020120", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fLYK3szIRhIl+dzVR9smLOpuXU5VIJm6FV7s68fy8Od597zdXJ3uq30HlEc+VLlJNm7Y4KefpUjBy+Z9HWIvJ3lFKOG0uhUzG4RGBmnTzXmGUWvIKo/me0UpojyBByspV569w1MtDf+qee5USskgOHnGyQW/1wHhSLsNih7lTctIo99cmfsDTPtOTrn+jS4tsPIgpL/5J3ZhuehaEd8TkwEc+7fhdZ/+nVb0DRLnqHNU4/y4vC23ZswokoTykn8Q1Qh4cWY9MzwpDh/BE4PsR4GDK040tGh4B0WleyZry+xGHq5xUcencmbJ55uSgJr1yoIFE+mWSRQSVFgIVuvscYhkRlcn1NmXKgljDLiWifcJbu7o7oxfz4pflA/a00PUiUIEjRWYNcZLXUInUyw/2ITaNSMpxzGifoKekgqA3xJdawzTgLxNAuKDfE+yeUm9nhPGD6pJPqzsZzB68POMLM68ey8FrIc2PxM3iDZ9n9Vw+wW3T9kwhspQsxiCUC6WTMSIZ5tTkFmz6TRkp3hi70eWiombAc5YTOVoA12vTQ0w4esPtv35b22gR8SAL7mXdG8peLTkhKwFHYCt5HwwA4CbpBFZTe5GjWlGTVC38CbdzzArzYgb5Xc6pjZLOEnWmRwwgJFMk=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VyEh/8wb3MIWrEBm8UrWvDBuN1YnSjV6jQfOj93ddVNRyrvxta/3TDp67x5RMLhqwb+ouNZidDf5gv3NiMl8f/xXhTPsdK2o90pI4XebRk3jyrYN3VJ75NwWONLlHkYjzxRHF6kHHCgnkWuJGy+CapTZojwQY51oh+rdw0NcTf2qee5USskgOHnGyQW/1wHhSJp8u46lGZ4JYwsI2LuCDI4LT9iPnV5J4EZEhGt4M/QFSyhLwA7D8sWMe6KB1Nsc3eZV3sYByrIk4e9sbu32B9w4dpSmgntBFJlsNQbdJ+05ykqD1wLch8HDat40UAw4Z9WQPWdqT4xGDhoHctfG4idoItuyIjpB2SJVFwjifcQiND1Jdq7ZAQgURlcn1NmXKgljDLiWifcJbu7o7oxfz4pflA/a00PUiUIEjRWYNcZLXUInUyw/2ITaNSMpxzGifoKZUa9DzrJZCbzTxBkM0oKjfk+ziLl87heWS0oIX8nJR/B/8idu2H3dy48gtyzqw4pQ3RGnNpQ2jz1Tk=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only Two", 
		"option_c": "Only Three", 
		"option_d": "All Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020121", 
		"question": "2523f9H+xBrit5EpXxuywfT7dX/YBiI1sX6FRqp6dzHAW6rPZ/nqzJIxM12CiBtv/TbWsaDg9kEKz6FP+s6bYiMFastgzpCd3+G3535PINJNjpVm7ZURI7YP35gZbPoTM0vVrLxotpDA", 
		"answer": "2+TvPtH30AD5tbN9S4L3N/6qpVHFbOs+h2Y=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHXwxjs44wuVV7RyvDyPH/EBmdRtH6QEqB7fmL3XbPXeuj6iZh/Z32cik5o5jaU+umwpgpb2OQb6ICbMDEWfIZm3MSM06T+0GIBNc9WiZQy4IgeeuAAwzvtYNzeYN1hwH2ULlHlczCyCjBgm3HCgnkWi4y15jOyQM8yzgFyt5Rr6MU+MM7f1qbTzki6lBODzmLRGuwoUQXA4Zbo30uZsod4osiftHKKo6K5nvnK454JZxxFuoNxI0+0krsMuD4vXoixfhdF5feQVVzoMi2lKBwYtYv33nEpxY07T2w34F9HjJBBZ9Iz34uknnJhaJsqETKjsAbdCelmvi8Jj89OsNm+M8Ve", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "120 days", 
		"option_b": "176 days", 
		"option_c": "240 days", 
		"option_d": "365 days", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020122", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t2MdiqlW64KaMC0FPp9nzZCq2Ork0HhVJtJNlY4y85sMPPFOzT65cdCbIvtowXyFZ1H4YnmvAWNg1D7QymhercOY+imoQNMj1QE7mYlE4/soPcOa1K2d/A2Rr1y+0julQLgkFFqNvNytq2CTrpEsvNmYpTvU+rT6m/XWsNcFdgcSuYltYF78mKZJ0is2RMmmcVIZp6iQMA24cBStGwAK8cLg3jRmwMI9VWx05wtHloZbZ85nxdjjtSQ1MY1rFzyspgRJ1Nt9TRLWd7Kqwm3n9Ap9A/QfNoTURN7u8MeBsuEw6w==", 
		"answer": "25yRKJ793QCoM596CAFrxx3aStwiPM62Ow==", 
		"explanation": "26asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhfTxNmTCEWcStz+BV6B1ZWLmFJPKa63O25JwKl6FiBt09DbSq6Cw1FwBnLxS/ZuLeS0NPpxu25CM2eX00HRFc8dCjoVgpI4XebRFwimkZtGbA/Fg3XqJM1DkbjazRGd1h3HXhm5TqYeitSK1VdkjxREOmLt2/tw9KNKS3KaHqGSRxg+RnHieWq9hEkDZt8ur6laPpcIqsMCMuDzS+vO5iurc5tcYawdcrMZwZRuon61J2yU2Qty9fAdf+OveLRTuLyawMwcJ7N/q2HMp0oosHWQ1/hBUwpNXcNQ/lpvlsTdwNsN+GnO8rFZDwtRzUVe8dbOt0Xr9oAdpOTp6PN898G0iqQafIBR3iSufSSBUlpJq6tUd1QVwPV1FjGPijjaIwEGOZdPX44nvxezxufl087BnKkmPJlnWFokJYPPUKCd73vrbBa9PJ5B1HiHnMZU99T73KZCd3DgD09xsb3b0tCON0tr0KiWuu5e5ndV7Ef8EN8iF4MX34QWUMWP2KXidJvvhSwbxD0/v0hxkvVghyThQ/2PLSIp6+SgPjH+kTEAklCjsYHO2n7BbqoPObYsi3Pn5yTsflrR3mdvj3Bh8biqYz+mvo8RgwTTre9kouaqFDpU=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020123", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRoG2KRqp3eWLuR+fVa//7iZN4NVmKmV5/smLJtKTi80BPm6BeqaeRdCsCcMtMx96aw+3j0XRPJ4ZliZN36ZgTZat8wgGjJZTvKPsu732TIkjyayD9E3Fn1DXZh3VYqZe+8We5TZo7wQIrk5VrrckyOJeP1qSa/ES7jweMz0efGv1QGVHZuMul6UaOs8I3s42ZuTeb1efqn/XR/MdLdQ1AusZ7akm5lLwF4Wo9Xc23fBdPsebJIUDlJWizIgEN9c7f2Ccp8oosHUo7+gxSi5dDdsl82NXpvTk5McoqBSG1oEFT1NRrXgTWd7K1wGTh9FA7NXMlJYstsCI7pk+IIVl7pmXIDBhZkcBK7cMcmAZvZC9XnWWggTCGkGqceZej5Ia8l+3gsrxw960zKFWJI1nLFosOar6AMWZgw+aOHuZfPJJqAizvKdwr7wX3HJi80C5N3dguNjfo8mqNmsi1KnG7p5f0i9piW6xAMdjT7MX3sV7IdyahKG7cZ9nxGQv/XW790Bo69VWdcbngkaoB7J99oRChpsA=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25qofJj831m7t4wzEh391+/6Nn+QIHAYt3aAQeN1Ynb2UaOCeuX/3ddlL1nJrlR14WLPt7D1+UdPrrtI7IOdfDtDaYp8iNSG2u35xWVEN4ZGg8B+5Y0GeeZTjDyjcJTLL/Jn2meDLkT+dHX9CHV1kDjYjTxCp8Ov/SL7Vs87yxw8k5RrrckyOJec1qWD5ES7hxKH2DudSbNjBFWesI6n7QOIqId4lsKDoibS4OHtk/fdzNA3bCdCq49wbRvu16EauCM2UsemehdI5aTzc135KSuwZx4S8MX303ApyZc9HX089QsGlotTIs1225rhriFwMMsqATu/42dPyYdoVgODcbOskEn381Ayd3YyJZ1orih1rwCIaFB3iG6fWCBI1IVn+9MNkAAjf3YAiH7lwi+Oj3WDedPs7cDVi+z5ofls/OMzIUTAN13LX55carWAMml73OyJHqdQc55jAi7yfdM8/Tf6KJ+H2nVNw9ZgO3/u52qKhszhPGi/vYa5h8c2F7AOIsPE+9L3pFOHdSvkYX6Bb9/9WgHjQkD27wBKpwwsxy9QuyLRG8l8+j8fm32kCWd2mzPpb2/hlbJd44+Le84l2/T4nSYYnbRbkJXkwBQoUgG1mT9ioZeaQl5D1BTCEcIMhAggTKEPEIPd6y2amnjXC2gEcsu2FafHzi1D36PlhmQ9nJ8ARpiHOAzPg9EohFekD/FwXmKtvI78ffoHC2kp6KExxevho8K+NdKpKXcjbBu5GcxW/YZFYRZuBQLSC2RYaLfuVZITUexKxnDO1xNAQnZbRU3D6aNITwGmq9DBeG/SevENGxfhaL8cL8DEQGjfIfimxnCdRraP1U6wXEs3XD+eNfAu9w7kc4/hZBe6l2Yj7YHrN1JeV5AWLi7/bSu4t6SWDkYudy0xaJ5Pfwf0WAMhmTzPPrl1iLcSdQsoT7yiHRAAlwNGkCvBTltKvUELUay5SVY0ar5ALFdKjT67UaYeXwiGxi4Ci0/cwTDlPfNIOFMmfySam1+gn51rlvHoloeOBJTgNP0Y158XKb9VBJ3EEE4MibERqmlrX36Tyjq9J9mtQ/M/", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "all Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020124", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb78y6pR853xAczkJM44s58KN+amYuc5l6sjxKXyHKeRv1rFxSwu8qh6g/csJA9pcyftDab9u25jvDWsPoZYw5Gtoh4I3izmqUA7D49VIT0fxNYsfTFY1jkMyCmI04U94vM1WBmxIc7HThtoEd6jMNkZ8Fg2Zak9AB5ZY1WG3OOq0EA44Z9WQOferr482fp7VwrYX8uJYlisj48shuZLBRxnCuPSTpUmsBm+90bkBZwMS9JknXslzuCjmLPWIGjybK8pOXypb1o87FnKFLAIVTdFq4UZLrSKmZ8hqmMBakcI5NmDififdRu7DDvL4KV03kf39Ulb37ptC6Lk8vhMGu984bxi5RVG7ETItjR/N++v1KHYC3lYW2BY9jxVxz5QXu4xwZg9x4sxiAcqGbKCY9rtTkC3mq4TARFgTTlYX6tj/wVtgi9LgJDWFBVF0uqo6Se", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddzMkjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOh1xrrfZCoGPohg2sKM1PC3wWlRP8dKm5R765Rfc/IA2DWoNNXIM/t82mePKQeeU2ZS9p4mF0BKd4fVoU9u", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5TnxRDl+cUpQV7m1+j6IWPVQ2QYsWyXEqdmcXf3FKjELvn2zNdSKFKamVJv52LPrKuw4FIcz7hO64KWYyoGestmxpCm1PD4xnRTc5cdztgy8JIaPNBSzTu5fdrcYN1hw2OJM1H1YnmtFnVklSPTjjxX6JC+9ii1UJoz0hQ0gsd364goNNLf+qed+1mxkhOW1XSfCL9lAlGd9cGmq1OJoo4xto2Ovj/W8frtibST88wCdgFRtpVycBf8lqYNuDktVs+xewZC/urDXVrRLhqmJh0S94vqxTRoypEmHX0m4RoGgJZCIs58wtjhpCIxM8xjG3OesUVG051yWFe1e7C12Xzw5VB/Yns4JZloqG0gsU+TJhRfj2yJXzgRxtknvoFAwVMjVHsAi3fzwiuDiXbPf5zu5onoke314K1r87dnPkCTdVnWQp8JdqfFIydlw/2TTbJUNt9zFjHtfdoovCnrJYaVzTAD15khb3P19SyN0sLzeXGyttL3i8M2N7AOJcXM/d6juVPJIQr1YX6caNj9Shz1Szz31U52sg4gxmEd7W/aDZtst4LraajnePC+C85RArUUTYs=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020125", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3G7SCb+/x3IMxM1SMzV5183XSrqD+4xMOgawb7ICZfzAAe4ZqxsTJ2OK30HlEc+9Knolz6to8c/pT2DS5YcDSL/Aux33PJlf1Jy2vEXUrqD/qhC0WnIu+tSGyWts7gBEgl4Fsrcc6fMOX3Oiw50Orkg+WyW+YR7MkBlWK9cem/1GTpJc7sMnNsyub3vXum/DS4tIKbkh8uo5tdmeyxeg98C94Qs23ZxxPsfbVYFDkLi/jKAhd7cPmlnB7x4Q9HUo7+gxSi5dDdsl82Njwsz07f91mFDC/40JSyJk8cRiAcbC61XqksQBzNStyMdIh/Dk64SCfPFt8n3ncHXsd1NEyqoklm1cjSWdF3HvvljaEjiWbc9Pz6pPvxfz4pflH4KIhPQGjOlLLQoQIcKfJKGky3eiITatTJZpjVyD/ffE8vBvLYLeZ3TwJ29gyb3jptASWhMj4O2Co88OtwpQnTetZCt/55+O4pxzKYC34YXKVJt/8XEjjW33s1gNguQxq22EX4XTdBsl+9yIbmz65WgtlgCKgb3OzhLtf/t3Mr+2QmAgbsmVbv1CL+8aHqQ==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "2+TxKLfy3Qrvt7EoV170zPP+OSvUEWMXtz+MVONgeHSjd6jMffn33YJlLlOHzUx64TbPrbHi+FcajK1fqYyGMAYRPqldiPGE1eHzz3BTf4ZKlZQyzpsIffxB3jGseJT1JfZ821KOG0uiLnmJFmVx1AXejzxFrYC0+yP7Rt82xBw8kcd364goNNLf3bqS7ln4pQmMz2+YXKhwGFuX9dqn5EjcsI45tsjNtyDU+bTXle7W/dwOcEgD6so/MgLoz+RJ7CV4fsugZxBO46SBNhitcXH3fkJd/d7x33puhpUhVGo8tE0S1dAWY8122JzpuTwkLI19ECG/40VD04F9UxuPNLmxw2vx80Y6cUYlWYQ+9W0BsxqZaHBs2kmuDA1cloVv9dEL1Qlsa2pE3GLoh3+Gj3GGc52j/4+8lenjs/l3+qZnDVOBM0iYdYISdqfJM3Jmw+aVTalSc7FoASfrP9A8vGitbNbFhm1Ukhv+S7QNwH7ztwpMmutAgHM=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "All three", 
		"option_d": "None of above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020126", 
		"question": "24KwZ9Hk1Avvt5EoV17/wPD9MHnDQ20X42uLV+NQYnDlQK7Maa3dxpp8LkidiF474HPVs6r+5FoNg60b74GNMDIRe5tu2tmH0KTjzHQBEMlKiZR78I8LdftOiy7tct3JM+ouynyBIVGvWzeBClE5sCOWqE4WiY658COwVcgLzjd/1qk4yscsPdueyr+S5VT4px+b3XWWSa8kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XLn+te02tzBsPUmIiVHsZV3X1WY2ug6+Tg8UNr0WBNf9OiS2ucJ0rdHTAhFxD0ZZEfBgg==", 
		"answer": "25T0KLO/kTqoNxxdfd7O6xmuV4/ZlcnfyQ==", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHXwxjs44wuVV7RyvDyPH/EBmdd422GQbN7fmLqVqvHLuvx29dhNVmZjEly/HGGt631t3AAgbtP4JqKZCsMcMx8iNaAxffjhHVTMsBQ1sBx65QMdedUyTnte9KbM/t4y2DAKkD9ZTyvFyo0sCOWqE4WiY658COwVch3iDY6l45q4MkydZvf9+i05125igeRy3qcUf1FCE2Yu8mp+Q/cgY40tMmE8RnJ/efxlPnA598Ge0hzpp9+cRf8lqYNuA4qEeOZKD9e//fYaBT6JTqmZw8R9Yvu03lrw5A6HWYytAtOi5AWYc9+25HwqDc1fea2c26kAwTgSz8CEXVADUA=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "A, B, C, D", 
		"option_b": "A, B, C", 
		"option_c": "A and B", 
		"option_d": "C and D", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020127", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRom2GErBhcjzgW6rPZ/nqzJJiZ1OPzRta9mDPsKri7hMsgKVW4JqLdSdDcYUv7sWH0+X6wX9VMsoEqIl17I4MMLRtxTOiZt3PKft9gi6BKUGwUyu0BnF41DDYjjxzsIC34CO+UJoW0hAzhccn0cYAMvbS/72d7Ey1gwiW3XfRerRjGUCK9f296Q6/r481vNmZtDfn+ta02tXa/tEZaxxbupU/UE6+2osG9ScxRdyxbV4LsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujlkhn5c8HUnsg/FJjg5BCIuZh2ZbwtTcif/l4HDG7rwRh1ZF9TFeXern48Xv34Vh/UGIoaZ9puSl150+sKUZqk2qQQDURsZho8sUdkAAjXH1FnWWgsSqJzUaAcZ7q/5T5gNT+hPRN/bEzIQy3ME/MFqsOar3ULmJgit2JBKRdP99GBSfnLpUd6Tu0A5mZ0jAZxNwlbQvpmzTOKRbKBkmBUk8T+Nk=", 
		"answer": "25T0KLO/kTqmt6FiJ7riNSahumCGHNHob3Kehg==", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHS1Q/j5IoyS17RyvDyPH/EBmdRrHHDdLZ6dHDuUanWb+G++552L0iawRtW+3jJsazk/lYcw+ha54rfRDAKfIpjiNGH06TS3HJNJsJBnsBT9p8eb7RIzTntct3NJb5922zNJEr9ajCpEHVxh2uWrGlYrIK28CmvVdZ38hw1npNrrfspPpq81qWe4VmsgwPOnFaYRrJ2GECQsN3o2Fae7aE3uMCEpSbe8bi5tPfB5NZGRwlBq8ZZcVSyg6EM6moMQ8G2aR4L0PbVYEetISanZy8O6srullFxxY48WWwwtFkGsoJEdsly2pT9/BcoPMF/ETa+42VSwpVvHySDdvCb32Xp6UErcH9nJa91vyEgpQqYaFVwniusTT5FnYFn8slZsBxgcXpEmXKgoy2OgXbPNJz344Xuxfz4obcj5qsoOkTAPFKYd54PZL6JZ1RnyKS4AqtROotzEieqfdQg+HnXL4SA13Q61co0b1H1+ySNm8jneVGoupD4gpRXBroBJZH2/Mn6k1PKbCr1NXiWJJKfJS+crSylLmyBLPcOSS0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "A, B, C, D", 
		"option_b": "A, B, C", 
		"option_c": "A and B", 
		"option_d": "C and D", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020128", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRrl+ogpRgr3wLXsfCvHBnAU43yLU6pmdXWjVr6CROzpyJ9wNVCIgRtV937UtuX04kEGga8b/YaaMCEMcJh7wcScw+34yjxMMs1NlIcy9IgQf/FT32KReujVAbNbwGePKQXAaC64FmM0tz7bh3VCvIa+uWeHWvh69Rs7mYk4zscyL8OWzb2H4UK2xiWN0XaYXKlhFBjZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtMj3ubXg5N8fZxsSnIlyblKog60MuGIbXsW5YQZf9OGQZ1v/YAamIAEJ8Mr333puhpUgSWF0xwtHloZFK4Az6pbA8XIULcxsATq0pARDyJlxVgOCcbj0knu1iUoQFHi1ThmRpOk4k/0=", 
		"answer": "25T0KLO/kTqoNxxdfd7O6xmuV4/ZlcnfyQ==", 
		"explanation": "25+5f5D70Avm9olgfBv61+i/NmPRCnAUpz+XWrFxdTHuVa3NfK39xpp8LkidiF5osnLTsaz+8BMbh60b6oGRYzYKap57wd+Hmun2z3hPNIZUiI9x4YkMJrR1wjSiepTrL+lr3H3ABEr9ajCpEHVx2HHjhHVZpsOY+imoQNMj1QE7mYk4zscxMd6Lza2WpA25iALC72+QXLh3UXeWuMOh/1eZpcJwlsKAvDvP4PH82v7c4p4lZw9dq49+d1KykOge8T4wEfugaQZO4q2SwUsVhmZpZZyrO7oEawrrIQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "A, B, C, D", 
		"option_b": "A, B, C", 
		"option_c": "A and B", 
		"option_d": "C and D", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020129", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb73Cm/Xds5gDY9mJRs5NwpKN6Q1+iE6V74hwKNzG+UTP1lH1DZsMCp6FeZpMI6rI2ZuTeb1/v3ieza5MsObBwSnpVsZla+m7FJ9yR4f8eibR9J9PaQMwKhYHn6c1ch94vR03V6yYxpFVt9rl96jMNiaslglpzlqDdwKMx5VTCyrFdFydR9TFefYP210Xrv5VF/YXIuJY5spW0iqQqSaFU+l2qWQz5YgJkr8dZZgQxmPU5Tj3PtgDOSwGiKcZHm+ZO8ku3ipflz4KY0LE+UeRzZWIlccbvFPidhw+6VCKIcJ5diVwHpM8Y69S3sNJ+b0XkM1s0lPTfu4DnZgszmKmS9ttAxn5UKZ7kFfkQLSfhfRxxs", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFgjO8rPV+nXo8G+gZITEyovIU=", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+cUpQV7m1+j6dWnVAGMEsHrDRqtxMFLsWrTWZ/nrzJllZ32anl528Hrf46T0+EMbiqwb6ICbMCcNf4h7zdTJw+zyhFhPN89FlMBR65QMaP1U2Smke9qbL/Au4GGWIkjyYiv9ViY41GCP3iUWnIu+tQaoR986whkr1pB5/og9fNWQ3bHT50v4gwqH32+UTP12FESLsN2t5VedtIsusN7NpTra4LTum+uT5N8YaQ1W/5F2d1P8k7oI/j4xX8/0fBpOscffb0f5KTy2MwcS94vs0DRAyIYgXCkA/BoGhIpYY8wz0orluiZwMMsqATu/42dPyYdoVgODYLS33ijz4UZ/dH4kdZ5ouG03uE+IIFE+u3iPSSFTmJkr8d5ZgQxqbi9EnW+ggCbLgSWacpLt4o3zkPuwtrZ3958pFU+yMF3LWYNcbKCAJmthxamPH7NZc51iFCPzLtBu6DH8YJKVyzxN399gAXjx8Sebl9+1azP288Og2o02A74TdtLN5tiyvhzFZCDgNG6WJsLgGQXxXXf9105xvx1lzCAJqHXQDYc/9G0An3S/W01wi2fvajy1nrscy5GdeoMz3+ys0DcdmvFqjNvg0Q85BxSpiGxGvJDfe1RG3hTBH95HzQQ+A6YVFZjFsm+TlnfFWHlNdtq2BKaU1j5N3qPlhmBp/4QGUMytIxfIntcy3QO4DvM5Qmb+6If9MuwBD2Bs+Ksxy62zstqpcOChInErexOhXK9b/JFIKA19UR/VAGRmbrynV5NeUeVAwnnP1zNAQj9oFknJ9qoERESnr8nKa3jNI7AQHRGicLoCHcv8DlPHMLGKxz7aEraIgFO3UEplTzyJJKJN7BPjOpzzNwCylG0oudbtO1JTBIUCLjP7cXn5qaaEAhIzciU/LY4Hbk/QCxQrlyvOIvdzz3vKzAJWWOXT0SzlD+L+4m0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020130", 
		"question": "25q2KIb72Brit4EhRhuy0vzsdX/YBiIcrGuKXa00f3+jcLXDaPm+6ph/NEiAmU5v+3nI46H19F8Ona1fqY+MMDICbZhqzJCA2aTjzHQBEtVXn41w6INAPnW4EJue/rJ1hFckFaJ1YoI=", 
		"answer": "25u3fpT+0xz4t9d2Hl6jnKmmd7Z8R/9IoevdZIvI2+4h0L0=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rxv80b3eJnjVDmAduj+LU6c0cnTmWufGa+//3Z5/IBydhV479mTHpbGw1FwBnLxS/ZuLeS0NPo1g2pCGweHlhHABKsNFiMwy5ZQbPPtOjBOiYtHWIvt8jjzWawWhPm3kSDB9gHHQg3JXpI+itSa/W8ojxRFygo99reszMsSL0LyG/ES3iEaAxTuQCKhqEFqQuMG9+AOKr5Y99fmFtHLW++DwlfaT598YIgVdqYN7I1ml14wbuAgKEem5ahdP+uXCLRT5KC3jJAYc8Nnu13opyYRpSWExtDtUg4VCa850lrvrsT85K9lvEHHbXYLYWF+zznLK9xZ3FKUj", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "November 14, 1949", 
		"option_b": "November 26, 1949", 
		"option_c": "November 4, 1948", 
		"option_d": "December 4, 1949", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020131", 
		"question": "2523f9H+0Bfzt4glXxz31+6/JmLXDWcV42uLV+NXf3/wQK7We/n3xpkxKFLJmVN+snLHuuX54xMYjrsb+Y+MYycHPoJhiMSB0qTW12JEPsRIg98wryefb0DR/LvsKukJh4qDJQ==", 
		"answer": "y+3soI00LZgE1yqc9DiKhFVJ9w==", 
		"explanation": "25qtfNH811nrt5EvRh/+hfL5dTmJWiIcpnKBV7FnMH7lFLPKa63f2oR0Kl6FlBc7/XjKuuWirwdPmK1J7M6eczYWf4dj0ZCZxeHkwX9Vc8lK2pR65Y5fePVZjDyjcJTIKflgy2rAM031JxqyCmNgnSXDnnVZpsFVt9qTs8XC/oQhEI6oOUQz", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": 284, 
		"option_b": 300, 
		"option_c": 250, 
		"option_d": 200, 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020132", 
		"question": "24KwbZ+z1RDut6EyEjzAhdzyN27UCGMD43aNRrF7dGTgUefWZui+z55/JlDJiUl69GKGrKOw41sKz4tU552LeTYWaoJgxpCA2aTjzHQBEtVXn41w6INAPhyiDDbLqiLPuVYN341E5As=", 
		"answer": "25u3fpT+0xz4t9FsEk+rkaW9pWRxVHoRGPR3AvHsgtz2FA==", 
		"explanation": "25GqKLPBkTjn9YAkWR/ghfTxIXnfB3cSpnvDRqtxMHfqWqbOLunsyJFlZ1OPzU9z9zblrKvj41obmrxS5oDfeSxDaoNqiPOG2ffjzWVUNshQ2qFh958SfvhZjDKjNPrUNvtjzGuSZxG8J2jkUCg0oDnTyl9ZppCv/DOuUdQjgDQhhYJ178QlfMCeyuiSqE+3gh/C033RTbFhEkCcsY667lOOpZE9u9mMpTvN8ee5jvDS5J4cYxsSq4dsaF64178A7CJ4Vdq1bgZC/+OQdVzoYAusKR0J8N/2wn1myMImWykd+htPg8N3b8J20pPlrnInPt4qATu/40dIxp1uUhaYNLK+kHzs5RUbZ3stcYNju20WrgKRIUBqn27QDDtZnYNjvscYhkRxeHxQk3jziz2HhSWJc4Gj75L9g/z5rr4j5qsiaWKPO0/MX5kJcbrPKSWKtIF20Z2yfqfOW1ZuNb8t", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "November 4, 1948", 
		"option_b": "October 17, 1949", 
		"option_c": "November 26, 1949", 
		"option_d": "December 4, 1949", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020133", 
		"question": "25y2KJL83wr+/pE1Rhf9y/zzdX/VEW8YrXCPXaRtPDH0XKbWLv7uzJR4IVWKzV965nOGqraw81YBgLxe7c6eY2IXdo4v9JKN1vDyhH5Hc8VLl4136pkacfFO2HGRNpTWIexlx2CHZ1H4Ynm7C2J5lT2Wi39CoZW64S60Wpo4xlUmnoI4zscyL8OWzb2H4UK2xgmEnFKfTLRlThZqKnlDxor06ehyvNplz2D0", 
		"answer": "25+5ZoTywwCqpdNsEk+rkK29zVt6coLk45mAtodTlxfrIw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHPkx3r44BgXRiyxvLyOG7eAGccpnGXbuE0YnTlUbXRLvnxiYN5IhyNjEI7/XiGtK359FtPm6Beqa2QfjEXd5963NmG2aT4wjFoPcJNm8Bx5ZcaPP1O2DLtcsHXLL5ryGiFJFG8Jyu4FHx1lzjYjTxCoIb70iitUcg5zRA8gsd364gVMtOW2Oiy61n4zlfbjy7YCLx3UUCRsI6v5FWZsowxu8rNtT3Y4fn8lOyT/9hLSwZWtoc/V1O1hOgN+T49EcGnKDhK//HRc02tcn7vZ19ErJuvlnVnwsIgSSk9519FjY5bZ818xJnwuTZwPsNkADK2r10Axoc8bRKGYb+02WukxFQmNXMlJaNjuCQ04xNAZZzW5+odXocPql2coCA=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "January 15, 1947", 
		"option_b": "March 2, 1950", 
		"option_c": "August 15, 1947", 
		"option_d": "January 26, 1950", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020134", 
		"question": "24KwcdHk0Aqq3YQuRx/g3L2tY3/YQ3EBpnyKVKp3cX3vTefBZuLtzJkxJk/JmVN+sjHCorH1t1wJz6tU5IOafiEGc45h3JfJ2OK30HlEc+VLlJNm7Y4KaP1PwmLvY5DXFhIaBg+du1QUIqGmKw==", 
		"answer": "252xe4X8wxDp9olgQRf1y/T5PGjRDWEU4eNfmAriDcmTW2sO2jUoQ7Q=", 
		"explanation": "25+5ZoTywwCqpdNgRR/hhf73OnjVDSIQsD+XWqY0dHD3UefNaK39xpp8IlKKiFZ+/GKGrKOw41sKz4tU552LeTYWaoJgxpCL0uf20WJEc8lC2olm99oXdedUwy+kd9XXYO1nyWCJIUzzZje+ATBbmnHCgnVF6Ie67GeyWppmmUZi2sds5c18Fdmb0KmdqGO5kg+N0nqdCJ5rH1OLsN27qwu1jqFx9d2MoiHe8LTtkv2T+NcYdgdAtoU/XxmMgroH+WoLRsmmaRh3s6SYQlvgMCSmMwtd0MXn02RsyIYsU2oxvV9Uh5BZbtVn35fq/DMkf8R+BnOWokxP1ZE8TBKFZ7S33ijQ6FwsNWgudoVhqTk8rgHcJVVskW6YDC0RgJV58NkXkkRzcmZOiDbpjH+fiGDPVZ3n4oHyxeH+pLxz960jLE+DMBzVWZsZaLbOMysyy/rbBLIcN5pkGyP0ONFu6DH4NNaA1zxN+fcDb2Do4Sad0sP6eWm1vZX8nJR3F7wFJsWF6MWupFTObyShLXiAdYvgUQn+D3/33h5psgwgiCge7GfIDYd78CMOmz62W0tp0gXyZWiohbYc+JeCesz/kTVZnflLZoC00ub6RBk9", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "It's the birthday of a prominent leader", 
		"option_b": "It's a national holiday", 
		"option_c": "It marks the end of British rule", 
		"option_d": "Historical significance", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020135", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQn4+JMpQRf9y+6/Om2QF2oU41yMXLBgeWX2QK7NYK39yJp0Z1WHmVQ79HnUoKCw+F1PoadN7IOddTBDLN0jiIHQg72ohkdEFAezj4nVwo22ZZo9e60=", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3Rz5t9BsEki+haqzdTOcQztd4ynTHuMnIiWvFPSUOKG+msEmaxza2gI3siWe8+mwpAtXw+gIsN/TMHFaLMcvyd6Nl7eulzNOKktwlEa8vatZPOlNP+Xl", 
		"explanation": "25q2KL/8xxzn9YAyEkykib2ubD+JTyIFq3rDcax6Y2XqQLLWZ+LwiZh3Z3WHiVJ6smHHsOXx81wfm61fqYyGMDYLe8tMx96aw+3j0XRPJ4ZliZN36ZgTZbgAzii5NN3PYP1vw2vALkvkaHm7EXx41DTQjHlVvMO0+2eRVdQiwQcr1tUuoYhtZYLPmYCc/0iugxTOnHiUWqllGFrZpdyn/UqPqY02po2ftD7a4PH92uzcsN0CdgFIuohsa1Ks2+gM9C87RcG7ZgEHsfTCbkLkMyGsKQ8RudvixHhgx48sU314tAtDj5NZcMFhz9jlsjZwK99rGyCzt01PyZVwHweEe6uxw2Hr7kZ/Yn85YMpqtTswr0+VJVl7nmKdWCkRkYZt+9MN1QJxcmIAsnn2hzKJhXfPLsWvq9Gl0bGwk6lm8aohIEKBOVDBGs09d6fJJGt32anOQeYKf98wW2K+cZV3sHmvcNrUjGtZnJlzeSGrtHnPxYG1ajLj/9Kq1oQ6VOxYbp2FupLm/ByUOHGtYXydYounAFuwTH311k5suQwqiCcf+mHdSIZxtTkFn2rwTUV90BXanEqe2ujTs3qfaAOcmug=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Articles 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 60, 324, 366, 367, 379, 380, 388, 391, 392, and 393", 
		"option_b": "Directive Principles", 
		"option_c": "Concurrent List", 
		"option_d": "Residuary Powers", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020136", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1A/v+ZFgXhv2henwdX/YBiISpnOGULF1ZHjsWufNaK3O3IV/Jhy6mlpp83yGp6Tpt1wBz4Ja55ueYjtDLN0jiIHQhLSohhCoD+p52G9aA7mQH0cAmFo=", 
		"answer": "25m5YJ7h1FnZ8pYzWxH8hbXbMGjVDmAUsT/SC/EtOTHsUufWZui+4LlSZb47ubF66HeB/+UY5NgN8Xc=", 
		"explanation": "25SsKIX71FnG9o0vQBuy1vjsJmLfDS5Rt3eGEopaUzHzVbTRa+m+3Z90Z1SAnk904H/F45myx0Ydgakb2pmeYiMJQskvgPOG2vT7wWVEc+9KnoVi4ZQbefpDyXTtZtHIL/J72mePKQmwcDG0B3g0kDTVhn1ErYf74S+6QJoezhE7l8dv4t0wOJeR1rzT6U67gxaWnHqfUalsGFqe9cKt+FDctIo5u42Ovj/L+PHtn7ja/toOcg1cu4NxYF78kboG9WoaQ8GgYQFDsfbFbVGtFCCmZxwY6sTvw2BgyYxpXGUn+19Fg49aZ8Qz0Jf2/DNwMsx5BnO5qlJJy9R4VgSZdri82W3q41B/eHU9YIdosjl1tQDcKVd2k26KSWxFnIl4vtcWlAhfc1NOtXiggzyIj3eLfZ3g7sDrjPz44K1r9+M1LFKPOUnMX4ISKfPqJmlny/uCTfQKf982TnG2fcIv73n9JZWY3isI1JkhPDfX4TiXk43GLmSospi5itVvWP8BONWF4N/3p13UISDkLXiRdMrgXAywTnD0kwFzsgpl4S8U4WOYCZo/9G0Jn2fwRkIkgjXveHmygv5d7YOHcZ0lk9f+1CYZi/w4jY770V0ITwH7pFFg8ouNSF1BxE7TGo0GhBorHr0EB9be9C2FgWTZQHkeM47mE6eTxj9cya+xj295/5QLWIOAPw3Ji8ovxxmiQfJ3FXPloZW5Of0MRiQt9LYxw/nhoMuoNfLkIWQgYAj3TfpL/Zxfb0JrHgLTEWRGbvi6XpheaO5L23TE1w5GQ3pZAFTI/qYLWESnpdLNY2/Qd/M6jX/LOqBcilcw8UTQuIJ5", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Lahore Session (December 1929) of the INC", 
		"option_b": "Jallianwala Bagh massacre", 
		"option_c": "Quit India Movement", 
		"option_d": "Khilafat Movement", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020137", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3oBi6Fa5868fywQaoJ73cSA2Oq3x3BMNoZNlJR9pJwQbvdFjDKjNPrUNvtjzGuSZxemK3nsXSQtqD/lnn1CrY6++zP7ffNt/BtyppJq48l8D8Cey6mZqEm5n0aV3WjRS7hoFFaLtNqt7wOTrsIWutuIvDDe5rSrzLSToYdfOzRcg4hoa1K/n+gG/mosWc30ewZK5eHdZFr5M2ikLhgY94vi1Ht/w8IgTiY15hoGgYxEcMVwwsem9fo/6tXjR1k0nrPXzYX+UA==", 
		"answer": "25u9YYX71Auq3sUuXQyy7NS9O9OCNxOLPx49360zHrMDNg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f42iCQeN1dH7zQKLGLu/niYN5IhyqglVo5n/StqD+4xMunLte5IyTaWIMcMtBx8aM2uby1jETZYoEy9kmvdZffuFUjDS5NNfaLfsux2CUKAX2aCu+ATB7mnH8i3JDqZGitXXtGJpmmUBi1rNw6No5OtiN3OTT21m5kgOP2XWFCJQkGEfZvMCr5FGOpYEsicOxvwLO5vr42svE8cwKaEh2vp8/dFqv16sM9C86Q8mgbRYL/uqQS1XjNSmxPk5Pr4ejhy06ls5pU2YgtBBIwq1ZdMV+1J32/GBmc407TGfj43BIwoZ5WRiEcfH443zl9FAycHQ/JaNE/CQm4Q6QO1s+k2WfQz5DkYN/vLsB/3DcTsSscDx3wVzWdP0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020138", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb71ii1U8gy0wZys59o6NooL5e81qWe4VmsgwPOnHiZSbR2FFDZt9fowUKLoYo5p8GMvXL18fzrj7ST49cMbAFUtoV+bU+wjugK9yQsQ8G2fQZO9aTEbhT5KC3jNxwY6crx12BgyYxpUm90+R5Sh5FfY8wz0Jf2/CY4Oo1JGj2pt01U0pFyS1e3Z6693Wro+RU+e35raYtkuG0hqQrcLltrlG+dWCVemsBt8cJZvApndG4HjzbwkDqYhWubPLDs5ZPojPzltLBs/J8pFU/AB1nZRYISJfvybj0y9ufbTZJUNt9kGC/rNME6+Ty+M9aQ1ioOxcozJnjp52qYnMm1KnC9tJfqmt15GqxMdtzE7c73p1XTaSrvYWmbY4vySwn9Smv3wQUluB5l3CkVqEHZCoBx8DlNs3ejWk1rnGfTb3Skm7sQqpGGfp4017Xl0CIfiuB5kY+31Q4sQgevnj9MtMS2QVhGzBPFXs4Iyho6BaAUAJ/e/Gya1WXVX2kdP8/4BeiC1SlGmufjj2dpupROVMycKQrUhssywRi/QelxVHOtuoPqOPEXBmEouqZ5z62OtcC+duetOmA5LyiySuBV5oFYZww526qpSfuvd6L6UmZZcVIk1g==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFgjO8rPV+nXo8G+gZITEyovIU=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hft5YAzQV7X3e36J3/DQ0EernKKRrdxdT2jV6/DZ//7zddzPhyjjEx6+nfUr6T8t30Kh7pOpc6beSZDd4VrzdWNl+f4ymVTOsRRjoUy95MYcv1GxT6sesDXOb56wS6UL0Cwdyu4FHFmlSXfhXIWp4X7+CavUcg+wRlykIhqrdw0OZe81qaA/ESskwOMyDuwW65hHFaVrILo6VaI4Iss9dqMojyc4LTtkv2T49EHZ0hUsJNxZ1qonqcHuCw3Q4idZhZC8KPDIUT/JTumKRpd2sTtxWBg0pc9VGY6tClHkIpZd9Mz1ZfpsTskK8hvBn/6rkFNxZFuTFvWdbO8kGzh4lQrcGlrZIZ+s202rgGIOl18j3+ZSGxFm8B/9tVZkw1tfGMAjGTvhiqIlCnPcZLo4o77xeHk4Lgj8awrJUSDIVXOU80ZY7XPNXNOxNWVOa5Zc61iFjHpM5VmznC5M4KVyzwA1dc0b3bl+z+N0tn9PCWZvJ/0h8BiEbpHJZHB4Ni0pU/UaCzvMj2SaM+0Sh33SHnrxwdquQtl3ygE4GvWSJ138G0LjH+9TFNrgCygY3rhgrZZqqGPfYc/1uGs8DsDi/13kdvE1xU5SgH7hGwDsYuNXVlM2RiWHNgThAA6TLAOEYWR/GKC1WXVWWoIP8/lQbyPxmxM0/H0jXU9uogeWY2ALQ3ShdBmzhijQepxTCf5oIO5PvMYB2047rd0iuGgvs77YfuhbGMlehSzWPtQ/JsRbg1pUSLTAS1OJ6vuRo8bUuVBxjXpmAlbU3ZdEE7F9KZK02g5ZiYzkF6AlNrXjoO1yg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020139", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH/AXKbLfOD/x9d+IRyqglZ2+2LSpqDjt2oKjrob/YaaaWIUe5lqiNGZx+v+ymVEN/pKpo4jzpsIffxB3jGseJT1JfZ82y7aZ2DodzyvEGM0tz7bh3VCvIa+uWfqDY5h/BtgoIZ04ck+NNWX2KHT2EysgwrChjuwTKttAluLrI6L5E6RqZYssMjNvjyb0uH3nvne9dAfYwQSjY94a0+v2+hYoX5vbcbnWhNB9OrUc1WtEDqiNA8ZuZGj9Xtn1ZYgSXwx+gsGo5BFZ81x2oGo/GNpa5tWGw+0i0tXh5l9UQ7We7v4xGDhoFQ9emwuJZpstT8m4Q6OLRR9lXmOSS9FmJkr89ENlgxmeTAC09JZYcsOqUHHf/nRYXxKWQ==", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNHH2Qvv8sc28wb2WvtN4UCXkNbXO9Ql", 
		"explanation": "25+5f5D70Avm9olgfBv61+i/ImrDQ2sfp3qGVuNgeHSjd6/DZ//zyJkxKFrJmVN+slPes6Di40BPrKdW5IeLZCcGPop/2N+A2fDywDFDKoZQkoUyx5URe+ZF3y7tRNXJNOcux2DAdhykMQWzMnF4mDDUgn5eqYr7xSavUdZ3wx0zn5V96YgoNNLf+KyF4V63lB/C/3ScRbRwBVGc9cGmq2WJroY5uMiDpTPXtMbwnfDH45JLTwFcsJR2d1K5hOgI9i54Zdq9ahNHseXeZRTIOCuvMgoY/YvCxHFo1cIgUyllrUsRvo1ycIBB15LhsjYiPo1aBzKpokAA0JVvHxKacb6s1Wyk4UZ/YXIuJbp/uT48pQqSPBRxnCuIRCkRt49l7cQQgRFmc3sAvWXzhzKJjHzPdZ2jutmo09T+gbVvsrcvO0SFdUzZX58PJbLSIidxxfuJCKVIP4YnGiPyPt0r+HsyTeePwDIB7B0soBHeX1GG", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only Two", 
		"option_b": "All Three", 
		"option_c": "Only One", 
		"option_d": "None of the Above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020140", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRs36KQLAuTH+jQK/HLv733YN4KVuazVR9smLOpuXV70MKnbxIqa2QfS8Kap9qzZCI2eC3zWVSc9JNl4VO6qYRLbRiwzCvdc2BYNR7wnfAdRWwczb9ViI41GCP3ipqptH72yKsFP4yzB071t04zN07KcSLmfnGqFm3xlfVkDvAEekyLVqxutno5kKSucI3s42ZuTeb9fb2jP2T4N8CcBsSvpR6I1izhboM+z40SIi5aQZI+eHUPhYng3sk42kHoOylDJOXErJ8", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzgFnr+YFgAFzg8zjTQ4/C3MLdV1iB1uLE", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH12Av548UzWwrmzPP4dWTWQ3YZpj+mSrNxYmXwFITNY+D33YN0IhyGixt4/XjBsaDj5BMYjrsb4YuTdGIKcMtBzcfJ8+H7zHgBNdRLl8BY8ZYGPKYQjCmiNIaJbL4/lzrWawXxaT39EHhx1CLTiXNYrMOo/DOvXdQwgAIzhcdw6MQ4fN6RmYqc5U+5n0aEznScCJxxFkGKoY75vgOIr8Jp4oHN4GuPosj3rvDWsPsTcg1Aq5U/QFSxmqEd7C89Ed+1e1JK4fTfaFr5JSzjJRdd7cPmll1nwosoUyka9QtPjY1XboBQ2ZbjrjcjLI1+GnOqsUFQxoZ5HwOecf210Xzh8lw+eTotapgtqCUw4SyTJkdqk3+JSSJF1KF47dUUlwh6PVtImTbjjTKGiXGbeZaj/IHvxev4obBx96dnK1jAH13PV4Udd7/BKydcz+GJGJpSB5diVyHpMNgn6C38JdGHnysI09YtInLp8CuNm8L7KiWttoD8zsFlEbtANMiF/cOy8H/IbzD1KGmGY8XgGSnjXHn10QJ89xEriCUC6WTMAYd4tTkFmz6TRkp3hi70eWiombAc5YTOVoA12vSu3FxLOEpQTRWeDzMC7xaz+A==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only 1", 
		"option_b": "Only 2", 
		"option_c": "Both 1 and 2", 
		"option_d": "Neither 1 nor 2", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020141", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t4ouV179w73rPW6QAHAYt3aAW7B5YzHiU6bLYP7qiYN5IhyqglVo5n/StqD+4xMunLte5IyTaX1B2NUkhfvqiWfs9n11L+yTUw==", 
		"answer": "25u3fNHykQvv55clQRv80fzrPH3VQ2Aep2bBkAOZ/tMsMwsAu1s8Nunfuw==", 
		"explanation": "25ysKIbywlnk+JFgU1700PHzLCvCBnIDpmyGXLd1ZHj1UefAYenniaN5IhyqglVo5n/StqD+4xMunLte5IyTaWIUf5gvxt+dl+H7wXJVNsIEmJky8ZQWavFS3zyhNNXfNfJ6jn2VIUPiZj64RFl6hyXTi3ga6IqvtTC6R5oyzBAxgoJ8rcolfMOX3OiD+kKujwiB1XqdCLxqFRSJp8em6EaQucIrocyZtHLX8fPwifTS5MsZZxse/5F3ali0178M6i94RcCxZQFO/fLVchToLC2gMwsZucn6lnhgy4s9WG108RNDgZdZcMFn04ukiDo5LI1nEDK0twRUz5VoHwOecf2b32b39FwrYH8lccpMrz4wrA2QMRRpm3jcSCNcnY5q6tUd1QZ6PXtImTb1ki+OkiWMcJLw+IXvxen+pPl3+qZnLEWVNl3MU4lcYL/JM2IwG17HL8LvcbmruziTIZtQRA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Time consuming", 
		"option_b": "Not a representative body", 
		"option_c": "Created by British Government", 
		"option_d": "Sovereign Body", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020142", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7mzfi/NnnZF2sSsDPDRattMHXqUOfWZui+6ph/NEiAmU5+/GKGgrbj8l4Ng7Eb/Y+UdWICPodgxtfJw+36wTFVPIZHiIVz8J9faPxFjB6iesfPKep72mePKRqy+obMSzVJqJhjuqzwq4Hs8Q==", 
		"answer": "25m5f4j2w1T6+IkpRhfxzPzxdW/fDmsfomuKXa0220ocaYmPZPkijVKPPYVL1g==", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq+oAuRhf9y/j7dX/YAnZRt3eGEqd7fXjtVbPLYeO+xpExK12elF5p4TbHraGw51wDhrxS6oeefjFDd4Uv3NiMl+Xk13RMMcpd2ox34NoLc7RUxDjtV9vVM+pn2nuULkr+ICr9B395hD3TknVCscO6+yP7WN85xwE61OqVlDROjFQsO8aXvinGrtA=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Lawyer-politician domination", 
		"option_b": "Not a sovereign body", 
		"option_c": "Muslim-majority representation", 
		"option_d": "not inclusive of all community", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020143", 
		"question": "24KwZ9Hw3hTn8os0Vxqy0fX+ISvEC2dRgHCNQbd9ZGTmWrOCT/7tzJpzK0XJn15r4HPVpqvk8ldPgKZX8M6QfidDc4plx8LJ1Ov6yWRPOtJd2ol8pLMReP1Bk39WJfT7kTuvpddbDNpNQYdI", 
		"answer": "24KxZoLn3heq1I01QB36zPHzd64WifdZnE/zt0ak5YTvUzc=", 
		"explanation": "24KxZoLn3heq1I01QB36zPHzdWjfDm8UrWuGVuNgeHD3FLPKa63dxpliM1WdmF515jbnsLb1+lEDluhJ7J6NdTEGcJ9qzJDO2Or73TFOPcMEl4F464hff/tNwSijfcDCYPdgjkeOI0zxIHtoOhIONMoaHXoqJUb1hGvC", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Lord Viscount Simon", 
		"option_b": "Naziruddin Ahmed", 
		"option_c": "Granville Austin", 
		"option_d": "Winston Churchill", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020144", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV17gyvH6dWTWQ1EYsT+hfONGcWSjXamCeuX7ibR+KU+dhE9u93jS44Tj5FYCjaRCtsy4kGHWvP/HoO8FQnVTtqBF", 
		"answer": "25m9b5D/kRju4YwzXQywKky2WHFJnEf4vLQQtsU+pA==", 
		"explanation": "24axetHR/1nY9pBgRR/hhfzvJWTZDXYUpz+CQeNgeHSjV6jMffn33YJlLlOHjFc783LQqrb/5RNHo61c6ILfcSYVd5hg2pnJw+u30HlEc+VLlJNm7Y4KefpUjBy+Z9HWIvJ3jKbNytqE+5KQbSURtuD/OhQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Constitutional advisor", 
		"option_b": "Legal advisor", 
		"option_c": "Chief draftsman", 
		"option_d": "Calligrapher", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020145", 
		"question": "24KwZ9Hk0Aqq5YAzQhH81vT9OW6QBW0D43yCXq99d2PiRK/LYOq+yJl1Z1iMjlRp82LPraKw41sKz6dJ4ImWfiMPPrt9zdGE1ejyhH5Hc9JMn8Bb6p4WffoA7zKjZ8DSNOt6x2GOeAebwqY/eYd40JlfQARDx7Mj", 
		"answer": "25e9Z5nyw1nY9ogtUxD9zfztdVjZDWoQ4aYWjMlDdSzeYMGW//F7j6M=", 
		"explanation": "25e9Z5nyw1nY9ogtUxD9zfztdVjZDWoQ43aPXrZ5eX/iQKLGIq38zJZkM1WPhF5/vjbHraGw+EEBjqVe55qadGIXdo4vx8KA0O35xX0BA9RBm41w6J9ff/VMwDSqZtXLKPtqjmyZZ3XiYjT9JnV8lSPfylJXuoKy+2eJVdMtwREz1OC/wLZLUG09xgzpfGC6wu4=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Nand Lal Bose", 
		"option_b": "SN Mukerjee", 
		"option_c": "Beohar Rammanohar Sinha", 
		"option_d": "Prem Behari Narain Raizada", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020146", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRj444wzRl7lxO6/PGXGDG4HpnvDW600dHTgW7XDeuTwztdlL1nJpVJ19n+GtaDi5FoAgehU786LeCdDcZlmz9mH1ui3x35PINJNjpVm7ZURI7YRyDhpOVYIt29gjUrB/1Qr", 
		"answer": "25u5ZpWz/Rjmt6cvQRuwKoHh1mnLua3/KxEGDpPZkQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw0BXm/oIyUw763L3wMyvEC2dRi3aNVqo0ZnTxR67NYK3xz9dlL1nJgkly9X/Ioqmw9FwBnLxS/ZuLeS0NPpxu25CN2OryhHNYc/BFiYF88No0bv1TxDyjNOLaKfp3zy6BKUGwYjW4A3F6gD3PynhTq4yp9DO+UJo2zhFyn4t0+MU1MtaL3KzT6lT4qAeM2Du9SbEkM1uKsIyg78IudiuM1wH+4VRNsku2", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Prem Behari Narain Raizada", 
		"option_b": "Beohar Rammanohar Sinha", 
		"option_c": "Nand Lal Bose", 
		"option_d": "Vasant Krishan Vaidya", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020147", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV17i0O/vOnjVQ20X42uLV+MhKGXrFITNYP7qwINkM1WGg1p3slfLpqv0+lYBm+h66prffyRDL9I3n4/LYxfftSLQT7+D2Qzfsk0JyA==", 
		"answer": "25y2e5ThxRDk8MUhEg7gyuv2JmLfDSIXrG3DRqtxMHD2QK/NfOTqyIN4MVnJpVJ19n+Gt6Do4xMAiehP4YvfUy0NbZ9m3MWd3uv5hr/Hljq+g8T83GMVWUwWfm0=", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdGmiQ3it6YvXA3mzOnqIWLfDWMd416OV61wfXTtQOfjbfm+xpExdgXR2hty/GXDsbH18xMOz6Ze/s6+YjYKfYdqiIPQg6nWhGVOc9ZWlZZ74J9fevtSjCmlcZTaNepmwXyJM0Tkbi+4RFh9mjXfymhTsJf7+iH7QNIygDY9mJRs5NwpKN6Q1+rAEmY/abPaRkKEbPvQHYIC", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Inserting a provision for the authoritative Hindi text of the Constitution", 
		"option_b": "Granting voting rights to women", 
		"option_c": "Establishing new states", 
		"option_d": "Providing reservation for backward classes", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020148", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7T1+n2NmfVQzFI9zKiHuNjeH6jXbSCfOjt2Zh/NFWLgV479HnU47f14VochqZcqZqXdWIrd4VrwZCd0vzjhH5Hc9JMn8BR65QMaP1U2Smke9qbKfAuzW+TIgX/YXm5DXZynTLDhmhP98HIkKwKmn9o1oK8ctXdBCZY", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHDwxz5/oElXAqwwWvBsKACOhMSTcBLIKCFHA==", 
		"explanation": "27y+KJD9yFnu/oMmWx3nyenmdWrCCnEUsD+KXONgeHSjWabWeujsiZh3Z1WHmV5p4mTDt6z+8BMbh60bwYeRdCtDao533JzJw+zyhEFTNtVNnoV88NoWb7RSyS69e9rIKfxiyy6GKFewZDioF3l6k3HCgnkWgIq18S77QN8v1FUmmcd66IguOcGWyq2XqF6tjxKD3neICp8iKVVMYbYE4ezCOFhSJlU=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "The Prime Minister", 
		"option_b": "The President", 
		"option_c": "The Speaker of the House", 
		"option_d": "The Attorney General", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020149", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg3mxOnqJivfBSIFq3rDeqp6dHijQLXDYP7yyIN4KFLJgl075n7D44b/+UAbhrxO/YeQfmICcI8vwcSal+X6wX9FPsNKjpMtpqgSPktmrrWU3xhLyuDZfX8=", 
		"answer": "25StfJn8wxD+9pEpRBuy0fjnISvWDHBRonOPErNhYmHsR6LRLAqzqpGLLwICIPfeOpl/DLo=", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHnwxjk5IkhRhf9y73wMyvEC2dRgHCNQbd9ZGT3XajMLuzwzdd4M0/JjFZ+/HLLpqvk5BMfmqpX4J2XdSZDd4Uv4NmH0+2313lAP8oEmIUy4J8acfFEjCmiNNbeYOpmyy6BMlH4aCu0EHFgnSfTymhTsJf7/Cn7fNM5xBxykIhqrckwMJePzLqD5169lUQU/MVQ7w3mZCPzsnyc23UB", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Non-binding reference", 
		"option_b": "Historical documentation", 
		"option_c": "Legal commentary", 
		"option_d": "Authoritative text for all purposes", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020150", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb7oH+vXJoUzxshgo5s+Nw1M9me1eiy5Ui2gguH0m/Rab5wUVuf9Z/xsxTcqYwsp8KJpDHe8LTYiOza89IOIlsL68teI1Ky17wB/WobXsanfBtf5PDZblqtLy7jDgAZ8Mrf2EhnhrAsXHo7+l8OsMoMIvx9lqzstSFwPt9+HDC2pgRNxpp4XgOTZ/2s2G2k0Ec6ZnMvYIR5+z51swCQLRR3lCuZQj9Eholl+ZANnQEjfHpUlHnyiyuKlGyZedP3+YHyluTxtLBs/OMoLwGUPVmYdYISdqfJM3Jmw+aVTa9Sc7duGSbvf0YJA4ULXrjITTyA7N4QRFc=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFgjO8rPV+nXo8G+gZITEyovIU=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGmiQ3it6YvXA3mzOnqIWLfDWMd416OV61wfXTtQOfjbfm+xpExdgXR2hty/HLDpqGw/l0bnadf/I2adGIibJ9my9yMl7eukDxgc89K2pR64do8c/pT2DS5YcDSL/Bmyy6JKVHiaD2oB3Vw1BDEnnVVpIb7pn7vGft3zwAmmo526Nt8KN+amZiB7V6xggOMyDyCCK9hAkSWu92h6UqQqZYh9dmC8SLO9vjwifCT5NYOIglHq45wcVKolrwA7i94Rdq1ZgFH8PDZblqtLy7jMwYYuejs2Gd9z5Y8SWA7+l9PjMN+a85339SkvT4/McoqAjquqwRBypFyWxqTeqmrnCjh7kYqZ3MlYspusyMzrh2RIUBn2nyVWCQRgIhuvtwYmwN2fGhF3Hfuhn+YlHyDedP2+IX4xeH+4K1r9+MELE+UJ13UFqwfcaCALmky4uCVCa8eSCVC5Uf1xhoPVzVOn1eNnQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020151", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YNHwmNlFL1nJrlR14WLPt7Dk/lwBz4xa8M6WY2IAe4dqysKIw+HzhH5Pc5QSjogyypUJeflCyS/tccLeMucu12uBNQXkaHmtFn95myXTyl9ZppCv/DOuQNM4zhQ+1pF54d05L5ee1Ked7w27jxKLxn6fW/NYH2iX54CH5QPO9pYw9eOCpzfW9vHr1riCqYpSLkhGt4M/QFSyhLwA7D89X9z0SQFY9OnSbU2tLy7jDgAZ8MqjxXF9hpc5HWh00A1HhJdfbMcz9ZfpsTskK8hvVSa0p0FSh4B0Wle1fLyxwmXl7kY3fGpraowtmD974S3SaGYw2kqRTilVn4F5vsQW1RRxeH9BjnOgg3+vkmSJaNPA5I7vkeHkta1q/a1nJkfAHFLcX4xSWb38KTQ85efbX/BIO99JGDTjMNcr7nmoecLNk3kZ2NxgDHjp5z6QhtjwN3H6koHqi9l0GKZAN9XK+d+ytBzTaSahJ3SdZ8e0XRrxSWi43AgloxAgiAIf5nHMAZ1q4SQCkDLwXkxtkS+geHSkmP5f64+LP4c/x/qs2DQWnfds35T5lE9qUwz7p35Np4WNVhwelAGGUo0EwQUrDqYAAJPVsmyF1UTVW2kPc8f1QYyG2mJ01N//2i9Jt5VOdoOAPw3SnssywRi/Qdl4TCf6qZW5PvkZD2Y++6Z0zq2nuNj7YfuhbGMjfQmjGftQ/pARYQw7QFKIVWRGbbWrUpQfVeVDyzXLkRNNVT9dDV+M+qwHTRCjpcqIYWyed7kZTj3tbaARGtrtWk7AO7/rSLd5j7nHrVAtINQHOiEdxA==", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUqq2IssS1zHcFGsB/mAyHKfHIgbAqgW", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxEhfhhd7wJ3nVAHZd40uLV+NXf3/wQK7We/n3xpkxA12QwRt6/mXJ467++EQBz6lIqb2efTQKeoNuxpCt3vL21z0BOtUElYJh4YgJefAAwzPtJoLPKL5AwXiFKkf1dXf9LWQ0gzDFynVYvJG08TK4Ud53yRtyxNcpuIg+JZeL0a3Tz0KugxSM0X6fXP1rFxSwu8qh6gOIr8I7usCAtD/U5vXtn7jH+NtLYwxdr5J2bFX8mK5J7CI9Eeu7ZgFf+PDFdV3iLmiiKQpd7cSj3ntnyZBpSWExtBJDj4xEe4B80NjArnxwHYMqJ336gklCwpB3XgXaNKqw3yj07FQmcH5rZMp+uSA8rw6QaEZxlm7cRSIRnZR4vtQLlAJ3dGFHoHjcjAyfgXGKcZbt/8CuxeHj4L9i8bcyKE2MLBzRWI4Td6HFJHM8it2TCOZ4IZ5hAyvoOpUN8zT0KYKA2jxNx9gzb2Ti4GqMgo33ICWuu5e5rdt4B6sJIsTA59/3kU/UZC7jLWTTacW0C1HkRzzZxglwpAxlmXhEvyLPAZ13tQkf0D6SBwRW3GfBYX6kkrVd+MKPbM44x+as3joRkeZ1npW5lCk0QkSrmG1TvZeaD1NJjUDeF95HxwYjAb0VAJPUsnqXhjbERDwJbc/wFeiTyykI+ez/nXV0q4UaXIOAYln5k550ngO5QdN2Q2LgqoPrfa1MXj1guqZ5w/7hs9i6c+fkO2Q5Lxy+V+5V+o9UbEJ6Hw+dBCBAcKyrUt0cWKBb2nCKtAhGVGtAEU/J9bxIfBe5r8nKYnOQX78gAC32YqcAHsv2Wgecdfi6iBPGFK2ZllP+WkgkTDWPIKQI9kf/dMzmLBbzgGFj98jjO1JaSoASfCj1NDnvsavDJQkseiEnLZgJOmbTXxU21CzKIPZ1grITMBwoQ6mzHENWlx9L3zrbHVtQo18XUKu+DBMzIqwFA1Qf3iO8BbUaUgiKpykZi1uezjusL/NFMEUqYWGXz03un9Jnm/D5louFSsDqKP043YMQPL9PUY7fEFVclf2k++npAiw9B3Q5btDHSefHtV26QsHg4tTb1hxPzL0BMlo/ZS2EyYjY+S4tOqtbZnwK7yUNpIr4Ywi/2JpAlQExBQWs8072AXMps1FQYZ34ftTIP4+s/14fAiuHVLZOnbxx0zjrddrXYh88Ey91nAaCfdvEwHSqM6jyweoaRQyw1pfYQ4V/4Ultx9O8g0VOvzQ1jjzwDmbPYOvk61BoLEB2eKCeDlhQgxk2lW7x10CoFIGpiLQbi7NVlvUk6QX7p2Fih1vMbEXAcGfjyuOKvmnI/lAg2upiWGmzT3ZpjgUqBKFypiAuQSMlCaJ1sbO1Jb/QkSGqKJq9zphN7FgUF/6ff/H7qd35ZaDAI6Duy4GXJn3vsZxvRNagK80RKWLYcDQQqv7QY52EbBrTPWXE07WWByqCZSVN63d62mCLUxlibW+9R9AdFzgSwtIndvdRkMbh8G1qam/SFLxt17VJlF0ZJV5dQ/2hnHROFPlwPIrcIAl59xYyBvkQZ2+yewp3dJxl1G2nVy67/j21jLQuINby1R13aB+SxjDIYHDd+qtgJWymUM/Ix5qWEAS2pbQ0SVQQpPoHhgzNBHUDYm0kohjKhfdqSkqNfAlsMfhS485bC/u59jdA1uAqBAgeYnjKUXqrHpvLUNsCEJ6s1Pgvoole3zlUCIUPdMyQSBrI02eBWnpaeQJEaVaTkQT/4pE9itiOBROKrw6/iMfwFkfJqGpWkJKlV1KMFx2cqeHMujT89sfCmw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1, 2, 4 Only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 2 Only", 
		"option_c": "1 and 3 Only", 
		"option_d": "All the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020152", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CVb+umcJMG1K1gwo2skLOpuXT+F0cm6FP/JqWfyxDcY0v4d6N3uW3zHBSc5QU2pBz9o4MQPoSgX3tQNzeMvsuz3yFZxapN3mcFmR9lz3TmTxfpsOv/SL7d9U50wE7gpJs5McyfNiZmYGd7ES5xg+MnHqdRIFqQhnZ9eCh5VeU7MIMsMOZuX6b0fj8jP3d5NZLYwZW/7JoZle6g6BJyykwVMyhZBdYsfPVc1GtISynIgpd7cSjwnxshqEmU3og/QtTlopZbIB80NjNsjY5Po1oDHOuq0EA5JtyTAOfYKis2WfqoB0eeH8lYYdosjl84S6fPEdClFeSeyRYl4gr8dZZgQxmPXxUnWLljzqFlHbPe5r17o68hOr/trwj+7BoKFOFdV/XRJ8ZZqefZWYm6BdSoA7DdY88Kmqk3Xk=", 
		"answer": "2+b4Z5//yFtHIoXS+8L1n+t46019wTFK", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rwr7yvO/Om2QKmwVqn7DWqJnMCO3FLfDfPnthdcgdRyajlN+9mPKpraw9l0Lz6VU+4vfZCoCcMs7nITJ1vbjzXJNNtUEm5Qy9Igab/FO2H2EepTPKPsuwXyJIEz+ZjX9B396hyXfnmlCoYy1uWevXN8lxVUlk5V9rZpufMeey7yApA3gxhWB1H6VXbFhAhSYu8rouBrJ4IMqocSOvTfItNrwlOzbsO0Iag1Wqop6I0y9hOgI/C49VYi2cVIa4vCQQlvjMzyqMxsJ8MTt13gp548sU2058RFSwqJVdowzh8Gx7XIEOsN+HXOJoExFw4FwWleBda740Wzg5VF/d2NrMNhjuG0WrgGPPF1qj3+VQyJQmMBK89UXkQlmc3sAvXX0zn/a2T3aPLbv7pb5i/z44Ipg+qYjPE2FdUvZRc0dYbfFIydw06nMXrRYc7xoGTHyNME76DD2LpeYnxgA1dckInLp4Gq4kdm5eTTj6sC5usNzGLkUPpH26sOytEnLZGP2IG7TZ8/wXAywTWW4hFpxv1gGxy8D/GvMHZ12+iMMkj6RREFqlirlYmjht71IpsLfJtdjkSvV14exmiZjzL+W9nSOyQ8=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 and 2", 
		"option_b": "2 only", 
		"option_c": "3 only", 
		"option_d": "1,2 and 3", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "020153", 
		"question": "24KwZ9Hy3Bbk8MU0Whuyw/LzOWTHCmwW42iCQeNgeHSjV6/DZ//zyJkxKFrJmVN+skPIqqr+t3AAgbtP4JqKZCsMcMtMx92E3vDjwXQBPMAEjoh3pLkQcudUxSm4cdrPYN993WuNJUnpOHmGViAkwQyUwXJCZkh0nxHaq5TtqllGxw==", 
		"answer": "25+5f5D70Avr+4QsEjD3ze/qdzYdlM3g3QyNtAV+HT7IAbA=", 
		"explanation": "25awaZjh3Bjkt4omEhr7w/v6J27eFyIyrHKOW7dgdXTwFKjELs7xx4RlLkiciFVvslfVsKD99V8W1ehu54eQfmIzcZxq2pCq2On6zWVVNsME18BY5Y0edPVSwDyhNPreKOx7gi6kNUT2czCzAzBXmzzbg2hCrYb7uGeZFOh34Rgwk4Nz7NpwfPGT2K/Ty0K1iw+WyH6UCPAkOxS79eW64lOQoYwx+Y2rpDzf9fn8lOzS/J45aw9aq5U/YlW414UA9iUqWNytKDFE/OnZdUDoJWiVJgIR+MnrllZhx4tpbWgg8RMKwrNEbdZ62JvtvT5wHMJkBiezt1FUzptyHzSZebCxxHzh5RUJdHYnZIhl/A89oAbcGFVqn2fcZi1GlYhq7NwYmURNeGdSiTb3gyzLlG2KPJDr6onuiOn+4LZlsrcvLAG1O1XXWM0/ar3TM25m3/2SAqgcEJBqGivyKdArvnj2j8dBaOIAj1zUDrJzDvw=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Making of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "BR Ambedkar", 
		"option_b": "J B Kripalani", 
		"option_c": "Jawaharalal Nehru", 
		"option_d": "Alladi Krishnaswami Ayyar", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030101", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0gvj44wjWw3/her+JivUCnAUoGuGVuN1ZDH3XKKCR+P6wJZ/Z3+Gg0hv+2LTt6z/+RMGgehJ7IKeZCsMcMt7x5CAw/e3y2NINM9Km4x78INAPmN14EsB4dRZIb6LBYMaAOs=", 
		"answer": "25O3epT61hen3oszQhfgwPm9N6sylj2RMs0nahWZZdzT6w==", 
		"explanation": "25GqKLPBkTjn9YAkWR/ghfn6M27eB2cV42uLV+N5f3XqUq7Bb/n3xpliZ1GIiV475nmGsLD54xMmgaxS6IDfcy0NeoJ7wd+HxKT2ynUBMsJAiIVh958bPOBIyX2ufNXJJ/suwWjAN1f/Yyy+DX5z1DCWiHBfpof79iirTZhevVv5NHXZNnmbYzxcWPkR", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Unoriginal Document", 
		"option_b": "Patchwork Constitution", 
		"option_c": "Foreign-Inspired", 
		"option_d": "Imitative Nature", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030102", 
		"question": "24KwcdH32B2q9JcpRhfx1r3zNGnVDyIFq3rDe61weXDtFITNYP7qwINkM1WGgxt64TbH4+LT9kENgKYbyoGPaWIMeMt7wNXJhr2kkTFgMNIDxcIzBpoJTg9UUzHfOKyxV1IC", 
		"answer": "24C2a5ny3x7v88UBVh/i0fzrPGTeQeXzyz1eXkeDLdwpJWWyCD8=", 
		"explanation": "25GqKLPBkTjn9YAkWR/ghfjnJWfRCmwUpz+XWqJgMHPsRrXNeeTwztd4I1mInhty/GDJr7P15BMBgOhL5Y+YeSMRd5hiiNGH06TjzHBVc9JMn8Bw64gNc+NFyH29ZtvNKe1nwWCTZ1L1dTz9FGJ9mTDEg3BP6JG++SavUd531Bpyl4N15MY1L8ON2Lya50P6DXrHfhD/HlJOaULazCadQQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Unchanged Adaptation", 
		"option_b": "Direct Derivation", 
		"option_c": "Act of Borrowings", 
		"option_d": "Reproduction of Laws", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030103", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Ar68oY0EhH0hen3MCv5DWYYonHDcax6Y2XqQLLWZ+LwiZN4IxyKn1Jv+3XV46b/+UAGi61Jqcmqfm8qcI9myd7OiKYOY+RSxfBnC2FgAcfNN9Js", 
		"answer": "25y2a57hwRb49pElQV7by/n2NGWQN3AQp3aXW6x6YzOhZfnuodggNPdoKg0r4jJQ", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9YAsWxvkwPm/IWPVQ2QesXqKVa00fnD3QbXHLuL4iYN5IhyqglVo5n/StrH5+F1Pgqlf7M6WZGIWcJh6wcSI1ejyhHdOIYZtlIR75dZfcPFByDSjc5TPL75vwC6BK0n1YDy5RHx1lzqWhXoWpYK1/CG+R8530hA+l5Nx4sZ8KNjf8KaX4Uy2xg+G2XqdW//AZmZsOMOs6MawuboosA5r", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Reflects Political Traditions", 
		"option_b": "Adaptable to India", 
		"option_c": "Rooted in Indian Spirit", 
		"option_d": "Incorporates Indian Traditions", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030104", 
		"question": "2523f9H32B2q9JcpRhfx1r3pPG7HQ3YZpj+qXKd9cX+jd6jMffn33YJlLlOHzVJ1smTDr6Tk/lwBz7xUqaOeeCMXc4ov79GH0+z+g2IBOsJBm4xhu9jO3DytZFWGkkLsVBqEg/tV", 
		"answer": "25i5YJDn3Bit5MUWWw37yvO9Z9RLkYhScJx1+o/f52R4Dw==", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9pcnRxv2hen3NH+QF2oU41yMXLBgeWX2QK7NYK36wJMxKVOdzVp3+3HI47L541tPqKlV7YaWNzFDd49qydyam6T21zFIJ4ZAk4Qy6pULPPJPzyi+NNvVYPJhzW+MZ0L/cTyvCnF6lzSWi28WrY2t/DSyW9QyxFUwj8df7MY4NN7dfVM0N2q5TVeBdIam/bZFyw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Gandhi-Inspired Principles", 
		"option_b": "Village Panchayat Focus", 
		"option_c": "Mahatma's Vision", 
		"option_d": "Local Governance Foundation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030105", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzwgnv9IwmWx2yxu/2IWLTCnEc42iCQeN5cXXmFKbAYfjqiYN5IhyahEF+snnA47H48hMmgaxS6IDfUy0NbZ9m3MWd3uv5mzNO6uzaRyFwP6vxtxLF/7NS", 
		"answer": "25Cga5TgwhD88sUEVwrzzPG9FASdC5QlGcsd0PPeSAVBqQ==", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq8Yo1XBqyw/zqOX+QFGsFqz+XWqY0U37tR7PLevjqwJh/YE/JiENv93jVqrP1t1IBi+hO54CacycQbYp90ZCZxevhzWJIPMhX2JgYkNmjYNbaQcXdkPhQ69w=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Excessive Detail", 
		"option_b": "Complex Structure", 
		"option_c": "Bulky Language", 
		"option_d": "Detailed Content", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030106", 
		"question": "2523f9H32B2q9JcpRhfx1r37MHjTEWsTpj+XWqY0fHDtU7LDaei+yJl1Z0yBn1po+3jB46r2t0cHiuhy54qWcSxDXYRh28SAw/HjzX5PbIS0JZzRMjsxtfdDXr4Co2zQ", 
		"answer": "25a3ZYH/1AGq24AnUxKy9fXtNHjZDWVTepcM6jOXdQ374cz6+if7QA==", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq+4QiVxL3wb3rPW6QIG0fsGuKRrZgeX7tFKbRLvnxxtd9IluIgVJo5n/F46T+8xMMgKVL5YuHMgcmwKiqd32Fu2nuTffsxIQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Complex Legal Phrasing", 
		"option_b": "Lawyer's Dream", 
		"option_c": "Legal Jargon", 
		"option_d": "Complicated Document", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030107", 
		"question": "24KwcdH32B2q9JcpRhfx1r3+J2zFBiIFq36XErd8dTHKWqPLb+O+6ph/NEiAmU5v+3nI47Lx5BMageV86ICbeCsCcNQtbhr6kO3medPrnu89sMOkjg==", 
		"answer": "24OxZJ3y1hyqx4QuURbz3PzrdU3fAHcC4ZfA3QEmOeEgDQgUfzrQfus=", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9YAsWxvkwPm/IWPRFyIFq3rDcax6Y2XqQLLWZ+LwiZN4IxyHgk874mTPrLf541oViuhX5o2efGIEcZ1q2t6I2efyhHBPN4ZSk4x+5Z0aPORBwj6ldc3aNO0uz33AIkvmbiq0C35xkHHUkzxxqY2//S75RSOfRZu7HiDhj2ofZeY3tw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Gandhi-Inspired Principles", 
		"option_b": "Village Panchayat Focus", 
		"option_c": "Mahatma's Vision", 
		"option_d": "Local Governance Foundation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030108", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0gvj44wjWw3/her+JivdAmYU422GVaJmdHjtU+fWZui+35JjJVOahE9isnnA47H48hMmgaxS6IDfUy0NbZ9m3MWd3uv5mzP0uVO84GE/in0d9Dl/43tO", 
		"answer": "24O9epP8whyqxJEyRx3m0O/6dw/wLj/xv+W7pJDZ3Nrbsj8=", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9pcnRxv2hen3NH+QF2oU41yMXLBgeWX2QK7NYK39xpllJlWHiF87927Fprbj/kUKz75e+4yWcSUGPophzJCZ1uDzzX9Gf4ZJm4t76p1fdeAAwyuoZtjCYPJrwGmUL1ywZje5RHN7mSHaj2QUh192IU5JZDZbeHHUC+UhuA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Excessive Wordiness", 
		"option_b": "Lengthy Composition", 
		"option_c": "Verbose Structure", 
		"option_d": "Complicated Phrasing", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030109", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV17x1/TrPGjDQ2EQr3PDRqtxMFjtUK7DYK3dxpliM1WdmE9y/XiGp7D1t0cAz6FP+s6WfiEMbJtg2tGd3uv5hH5Hc8BBm5Rn9p8MPPJSwzDte8DTJewuzWGONFH5cyypDX96h26U79I2d3lnelQoSdFft2W8Og==", 
		"answer": "25e3eoP8xhzut6YvXA3mzOnqIWLfDSBoHZwMbgxPIUab0EgwplS3", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHwwxD+/oYzEgz3w/jtJ27UQ3Ye42uLV+NdfnXqVamCTeLw2oN4M0mdhFR1snfV46SwsFEAnbpU/oubMAEMcJh7wcScw+34yjYBN9NB2pR9pJMLb7RJwimoc8baNPdhwC6PIQX1azywAX5gh3HQmHNb6JW65y60Qcl3zwE6k5U47scyL8OWzb2H4UK2lUQfbzhb78g4KZw77/AmbDCV", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "A 'Bag of Borrowings'", 
		"option_b": "Borrowed Constitution", 
		"option_c": "An 'Un-Indian Constitution'", 
		"option_d": "A 'Complex Legal Document'", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030110", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRXv8IwzXh/mzOv6dW/fAHccpnGXErR1YzHgRq7WZ+7305J1Z1qGnxt593/IpOXk/1ZPjalI4J3ffyRDaoNqiPmH0+32yjFiPMhXjolm8Y4Wc/oH3329ZtvNKe1nwWCTeAePd9LgXoBWfPGVb8aMBb22", 
		"answer": "25K3fpTh3xTv+ZFgXRiy7PP7PGqQImEF43CFEvItIyShzegu6c9H6HdYHsqzU5VrFw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHwwxD+/oYzEhLzx/jzMG+QF2oU41aNVqp1fjHAW6nReuTq3IN4KFLJjEg78zaBgKTi9VwBz4tU+ZfffyRDaoNqiIHQhLG35XJVdIZAj4Uy8JVfdeBTjDSjd9vJMPF8z3qJKEuwaD/9CXF6jXHGmHNAoZCy+imoFNwlzxhygo99re8zKtKN16WW5ln4iQDC9XWVQbwkMFeN9cGuqxLF89d6LMxNdN3oMwvDMAesrqF69w==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Annotated Constitution", 
		"option_b": "Universal Declaration of Human Rights", 
		"option_c": "Government of India Act of 1935", 
		"option_d": "Treaty of Versailles", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030111", 
		"question": "24KwcdH32B2q5IotV17x1/TrPGjDQ2EerWyKVqZmMGXrUefrYOn3yJkxBFOHnk9y5mPSqqr+t0cAz6peqcmKfm8qcI9myd7Ol+vlhDZAPdJN16l84JMecrMfjgq0TFY0GruxS355GxMWJJY=", 
		"answer": "25ysKJX61Ret48UyVxj+wP7rdULeB2sQrT+TXa99ZHjgVauCev//zZ5lLlOHnhn32ltIVMkAvb7ksc/qBK/O", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9pcnRxv2hen3NH+QF2oU43mMQKZ9d3+jWqbWe//7iZh3Z0iBiBtY/XjVt6zk4kcGgKYb5I+bdWIKast6xsOc3vD2xn1Ec8BLiMBb6p4WfbRBwjntetvPYOxryGKFJFH5cTz9C3Y0nSXFymxZpIqv/CS6WJoj0hQ2n5Nx4sYvfuqZexecGIV0yHZ67uZ801c=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "It was too progressive", 
		"option_b": "It was too conservative", 
		"option_c": "It focused on rural governance", 
		"option_d": "It didn't reflect Indian political traditions", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030112", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Ar68oY0EhH0hen3MCv5DWYYonHDcax6Y2XqQLLWZ+LwiZN4IxyKn1Jv+3XV46P5+VdPirBY7J2MeTQGPophzJCc2fP+wX1FKpkGrszdVbW5uGjeKOJoPxHHFQ==", 
		"answer": "25yse9Hg2APvt4QuVl72wOn+PGeSBLnTHnEJiGBMlnluCluFIA==", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq84AlXxv2hen3MCv5DWYYonHDcax6Y2XqQLLWZ+LwiYN+Z16MzU90/TbEtqn77h9Pi61P6IeTdSZPPophzJCK2OrjxXhPOshD2pV86p8ceedTzS+0NNHXJfNrwHqTZV3wMPs2a/zif2Irw0QgpDU=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Its simplicity", 
		"option_b": "Its brevity", 
		"option_c": "Its size and detail", 
		"option_d": "Its modernity", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030113", 
		"question": "2523f9H32B2q9JcpRhfx1r37MHjTEWsTpj+XWqY0fHDtU7LDaei+yJl1Z1+GgEt3927Pt7yw+FVPm6BeqaeRdCsCcMtMx96aw+3j0WVIPMgb2KrAkwSom8seavKPhSljNcw=", 
		"answer": "25m5f4j2w175t5UhQB/2zO76dzKUmH9HE277xmX1Gfaf6YQ=", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9I0hQB/x0fjtPHHVByIFq3rDe61weXDtFITNYP7qwINkM1WGgxt64TbSrKqw+1YIjqRS+pqWc2ICcI8vy9+Ex+j+x3BVNsII2pJ34p8Nbv1Oy325e5TSNL5v3S6BZwL8Zi6kAWIzh3HGi25XrIqo8GD5tzdR+36WKKHlNA3atfp8ag==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Public's delight", 
		"option_b": "Lawyer's paradise", 
		"option_c": "Educator's treasure", 
		"option_d": "Historian's chronicle", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030114", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTrl+ZY0Wwrn0fTwOyvZECIFq3rDXqZ6d2XrXaLReq3p255lM1mHzXh0/GXSqrHl41oAgehS586LeCdDaYR9xNTWlTHxhLsgSj6v17UJbBxVJZM=", 
		"answer": "25a3ZoLn2A3/44wvXF79w73WO2/ZAiBU3bWdp+pCNEBSijMdltfL", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f43aQErd8dTHvUanFeuX3zIRlZ12EglV8snfKr+Xk/1ZPmLpS/ZqafmIAcYV83NmdwvD+y39Sc9FLiIx285MbebZfD+JPvWBKMs+QFrUYjLr3", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Constitution of India", 
		"option_b": "British Constitution", 
		"option_c": "Australian Constitution", 
		"option_d": "Canadian Constitution", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030115", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0hbk45cpUAvmwPm/IWSQF2oU43OGXKRgeGijWqbWe//7iZh3Z0iBiBtS/HLPoquw1FwBnLxS/ZuLeS0NIckITAZ4URap5SjKBPprmRnJ", 
		"answer": "25K9Z5bh0Ani/oYhXl7zy/m/PWLDF20DqnyCXuNycXL3W7XRIq3twJl2K1nJrlR14WLPt7Dk/lwBz65U+868dSwXbI4vyd6Nl/fjxWVEIIoEno9/7ZQecvdFjDKrNNjeJ/9ijmKVKkz+Ziu0AWM2LnHHZS7Pm1+A9hf7yK2Cdw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f5GzDRKJnZH/mR7SOLuX32oN+NVWKjFc7+3jAr7D1+VAKnOQb+oeRdy4GPoxg3tWb2e35wzFFPMVRl4V88NZfffpEjCmlcZTSLuhhwniFKkD+c3myAjB4kTbXhjxTsJO+5zOoFNYyxFUmmcdx+dt8Oc+L3KaA4Vu9xgqH0nyFQP9J8WSjy6oMsTmV4l5K+Fre", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Influence of global powers", 
		"option_b": "Economic factors", 
		"option_c": "Geographical and historical factors, single Constitution for Centre and states, dominance of legal luminaries", 
		"option_d": "Cultural diversity", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030116", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0BTv+YEtVxDmhfTxIXnfB3cSpnvDdLZ6dHDuUanWb+G+7YJlLlmazU90smLOpuXZ+VcGjqYbyoGRYzYKap57wd+HiKZKOmjRTIoJwJ8wgpwbDwDY", 
		"answer": "2+HqZpWz8hbk5JEpRgvmzPLxNGeQIm8UrXuOV61gMFDgQOfNaK2vkMAnZb9HmBeieeGbY2vwsMSqRUI=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHVxBfu9oglXArzyb3bIH/ZBnFRtHqRV+N1dHXmUOfWZv/x3JB5Z0iBiBsvoHjC44b/+UAbhrxO/YeQfiMPPqpizd6N2uH50DFgMNIElYYytcNIKraoGbLbTZ9BIFH6hMuZeRgM", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "44th Constitutional Amendment Act of 1980", 
		"option_b": "42nd Constitutional Amendment Act of 1976", 
		"option_c": "86th Constitutional Amendment Act of 2002", 
		"option_d": "96th Constitutional Amendment Act of 2011", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030117", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQn4/osjWw7+wL38OmbSCmwUsD+XWqY0UmPqQK7RZq39xplyIkydzVR9smbHsan59l4Kgbxa+5ffYy0Ve5lqwdeHw/23xX9Fc9JMn8BT6Z8NdfdBwn29Zt3VI/d+wmvAKEOwbSy5DXN9lT2WmWlGuoa29CSiFNM5gAE6k8dR48w1Pdnf+qed+1mxkhOW1XSfF/8C8xmuAHaYRSTNxq8yM+Ih", 
		"answer": "24ahZoX71Arj5MUvVF7ixO/zPGrdBmwFom2aErB7ZnTxUa7FYPnniZZ/IxyDmF9y8X/Hr+Xj4kMdiqVa6pfdGtlbCSBWHnQH9bjvSu7Rrg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f432PV61wYzHiR7fHbfntiZh3Z16GmVM70GTPt6zj/xMfjrpX4I+SdSwXf5l2iMOGweHlwXhGPdJd2oF84No+cfFSxT6sepTRNfpnzWeBKwXjcimvAX11lyiaymxEp5Wy8S61U5o2gAA8n5Zt6Ig+Pdue16uWqj4qAN2c/+9jKoU524ijsqo=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Separation of powers", 
		"option_b": "Federalism", 
		"option_c": "Synthesis of parliamentary sovereignty and judicial supremacy", 
		"option_d": "Popular sovereignty", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030118", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kR//+YEhXxv80fzzdXnZBGoF43iWU7F1fmXmUbSCaP/7zJN+KhyGixt4/XjVoKz1+VAKz6lV7c6LeCdDbIJowMTJw+u31GNONcNXicwy9Igef+BJzzjhNNXVJL5+3GGQJkLxczz9BX5t1CPThnVRoYy1qmWMEcHfiYdo987gkSLkIu7x", 
		"answer": "24exb5nnkQ3lt6MyVxv2yvC/Om2QMWcdqniKXa00OFDxQK7BYui+m8I4Zb/mgwh9RGkmbDPJrQDrQic=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpdBgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+zJliMk6Mnht94HPDp6r9t1wJz7pe5YeYeS0NMstmxtOFwuD+ynYBJ85B2pJ745ILPOBPjC2/ddfPKf1rjm+OIwXgdTatBXd1gDSWi3JP6JG++S68XdU5gtHTb2L5UEaQE7UATYJ8qKU=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Right to Equality (Article 14)", 
		"option_b": "Right to Freedom of Religion (Article 25)", 
		"option_c": "Cultural and Educational Rights (Article 29)", 
		"option_d": "Right to Constitutional Remedies (Article 32)", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030119", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxRz4+sU3Uw2yxPn7MG+QF21Rt3eGEpNmdXDuVqvHLuL4iYN5Ihygg19y83iGgKr+5EcGm71P4IGRMDYMPphmz96A0f23zWVSc9VBmZV+5Yhff/xB3jyuYNHJf7xCC7lzYrk5u5hrVil3UGX9", 
		"answer": "24a9a4T/0Auo3JHNMAZi+JT98R+jmQ7PhQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt8IzVx3nyfztcivHAnFRonuHV6c0ZH6jQK/HLt3szJZ8JVCMzVlismLOpuWkpV0Lz4tU552LeTYWaoJgxtGFl8X6wX9FPsNKjsBT545fc/IAnWT6IpibKPdpxmKJIE3kbje6RFl6kDjXzW8Wu4a44Cu6Rpo5wQEnhII6rOIKAqsW2gtSQ1I2EN5Nww==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Socialist", 
		"option_b": "Sovereign", 
		"option_c": "Secular", 
		"option_d": "Republic", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030120", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTrl+ZY0Wwrn0fTwO2rcQ0McpnGHX6Z6ZDHCV7OCZ+Pq25h1Ml+MiRt4/XjVt6zk4kcGgKZa5c6NdSEMeYVm3NmG2aTxy2MBI8dKmYhz/ZsLb7QI3ii/ddibLPFtz2LAIErmYiuzCXV6gCKf1T6lXBgcpD/nkJbqXTnPiDKK", 
		"answer": "2+LrepWz8hbk5JEpRgvmzPLxNGeQIm8UrXuOV61gMFDgQOfNaK2vkM4jZXFmTtaRLgP6ox0m1WXlIDA=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGkggvut6QtVxD2yPjxISvxAHZRrHnDA/otIjHxUaTNaeP305J1Z0yIg1hz82/Ht7awv0EanalXqYKQcyMPPoxg3tWb2enyymVSeoZFicBzpJkQcudUxSm4YN3ULv9ijmuOM0zkfntUhz0q+A5SUASWnvxuy2TH", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "73rd Constitutional Amendment Act of 1992", 
		"option_b": "42nd Constitutional Amendment Act of 1976", 
		"option_c": "86th Constitutional Amendment Act of 2002", 
		"option_d": "97th Constitutional Amendment Act of 2011", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030121", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRrl+ZY0Wwrn0fTwO2rcQ2Aep2bDW7A0YnTwRKjMfeT8xZIxIVObzV514WPUqqv3t1Udiq0b6ICbMCQCd5kvzdyM1PD+y39Sc89K2ql84JMeI7ZkDL0X8mabiLYE0jwIQWtm", 
		"answer": "25C0bZLn2Bbkt6YvXxP71u72OmWSWS//ypu+C5rxaoW8PhzFbQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHW3Rzp44wvXF7RyvDyPHjDCm0f43aQErd1Y3rmUOfVZ/n2iZR+KVicjk9y/HGGpbf18hMOgawb74+WYmIGco5s3NmG2fe30H4BA8dWlolz6Z8RaLRBwjntZ8DaNPsuwmuHLlb8Zi2oFnVn1hYfMLCk6upY7oWM4VUzk68=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Comptroller and Auditor-General", 
		"option_b": "Union Public Service Commission", 
		"option_c": "State Public Service Commission", 
		"option_d": "Election Commission", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030122", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzwQvj+YYpQhL3hfnwMHiQF2oU41aNVqp1fjHAW6nReuTq3IN4KFLJi1R3/nnR47L48l1Phrwb6oGSdTFDaoQvyd2M2eD+ynYBOtJX2pBg64wWb/1Pwi7yNiMAeWprHJLme2fWU/tE9NY=", 
		"answer": "25e0bZ/3kRbst7cpVRf2zOnmdWreByI3r3qbW6F9fHj3TeWRVnVZYjgKM3juTmoY1IED", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f43yMX6F9fnTwFKLOa+D7x4NiZ1OPzUly9X/CqrHpt1IBi+hd5YuHeSAKcoJ70ZCA2aT+0GIBMstBlIR/4ZQLPORSwz6oZ8eZQLZNgWX6kZXwprzhKnuQCg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Parliamentary Sovereignty", 
		"option_b": "Judicial Supremacy", 
		"option_c": "Blend of Rigidity and Flexibility", 
		"option_d": "Unitarism", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030123", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTrl+ZY0Wwrn0fTwO2rcQ0McpnGHX6Z6ZDHCV7OCZ+Pq25h1Ml+MiRt4/XjVt6zk4kcGgKZa5c6NdSEMeYVm3NmG2aTxy2MBPtNKk4N79JsTdeBJyS7tPMHJIv9gjmKPJET8Jz6yEnVmmjzThGhF4dz5lyYYRIQI+sSlLWQl/6WO1Q==", 
		"answer": "2+LsfJmz8hbk5JEpRgvmzPLxNGeQIm8UrXuOV61gMFDgQOfNaK2vkM4jZScFLotA4HWL4nvOUr2Kplw=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGkhQ3it6QtVxD2yPjxISvxAHZRrHnDA/otIjHxUaTNaeP305J1Z1Gcg1J4+2bHr6zk/lYcz+BO+4yefmIPcYhuxJCO2PLy1n9MNshQicky5YlffbRDwzO+YN3PNepnwWCBKwX1aS20EGk2seIoP64oEtn82/SGtZPqFA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "73rd Constitutional Amendment Act of 1992", 
		"option_b": "74th Constitutional Amendment Act of 1992", 
		"option_c": "86th Constitutional Amendment Act of 2002", 
		"option_d": "97th Constitutional Amendment Act of 2011", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030124", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kR//+YEhXxv80fzzdXnZBGoF43aNErd8dTHKWqPLb+O+6ph/NEiAmU5v+3nI46zjt1IGgq1fqY+LMDIRcYZg3NmH0KTjzHQBOsJBm4wy65xfb/tDxTyhNNXVJL5rzWGOKEj5ZHm5AX17lyPXiWUJ6uw2teSNd04fd5IR9rNWjIA=", 
		"answer": "25GxepTwxRD88sUQQBf8xvTvOW7DQ20X40yXU7dxMEHsWK7Bd69yq7/A+9g5XhuHjreaoKE6", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHX2Avv9JEpRBuy9e/2O2jZE24UsD+MVONHZHD3UefyYeH3yo4xNFmMhhtv/TbWsar9+EcKz7xT7M6WdCcCcstgzpCa2Of+xX0BMshA2oVx65QQcf1DjDmoedvYMv9t1y6JKQXZaT20BTIiRTwQEMsfcHWnMy2BiEnO", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Right to Equality (Article 14)", 
		"option_b": "Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"option_c": "Right to Freedom of Religion (Article 25)", 
		"option_d": "Cultural and Educational Rights (Article 29)", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030125", 
		"question": "25Gtepj91lnrt4shRhf9y/zzdW7dBnAWpnGAS+80Z3niQOfKb/3uzJliZ0iGzU9z9zbApqH15VIDz6Za/ZuNdWIMeMt7wNXJ/urzzXBPc+VLlJNm7Y4KaP1PwmLvfEY0Q6o+Q6TPAl6bEZx9BQ==", 
		"answer": "25ysKJP20hbn8pZgRxD70fztLCvZDSIes3qRU7d9f3+h+1Y48s+FoNhuZqQI7WzqQA==", 
		"explanation": "25Gtepj91lnrt4shRhf9y/zzdW7dBnAWpnGAS+80ZHnmFKHHaujsyJsxNEibmFhv52TD46r2t0cHiuhy54qWcSxDXYRh28SAw/HjzX5Pc8VMm4514YlfaPsAzX24et3PIex3jmGOIguwUzG4RGB7gzTEynNQ6Jez8GeoQNsjxQZykYJs/ogvNdCR0K6a60y2kgqbnGmUTKhnFFDV9c+m7wOIqId4tsiDpSDa+LT+le7W4tAGZwZG/4F+alWv17gb9ycxX826axcFsdDYZBTdMi2wLgoY99+j2XIp74wtVGh4tApWjY0Wdsh2lpngqjszOo1lE3Ouq0EAxJFySwWXeP2/337h8lsycHQ/KcpuvSN1pgaKLRR6k3mZTzhYm454vsQW1Rd3fHtFjzbvjH+Dj3LPaJyj7pj5l+v5s7wj5qsiIFPAMETdVZgIbKXFZ3d93eyJHugcFox0EizyNNQi8CC1YIKc2nkJ2co0PX7l4T6QncO1NmP6o53ui8ZlVL0FIsbA7MX3pFTCISDkL2mWdIv1VwywW3T9kx1xtgwg22ET6WyYCow/9CEZm2y1TQRmi2f0ZHnhg7BV5YzOeIEn1ufi0DcejLo4q5P+x10/Qgqvn35Pu56aSxxO2EDeEd8O0BBuCboSAYTU4S2X1XXfRG4JdsD3Fa2Dgz5NyfP+gHJ4/4QBFZiGKVneh9s0zxK/AuQ1FWX4vMbtNflVDGEo/6Bwxq2vtt6uZ/bkI2NqexKyGcxW/YZFYRZuBQLSC2RGc/i8U44KTvJK1jXFmQRNB2tBABrJ9q0aWgGkqd2IZ3mecbQKARXnZ/1HgLafChXDYRws8q8I/4E0vA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "It remains completely federal", 
		"option_b": "It becomes unitary in operation", 
		"option_c": "It gets dissolved and becomes a presidential system", 
		"option_d": "It remains unchanged but with enhanced powers to the states", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030126", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEgv8zOzqMCvWBmMFtm2GEqxyMGXrUefrYOn3yJkxBFOHnk9y5mPSqqr+t1oBz7xe+4OMMC0FPo5izcKO0ur03TFRIclSk5N765QMI7bLxhzMCnjFtEvADoXOJF6H", 
		"answer": "24GqaZ/g1xb4+oQ0WxH8hfvtOmaQBWcVpm2CXuNgfzH2Wq7Wb//niYRoNEiMgBt/52TPraKw8l4Kna9e542WdTFBMzVM6MQsEl33KpxniZ1dlQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f42uRU61ndn7xWbSCaP/xxNdwZ1qMiV5p83qGsLzj41YCz7xUqY/fZSwKaop90ZCazvfjwXwBN9NWk451pJ8SeeZHyTOufdHIbL5rwH2VNUz+YHm4AnZxlyXfnHkWuoao5Si1R9931Bpyk59s/8kzLtOW16mB8Q2rjxKX3W+YR7N3U3dVuRKmzTLPB3Z/fzR0k88=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Continuation of federal structure", 
		"option_b": "Creation of a separate emergency branch", 
		"option_c": "Transformation from federal to unitary system during emergencies", 
		"option_d": "Expansion of state authority", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030127", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEh39y+7rPH/FF2serX6PErBgcWX2R+fNaK39xtp+N1mbjE9y5HOGsKrz/lYbhq1IqYeRMAsNeoJuiNGPw+HlhGVJNoYdzZR6pLkQcudUxSm4YN3ULv9ijk+NIkv0ajyzEDBVlyWJyCkNAIreTgcBLRDeFaY+SpE=", 
		"answer": "24GwbYiz2Rj88sUhEh39y+7rPH/FF2serX6PErBgcWX2R+fVZ/n2iZFkKViIgF515nfK47f58FsbnOha54rfVCsRe4h7wcaMl9TlzX9COtZIn5Mw3XZLVTIEvLFgxcfU/mbSTQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGqhg3it6YvXA3mzOnqIWLfDWMd416OV61wfXTtQOfjbfm+yph/IVmbn15/snXJrbbk/kcam6FU54+TMDEXf59625Cd2KT0yzxOI8NWm5R78p9fb/tDxTi5fdHIbL5nwHqSKEHlZDCzAzBygT/Si3FTppe6+WepXd0/1AZyl4l8rew1LtKczaGF7Q2IlA+M33KBRLh3UUacuc+87kfctI14ocWIvHA8lTZ5PBIUYPbZD+QYivuq", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "They are regulated by ordinary laws", 
		"option_b": "They have a constitutional status with fundamental rights and Directive Principles", 
		"option_c": "They are under the purview of local governments", 
		"option_d": "They are governed by the President", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030128", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEh/1wL3tMHrFCnAUrnqNRuNyf2OjQanLeOjs2pZ9Z12NmFdvsnDUoqvz/1ociuhS5862fiYKf9QtbeHYZT+2sJ+sDU5zXOH+8w==", 
		"answer": "2+TgKIj20Av5tcJVk0ppcXMXYhvxGRPzaaQ=", 
		"explanation": "25CubYPqkRrj44w6VxCy0vXwdWLDQ2wetz+PV7BnMGXrVamCP7W+0JJwNU/Jgl0783HD46zjt1YDhq9S64KaMCQMbMt6xtmf0vbkxX0BMsJRlpQy4ogecvdIxS6oNN3VYNdgymeBZY8e92v17HyPDvTAz16hPf0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "18 years", 
		"option_b": "21 years", 
		"option_c": "25 years", 
		"option_d": "30 years", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030129", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRb48IQuEhH0hen3MCv5DWYYonHDcax6Y2XqQLLWZ+LwiZ5iZ06Mnkt0/GXPoan1t1UAneha/IqWZCsNect7wNXJ1uf0y2RPJ9UElYYy8JIaPNdFwim/ddibIfBqjn2UJlH1Jz6yEnVmmjzThGhF98FhKaTWGEH0Cn9YOOzVNpAw", 
		"answer": "25a3ZYHnwxbm+4AyEh/8wb3eIG/ZF20D7liGXKZmcX2jW6GCR+P6wJYzi3CjVUPZBN0wzg/c3n9adA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hT645cvXhL3173+O2+QIncVqmuMQO5TdX/mRqbOLuzrzZ5lNBydhV4783XFrLD+40BPgK4b/YaaMAEGcJ99ydzJ1urzhGJVMtJB2od98p8NcvlFwim+OJTeLu173GeOIAX2bje8CnN9lT2Wi39Vp5a14Sa5XdY+1Axwd5K53FIJ5jQKIUAhs11NSA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Election Commission", 
		"option_b": "Union Public Service Commission", 
		"option_c": "Comptroller and Auditor-General of India", 
		"option_d": "Reserve Bank of India", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030130", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kR//+YEhXxv80fzzdW/FF3tRtH6QEqJwdHTnFKXbLvn2zNcpcUiBzXh0/GXSqrHl41oAgalXqa+SdSwHc45h3JCo1PC3y3cBYZYUyN8wm2f3wHLZpSuNTD+TmLsIhg==", 
		"answer": "24G3KIHh3g3v9JFgUxD2hfTyJXnfFWdRt3eGEq11ZGTxVauCa+PowIV+KVGMg085KT9VaqrzteNncSZKhc9s9g==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGrhw3it6YvXA3mzOnqIWLfDWMd416OV61wfXTtQOfjbfm+xpExdQzZ3xt69nLDp+Xk/1ZPib1V7Y+SdSwXf4cvzMWdzqTjyzFRIclQn4NmpJsReLRJwS2/e8LeYOpmyy6OJlHldTixRHV6gjjEhXJbrY2vt6CQ99SR+0X4DW6qJS9ErjM=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "To respect the Constitution", 
		"option_b": "To promote the spirit of common brotherhood", 
		"option_c": "To protect and improve the natural environment", 
		"option_d": "To preserve cultural heritage", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030131", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTrl+ZY0Wwrn0fTwO2rcQ0McpnGHX6Z6ZDHCV7OCZ+Pq25h1Ml+MiRtv+nOGt6Di+hNInK1Y/IKeYmVDd4Uv3NiMl9TlwXBMMcpB2o90pI4XebRpwjmkddqbA/Fg3XqJM1DkbjazWzIddG0IBtViWI1CuG8PKv8O", 
		"answer": "2+HqZpWz8hbk5JEpRgvmzPLxNGeQIm8UrXuOV61gMFDgQOfNaK2vkMAnZb9HmBeieeGbY2vwsMSqRUI=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGngxfut6YvXA3mzOnqIWLfDWMd416OV61wfXTtQOfjbfm+xpExdgXe2xt69nLDp+Xk/1ZPm61J5M7YYycAa4du2pfJw+u30HlEc/ZWn4F/5pYaMLRSyTuhcdfPKfBpjkeOI0zxICr9F3V3gT3XmDxVoIKp9CSvUch1egIYSO0gAI7BAMWbTJXv5Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "44th Constitutional Amendment Act of 1980", 
		"option_b": "73rd Constitutional Amendment Act of 1992", 
		"option_c": "42nd Constitutional Amendment Act of 1976", 
		"option_d": "97th Constitutional Amendment Act of 2011", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030132", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRvl85xgWw2y0fX6dWPZBGoUsGvDUaxhYmWjW6GCb/3uzJZ9axyOmFpp83jSrLew+FVPib1V7Y+SdSwXf4cv2tmO3/DkiDFAPcIEnZVz9p4WffoAwzvtYNzeYN1hwH2ULlHlczCyCjB9mnH/hHhfqdz51h9og+btzKI+tNefkwBeWQ==", 
		"answer": "24ateIP23Byq1Io1QAqwzxOW37NpeNuQZ39H1/f/qA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHAxAn48oglEj390O/rdXjVEXQUsD+CQeNgeHSjXK7FZujt3ddyKEmbmRt09DbHs7X19l9Dz7hJ5pqaczYMbMtgzpCPwurzxXxEPdJFlsBg7Z0XaOcMjDyjcJTcNf98ymeBKQX/YXmpDHU0tz7YmWhfvJav/Ci1FNM5gDw8ko55rzJ3TU0TyNpw4dB1s+fjQGg=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "High Court", 
		"option_b": "Supreme Court", 
		"option_c": "President of India", 
		"option_d": "Comptroller and Auditor-General", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030133", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3v5YhgVhvhxu/2N27DQ3YZpj+qXKd9cX+jd6jMffn33YJlLlOHzVposnDDp6Di9l9PhqYb74GNfWIBa58v3d6Aw+Xl3TFIPYZXiolg7Y5APgcBMg9rhm+0bgV/9hakR2Q=", 
		"answer": "25O9bJTh0BWq/otgVBHgyL39IH+cQ3cfqmuCQLo0eX+jR7fLfOTqi9I9N/hKzIpL27FF80ZGeFM=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f43aQEqxyZHTtFKPHfe7swJV0IxyInhtHsHDDp6Di9l9PhqYb74GNfWIBa58v3d6Aw+Xl3TFIPYZXiolg7Y4jPrRE2TjtYNubKep9jmOJPwX/YXm7AXRxhjDayn1YrMOu+y6vVcgugBM3l5Nt/80vfuEhG2T4L4Fakrky8WRWh30=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Quasi-federal", 
		"option_b": "Co-operative federalism", 
		"option_c": "Federal in form but, unitary in spirit", 
		"option_d": "Unitary in form but federal in spirit", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030134", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTj444wjXhuyyvu/IWPVQ0sfp3aCXONXf3/wQK7We/n3xpkxI1mPhFV+4TbvraH59hMOnOhaqcmqfisMcMtgzpC6w+XjwWIGbIQKI3lsEZ8JBsq9LmKi+U6w", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpseXcG+dWDPUDYvFA2GmkIap", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpsUvVF7mzfi/HGXUCmMf41yMXLBgeWX2QK7NYK36zJF4KVmazXJ19n/H46Tjt1JPyJ1V4IGRMC0FPrh7ycSMxKO5hEVJNoZQn5J/pJMSbPhJyS7tdZTdJfpr3G+MZ1bkdSy+EGVmkXHBg2he6IL75jOpW9QwgBY3mJN9/4R8K9+W2qDT4V74h0aX0nKAXbgkF1GYodu67gOTpsIsvcjNmDzf/fX32v7W9NsZYxxbsIgxI26ym6EC/Wo3RcCxelJN9ODVc1X5KSetNE4K8cLg3jRo1IdpSWExtA1DkZZadoB80NjlsnIxON9vED6/rVAAxZFoSBKTev2x3mzh8FAxcX8lccp4siQhskPcAVp6k2qSDD9FlZRu7ZARlBJmPWFP3GX1gTfLk2CffYHi/4W8gPD5s61m/KAiaVGSPFPKFpkTJafIIid0xfuWDLJVPJEnGCSmKd0rvAv8MIOW0zAOnpkIKnnk8WbZhsXweXG/oZ+5yeF4HbAOdt7DqfijsUjCcmShKXyAJsnxXAawWm/9105xuFggxTEY6XHREow/4SUI3ne+TUF3hjX1b2iolLdQ45aXP4E3k+Hk2HIFlv13kdlKdklvr2fIRyhfilgbhEzI", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Article 1", 
		"option_b": "Article 21", 
		"option_c": "Article 25", 
		"option_d": "Article 32", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030135", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhPzzPO/M2TTFnFRrHnDRqtxMFXqRqLBeuTozNdBNVWHjlJr/nPV46r2t2Abjrxeqb6QfCsAZ9QtfLt4H5LAwZLQj9xgvp+DVA==", 
		"answer": "24WqZ5z8xRDl+cUvVF7hyv72NGeQAmwV43qAXa17fXjgFKPHY+L925ZyPh7i96Gv+nBkRbPdBg3kjZT5", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHX2Avv9JEpRBuy9e/2O2jZE24UsD+MVONHZHD3UefyYeH3yo4xJlWEzU90smbUrKj/41ZPnKdY4I+TMCMNestqy9+H2On+xzFFNstLmZJz54NfdfoA5TOpfdWZOET7d3L0L6Q8ap7FC2CDQQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Protection of fundamental rights", 
		"option_b": "Establishment of religious freedom", 
		"option_c": "Promotion of social and economic democracy", 
		"option_d": "Electoral representation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030136", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQE3cDs3CQV+N7djH3XKKCSPjwzZZ8IlKdjFc7wH/Bq7Hjt1oBz7xT7M62fiYKf4Uv69+HxPD+0GRVOslKxcKMzZn57E1jtJFLuoxIkgO6", 
		"answer": "25mxZZjn2Bftt5EoV17iyur6JyvfBSIFq3rDV7txc2T3XbHHLuzwzdd9IluAnld65mPUpufCdTSvUbDAPDm8y24DTsHn", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHVxBfu9oglXArzyb3NPGzYF3FRonyXEqJnMHCjV6/Hbea+xpkxM1SMzV5j93XTt6zm8hMOgawb5YuYeTEPf59m3tXJx+vgwWNSf4ZUiIVk4ZQLdfpHjCm0ZtXVLucuz2CEZ0TiZTCpFnFmjXHai2tF6tyvF4KoH/iA1OxhVjSstxI=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Promoting economic growth", 
		"option_b": "Establishing social harmony", 
		"option_c": "Limiting the power of the executive and legislature", 
		"option_d": "Ensuring religious freedom", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030137", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhPz3fTyIGaQAmUU43OKX6pgMHfsRufDLu733Z5rIlLJmVQ78HOGpqn58FoNg60b74GNMDcNd51q2sOI26T2wGRNJ4ZCiIF855IWb/EAxTPtXdrfKf8xjNGY0ijYapyy0P9VndHHOEw=", 
		"answer": "25u3KJzyyRDn4ohgUxn3hfH2OGLEQaHbQ8jlkNA8b093EzakGdI=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbYP2kRD5t4svEhPz3fTyIGaQAmUU43OKX6pgMHfsRufBZ/n305J/NBydght+6nPUoKzj8hMbh61S+86NeSULast7x5Cc2e3hwWNSMsoEm4Rn6I5feuZBwj6lfcfeYPdgjkeOI0zxJc+z+0/tCaW7yTqcISuMWrk=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "No maximum age limit", 
		"option_b": "21 years", 
		"option_c": "25 years", 
		"option_d": "30 years", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030138", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTj444wjXhuyyvu/IWPVQ0sfp3aCXONXf3/wQK7We/n3xpkxKEmdgVJ192WGt631t1YCirpc7ICcaWITbIR5wcOA2OrkmzNb3elR9w8lIpZ9pFvRJRHo", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNByHl7T1+n2NmfVQzFE9TPDc7FgeXLvUeeROL28GWNt1tl4y3KNX0H58mcdWg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH23Bz48IAuUQey1e/wI2LDCm0fsD+CQKY0f2T3WK7Ma+m+wJkxBk6dhFh39zaV9vewv30Om6FU54+TMCcOe5lozd6Kzq27hFBTJ89HloUyt89JPLxz2Dy5cZTeLft8yWuOJFy5K3m8CnQ0tSPCg39arcPoo3f7HPw+zhQ8lY554Yg5MdKN3q2d61TxxLNekeRmOwV2XBMAi+U4sPY=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Article 14", 
		"option_b": "Article 25", 
		"option_c": "Article 352, Article 356, Article 360", 
		"option_d": "Article 44", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030139", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTrl+ZY0Wwrn0fTwO2rcQ0McpnGHX6Z6ZDHCV7OCaezozNdwZ1+Gg0hv+2LTt6z/+VIDz7tP6JqKY2ICcI8v2MKGw+H00HhOPYZQlcBx69cQbPFSzSmkYtGbM/Ftx2uULkDjJzCzRFl6kDjX1T7vi6i16/mk9wee95gp7zT0", 
		"answer": "2+zvfJmz8hbk5JEpRgvmzPLxNGeQIm8UrXuOV61gMFDgQOfNaK2smcYgZT5y5+vTTx1cWmUMrm6AwRg=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGqhg3it6YvXA3mzOnqIWLfDWMd416OV61wfXTtQOfjbfm+xpExdQzY3Btr4HnQqqH18xMMgKZI/YeLZTYKcYVuxJCaw+Xj0WIBMshA2pBg644af+BJwzPtYNubI/EjwX6FNUTkbi+4RGN7lzjTnnVTu8Oy+2eSWt4+wVf2ugBZI9uj6KCLZjvxb+Ct", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "44th Constitutional Amendment Act of 1980", 
		"option_b": "97th Constitutional Amendment Act of 2011", 
		"option_c": "86th Constitutional Amendment Act of 2002", 
		"option_d": "90th Constitutional Amendment Act of 2010", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030140", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EYj0KFILsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8H1fWNP34kCikoBV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LwCXPPNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyYFs1cJfOAZycyiqnbTeYcc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbUn3lNkJlgbzentGrZ0o21eSX689K5zpQ2VP9AdpGFqYv38ByHIWOhYT3TJou0GUiwDzy4k04l91hliGFQqCKYSMk/tW1N3j7wCQQk0megLDzh1v4cqsLOP85xk7WsnXJQ2LQ439u3lF18B0T7zT8D8sTfbk9cyEbCF8IJnkkaBLFBPZjV+2yY1VXfRW8ZdtrjFaGIzWxByaPlhmQ9s5UAUpiGJRzInp4pzlewDfE5QnXkvJL8M7w2BWo/7rtl3/mouMSoNfqqbHEialqgVv1V99URKEI7UUudRWQPIPjuFt1eAaAPkjWK10cIBz8JRRqMu+hIHUTq6oSILiqeI/FcTl6iI/NFU464DgePdbHpiHCJRv/c1Qf+HwRlDnrdYfBNpUewOsyyZFPz0ygkuYGlchEbBMNXfGezNCv55ePDS0Z6P2xlaMoHOgeVC1Bk1H6DZ7knzedAMFhtAejnWRBW1lEP336SThgF8AxeH+XtABNnaukFYBtRjXf1UeBfHFyKxnpKzhbcgmKsaboLcQljOyTTzwyg29Im37+pwryEC8ftI+db+5lDK7lVUJvfEUhcm7PU/eThHG41AyE3IO3FW/DepVy2I9rgq8DWwE8Hib8GMh8IJjGOjYrV9SktO61OezBJsmUcvorEYxSj1p1KlVF7QFDv4VKkTmFhsR5la4Hla9PfL9nsCXywB2STRiUfBAQoVg7P", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Ar58pc0WxH8hfzxMSviBmMCrHHDU7FxMGXxQaKOLuzwzddDIl2aglU7+2WGt631t1AAnbpe6prfdToTcophycSA2Oq3y3cBEtVXn5Jm7ZURPpj8mlgY8S9+7q+6nUJOO0w=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f43aQEqp6dHTmUOfWZui+xZJ/IEiBhF5o5jbRsazk41YBz4tU552LeTYWaoJgxpCA2aTjzHQBJMlWloQ8pLMLb7RDwzC9ZtHTJfB9x3iFZ0vxcyyvATB3lT+WiHkWqZev5y65Qc4yxFUmmcds5c18OtaczeiH4Eysxg+WnH6fS7JpAVWKpsu7q0LckJA9tMCPvTeXtPW5lvnB99tLbB1fvYNtI1S614kb7CM7Xc2nKFpP+PLZZVHpYCGtMwFd6crxwmcpx4wtHWo89Q9Sh5FFK4wz15bg/CE1Kch4FD/6kEdIwpBpUxKFOP2v2GHn6BUren0ucYJorm0lswCKIVB72mrcSClFlYln+9RZkxZicGpXk2TrwjmEkiWIc4Xm+Y79i+v14LBtsoopLUiBexzsXohcYKvUImlhw/+eA6NPIN9oEWLyNdBu3zb3M4KdyywZ2dYub3b1/TmcgY3zK2q384bxi5R4EboEdsXKqcqztE7CcjChNXWWJs/9Tw3iXHm40gBh9w4k2igV7CLKDZhq/D8Ik3u+XVcknSGgbTyimbNM5oeWP50+0PzjkDEFlOBtjZr7lBM9Uw20gz9Pu4+aD3VByV3XUo0Cyho7Hr0PE9bB4GKAnGXZRHIeP8j5E+iC1Slaw6PwnXF4vIROWorOKxbNj8woyRmyBL14W2OtpIfuf4smW49S7a6ye9NpbZolOGI=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both Assertion and Reason are true, and Reason is the correct explanation of Assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both Assertion and Reason are true, but Reason is not the correct explanation of Assertion", 
		"option_c": "Assertion is true, but Reason is false", 
		"option_d": "Assertion is false, but Reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030141", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQrp/4AkRxL3hfL5dX/YBiI4rXuKU600U37tR7PLevjqwJh/Z0+ZiFhy9H/DsOXk/1ZPn6dM7JyMPGICa59nx8KAw/27hHBPN4ZWn5Ni65QMdfZJwDS5fdHIYPFojkOVKUzzbim8CHlgnTTF1T6Kd2l8vpow5NW7KTWni4qK", 
		"answer": "24GvbZ31xRGositjqg5pXNjUICy9p6xdZg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHHxhzm8ZEoEi3xzfj7IGfVQ20X42uLV+NdfnXqVamCTeLw2oN4M0mdhFR1smXWpqb58VoKnOhP4YvfYC0Ue5l8hJCIwvD/y2NIJ98I2oF84NoNeedQwzO+fdbSLPd6x2uTZ0r2JxSoCnl3nSHXhnVCoYaotQ6vFM0201UzkoN96Yg+JZeL0a3Tvxmsjkaj0X6fTLBhH0DZlM28q0ya4NNh7J/PaZoKIO7tyNB3tuASyPGaOw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "First", 
		"option_b": "Eighth", 
		"option_c": "Fifth", 
		"option_d": "Twelfth", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030142", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQrl4pcjV179w73rPW6QKmwVqn6NEoB7fmL3XbPXeuTxx9dzKE6bgkx+9jbSq6Cw9FwBjK1L/c6QdmJEeJ5hzNGE0urjxX0BIc9DkpRho8VdL0GD8d7cslBpKjHsc12uJg==", 
		"answer": "24CLKjuYFvFSiEjYi438nd1iyEQ=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f432MQLF7Z3TnFLPKa639xplyIkydzVR9sjHAtqv09l4Kgbxa5c6NeSULapgoiNab2Om30HlEc/N32qN96okLdeBV2DSiepZrOfqnitR88PsykDqtHDvy", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "British", 
		"option_b": "Canadian", 
		"option_c": "US", 
		"option_d": "French", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030143", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQnr5ZFgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+yphnIk6azU9z9zbzraz/+RMogL5e+4CSdSwXPophzJCAw/e3wmRPMNJNlY5hu9iyNwyGvJ/2XUIie62UBuS1", 
		"answer": "24W5eoWz51v2rEhhLyiEBoMdLtVebl5y", 
		"explanation": "24W5eoWz51nl8cU0Whuy7PP7PGreQ0EerWyXW7dhZHjsWufBYfv724QxM1SMzW51+3nI44L/4VYdgaVe55rfcSwHPoJ725CPwur00HhOPdUGx+nquerMqiHGnmSW2htJIQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Part V", 
		"option_b": "Part II", 
		"option_c": "Part VII", 
		"option_d": "Part X", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030144", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRj444wjXhuyyvu/IWPVQ0sfp3aCXONXf3/wQK7We/n3xpkxI1mIgUg75X/Sq+Xk/1ZPiadJ5I+LeS0NPoRpiN6MwKTk0HBVNtUEm452pJsTaPFSzSmke9qbL/guz3yFJla8JzuyEX5wlSPfj28a6IyptSm6Wd8kgBo01oJg5NsoNdmYmbuH6Vm9lVnAglxX1Jv8FApCBlUwrkDQYg==", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpMfN395poHWcSVTHmJ7agc5c", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpMUvVF7mzfi/HGXUCmMf41yMXLBgeWX2QK7NYK36zJZ9NByehE9zsmLOpuX2+EECjrxS5oDffyRDcI54iMOd1vDy1zFAPcIEm4xm4YgeaP1Pwn2icpTaMvtv3SLAJUrlaT28Fnlxh32WhW4WpoK28DT7W9x3xQ07hZNx4898L8Oeza2AqsA16ztw1rIDFyvmdFdCMaM=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Article 1", 
		"option_b": "Article 3", 
		"option_c": "Article 5", 
		"option_d": "Article 9", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030145", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRri9pU0Vwyyyvu/IWPVQ0sfp3aCXONXf3/wQK7We/n3xpkxJFOfiElosmLOpuX88lQGnKRa/YeJdWITcZxq2sPJ2OK30HlEc/ZWn5N74J8RaLRPyn2EetDSIaEsYHioy0QjuBrq+KiDtcvIFQ==", 
		"answer": "25awaYHn1Auq3sUvVF7CxO/rdV2SJh4bGl+6KvvNMrYxasc8BA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH/1B7j5IkhRhfkwL3vOnzVEXFRrHnDRqtxMEHxUbTLaujw3dd+IRygg19y8zbHsaCw+EYbg6FV7IrfeSxDXYNu2MSMxaTehH5Hc/ZFiJQy0toQerRUxDjtXdrfKf9gjk2PKVbkbi2oEHl7mn+WvnRfu8O4/SarQN8ljFUmn5N06Mx8AJWr0a3TzVW9hROW1W2UBIEmUVGXtsGl+0KPs4cr9eyfpTvY+PHq2q2BsMoEIl8K/4dxZxu4krwI8SYrEdy8bVJZ/ujVchitMCe0IhwOtYvi2HApwJcnXn09+xFVwoxQItR709jRsjs/MY1PDTa5tlBJ0ZEwHx6Yd7Gt1GHq5xUrfX9rVZhoryQxpAGIZBRIk2iZARxDkZNi+tUXgUgjXmBVknXpjn+EhiWidZ3q+JT5l/u84Lht9uMzIUTAFEjMWZ8SYKqAAGJ8z/uaAeZaPI0nPiziNNRgvA3xJdaY2j4Ew9UhO37x8WqJndrwK3b6vJS5mtxzVI8SM8LM7c65pBCHcjbiKT2SdYvzUB75QXu40h12shYxiDUfqGDRBIVsuW0ei3O9RkptnCCgbXKl1q5O5ZCBeJs43fKs7TMClP15kp75wFF8Rgq/zXZQoZGWQVsPwkbSF8MGygorH/hBFYTUsmyahnmQTnAMfcHkALyCx2xB1KPlhmhu/4MLVpiHIxeZNk1/2SU6MeXFtpXBMp8/cw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Chapter II of Part IV", 
		"option_b": "Chapter III of Part VI", 
		"option_c": "Chapter I of Part V", 
		"option_d": "Chapter IV of Part VII", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030146", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kRzr9I1gRhvgyL3oPH/YQ2sFsD+AXbFmdWLzW6nGZ+P5iZN0NF+bhEtv+3nI4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EYj0KFILsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8H1fWNP34kCikoBV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LwCXPPNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyYFs1cJfOAZycyiqnbTeYcc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbUn3lNkJlgbzentGrZ0o21eSX689K5zpQ2VP9AdpGFqYv38ByHIWOhYT3TJou0GUiwDzy4k04l91hliGFQqCKYSMk/tW1N3j7wCQQk0megLDzh1v4cqsLOP85xk7WsnXJQ2LQ439u3lF18B0T7zT8D8sTfDxwPjRSWXo1HhEluTPRBVNaRsi3W1TaQCzxNP462QejHg2wImqOxziE9/9BOFczObFmbyp5miFfxQb05FSet6Ma5fbxVSiRsuvIxiq3h94r7NbPkbCVqL1r3Ga8Zs9URKEI7UUudRWQPIPjuFt1eAaAPkjWK10cIBz8JRRqMu+hIHUTq6oSILiqeI/FcTl6iI/NFU464DgePdbHpiHCJRv/c1Qf+HwRlDnrdYfBNpUewOsyyZFPz0ygkuYGlchEbBMNXfGezNCv55ePDS0Z6P2xlaMoHOgeVC1Bk1H6DZ7knzedAMFhtAejnWRBW1lEP336SThgF8AxeH+XtABNnaukFYBtRjXf1UeBfHFyKxnpKzhbcgmKsaboLcQljOyTTzwyg29Im37+pws7BSpSibf1bks1DaPYbBNqWXxtc2rOkr6GgUSx5Ri03briIHqKR8A+2Qoi04oOahRwLif5Idh97ZXnLyd+ZsHotb+UPLzAK/TNZ7IqSIkbqmcgZlRAoEBWstQGkASdh9lEzLtOrKp2catvlsBAfVmSHF/kD2Lw4nWykdZ+RJFp/RyN10UfQNpKKh3TDfey7gO1JRVjil9mLBcotrAg5jpzygwwA63s1zzyiSzaaIqetqF4UYjw4C/TfWh0dxldilXrxnhOofc/qx+ZJzvABmPVToUy34mE2zx7MDwqOIzOqnrbe9yaG/gdhieojHCbjGzMtjkxkBLBrsjkuAG1hCeE0/Pa1bPGE3iHvbtz4jcxNpRYUBueKb/37/ZW8ZeOFb+WsmcDDbzKhsdNFDea7aPdFYGHEcDVfiLfndsTtREtFotKyuq3Uay6HV0N7uF4y", 
		"answer": "24G3KIP2wgnv9JFgRhb3hd7wO3jECnYEt3aMXON6cWXqW6nDYq34xZZ2Z12HiRt182LPrKvx+xMOgbxT7IPfPWIxe4ZmxtSA2eO3x3hVOtxBlJMy65xfaPxFxS/tcMHPKft9jm+MKEv3Jy60EHg0hjjRgmhF5MOP+merRtU6zwE31pNw6IgvLN6N0LzT50v4hQmP0XSfCL92HkCRsNyg5EyY4IM1usOK8TPX+LTpn/fD/NtLL0hzu4J2bVz8mKYMuCc3Q830bgdF9eXdZFr5ISTjIxsJ4Ivq2DQ7ltJ7ESkA+19WkIxCZ8NnlozsuXIjMNtvBzazpEpU3tRpUR6Cbf253myk6VsrcH05bJ50/CIz4RuULRR9lX6SWD5I1M0rzsIWgQFgaWZOmzb0ijrLlWuGaIqj6o74xeH+tLxk4KozMAGPMxzMXohcZrzVKXNg06XbOakcI41iBCf0K9Bu6DH8YISd3DFN2NwyJmPm8y/Zncu1NnCo85H2g8R5B7YUM5HG/MejpU7CIW6hEW+Wdc7mTwH+SDzs2wslpREmwGEY7XDRHIh48G0CmD6zRkl0nTTpeHnhlatQ/pecesyLfam756TzhBfkHX7TBmAC", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avn5MUmQBH/hdH2Jn+dKiJZhWqNVqJ5dX/3VauCSvjqwJJibhyIn15282LFq6D0t0QGm6Ab/YaaeTBDfYR92tWax+v5wHhPNIZAn5Nx9pMPaP1Pwi7tcsbULb5Cx32UamzZJQh2E4pYjvrnkgLxel0eYdM=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "To promote the spirit of common brotherhood among all people,Adding one more fundamental duty in 2002", 
		"option_b": "To respect the Constitution national flag and national anthem ,Reminding citizens of their duties along with rights", 
		"option_c": "To preserve the rich heritage of our composite culture,Preserving the rich heritage of composite culture", 
		"option_d": "To protect the sovereignty unity and integrity of the country,Protecting the unity and integrity of the country", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030147", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kRzr9I1gRhvgyL3oPH/YQ2sFsD+AXbFmdWLzW6nGZ+P5iZN0NF+bhEtv+3nI4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EYj0KFILsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8H1fWNP34kCikoBV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LwCXPPNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyYFs1cJfOAZycyiqnbTeYcc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbUn3lNkJlgbzentGrZ0o21eSX689K5zpQ2VP9AdpGFqYv38ByHIWOhYT3TJou0GUiwDzy4k04l91hliGFQqCKYSMk/tW1N3j7wCQQk0megLDzh1v4cqsLOP85xk7WsnXJQ2LQ439u3lF18B0T7zT8D8sTfDxwPjRSWXo1HhEluTPRBVNaRsi3W1TaQCzxNP462QejHg2wImqPdh3Jp8rlOFczObFmbyp5miFfxQb05FSet6Ma5fbxVSiRsuvIxiq3h94r7NbPkbCVqL1r3Ga8Zs9URKEI7UUudRWQPIPjuFt1eAaAPkjWK10cIBz8JRXbF6LxFdC3q6oSIUmT/I4EdHAqiSvNIU/rwSwf6O/imxnDICLvcnFOtH1AgXCiUNb8f/EewOsyyZFPz0ygkuYGlchEbBMNXfGezNCv59OOkDgg/bS0paJpVdVHcWBkrmi2DNfxrjLMFdFg5TuizEVVWox9GkDCSD1ZB8EUKTOW5RUE1I71KMkJRhRanBakcUBmK13dexxbcgmKsaboLcQljOyTTzwyg29Im37+pws7BSpSibf1bks1DaPYbBNqWXxtc2rOkr6GgUSx5Ri03briIHqKR8A+2Qoi04oOahRwLif5Idh97ZXnLyd+ZsHotb+UPLzAK/TNZ7IqSIkbqmcgZlRAoEBWstQGkASdh9lEzLtOrKp2catvlsBAfVmSHF/kD2Lw4nWykdZ+RJFp/RyN10UfQNpKKh3TDfey7gO1JRVjil9mLBcotrAg5jpzygwwA63s1zzyiSzaaIqetqF4UYjw4C/TfWh0dxldilXrxnhOofc/qx+ZJzvABmPVToUy34mE2zx7MDwqOIzOqnrbe9yaG/gdhieojHCbjGzMtjkxkBLBrsjkuAG1hCeE0/Pa1bPGE3iHvbtz4jcxNpRYUBueKb/37/ZW8ZeOFb+WsmcDDbzKhsdMpRLXvZZ5FYDaNJH1f5P60IsSELUnTfCvEkvvYUmvOZWAbrjku2iLOFFgsbSDzC4kdXnYS0MI2Y/lR5I6k8AolPCqAWvEomeFJ2xsZTBAZCryh2DENWLgiec7cMh8tvxZcSa9VKi33KQo2J5wGmyP0A2fvq2n8w/ouRJer1VQ5aEvah2TIOTWcqKs0amzlH4KFgtfZQkXi4LRgAREQtegS0kTNRjxRNiUk41aEzKEvGBnMLlBsfr5Sh5xVC5m39kVO1oFnRk1aKTmYXXr5W9iEF5VLStfik/hn69pej3ACR9FOOMzCB1aN0y7PWi4SPAICJgTe0FC2rd89xZ6OUVvPr23wxpSkXxOc/CMZ3pynWo5SnBNiKMyz3/fnEfd0ttGhQWQpT9QV/3QajGBWMjPWUhYtgbelaGmRIE/+oh9ti8biyNcxyK3ZknPlf2NjDbtQCZZrhZMYg8P3vf4SfI1+M2sCBDIA8XdeLcJZhKWPXwA6LfCbsCKrDpFpXyA6X1E3ggrkt+2Q6Zp7TSL/vfNLOynG1dv7peRhfQI5QlL4+b5e67d/nqObXijRMm8LqvwW7jDBMF68dEri6rHgwUPOkzb785lOnxEcnNRB1eKfXwADribfjscbuCH0QVpvmZOgAq+Y3gTYlIq4/YTi8aZYVb6wGurliFD2Dc1orvkxH2E0QbBVoZzQXHE/XsoZKS9dLJCdNeRWmIindCyAwYiyPXTkYS2TaltrS5xz/yaPvKlTUGoFS7yBzf5kGtkxAqv/Xw7LiUR1BBpmYsQKzEq5YpeIilTiE7vcoEOj5IdjiT1G9pYK5Kky6UCZdzyG5jYnmjGmQSB+FqcEtzT8Jvf2Faf1K8eady2daNgS9LI4cBeOllyix/Df/Jav2W2MC4pyA/w1VcR4tVobUN+taCyP4PW9VCks7ikwKqTBEEaKfXtRPRv9gdoLlfkdx96z3lqPYKTKeAyIQS7NNw2UXItG1hZ2HWfWHTx9fkB+EkaCsPMfd4KN8QoNCkTKoX42idfpw6xeHJdecDNZdmk9xNcwHYi2sR98zL86AhzYobuyXAug7G5COpCaUfC7fiLO2KREhCE9W4c16GRE8RdFUW4dT3hcRrvR+atLcO1iqYhbWAq2t8m2juiw7llCiHOh3ynbt/3ZAUfOWbOGOCjyGNgsGYp9H6xmhXEm9VWJ1hUApHCHXLqVH/ZRa8kvdaz+a5AemA/E+MjPPvLAo3GPzqZzZKdIrfiSXmbqv0EviABOiPJNj00WOh2kjTiltzxFdvOp4yOhBbRUszdjmntsTegs/dvuJymDkwjYdTTGbcPX400JPIZ3dCrzyPfPn/v3jtMX+2qgqrQB9cOmrbsqptztShyh3kZxaAppgiv+V5YxtTwMkzDfX1HRSbsRgR275luTFFXs/Lu9TXohAh6Dgd3nJHAzAw0tQAfo6JWN5ysRsObxOtk+hv344SOxYmp/2ueI8QuaJ6it1pO5aAJmMdbUwQMswcqYL0dzl+T0qhrxzCAtqmou7zbtiqyeHrilvEE7ofcu/2+JqhrUwHOEaWd7ZkUGvfN4ArSktIoUlm99TcEsFxCXZ7QEbcbcQfNJlEddAnJp8c3n2CZrsPXxpES05X+X3+qVcTXFARlYh59c6pnW15CqzgBonuFSVU1YT+JLb3T9RVujO+7Xqs1CAkLw/JUQ5P4biXxKdnuN10z08W1Fyx+uBHtNW2PTd1FzYxKYlSwDv31/o0K1C6xYm+46Vg8A9W2PIPydnybe5uJ6khsdPr05M6WQtU0UotWR5a4slL3A/cKI2MheeeHYb9/GJiRaxBtUrBAghnK7gkgqY4/5MoVNW7Lf4ruHuJ31b+G/28ZtRhKW9iJ4osI2ujXx8ia1xp0dNcLIL5TJYxMudCfEmFIQAsL3qNez/F+y1xgtz/rWBKWEQxgIj6/7hw+wz42nVjn9vUSxWy7BfQ7Wjg==", 
		"answer": "25T1Od2z81S4u8UDH02+hdmyYSlSamX2STV3ViBon6vXe/GJ", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avn5MUmQBH/hdH2Jn+dKiJZk36RRrA0f3ejQK/HLs7xx4RlLkicmVJ0/D+Gorf1+lIbjKBe7c6IeTYLPp9nzdmbl+f41mNEINZLlIR76p1fb+FCxjiuYJTWIep6y3zAJkv0JzivEHl3mDTFyn9Zvoap8CP7Usg4zVUen5RsoOEVflokQcje7z0/RMIUbXbtCJM=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A-4, B-2, C-1, D-3", 
		"option_b": "A-1, B-2, C-4, D-3", 
		"option_c": "A-3, B-1, C-4, D-2", 
		"option_d": "A-1, B-2, C-3, D-4", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030148", 
		"question": "24W5eoW++DCq+INgRhb3hdTxMWLRDSIyrHGQRqpgZWXqW6mCauj/xYQxMFWdhRtEzUn5nJrPyGwwsOqkDNr3bH5OJAY3QUdOCDVp", 
		"answer": "25axfJjp1Bf5/4wwEDiP41bOQDYhlweFzuCWOgw=", 
		"explanation": "24W5eoW++DCq9Io2Vwzhhf72IWLKBmwCq3aTEutVYmXqV6vHfa2riYN+Zw3YxBmwgjrh5Ey6YNjatGzETFH6", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "ci,ti,zen,sh,ip", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030149", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRD5t5EoV17xyu/tMGjEQ3EFomuGX6Z6ZDHlRqjPLvn2zNd3KFCFgkxy/HGZn6vM+XJBz5xT7M62fiYKf4Uv69+HxPD+0GRVOslK2ol855YKePFTjC2/e8LSM/dhwH3AIVf/anmpDHU0vSPfmXQWi4y15jOyQM8jyRo81pV96skuON6R3uiH4Ej4lhSN336VXa9hUVKWp46p5kaSpIs2so2ZuTeb1/v3ieza5Msfawdc8bpxX1We2eg98C94eMawYRNFscffb0f5KTy2MwcS94vq2Hdm1JImT2gg8QwGkpFfbMN6xpThr3I2LcJnVSeypgR19NRfUBmFYLSsxXzt71t/Z38nZJ5ouG0hrk+IIFE+m3uMQyVfgI1u8MRZmgIjbntBiHOghTCdhXeBc4HwpbzyuebT7vlX+qZnAE+EPF3WFq4Ta6DULnNn3uCUA+ZYIZ5wBGLvOdAv73n/MpmZny0F1ZkCPX7z/TmR0u76N3auuobsmt15Gv8DOd/G7Nm5uVLAITfpJD2Ac9jkXAbjRnP2kwFj9z4wxiUR5WfWHIhztR8EmXakWgRghzXpYnvhk7NZ+IWLcY041uai4TwsltA236//0V0VSQCyjHEDkYuRXEhG2UHCF8IJhAshHqYOA4WR5mWT1XXfRX8Ib9q2Dq7Hwmxb0+32gmQ9vJkaXJaLIgrTg85mzgW+DL1tXWKtiZPqKe4UBm0t9PJSxeOyo8OvYOetI2tkLbmiFttu9vqV2oLtgTmFGZk=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz8lvNZVVVGS0brA2j0aqjhLVI", 
		"explanation": "24KwYZ32kQ3i8sUJXBr7xPO/FmTeEHYYt2qXW6x6MHniR+fAYf/sxoB0IxyPiFpv52TDsOX25VwCz75a+4eQZTFDfYRh28SAw/HjzX5PIIZFmZJ994lfaPxFjCqiZtjfbL56xmvAN1f/cTCuDX961CPThn1CrYf74Sj7QNIygAYnhZd949s1M9nf1q7Tzli2ggeP2XWFSbEkI12evdq7q0eJsos2so2IvDfJ8/H3mfHW454CcUhWrYdobRu6hacEuD4wVIiWehtf+PfYIXfiLju3LhoI7cLs2Dop8oosHWYg/BpUwpBCY9R2253qqCFwPt9vVT21twRBxJdpTRaCcf2x3ijw6FB/dnUlcY91qG06p0+IIFE+iWSJXi9Uh8Bk+JANnQEjVGFElXfuwhyEjnabdYf2/4nzi6/j4Klx/bUuOkiPO0+WFHi/JyZ/LaSUJok3IWNqxjU=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only A", 
		"option_b": "Only B", 
		"option_c": "Only C", 
		"option_d": "Only D", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030150", 
		"question": "25SqepD91hyq440lEhj9yfHwImLeBCICt36XV65xfmXwFKXDfej6iZh/Z0iBiBty/HDJsajx41oAgehL+4GJeSYGestmxpCd3+G31HBSIMdDn9pO6qYRXboA+DWoNP3VJPdvwC6jKEvjczCpEWR9mz+Wg3JVpJa/8DT7UdYyzRA8gpQ469ozMZeL0a3T20KujwOWnFieRq5wGECMocen5QOIqIMs9ciAoTra5/3jn7jV5dAPYwVXsZJ+bxu4grwA/Tl4UMawKAZD9KTZZVHsLGisIU4X7Nj333dshosnHX088V92kIZXb8J/09bYsg4+HYMqITu/421Ow519UVe1e7OrxGHw9UE2enRrYZhsqz51rgHcPFx72kidQi1VnYFlvvMWmxd3dHtViH/vjH+Nj3fPf5zt6IXskfuwrLBo9+MmaVKUJ1PWUc0/YL3UNWIyw+fbDOZaNptiBSPqfcY37y38LdaV0T1N0d02JmTo5jPZmNjnMHa+upHth9t4VLAGdsXN7IuEpUzVZC7kYV6cc9ngFzT+c3LbnU5Rvx1l4S8U4WPWSKpw+z4Zl2qlXU1rnGfpYn+uhK5T+IOaep1x1fDtyScCnec4mYn42V0oTwH7unpKv4WND39Aw0fCF9kS0AAhAvQOEtb293+blHjJC24IeM/kBaGJxGxc0uaxnXRur5UARoWBIlnUjJ4A3Rm1APB8W3PspMbLNPsdHnds/qdjw+Om98+2cOGjKWspZh+kF9NXz5t1JkJPGQ6dLCpLabmgFr4RT/Nb22Hfgw5HST9LCkje9L8bHQK4pcmIemLbI5MOBwrrcLtFMMH2XVPGIeS9wT/HRrmThweuXlYpRzuQJL4Z5BXpOov9MhahnWVh99WpckJSSoQbOWfwfX+wv6aNGA4zb2BlKYRDOkTUSRkqkSqDNOB0maINMpJZlEEuDdngltWqLHxJNVM=", 
		"answer": "25a5ZpD32Bjkt6YvXA3mzOnqIWLfDS5RgW2KRqpneDHAW6nReuTq3IN4KFLFzWh05H/Dt+XT+F0cm6FP/JqWfyxPSY5mxdGbl8f4ymJVOtJRjol96toQerRnyS+gddrCYsGAfMoQ0xey3KM8Q0G2+UU=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eh/g1/zxMm7dBmwF43mMXq97Z2KjQK/HLuLszZJjZ1OPzVl04GTJtKD0t1YDiqVe55qMMCQRcYYv3NiMl8f2ynBFOsdK2qN96okLdeBV2DSiepibAuxn2meTLwXTaDeuEHlggSXfhXIa6LC04y6+QJoUzxshgo5s+Nw1M9nTmamd7A2Pgw+P3WnRa7JqAkCQodu84kyS4I0+9eqIoz/a+u212vnAsNMObBxbsIh6Zxu1megd8C94QcmnexNM9KaAHFJpgFGicM6SuUemwR0t", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "British Constitution", 
		"option_b": "Canadian Constitution", 
		"option_c": "Weimar Constitution of Germany", 
		"option_d": "Soviet Constitution", 
		"quiz_type": "order", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030151", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbk8sUvVF7mzfi/M2TcD20GqnGEErR1YzHtW7OCfv/x2ZhiIljJj0I75n7D4/Kj5VczgYtU552LeTYWaoJgxtGFl8X6wX9FPsNKjsB76toLdPEAzS+odZTUJr5ez2CDL0TpZi20REJ1nm6WsS0P8dSGt/xVKyP3FobgRJMZTh3vWuE=", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHD0Bfp/4Q5Uwr7hc/+PyvWFmwSt3aMXKJmeXTwFLDLYuG+y5IxI1WanE56/n/AqqD0y10bgOhT5oKbMDYLe4J9iN+P0e30wWIBOsAEjoh3/doXfeJFjDCiZtGbNPZvwC6UMEqwZDG0CHRmkT+UidEJ3lpBF5w5Ed49FlxGhQ==", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UnWwj3y73qO2/VESIes2uKXa00OHKqFK7RLuPx3dd8IlKdhFR193KGqquwy11Y3LpfqY+SdSwHc45h3JCI1PC35mRVc9JMk5My6pUNcbRJ332sZMTXKftqjmeOZ23xdSC8CnE41A3YuH1cqZCv/Sa1GJoa8FlyuYNx/sA9fNaR3eiy5kmwlAfC7GmQTLh3GRbifugr//av9FNBERNavDTS", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Thirty percent seats in all elected rural local bodies\nwill be reserved for women candidates at all level", 
		"option_b": "The States will constitute their Finance Commissions\nto allocate resources to Panchayati Raj institutions", 
		"option_c": "The Panchayati Raj functionaries will be disqualified\nto hold their offices if they have more than two children", 
		"option_d": "The elections will be held in six months time if\nPanchayati Raj bodies are superceded or dissolved by\nthe State government", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030152", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRom2GEq51ZGXmRrSCYeO+3p94JFTJjBt4/XjVt6zk4kcGgKZa5bKRcS8GcI9izd6dl+3khGFOINVNmIx3pJURcO0A2zS5fJTPKPsu3G+ULkP5ZDipDX961D7Qymherb+1+SK8Xck7wQEnhII44s58MtiLmaSW+174kg6D0jueRrgpGVWVs46n7QOIqId4ptmMpTfIq7TCy6GKpeM3bFkSmop6YE+1mKZJ9yx4RcCxKCJZ9PfZZVHjNBStdU4v/Nvx02dsyJYoSWA7+l9JhMNFdsFn04uktTxwK8VvVQO7sUhJxpl5UQOqeu74/GH39EZ/fHRrcYJo/HohqU+vK1x7nn6QSRBfwMBK/N8VnBBqcmEAk3CgljeOwEmKe5rw54HokPr14Jps560kIE3APFKYV80vcbLUIiWB/K/0alBg9uTPZ3HZdq7O", 
		"answer": "2+T0OtHy3x2qpMezq9JhX5iCirwwYJp+TCk9", 
		"explanation": "24W5ep360BTv+ZFgXx/rhf/mdWfRFCIBsXCVW6dxMHfsRufWZui+yJV+K1WdhFR1snnA47H48m8Bo61c4J2TcTYKaI4v69+c2ef+yDFONYZF2rNm5Y4aPPxB2jSjc5TINf1mjm/AJErlaTq0CDB7hnHQhW5qppez8Ge4Rt821Bw9mMd364gvKdSXmanT60KtiAWL0DuYRv1lUUeNtNqtq0udtos2so2DvnLI4ffx2sTd89EebAtbs8o/al38g6AMuAY9VsGnZBNf+PLVIXX+My2uJQIEucTllmBhw8I6SWgg8V9Wg5BFZ9Mz16TqrjcjMMF/ATq1rQRUyNRoVxaCNLi+1m3n9BU9bDoqJYdstiInqBuFaFt42n+USWxFm5Rq8pAUkAlheH1TlH/wwgOFj2PPaJvmq6Hvlu39orV6sqIpLQGCLBzZFoAdb7zSLnNriuadTahTJ99rEjH1fcEm/Te5NIGb4yxdgIlyO3/u5i6K0sLzeXGyttL0i9l0Ea0Tdt7Dqd+/tRzmcjDkLH+ff4vkSw3jSnLskw9rs1gzxzUZ5mWaxQQeAA0Fsb1bD6fIxdQSsA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1,2 and 3", 
		"option_b": "1,2 and 4", 
		"option_c": "1,3 and 4", 
		"option_d": "2,3 and 4", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030153", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YMzwiZZ8IlKNgF515jbSrOXk/1ZPrKdV+pqWZDcXd4RhiN+Pl835wHhAc8VFlMBw4doWcv1UxTy5cdCbHPBs1y6UL0CqJwLsXSktqQ3Y2zx6p4j7xia5XNt3klUAl41h7IgPPdWX2JSduw2LkgeW2Tu9TbptAliYodu67gPI4LIqsN6EtTfV4Mj3rfDa89ZLbQ4Sq456I1q+mL4MuDksUNyxZRdF5feQaEeiITqmZw0S69nm1WA2hL5s4kDvpmDXmT6MEoZGB1k=", 
		"answer": "2+T4aZ/3kUuocWEOEhwNBe0zN4qxEabNUg==", 
		"explanation": "25S2KJD+1Bfu+oAuRl7myr3rPW6QIG0fsGuKRrZgeX7tFKjELsTwzZ5wZ1+Igxt590rIqqv541oOm61fqYyGMCcKaoNq2pCh2PHkwTFONYZ0m5J+7ZsSefpUjCijcNHJYP982meDK0CwNG/lRFlgqD/ShXlF6I204WepUcsiyQc31pNw6IgMLtKM0KyW5lnBlUaQ2XieRbBhH1CYocen5QHYLnDz6nIv6slNlnwgNWv2", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only 1", 
		"option_b": "1,2 and 3", 
		"option_c": "2,3 and 4", 
		"option_d": "1 and 2", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030154", 
		"question": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rwr7yvO/Om2QKmwVqn7DQKZ3f3btXbTHfbe+8sYofgW0z60A/nTb30zHP2dEGTXYHp0=", 
		"answer": "26e9ZJj02Bb/5MUhXBqyyfTxMn7ZEHYYoD+OW617Ynj3XaLRLJRVy3/ke6SNPio77fvbp5I=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rwr7yvO/Om2QKmwVqn7DQKZ3f3btXb3Hfa3szJt4IFWGmEg783jC45n++1oBiL1S+pqWc2IOd4Vg2tmd3uHkhGRPN8NW2oFg8JMccPEAnmTtddrfYK0+jiajMknkciu8CDB1mjXqhFlSvYC64S60Wts7gAc7kY9s/oF8FNiI3L6W+g2xkkaG036CCLNrBRSdsMih5UbctIo99dmIoz+b2f33lera5MdJhR1mczv9FFM45zNeJY7uFg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "only religious minorities", 
		"option_b": "only linguistic minorities", 
		"option_c": "religious and linguistic minorities", 
		"option_d": "religious, linguistic and ethnic minorities", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030155", 
		"question": "24GwbdGkggvut6YvXA3mzOnqIWLfDSIwrnqNVq5xfmWjdaTWIq2vkM4jZ06Mi15p4TbSrOWwtxNPtPoLud6iMkBxbg742fjVXE1wGyrBDlc=", 
		"answer": "27m5cZj91ln+/4BgVBHny/n+IWLfDSIXrG3DQbdmf3/kFKbMaq3owJVjJlKdzWt6/HXOorzx41pPvalRqYeRYzYKap57wd+HxKT+yjFVO8MEmY9n6o4NZbZuFNWKdZCRN0FksdB5sj08", 
		"explanation": "2+LrepWz8BTv+YEtVxDmhdz8ISvRB2YUpz+mXqZidX/3XOfxbeX7zYJ9Ihydghtv+nP6rYb/+UAbhrxO/YeQfmICcI8v+NGbw6Te/D0BJM5NmYgy9IgQav1EyS7tctvJYOpmyy6wJkvzbzikBWR9qD/ki3YWm5qo4SK2FgnNLiwDiEnP8UTXN9KtAbU=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "generation of gainful employment for the unemployed and the underemployed", 
		"option_b": "generation of employment for able-bodied adults during lean agricultural season", 
		"option_c": "laying the foundation for strong and vibrant Panchayati Raj institutions in the country", 
		"option_d": "guarantee of right to life, liberty, and security of person", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030156", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbk8sUvVF7mzfi/M2TcD20GqnGEEqJ5dX/nWaLMev6+3ZgxM1SMzXJ19n/HreXT+F0cm6FP/JqWfyxDe4Z/x8eMxfe30HlEc/ZWn5N74J8RaLRUw32+cdrfYPxvzWXAJkvpJzS8EGRxhnHQhW4Wuoa4+imoXd4y0hQmn4h2rcolfMOX3Oiw51i2hQ+OnHSXCJBtH12Kocu6+Bzcm9Bo5Z+w82zgZo0ePZPlHm7XiMkVXrM=", 
		"answer": "2+HsfJmxURvXctCqlA1gst+s1Ljj1Q==", 
		"explanation": "2+HsfJmz8xzs+JclEgr6wL2rZ2XUQ2McpnGHX6Z6ZD2jdbXWZ+7yzNcmcxTJ3BI74WLHt6D0y10bh6lPpc6jMjYLe5lqiMOB1uj7hHNEc8cEuY9n6pkWcLRPyn2AfdrSM+pr3H3AMEzkb3mpDHU0pCPfh3lqpq6y+y6oQN8lgBQm1pNw6Ig0OdabmbycqEyxgkaD0n/RSblyGEec9dqg7gOssocrvMmIvyab/fq5jvDWzNAOeg1AvI9sZhuzkegB8Tl4V926awZC/urDXRatCCe0IhgY64ejwnxs1IdpSmgntB4GkY9fZchn6pblsTA5ONhjASr6tExF05x5TVeCfLj40Wzy6VY6NXUtJZ5luW0WrhqSK11y2mSaDAFYmol46tULhkRqblNOnn/uhjaFhyWActP344W8tfr1s7Bn960zaWePJ0jBG54ZZrzOIydTx+yVCatZPYsnGCSmKd0rvG2rLpLU/DYDw80pO2Lz/SWXk8G1GGi/vZb0i9piVPdRb4aToIu6sVjCISr1YXiLdsf9WgHkD2jw0hpZuQwtzWEg+mfLAY16+zlNjXaxRUgo0huibX+11rdSqoONfIEj1/Ti3jdQj/1sl9vkwR40BwW/m3ZAt7jdD2BB+VzTXswKwQcqAbEPANbG92OC1X/eX3NNesjwBKuTgypa1e6x3SFXvp4bVJ6XYFmK04lxiCO5BMF3ATP5oMbYMPkbDmkp9KYxgrz44JLyNfurO2A8agj3WOtd9pERfAp6BUvJDSEPUKqrRZQaRO5b7nvJlgkIVHpHARrY861IXAC8o8fNLmjfYLpcCBHwI6EAEMH2XU7LMOOo3DnGCP+Tm0S7H2YwWnqUJ4wD8Q/1Oq/9MR2wmmQk9selH1hVTZADOTXgNHi8q6eQSxIyemw2KYdCOkbRXRknkX7CIPhug+cUf1g5Sa2bF2AEkwJGmzvcGhhRuEkQH7GlRRMXOKxWKV8UwyP1HLUMSFzLhTkPnkLcyzasHfJOcUgufmqXgknuj65oiPrnls6IBMDtbbgd1IgAPPZdVpXbXwlM2tnx4eSsUT1gUTQ1bNc3gnCzOsT5AoR8fvcDeA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "39th", 
		"option_b": "40th", 
		"option_c": "42nd", 
		"option_d": "44th", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030157", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRgHCNQbd9ZGT3XajMb+G+6Jp0KViEiFVv4TbHsaCw5VYDjrxe7c6Lf2IRf4J8wd6Ol/D/wTFPJstGn5Iy65xfUfFNzji/Z5TUJr5CwWXAFETybzj9EH80ljSWj3BTq5e+8We9RtU6gAE6k8dL+ckoOcTAmZPBuB3ru0R1D1j2PGyxW/gOiikMzPNN", 
		"answer": "2+KsYNHy3x2qpNQzRlyODtXKkH9UipobVBMr7klU", 
		"explanation": "2+KsYNHS3Bzk84glXAqy5P7rdTqJVjRRs22MRKpwdWKjUqjQLu7xxId+NFWdhFR1snnAn6vk/1ZPp6dO+ovffyRDaoNqiOCM2PT7wTFAPcIEiIU/5Z4VaedUwTijYJTaJupr3C6FMUDifnmBCnNxmiLDmTwF+ZCvtSa2UdQzzRA8gsd57tx8bY7IiuiD+kKujwKHzzuXR68kA1WQpsem7AOIqIcEu9idoTfJtPjwl/HHsNgEcEhGt4M/cV6sha0a/SQsUNy9ZxwL/uKQckDsNC2wZwcTud/r0zRFyYlpbmg2/B56jIVEbc0zg8i0/CY/f5g4QHO7rUAA1ZF4ShSferr4xGDhoEAvZX85JYZksSQh4QmTOhRqkm6gQj5UhJJu7dUXgQV3dGBO3Hnmwgq/kyWJbpzuq9Kpxfz/4OszsOnz9kJf0F2LX/qKPsX5ihE=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "6th and 22nd", 
		"option_b": "13th and 38th", 
		"option_c": "7th and 31st", 
		"option_d": "11th and 42nd", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030158", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kTXj5JFge1665O/rPGjcBnFRrHnDRqtxMFLsWrTWZ/nr3Z5+KRyGixtS/HLPouyw4Fobh+h34J2LTCwqV8sn+MKGwe3kzX5PeoZFlIQy958TefdUjCmlcZTYL+x8y22UZ0T+dC64FjBhhzjYjTxCoIb79ii/UckLzhI7gIJ2rco5MNiImbyb7Q20jxWWzyHRCIY2QQTNiPKmx0qPtM8R9YWsoybS9/j8ibjc9p4fag0SnIlxcE+1g70d8SU2EceyKDtF9e3RKBT6KTyrZ04x8Nj3m11AhsoZT2Yi/QxPjY0fIHNFNxnAB9TnajhlRu/zgaY=", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqptFgH17Gzfi/Bn/RF2dRsHeCXq80fn73FKPHYPS+3ZgxJlKQzUt+4GXJreX15kYOg6FP8M6ddSQMbI4v3NiMl+j20zFOIYZQkoUy4YsKffgA3C+iYNHYNPdhwC6PIQX8Zi6uRGd9gDnfhDxCoIb74SKpRtMjzwcr1oh+reEyON6eleiy+lmxhQqHnCrECPAkJVyc9f286leZ4JEwtMGB8TzU4LT9k+vQ4tcGawZTq4M/Yly9nqYa7Go5X9H0axtf+P7VbxTiLmikNQEI98/wlntnyptpUm905hpKi4Rfbc4/lorlvzd8f85rBie/7wRTwowwHweadb69kGfioFc2Z24jJYV//Cw7uE+TLhRqkm6RAGxwhpRi/dwc1VU1PSIAqH7lkDrLk22OcJ+j6YW8gPnlobVq5rpnJkfAOkzIWZ8IcL3JM34yzOaJTadQP99kHjbvJ9Ag73nwLtaZ3i0Z1cszb2Xi+CuNm8PyeXG185f0nth5DbIFOMWF5tn3sUzXbirvNXCWaN+0TQewTnLhkwFjsREmzWEF5mbdGslr/ShNrWqxXUEo0gbyeHWimrscu9XOMs525vv40icTkPV6lpf+wAR7Bw2ozX5BvYiWXFRKyRTXEMlHzR09TKQTFZXF+26T1X/eC30DZo7wDrqKgyVbmuX+nGN0u5QLW8LMPvsVAOQVUd1fAQuL7hsfTw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbYL2kRj48sUGRxD2xPD6O3/RDyIjqniLRrA0ZX/nUbWCXuzs3ddYDnXJgl075n7Dn6vT+F0cm6FP/JqWfywOMst93d6al+Lly3wBEtRQ2tEmqclNPmYjS8Nv4ir3sEG9a4H2K2s=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Article 15,The State shall not discriminate against any citizen on grounds only of religion, race, caste, sex, place of birth or any of them", 
		"option_b": "Article 14,The State shall not deny to any person equality before the law or the equal protection of laws within the territory of India", 
		"option_c": "Article 16,There shall be equality of opportunity for all citizens in matters relating to employment or appointment to any office under the State", 
		"option_d": "Article 17,'Untouchability' is abolished and its practice in any form is forbidden", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030159", 
		"question": "24C2bJThkQ3i8sUDXRDh0fTrIH/ZDGxRrHnDe61weXCvFLDKZ+72iZh/IhyGixtv+nOGpar8+1wYhqZcqYeMMCwMastuiNac2eD2yXRPJ8dI2oRn8INAPM8SnGz8NJmKHbw3OZ2nMIHWM5Yfm9OcLQJf", 
		"answer": "24G3KIf8xRyq/otgQgvwyfT8dW7cBmEFqnCNQeEBjqpB0ZWjjvLYM26zbYYT", 
		"explanation": "24G3KIf8xRyq/otgQgvwyfT8dW7cBmEFqnCNQeN9YzHtW7OCb6343Jl1JlGMg096/jbCtrHptTUXO9rhEdH4+YdtLjjFra0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "To vote in public elections", 
		"option_b": "To develop the scientific temper", 
		"option_c": "To safeguard public property", 
		"option_d": "To abide by the Constitution and respect its ideals", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "030160", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CUuOvibZ/Z12EiFV//3PIt+Xk+BMbh60byoGRYzYKap57wd+Hl+vxhFhPN89F2oNz6todechOxTOkYN3aNPtqjmyZZ0T+JzCzEGJ7kCTVnnVZpsO082e6FNg+zBlyn4k4+cA5fPuQ0uig6U+wh0aN0neIdLM2UX2f9d296EvcoYx4tMCIvzbW8frt2uvW9dUYIhxd/4t+aF78lKAI9i09Qoi9ZlJf+eHsb1LoJC2xJgJd+sPixHVq0oc7HWYytAtOh8N1bc5gwpHwqSY5MMMmVSeypgRBypFyWxqTeqmE3mno81p/Z386cIN/uT51tQDcKlE+iGqIRSpYkYQr/MlZgQxmPWNFm3/zjj6flXeKPJzlq4HwiajkqLxf/JAzKFWFJhzXUM01a7fJJlt8/eGSDq4cPJknAyrjfcY6/S38LZOayypN19A2Knmn9SiWhMi1MHb1soD8ztd5Bq0FNcWaqYuM4gyWMmOscEDRJsL+rtRlPggKSHqnYQdkbw==", 
		"answer": "25u9YYX71AuqpsUuXQyyl79ela3U42WySHAW2K8+xELv", 
		"explanation": "25S2KJD+1Bfu+oAuRl7myr3rPW6QAG0fsGuKRrZgeX7tFKjELsTwzZ5wZ1+Igxt59zbPrazk/lIbiqwb1YCdaWICcMtmxsSb2ODix2VIPMgElYYy5doddfhMjDSjNNHSNPZr3C6IKFDjYnmyAjBgnDSWmn1EpIq6+CK1QJoLzjw01pRt7sB8Pdnf2KWW5km1gwiWnGiUTbZ3UUCW9cOp4Ebco4o5u8qIonLS+rTtkv2T9tsPZxpTs7pxYFO9hakK7C8qEceyKAZD9KTTblr+NCG3MhoU9sWvlmBhw8IoUGw68BJDjJcWY8xg2dj2uSMlNt9vBg+0t0sAxZE8TRaCfbux1Wyk4kx/YXIuJYZouyQmrQ6IPUZ72mSaDC1F1Ixu/8MN1QxicWkAk3CgljeOwHabfYfm+MIqXv0Fd5g9BvS/UERqYk/l", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Salient Features of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 only", 
		"option_b": "2 only", 
		"option_c": "Both 1 and 2", 
		"option_d": "Neither 1 nor 2", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040101", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut6sBEi7zyfb3PH3RD2NRsXqFV7E0ZH6jQK/HLt3szJZ8JVCMzVporTR6VpBPomcVi3/cwleJNTTn", 
		"answer": "25y8bZ/n2A3zt4YhQBqyyvu/IWPVQ0EerWyXW7dhZHjsWuW37eXHi9xMb0eoHIyD7WrQ", 
		"explanation": "25uZKKHy3RLi/pMhXh+yxvzzOW7UQ3YZpj+zQKZ1fXPvUefWZui+jp51IlKdhE9isnXHsaGw+FVPm6Beqa2QfjEXd5963NmG2aO1jmGMkS7NNjEq60+yfhEVDA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Identity card of the Constitution", 
		"option_b": "Essence of the Constitution", 
		"option_c": "Introduction of the Constitution", 
		"option_d": "Overview of the Constitution", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040102", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTrl+ZY0Wwrn0fTwO2rcQ0McpnGHX6Z6ZDHiUKPHaq3qwZIxMFObiUg7zjT1rKb59l8GnLwX1czfTGAwe4h6xNGbm9i1hHBPN4Z42Kl88J8Ybv1U1QHvNMDUYOpmyy6wNUDxajuxAS82sajvlBIqpo9VYhf494Fz0w==", 
		"answer": "2+HqZpWz8hbk5JEpRgvmzPLxNGeQIm8UrXuOV61gMg0zc5Sulkz4UKE0j4kioUI=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHk3gvu5MUcEC39xvT+OWLDFy4t4T+/EJBxc2TvVbWOUq++yJl1Z2DLpFVv93HUqrHpyxFPmK1J7M6edCYGest7x5Cd3+G39GNEMstGloUy65xfaPxFjBSjcN3aLr5NwWCTM0zkci20C340liiWnnRT6Nfp+yP7ddcyzhE/k4lsrek/KJeQ3+jCsRruxjKK1WjRSbBhH1CUsMC8q1Sds8I59d6EtjzS8v36m/bHsM0fZxgSq4d0ZlX8k70b8SQ/Edy8bVJb9PbZblCtLy7jAgMY68zm2HdwhosnHUA68BZHwssHO5cmm8m962V5c41rGzf6qlAAxp1xWhPWYLL4wm3i7FA8YTooYJh5vSQ74QSZMRRom2eJST8RlY5vvsALnApgdH9MmWWgljeKlCWIaZrn7sDoje2wibdn+6IpaVKUNEjdFJF8BRpPVBPVh3NSycglAzU=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "42nd Constitutional Amendment", 
		"option_b": "40th Constitutional Amendment", 
		"option_c": "45th Constitutional Amendment", 
		"option_d": "41st Constitutional Amendment", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040103", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5EoV170yujtdWjfDnIerXqNRrA0YnT1UabOa+m+y44xM1SMzWtp93fLoan1qBE+5OdM6/YgaYsFf+ZFsaa8", 
		"answer": "24a3fYPw1Fnl8cUhRwr6yu/2IXKcQ0wQt2qRV+N7djHKWqPLb+O++oNwM1nFzXR5+HPFt6zm8kBPgK4b/YaaMAEMcJh7wcScw+34yj0BF8dQn8B94toeePtQ2DSiepajvpJaBe0g7VLx8e2PtJl5", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHDwxzr+ocsV17gwOv6NGfDQ2Qetm3DUax5YH7tUanWfbe++phkNV+MzVR9snfTt63/5VobluQbx4+LZTAGPoRpiPmH0+32yjFyJ8dQn8wyy5gVefdUxSuoZ5TUJr56xmvABEr+dC20EGVgnT7YxjxyqZe+tSi9FNszzwUmn4h2r+T92iqmgBQk5vX8U1/Xudc=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Purpose of the Constitution, Objectives of the State, Fundamental Rights, Basic structure", 
		"option_b": "Source of authority, Nature of Indian State, Date of adoption, Key words", 
		"option_c": "Source of authority, Nature of Indian State, Objectives of the Constitution, Date of adoption", 
		"option_d": "History of the Constitution, Political structure, Economic policies, Legal framework", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040104", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2hDk88UvVF7hyv72NGfZEG9Rp3CGQeNgeHSjfanGZ+zwibR+KU+dhE9u5n/JreX1+lEdjqtetsxQo2qfgSrpG5RSOBjzz6Zs", 
		"answer": "25G9ZZ7wwxj+/oZgQRHxzPzzPHjdQUXQPqjtbEo4hk9VY+auQB4=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgUAzzy/m/Om2QEG0Sqn6PW7B5MHjwFKaCKen7xJhyNV2dhFg74XnFqqT8/kACw+8b/oaWcypDd5gvyZCL2+H5wDFONYZpm5Jq7YkSPPVOyH2KddrfKPd9wyz3YXXxZaoUQIUGI4vkBtzV", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Communist socialism", 
		"option_b": "State socialism", 
		"option_c": "Democratic socialism", 
		"option_d": "Capitalist socialism", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040105", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhj90PP7NH/ZDGxRrHnDU+NwdXzsV7XDeuT9iYd+K1WdlAQ5ymkYQWND9Uua3z3ct9nbbQ==", 
		"answer": "24W3eIT/0Auq5Io2Vwz3zPrxIXKSLtpBwfpEbh7aqvj4a1AxOA==", 
		"explanation": "25T4bJT+3hr49pEpUV7iyvH2IXKQCnFRoX6QV6c0f3+jQK/HLunxyoNjLlKMzVR9smbJs7D89kFPnKdN7JyaeSUNapIjiMeB0vbyhGJUI9RBl4Uy9JUIeeYA3ji+YMebN/d6xi6UL0CwdzyyFHxx1qiY3GpRGu7v2JNNfxIBX1Q=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Dictatorship", 
		"option_b": "Monarchy", 
		"option_c": "Oligarchy", 
		"option_d": "Popular sovereignty", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040106", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxQD68sUvVF72wPDwNnnRAHtRp3CGQeNdfnXqVefSfOz93Z5yIhDJmlN+4HOGpqn19EcKi+hJ7J6NdTEGcJ9u3Nmf0ve3x3BTId8ElZVmpJ0QavFSwjCoesCbJutgzXqJKEvjOHuA86nBv8/2YZRAc6qaPfta", 
		"answer": "25y2bJjh1Br+t4ElXxHx1/z8LCkz8AG79q3yIGMvlrca5jsk", 
		"explanation": "25y2bJjykQn49oY0Wx331r3tMHvCBnEUrWuCRqpidTHzVbXOZ+zzzJllJk6QzV9+/3nFsaTz7h9Pjuhd5pySMC0FPoJhzNmb0ufjhHVEPslHiIFx/diPdZiuFglTF1odTFUn3veX", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Direct democracy", 
		"option_b": "Indirect democracy", 
		"option_c": "Semi-democracy", 
		"option_d": "Participatory democracy", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040107", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5EoV17/xPP2M27DF2MFqnCNQeN7djH3XKKCaujzxpRjJkiAjht4+nfUoqbk8kFPgK4b/YaaMAsNeoJuxpCZ2Oj+0GgecdHJ1Dg8mgpLwiXktcGklG4=", 
		"answer": "24C2YYf2wwrr+8UhVgv+0b35J2reAGoYsHrPErNxYnjsUK7BLujyzJRlLlOHnhc74GPKpuX/8RMDjr8ZYVX1SEuUasG5ci0OnPIc1Q==", 
		"explanation": "25i5Zpj11Ar+9pEpXRDhhfL5dW/VDm0SsX6XW6A0c3niRqbBeujsiZ5/JFCciV4753jPtaDi5FIDz6lf/IKLMCQRf4VswNma0qi31HRTOslAk4My4ZYaf+BJwzO+OJTaLvou2maFZ1flazz9C3Y0mDDByFe/qNf8RVqMtvhrLlteljU=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Totalitarianism, censorship, absolute monarchy", 
		"option_b": "Caste-based politics, monarchy, single-party system", 
		"option_c": "Universal adult franchise, periodic elections, rule of law", 
		"option_d": "Oligarchy, aristocracy, dictatorship", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040108", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQAmsc43CFEqdxfX7gRqbWZ+6+2phyLl2FhEh2snPLobfx9FYLz6pCqZqXdWIqcI9myd7J9Ov512VIJ9NQk498u9g2sieyERhc00EJbMCNf5HV", 
		"answer": "25C2bJj91ln6+JMlQArrhfzxMSvZDWcAtn6PW7dtMmnOCcLrwfdFR5hvVcjnXqI=", 
		"explanation": "25G9ZZ7wwxj+/oZgQRHxzPzzPHjdQ2MYrmzDRqw0dX/nFLfNeOjs3Y49Z1WOg1Rp83jFpumw81ociqlI7MLfcSwHPoJhzcGc1uj+0GgBPMAElZBi64gLafpJ2CTvkBbsVS0cdK+uh2ttLMVsKw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Abolition of private property", 
		"option_b": "Nationalization of industries", 
		"option_c": "Ending poverty and inequality", 
		"option_d": "Promoting capitalism", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040109", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3v5YhgWxPiyfT6JivEC2MF41aNVqp1MHjwFKbMLuTwzZJhIlKNiFVvsnjHt6z/+RMYhrxTqYCQMCQMbI5mz97J1Ov50GNOP5kGsmC6HAiXlskKYuK8+ybgkA==", 
		"answer": "24a3fpTh1BDt+ceI1r13P7p5nUrxWMRc74j4", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt8IzXQj31/j2MmWXQ2scs3OKV7A0ZHniQOfrYOn3yNd4NByIgxty/HLDs6D+81YBm+hV6JqWfyxDaYJ7wJCH2KTxy2NEOsFK2oN96o4Nc/gCpcDOlLFpKzRNJVTzXJi+bw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Secular", 
		"option_b": "Sovereign", 
		"option_c": "Socialist", 
		"option_d": "Democratic", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040110", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2hDk88UvVF7hyv72NGfZEG9Rp3CGQeNgeHSjfanGZ+zwibR+KU+dhE9u5n/JreX1+kMHjrtS84vTMDULd4hniNmH1OjiwHRSc8RLjogy9I8dcP1DjDyjcJTLMvd4z3qFZ1b1ZC2yFmMr1rDvILufqyQzlfofKkBv/a8=", 
		"answer": "25G9ZZ7wwxj+/oZgQRHxzPzzPHjdQUXQPqjtbEo4hk9VY+auQB4=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgUAzzy/m/Om2QEG0Sqn6PW7B5MHjwFKPHY+L925ZlLl/JnlR4+3fKqrb9uxMYh6FY4c6WfjQMcp1q25CL2PD/hGFUMcpNmcBz6p5fbOZJ2jy5cZTIJf16wXyTZ0b/KjylDWNgnT/RyP9LZum54gBOURB0paWl3cI=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "State socialism", 
		"option_b": "Capitalist socialism", 
		"option_c": "Communist socialism", 
		"option_d": "Democratic socialism", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040111", 
		"question": "24GwbdHDwxzr+ocsV1nhhf7wOGbZF28UrWvDRqw0TDPnXbTWfOT83IN4MVnJh05o5n/Fppmyt1ocz6lVqYuSci0Hd4ZqxsTJ2OK303lIMM4EnI9g6doQerRK2S65fdfeYOpmz3rANED1bCr9EH80hjTVnnVQscO8+SapXdQwgBw8k5Zt7MQ1KN6ayuia5g2vgweOyHPdCK12HkScp9qxpwOdroZ4sM6Cvz3W/fe5nPnQ5NEZcUQSrYN5b16/g6EH/2osWc30YRxN/fHVb1foYCelZxkV8Mjrlnxg1ZYmT2A39RMGh5VTbNQslHsARRESmEaEXmlNYvFOAKo=", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHBxAr5/oQuEiz30/LzIH/ZDGxTnFUPvALcTy9JgZq19oWorQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt7liVhfh0e/2N37ECnQU43WWQbd9c3TfFufDfa3zzJllLlOHiF87+3iGt631t2MdiqlW64KaMDAGeI5925Cd2KTjzHQBOsJBm8B94toacudV3jSjc5TaYPhvx3zAI0zjcyu0BmVgnT7YynNQ6JG+5iiuRtky01UzmIM44tgsM8WLzKaa/ES9lUaV1W+ZQbMkEBSKus2h7leF4Kss9cyEvCGb4Pu5m/zX4tsYcUhGt4M/cE+9haNJ8SQ9QN21ZBtf+OHDIV3jYD+mJgIJ8Yej33pqyY8sESk1+hsGkpFZcsVhwoGo/CY4Ot9vFyr6oFZFxoB1URDWdf2133rhoFAuYHM/ZIhhuW0wogCSJ1l3mSuZQjpYho9l89UXgUZM1B8P1G2WJP8g03+3/VSX", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "The Enlightenment Movement", 
		"option_b": "The Renaissance Period", 
		"option_c": "The Magna Carta", 
		"option_d": "The Russian Revolution", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040112", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MU0Whuy0fjtOCvsQWQDomuGQK19ZGjfFufLYK3qwZIxF06MjFZ5/nOGrKOw41sKz4FV7YeefmIgcYV83NmdwvD+y38BIM9DlIl0/dZfffpEjDWiY5TfL/t9jmeUZ0b/aS2vDXJhgDSWnnMWvIu+tTK1Xc4ugBQ8ksdx49w5O8WWzbHT50v4kg6HnHWQXLRrHwvb6ZSTVt3y1lpUDpR6rhsOzA==", 
		"answer": "25T4e5T9whyq+INgUAz90fX6J2PfDGZTG05xU2xRChixQhJxyOoGTA==", 
		"explanation": "25OqaYX2wxfj45xgXxvzy+6/NCvDBmwCpj+MVON2Yn73XKLQZuLxzddYMxyZn1R2/WLDsOXk/1ZPia1e5YeRd2IMeMt6xtmdzqT2yX5PNIZFlowy55MLde5Fwi7tYMbaLu1ty2CELkv3Jz20EnVmhzjCg3lF6KqvtSS0Ws4lyRcngoJrrdwzfMOX3OiG5kSsn0aD0n/RQbNwFFOLvNqxq0ya4JYwsI2DsCbS+/q5mOGT9tEYdg1Atoh4I1r8hK0H6y94Xs70ax1G/OveIUT4MjisNAtd+MXnlnZsyo0nWmA6819Hj4xYZYB62Jztqjs0KsxmBnHDUIEYzGW5QuM0VKMgJTeO", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "A sense of brotherhood", 
		"option_b": "A system of single citizenship", 
		"option_c": "Protection of fundamental rights", 
		"option_d": "Economic equality", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040113", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhDz0ejtMCvfBSIFq3rDe61weXDtFJTWb/n7iZZiZ1iMjld64HPC46z+t0cHiuhr+4uefSAPe9QtFpeDIB3BTr+Fu3i00h6Plw==", 
		"answer": "24a9a4T/0Auo3JHNMAZi+JT98R+jmQ7PhQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHDwxzr+ocsV172wP7zNHnVECI4rXuKU+NgfzHhUefNaK3/iYR+MVmbiFJ8/DqGsKrz/lIDhrtPpc6MdSEWcop9iNSM2uv01nBVOsUI2oF84NoNeeRVzjGkd9XVYO5hwmeUPgeNUVztEQxHi26C+jibGy4Y", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Monarchy", 
		"option_b": "Secular", 
		"option_c": "Oligarchy", 
		"option_d": "Socialist", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040114", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MU0Whuy0fjtOCvsQVEetXqRV6pzfk2hFK7PfuHniZZzKEmdzXJ19n/H5Law5VYDjrxS5oCMeCsTPpxm3NjJ2PD/wWMBPcdQk49898VdTwc8w13qCXSzkCEEgRfC/Q==", 
		"answer": "25y2bJjykRD5t4QuEhf8wfjvMGXUBmwF42yXU7dxMGbqQK+CYOK+z5hjIlWOgxt4/XjSsar8tbhJycOA5Tp8GZnxubK+SZw=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt8IzXQj31/j2MmWXQ2scs3OKV7A0ZHniQOfrYOn3yNd4NByIgxty/HLDs6D+81YBm+hI/Y+LdWIUd59niN6Gl+L41nRINMgEmY988IgQcLZupcI9j5k2kKHQIYwQZAA+", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "India is a dominion of other nations", 
		"option_b": "India is an independent state with no foreign control", 
		"option_c": "India is a dependent nation", 
		"option_d": "India is a colony of other nations", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040115", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxQD68sUvVF7hyv72NGfZEG9Rp3aHEop6dHjiE7SCS+7xx5h8Ll/JvVR3+3Xf46r2twJW1vkb6IeSMDYMPpt9x92Gw+GohvCNSscLOyGYbAnF0AcxjXY=", 
		"answer": "25a5eJjn0BXj5JFgQRHxzPzzPHjdQeiVDdnA6HWdwYZtXyDzP4o=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHW0hbk+IgpUV7CyvH2NnKQDGRR8ibaA+N5f2fmUOfDeezniZFjKFHJnlR4+3fKqrbkt0MAg6FY4IuMMDYMaYp9zJCK1vT+0HBNOtVQ2pBg7ZQcdeRMyS7vXL64KwhAcrdQdmoO6D2V6w==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Communist socialism", 
		"option_b": "Capitalist socialism", 
		"option_c": "State socialism", 
		"option_d": "Democratic socialism", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040116", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxQD68sUvVF72wPDwNnnRAHtRp3CGQeNdfnXqVefSfOz93Z5yIhDJmlN+4HOGpqn19EcKi+hJ7J6NdTEGcJ9u3Nmf0ve3x3BTId8ElZVmpJ0QavFSwjCoesCbJutgzXqJKEvjOHuA86nBv8/2YZRAc6qaPfta", 
		"answer": "25y2bJjh1Br+t4ElXxHx1/z8LCkz8AG79q3yIGMvlrca5jsk", 
		"explanation": "25y2bJjykQn49oY0Wx331r3tMHvCBnEUrWuCRqpidTHzVbXOZ+zzzJllJk6QzV9+/3nFsaTz7h9Pjuhd5pySMC0FPoJhzNmb0ufjhHVEPslHiIFx/diPdZiuFglTF1odTFUn3veX", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Direct democracy", 
		"option_b": "Indirect democracy", 
		"option_c": "Semi-democracy", 
		"option_d": "Participatory democracy", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040117", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gZhb3hc3tMGrdAW4U43CFErd8dTHKWqPLb+O+6ph/NEiAmU5v+3nI46zjt1IBz6FV/YuYYiMPPptu2sTJ2OK30HlEc+VLlJNm7Y4KaP1Pwn2ReujVEvtv3WGOfQXZc3myEWR4nT/TmTxCoIb79yaoXdl30B07mohr4tg0JZee16zT7li2ggeP2XWFSbEkB1WVoMu7q0ya4JYwsI2uvjzI4P3tj+za/9BJdtslxfyAYwEDbvXEkIX9iA==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Ar58pc0WxH8hfzxMSviBmMCrHHDU7FxMHLsRrXHbfm+yJl1Z06MgVpv93KEf2txpolthYGm19vLfiNzhQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHDwxzr+ocsV1771r38OmXDCmYUsXqHEqJ6MHjtQKLFfOzyiYdwNUjJgl075n7D44b/+UAbhrxO/YeQfmICbctm3JCM2ub4wHhEIIZQkoUyx5URb+BJ2Ci5fdvVZ+0u3maJK0rjaCm1HTB1mjWWnH1avYaot11wJQCpfbzUDBRVMyqVP3E=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both Assertion and Reason are correct and related", 
		"option_b": "Assertion is correct, but Reason is incorrect", 
		"option_c": "Assertion is incorrect, but Reason is correct", 
		"option_d": "Both Assertion and Reason are incorrect and unrelated", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040118", 
		"question": "24GwbdH61Rzr+5ZgXRiyyfT9MHnEGi5Rpm6WU699ZGivFKbMaq3425ZlIk6HhE9isn/I47H48hMmgaxS6IDfUy0NbZ9m3MWd3uv5hGZEIcMEk45h9JMNefAAziTtYNzeYMFR8VG/GHqy3vzbDZhvGD0VvDuhS6TsEw==", 
		"answer": "25OqbZ/w2VnY8pMvXgvmzPLxd7lPuhBt8yLsps3/P+9rUBo=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH61Rzr+5ZgWxCy0fX6dVvCBmMcoXOGErRxYnSjXanEYvj7x5R0IxyLlBtv+nOGhbf1+VAHz5pe/4GTZTYKcYUtT2DIMeZWzSIFl0YGDXvDLg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Fr,en,ch Re,vo,lu,ti,on", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040119", 
		"question": "24GwbdHDwxzr+ocsV17hwP7qJ27DQ3Ye436PXuN3eWXqTqLMfa3xz9dYKViAjBtEzUn5nJrPt1wJz7xT5puYeDZPPo532MKMxPf+y38Nc8RBlol34tZfevVJ2DXhNNXVJL55wXyTL0zgJUBx7PLoH9/TKxc9HbBwKcQ=", 
		"answer": "27mxapThxQCoG/AmbJLvDKmqMESC3K/hhQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHDwxzr+ocsV17hwP7qJ27DQ24YoXqRRro0f3ejQK/Ne+r23dsxIkSZn15o4X/Jremw9VYDhq1dpc6ZcSsXdscvyd6Nl/P41mJJOtYGzTojPO9BxIg8led2FRCvUg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "li,be,rt,y", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040120", 
		"question": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rwr7yvO/JXnfDm0FpmzDRqtxMHfmUavLYOq+xpExIU6ImV5p/H/SuuXk/0EAmq9TqZqXdWIQZ5h7zd3J2OK3+05+DPl7pcBx7Y4WZvFO3zWkZJYZhZLjMd9G+QcC3yK8NMty", 
		"answer": "26axZpb/1FtydtsB7sAoaPXeESgM5hf0", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rwr7yvO/JXnfDm0FpmzDVLF1ZHTxWq7Wd63qwYV+MluBzU9z9zbVurbk8l5PgK4b+oeRdy4GPohm3NmT0urkzHhRccsrKMqdbyOavhQ5Xbrozls=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "si,ng,le", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040121", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YNHw+oNwM1mEiFVvsl+c44Tz9Fwdi6FV7s6Lf2InbMtOxdKM0+/21j0BJ85B2oZ98ZQbfeBJwzPte9KbLP992meOIAXgaDW0EHl3lT2Wjnlbp4Cp9CSiFNMkgCY9lY554Yg4OdqQ2rqS61SEiDWW3W+URbhqBRSwnJTo2EyfqYM09cmIvD3Y5vX6g7ja454KYQBbupB6Zxurn60HuD4wVIi5bRNF4qTfZxT9MienMg0J8MTtlnV7w8ImSmcx8F9Em8NCasUzxp3rrD41A8NdHTq5qwRPyZE8UBHWYLW9kG7r7FkwYnMlYspkr202rh2OLVdq2mKSDD5Uh5Bu/cRZmgIjaWdF3HfijSmOwHabfYfm5oXykfuv4jJoa893GirBmyihDBbtS2I=", 
		"answer": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhf7wJ3nVAHZd432WRuNHZHD3UarHYPm+4L4xLk/JhFV4/WTUpqbktZu/cfQC6zDHBoJgO4UuU+E=", 
		"explanation": "25GqJtHS3Bvv844hQF7wwPH2MH3VByIFq36XErN7fHj3XaTDYq36zJp+JE6IjkI78XfIrarkt18OnLwb/ICTdTEQPp9nzcKMl+j+wWIBMtIEk5RhpJgeb/EA3zKufdXXYPprw2GDNUTzfnf9N393nTDaynhTpYy45ya4TZZ3yRtyno5rrd41OcDTmaWW6UOrxgfCy3qICLJiUViQs8vo/0udtMIqsM6CtjzS7vHq2vTa8tsZdhEe/4NudlqwnrwQtGo5X8z0bgBK5eHCb135OWiiNE4U7dij0WFgwosnWikk5hZIgYpGbsVgmNjXqDMkOsBvGyf6im0Aw5F6VhmTZ/2r32vt4Vl/cX8maol/vS4s4QaSaEB7iGaPDCNX1JNk/dkYmQ1waS9Qjn/ugTabjGCcPJzlq4/ri+3is7Fq4uMoLwGNMF3WRc0TY/PQNWh23+qPBKlSf99wHyvlNZUn73n3L4LUyzEIkNw4LnTztC+Kgcj7OmD6vJS5mdx3AP8kJJ+FyMa1tVjMYDGhInKdcM7tXAy+D0jwxh0p9ysxyTUV5WfWHMlWtSQe3n2/W1ZhkTOgZXLhlb9M/pecdoA2k9H+k3IxlfZ9m5D2xlovBxKyiGhQ8ouRD09Azl3XEo0DwQQhD6YAF4+dsm+DgTbjX30ZesPzD7zH6gUI3uz0nSFzsIRORZ6BOhDfj54ywBLxAvJrR2LuvMb6MvIBD3w4uIRswOSyzyLiVLAdvsivU38=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both Statement I and Statement II are correct and Statement II is the correct explanation for Statement I", 
		"option_b": "Both Statement I and Statement II are correct and Statement II is not the correct explanation for Statement I", 
		"option_c": "Statement I is correct, but Statement II is incorrect", 
		"option_d": "Statement I is incorrect but Statement II is correct", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040122", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YNHw+oNwM1mEiFVvsl+c45H48hMbh7pe7M6PYisNfYJ/xNWal+H5x35MI8dXiYV2pJgGPOBIyX25ccbWYMIs3WGDLkT8Jz24CX93hjDVk0AU6IKp8Ge3Xdgy0gEr2sd9/N09MN6LwOTT6UO8xgCQ3W+UWrNtBU2lu/Km2FedtIc1sMOZ8RvyrrTYmfvc4toCbA8Sq4k/R0n8tqUL/S4zUNr4KAZD9KTAc13jIyGzKwsOucTllnhgxIc7SXB4tBpXl4Jaa9RqmtjlsjZwOd9rATaorU1U3tR9TRLWfbOs1Xrw91wxcH5rZIRp/Dk9oBvcLF1olXmfRSJW1JRj+91ZgApneH1NlXjlkX+fiGDPeYDw7o7/gKj/pvln964oKlOBNkXkWLESVqfBM2J/z+ePTY91GsUnIyrjfd0n7y32Mp+X3jVN1c8lIWOn4CKYho38N3aquoD8ipRiHLpAP9XA6Mek8FPBIS/oI3iBctK4GQ3hWn302hp8+1gkxiVQ7nDZHIxt+yQZhz65RwRwmiKgXG6kl7Ne5ofOcIhxx/3pnRsenP15kdvU2xMvUw2vmGtKvYrfRk8P2VzTXusVwQctBPQzEYDe/niCnHned3I6d8f1CeiIxWxc0uaxiG5xs58ZXIKJbBDIyt0p2gW0Auk5XGmtuoPqLfkWHiQj/PJlwujhtsi0Y/bkP3Erex+6XOFN4MoTZrpNFmfnxuIjJLm52FfDaA==", 
		"answer": "24asaYX23Bzk45Zge1Ky7NSzdWreByI4ilbDU7FxMHDvWOfBYf/szJRlZfiBHXFQtrEwyX/I+MvhDW8=", 
		"explanation": "25GqJtHS3Bvv844hQF72zPm/MGbAC2MCqmWGErd8dTHzRq7MbeTuxZJiZ1OPzVdy8HPUt7y8t1YemqlX4JqGPGICcI8vzsKIw+HlynhVKoZFicB0648RePVUxTKjddibNPEu2maFZ0z0Yjj9C3Y0hz7Vg31a6Ie++Ci4Rts02VsOmK99rckwL9jf262f4UiugwLCyHOQXP1wGVGKsI64+UqSo4soucie8TPJ8bTwlOzW4socawZXu8Z+bV/8lKkH9iUsEcqxKAFO4eXCYEDoJGi0LhoV9t73lmFnwoc7UGA6/RFBwpdeZ4Bl04r9/DcjLMhkFjb6rEIAw5FxUBSEdb6hnlTq1F06NXMvYIthr206p0+QIVZ7iH+FAGxUhZVq8tkNjEgjfGFE3HDygyuOkmuGaIqj/IXugKj5rr1m96dnIE+TJVXKU4lcZ6qAM293is+JCKhfO99VEjTpMcA69Tb3YJea23ka1cslb3vm4C+L0sT7Omqoo53rj8BzEP8JOMXKqd+/tRz3cybgLH+fY4v7X0jkR3m4+gBhvhkriAIf5nHMAZ1q4SQCkDDyv3HLTd497A/D0TnvSX2jug==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Statements I, II, and III are all correct", 
		"option_b": "Statements I and II are correct, but Statement III is incorrect", 
		"option_c": "Statement I is incorrect, but Statements II and III are correct", 
		"option_d": "Statements I and III are correct, but Statement II is incorrect", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040123", 
		"question": "25y2KIX71Fnp+Is0VwbmhfL5dX/YBiIhsXqCX6F4dT2jQ6/Deq36xpJiZ0iBiBtv92TL45my5VYfmqpX4I2jMmIKc5tj0ZCI1evi0DFVO8MEkoVz4NoQerRT2Dy5cZTSLr5HwGqJJhqyqNlWCHkwj39uS/KQMjOb6w==", 
		"answer": "25C0bZLn1B2q54ozWwr7yvO9L5X00F5+aaSoYJV3eBegfQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt7liQBvi0P/zPGjsQSIYrm+PW6ZnMGXrVbOCR+P6wJYxL12azVp1snPKpqbk8ldPh61a7c6QdmIQaop7zZzJw+zyhGFTNtVNnoV88Nj2LieBZnT9VH+D+MV3GN4f", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Hereditary position", 
		"option_b": "Elected position", 
		"option_c": "Monarchical position", 
		"option_d": "Appointed position", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040124", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MUcEBjgxOn6J2XZF3st4T+OV6J6MHjtFLPKa639xpllIkSdzVR9smLOpuXA5VYOgqpX7NHdF5EkcYOsMAdI8r/Yan7QLQ==", 
		"answer": "24a9ZoL2kRbst4cyXQr6wO/3OmTUQZhBPwCVJc5wVnOdntCsCWQ=", 
		"explanation": "25OqaYX2wxfj45xgQRf1y/T5PG7DQ2NRsHqNQaY0f3ejVrXNeuX7259+KFjJjFV/smPIqrHpt1ICgKZcqY2WZCsZe4V8iulinEh1Pk3T+j/xh7B4JNE=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Religious unity", 
		"option_b": "Sense of brotherhood", 
		"option_c": "Economic prosperity", 
		"option_d": "Political affiliation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040125", 
		"question": "2523f9H33hz5t5EoV17RyvPsIWLEFnYYrHHDQrF7fX73UefWZui+2YV4KV+AnVd+4TbJpeXMtVUdjrxe+4CWZDs/PNQtaqAqTCU/AX0We1mXtGU8GQ==", 
		"answer": "24Gwep7m1hGq0ZAuVh//wPPrNGeQJ3cFqnqQENsjkIfMMTw18m+ijQXywvw=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rwr7yvO/JXnfDm0FpmzDVLF1ZHTxWq7Wd63qwYV+MluBzX1u/HLHrqD+41IDz4xO/YeaY25DeIR83NWb3urwhGRPOtJd2oF/65QYPPdJ2DS3cdrIYOp8z2CTJED+YzCzAzBwnSfTmG9fvIq+5mWk4G3NNRqlHQTKb1aJ1t2u", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Through religious freedoms", 
		"option_b": "Through economic privileges", 
		"option_c": "Through political affiliations", 
		"option_d": "Through Fundamental Duties", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040126", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg37wvP2M2LTAmwSpj+MVONIMnTyQabOZ/nniZV0IVObiBtv+nOGr6TnyxFPjrsb+pqeZCcHPoJhiMSB0qTH1nRAPsRIn98wFZ7s9N/xesFpR0VbhNgkpw==", 
		"answer": "25C2e4Th1Aqq8pQ1UxKyyu3vOnnEFmwYt3aGQeET3bUwKO05Ec2uy2wrP8qp", 
		"explanation": "25CpfZD/2A3zt4clVBHgwL3rPW6QD2MG43qNQbZmdWKjUbbXb+G+3YV0JkiEiFVvsnfIp+X/50MAnbxO54eLeScQPo1g2pCI2+i3x3hVOtxBlJMwJ/7uRKnwe0ZKuxj1WtNrAg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Promotes economic privileges", 
		"option_b": "Ensures equal opportunities", 
		"option_c": "Fosters religious tolerance", 
		"option_d": "Establishes social justice", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040127", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MUcEBr71untPGnFF2sHpj+JR7BgeXLmaOWCb+TziYN+Z12KhVJ+5HOZ4QtUgm8yM9m9EqjCnRlM71w=", 
		"answer": "25C0YZz63xj+/oouEhH0hfj8OmXfDmsS43aNV7JhcX3qQK7Hfa+fpHH6wpXJpwMDpBuVC4Xa", 
		"explanation": "25Gxe4Xh2Bv/44w2V1740O7rPGjVQ2sftXCPRKZnMHTvXarLYOzqwJl2Z1uFjEly/HGGqqv15kYOg6FP4IuMMCsNPpxqydyd36i3zX9CPMtB1sBz6p5fbOZP3Di/YM2Z3snNXlXQ3lI90yK1v5cBpw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Equal distribution of wealth", 
		"option_b": "Equitable taxation", 
		"option_c": "Elimination of economic inequalities", 
		"option_d": "Social welfare programs", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040128", 
		"question": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f5GzDUax5fXj3WaLMeq3qxtdOGGO2smREzUn5nJqw/UYcm6FY7MLfZyoKfYMvydmExKTjyzFEP89Jk45z8J9fe/hB3jSjc5TSLvt/22+MLlH5Yir9DX40gzTXhmhe5MOy+yS0Wd97gBQ8ksdo/8csOcWLwOTT+ki+igOByGjRXLVhUV2Xs8K97k2fpcI3s42ZuTeb0ub8lPvbsOwOdAdeqpJ2bFX8g6AI7Go5Vd67axNf9OCQcUbkLiuqNwIY6ovs0DRlz4AsT30tuF9Dk5ZXbslnz9SkvTw0f8t4FCe/sUpJ040+q5wxOnNLuPsF9WdwPXvFYA==", 
		"answer": "25Gxe4Xh2Bv/44w2V1zYcDDT//OMkaTr72qaa4Zu", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt7liVhfh0e/2N37ECnQU43WWQbd9c3TfFufGa+Px3ZJiZ0iBiBt+/n/Lqqvx41oAgehU786WficSa4pjwcSA0ve3zX8BJMNFlpR6qNoWcvdPwTjhNNXVJL5+3GGQIlfkfnmJDHln1DfZmHEWp4X7/zKoQNM0xVU7hcdq6M4wOdSL3KzT4UP4kg6HnFKfTLRlHxS6usC7/0qItZYxusPNsDzftP3q2vnA49EIawlGuoI/dFKon+gd8C94WMayZAdO/+fVIVvrYDyrIk47687t1Xwp9Ic/UmUh4BZJjMNiasUz8IrhsjE4f/9vAzy2tlBJyJo8F0bBLOTLgT+9uRx/cHc7bYt+tTcwpU+MOl1wmWKMQClC1JN+/dhZlBcjcWZCmWT0m3PLhXSafZ/q/5mwxen+pPll4KIzLFOOPEjBGs0LbbrDLydzxuCcA+ZLOotvVzbuOJUt8zf6JYaAnzYLkN0pPGP1/SiMhsTjPCWwpoHth9dzVL4JO9jL7oujvxzVZCD1KHuKJs73Vgb/QnX7kwdrsgkwyS0Z/GvdG8scHyuFiSMOl0KQJE/VzyOu", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Dis,tr,ib,ut,ive", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040129", 
		"question": "2523f9H6wlnWtZUvXhfmzP7+OSvaFnEFqnyGbuE0dHTlXanHaq33x9dlL1nJvUl+83vEr6CvtRuu6cEJ7XePYjsje9a0Cgg=", 
		"answer": "25CpfZD/kRjp9IAzQV7myr3vOmfZF2sSonPDXaVyeXLmR+V6VE+6+VHmNIZ67JudtQj2", 
		"explanation": "24W3ZJjn2Brr+8UqRw3mzP76dW7eEHcDpmzDV7JhcX2jVaTBa/7tiYN+Z0yGgVJv+3XHr+X/8VUGjK1IqY+RdGITf5l7wdOAx+XjzX5Pc89K2od98p8NcvVOzzjvZl/AiE7dN2qDtof/X0wyqg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Equal representation in government", 
		"option_b": "Equal access to education", 
		"option_c": "Equal access to political offices", 
		"option_d": "Equal access to economic privileges", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040130", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzwQvl4YwzWxH8hfjxJn7CBnFRs3CPW7d9c3DvFKLTe+zywINoZ12KjlRp9n/IpOXk+BMbh60b2ZyacS8Bco4winX7qTZdOsgYJtfaY9OSZwc=", 
		"answer": "24C2YYf2wwrr+8UzRxj01/z4MCnfPLL65tC6TmD6Tw3dBt9c", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHDwxzr+ocsV173yO33NHjZGWcC42+MXqpgeXLiWOfIe/7qwJR0Z16QzUtp/XvJt6z+8BMagaFN7JyMcS5Df496xMTJxPHxwmNANMMGJutUqUCi00p7Vlvp2d26Fw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Religious freedom", 
		"option_b": "Universal suffrage", 
		"option_c": "Economic privileges", 
		"option_d": "Linguistic diversity", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040131", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq/4wnWhL7wvXrMG+QAXtRt3eGErdxYnyjaOXQa/3ry5t4JGDLzVJ1smLOpuXA5VYOgqpX7NHdGG08qDITLYUUnSSXCApu1Q==", 
		"answer": "25C0bZLn1B2q/4AhVl79w73sIWrEBiAnwhHT0oIpKsp12sWVPDZx", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt7liQBvi0P/zPGjsQSICqniNW6V9dWKjVamCa+H7yoN0IxyBiFp/snnA47bk9kcKz6lV7c6LeCdDf4l8zd6K0qT4wjFJNtRBnolm5YgGPPlPwjy/d9zCYky7VTq8mzB0tpZcD3TlSOQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Political sovereignty in people", 
		"option_b": "Economic privileges for all", 
		"option_c": "Absence of government", 
		"option_d": "Elected head of state", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040132", 
		"question": "24GwbdHw3hfp8pU0EhH0he7wNmLRD2sCrj+KXONgeHSjfanGZ+zwibR+KU+dhE9u5n/JreX55BMMh6lJ6I2LdTAKZI5riNKQl+W3xn1EPcIElYYy26UgQ8t/8wKSS+uZmqM4fHUJagJP3lgaTMn73g==", 
		"answer": "25i5eon6whSq9oskEjnzy/n3PHjdQX5q2u6e1RRRbskQQU/VXC8=", 
		"explanation": "25ysKJn61hHm/oIoRg2y0fX+ISvEC2dRinGHW6J6MHPxVanGLuL4iYR+JFWIgVJo/zbFrKjy/l0KnOhe5YuSdSwXbctgzpCk1vbvzWJMc8dKnsBV5ZQbdP1TwXHtd8beIepnwGnAJgXlaTCsEXU0lSHGmHNXq4v7/im0Q9R3wQZykoJ14ssuPcOW2uiA506xhwqLz3bTVUn74ysH/VdZMGnCNrc0tg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Ma,rx,is,m a,nd, Ga,ndh,ism", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040133", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YN7qyIN0KlmHmRtSqErIl631t0cKnaUbrp2aczcPf5koiNmHl/D/wTFxIcNFl4J+4doQerRUxDjtXdrfKf9gjk2PKVbkbi2oEHl7mnHfh2xaoYaotTOzVc531B031pRs7Nw5fN+eyuid5w23gACL33KQRP12FFiQssen5QOdroZ4psyLtDXO9eb9ibjH+NtLZBpXuoJwbhuzkegb/SYxVsG7ZlJE96TRbVitIyG3LhQY99jf2Ed9x5YsUGw64F9vq9lqbPR709jwuSA9f4p5EDCvr0VSgNR1UVeCfLj44Hrh4Vg9eX9raowtqCUw4TqSIUB7niuvWC1FkZMr3d8XhhBqaXpUlXnuwjaGkGmGeYCj/4j5xfv1sLhx87cuJk/AOlqYVYUJd7DIZ2Z8zqmIGadINtMnBzDpNdws9S3wLpHUyzEIkN4vOXL1+iecnNm1P3e1vtL8ncB3FrMJJdnM58z3sRzVZC/oJnScaIv7S0j5QWj9wQhgpRErz2EH4XbQSI9t8ChNm2a1W0dtgSKgY3rhhLtQ44WHcIAN3cni6joZm/w4kJ23wBU5BxevjGtGv4GRW08Pyl3AG8NHxQshGrFBHYWe83+T1XXfWW4IfNqpQ/NcctAXZJXQrol6bGbPK14=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz4g3r44AtVxDmhdS/NGXUQ1EFomuGX6Z6ZDHKfefDfOi+yphjNVmKmRkLVOIyd5Z+GmAHsNL3g1F0", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJCF7by73rPW6QAG0ft3qbRuN7djH3XKKCR+P6wJZ/Z3+Gg0hv+2LTt6z/+R9Pm6BeqZqaYi9DOZhqy8WF1vawhGJINMhNnIl399oLdPVUjCmlcZTINP96yy6EKEDjJzeyEDB8lSfTyn1Y6Iy98y64Xds7gAc3mo5/5McyfNaR3eia+w2xixaDzm+YSbEkGFrZuM+8/0aOs8I3s42ftD7S8/32lLST4MwEdAFWtoh4I16tgqkFuCUoQcemfAdF+PDZZEetNCfjJgIRudnm2n1uz408Tik3+xJLl41fdsl2xdjQtDdwLNlrATb6sEVGwpNpXgWSZ/2s2G2k5kc6cH4kaMpium0npAOVL11xlCuTSmxQmIwr98QK1QdqaWZamXjzwguDiXbPdYCj4o68ieH+pfl0+7cvaVWIMBzoRIgdaLHMIisy3eGSDq4cN5pkGyP0OMZu1Tf9KZfUyzZN0txgLjfbthmWhMjnPGy9vd65vdt1Hb4MP8LRpYuEtV/SbSLzbT23Y8b7WhrxW3X7kzxgpw0nxCgT1CDkBrVxxjkMinu9TEpw0g7JNjyImP5I4ofOSoA4x/DonQEEmeB9jNe3wBU5Bwe0g3xGopDfQFoPikfTHdgLxRsnH7lGVJ/CsmqTm3PCSnABZo7jD6yC0T9c1ez1zmBu/4QGUMydKQnamN8ywRi/QfJ/FWTlvZT6NbwUBGBs6aZw3ujhg8K+NdWtPnY+Lzu6XOFd/pBffEJvHkvJDSEPVYvudZIQUvRGxmDenghGB29bClLF+aEcTkS+osGIaG/aZqMdAl7lbKUAAcD1S0nbdfe7xz2JC76XnEm5H0UrV3qRIKdN2UXif5/iIRCnmmZjucDrclRIUIIVMC7gfGa8q7fDBAB6bSkpIY1OdUmZCx821C7RKPFuj64UeRYqAbyvHBAQhBRK3zvKC0pGuV8bH7GlRUEiJa8JHBlRyDGzFKMLVQrPiiNKi0WIwyDgIOlDOEckO3CbigzVlZtymvupsZqAHtHxbbwIkoxDO7NYUZbXDRsSm+ft4O+ixDtDoS10C5u1Agrc3OgQ3Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only Statement I is correct", 
		"option_b": "Both Statement I and Statement II are correct", 
		"option_c": "Only Statement II is correct", 
		"option_d": "Neither Statement I nor Statement II is correct", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040134", 
		"question": "2523f9H33hz5t5EoV17C1/j+OGncBiIVpnmKXKY0TDPpQbTWZ+779dUuZTZ1ItSwzB8XL7K+SgBomdw=", 
		"answer": "24a3a5jy3VWq8oYvXBH/zP6zdWreByIBrHOKRqp3cX2jVbTSa+7q2tXyAKLgUmvOiTDEl1Sw0nsn", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHDwxzr+ocsV172wPv2O27DQ15TqWqQRqp3dU2hFLPNLujwyph8N12anhto/XXPoqm8t1YMgKZU5IecPGICcI8v2N+F3vD+x3BNc8JNl4V895MQcucCVH0JaJxCL+HOqvTQZfDVMw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Judicial proceedings", 
		"option_b": "Social, economic, and political aspects", 
		"option_c": "Criminal justice only", 
		"option_d": "Civil disputes only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040135", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MU0Whuy0fjtOCvsQWQDomuGQK19ZGjfFufHYO7xxIdwNE/JhFU75n7D45Xi8lICjaRetsz3pNHveuoQS5DnyBDAfJe2", 
		"answer": "24a9ZoL2kRbst4cyXQr6wO/3OmTUQZhBPwCVJc5wVnOdntCsCWQ=", 
		"explanation": "25OqaYX2wxfj45xgVhv8yun6JivRQ3EUrWyGEqxyMHPxW7PKa//2xph1Z12HiRtu/H/SuuXx+lwBiOhY4JqWaicNbckqbZcJevn2DIirqXDIWCn/", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Sense of brotherhood", 
		"option_b": "Cultural identity", 
		"option_c": "Economic prosperity", 
		"option_d": "Political affiliation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040136", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0hbk9IAwRl79w73xNH/ZDGwQrz+KXLdxd2PiQK7NYK332td5LluBgVJ8+mLDp+Xy7hMbh60b/YuNfWI/PIJh3NWOxe3j3U0Dc89K2pR64dovbvFBwT+hcYuZ8CxQ8oJlZDLFCq1lhMtDjg==", 
		"answer": "24G9eoP6xRb4/oQsEgv8zOnmd0vzPTpiEYwFz+n9Ork+1Fg=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt7liWxDmwPrtPH/JPyBRtnGHV7Fnc37xUbSCeuX7iYN0NU6AmVRp+3fK47D+/kcWz6lV7c6WfiYKaIJ8wdKA2+3j3TFONYZQkoUy6psLdftOjkWldE7IvD+ViWIwEbhRX8A=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Cultural diversity", 
		"option_b": "Regional autonomy", 
		"option_c": "Linguistic divisions", 
		"option_d": "Territorial unity", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040137", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kRzr9I1gRhvgyL3oPH/YQ2sFsD+AXbFmdWLzW6nGZ+P5iZN0NF+bhEtv+3nI4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EYj0KFILsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8H1fWNP34kCikoBV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LwCXPPNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyYFs1cJfOAZycyiqnbTeYcc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbUn3lNkJlgbzentGrZ0o21eSX689K5zpQ2VP9AdpGFqYv38ByHIWOhYT3TJou0GUiwDzy4k04l91hliGFQqCKYSMk/tW1N3j7wCQQk0megLDzh1v4cqsLOP85xk7WsnXJQ2LQ439u3lF18B0T7zT8D8sTfDxwPjRSWXo1HhEluTPRBVNaRsi3W1TaQCzxNP462QejHg2wImqOxziE9/9BOFczObFmbyp5miFfxQb05FSet6Ma5fbxVSiRsuvIxiq3h94r7NbPkbCVqL1r3Ga8Zs9URKEI7UUudRWQPIPjuFt1eAaAPkjWK10cIBz8JRRqMu+hIHUTq6oSILiqeI/FcTl6iI/NFU464DgePdbHpiHCJRv/c1Qf+HwRlDnrdYfBNpUewOsyyZFPz0ygkuYGlchEbBMNXfGezNCv55ePDS0Z6P2xlaMoHOgeVC1Bk1H6DZ7knzedAMFhtAejnWRBW1lEP336SThgF8AxeH+XtABNnaukFYBtRjXf1UeBfHFyKxnpKzhbcgmKsaboLcQljOyTTzwyg29Im37+pws7BSpSibf1bks1DaPYbBNqWXxtc2rOkr6GgUSx5Ri03briIHqKR8A+2Qoi04oOahRwLif5Idh97ZXnLyd+ZsHotb+UPLzAK/TNZ7IqSIkbqmcgZlRAoEBWstQGkASdh9lEzLtOrKp2catvlsBAfVmSHF/kD2Lw4nWykdZ+RJFp/RyN10UfQNpKKh3TDfey7gO1JRVjil9mLBcotrAg5jpzygwwA63s1zzyiSzaaIqetqF4UYjw4C/TfWh0dxldilXrxnhOofc/qx+ZJzvABmPVToUy34mE2zx7MDwqOIzOqnrbe9yaG/gdhieojHCbjGzMtjkxkBLBrsjkuAG1hCeE0/Pa1bPGE3iHvbtz4jcxNpRYUBueKb/37/ZW8ZeOFb+WsmcDDbzKhsdNFDea7aPdFN3/ZbH0zra3gL63tL2iPBtgQ9IGnlSS7prkKwOk=", 
		"answer": "24axetHS3RXr84xgeQz71vXxNHjHAm8Y41aaV7E0PTHLW7XNfe7x2ZIxKFrJgk5psmXJtaDi8loIgehf7IOQczACaoJsiMKMx/H1yHhCf4Zvt8Bf8ZQMdP0AgX2ZfNGbM/F7wi6PIQXkbzz9J396hyXfnmlCoYy1uWeLVdQzyQFyoo955t0ufPOeyuix4EyqgQeU3TvcCJBrAkDZpdyt6EqTtZF4pcyfpXLU8rTtkv2T09EFcRxbq5NralSy2+g68Th4dNq6bQFfscbRc1/oMmjuZyUY4Ibt2WBshpYmHX088V9ljY1Fdslnw4ztszx+fQC+8jRHfGDju8sqEdxlLO4=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avn5MUhQBv/xOn8PW7UQ2AQsHqHEqx6MGXrUefRZ+rwwJF4JF2Hjl47/XCGt631t2MdiqlW64KaMCMQPo9q29Ob3ubywDFDKoZAk4Z04YgacuAAxTOpfcLSJOtvwn3CAMAnOyP0YgVUNc6SWfH+uw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "KM Munshi,The soul of the Constitution", 
		"option_b": "Pandit Thakur Das Bhargava,Most precious part of the Constitution", 
		"option_c": "Sir Ernest Barker,Key-note to the Constitution", 
		"option_d": "Sir Alladi Krishnaswami Iyer,Horoscope of our sovereign democratic republic", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040138", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kRzr9I1gRhvgyL3oPH/YQ2sFsD+AXbFmdWLzW6nGZ+P5iZN0NF+bhEtv+3nI4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EYj0KFILsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8H1fWNP34kCikoBV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LwCXPPNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyYFs1cJfOAZycyiqnbTeYcc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbUn3lNkJlgbzentGrZ0o21eSX689K5zpQ2VP9AdpGFqYv38ByHIWOhYT3TJou0GUiwDzy4k04l91hliGFQqCKYSMk/tW1N3j7wCQQk0megLDzh1v4cqsLOP85xk7WsnXJQ2LQ439u3lF18B0T7zT8D8sTfDxwPjRSWXo1HhEluTPRBVNaRsi3W1TaQCzxNP462QejHg2wImqOxziE9/9BOFczObFmbyp5miFfxQb05FSet6Ma5fbxVSiRsuvIxiq3h94r7NbPkbCVqL1r3Ga8Zs9URKEI7UUudRWQPIPjuFt1eAaAPkjWK10cIBz8JRRqMu+hIHUTq6oSILiqeI/FcTl6iI/NFU464DgePdbHpiHCJRv/c1Qf+HwRlDnrdYfBNpUewOsyyZFPz0ygkuYGlchEbBMNXfGezNCv55ePDS0Z6P2xlaMoHOgeVC1Bk1H6DZ7knzedAMFhtAejnWRBW1lEP336SThgF8AxeH+XtABNnaukFYBtRjXf1UeBfHFyKxnpKzhbcgmKsaboLcQljOyTTzwyg29Im37+pws7BSpSibf1bks1DaPYbBNqWXxtc2rOkr6GgUSx5Ri03briIHqKR8A+2Qoi04oOahRwLif5Idh97ZXnLyd+ZsHotb+UPLzAK/TNZ7IqSIkbqmcgZlRAoEBWstQGkASdh9lEzLtOrKp2catvlsBAfVmSHF/kD2Lw4nWykdZ+RJFp/RyN10UfQNpKKh3TDfey7gO1JRVjil9mLBcotrAg5jpzygwwA63s1zzyiSzaaIqetqF4UYjw4C/TfWh0dxldilXrxnhOofc/qx+ZJzvABmPVToUy34mE2zx7MDwqOIzOqnrbe9yaG/gdhieojHCbjGzMtjkxkBLBrsjkuAG1hCeE0/Pa1bPGE3iHvbtz4jcxNpRYUBueKb/37/ZW8ZeOFb+WsmcDDbzKhsdNFDea7aPdFN3/ZbH0zra3gL63tL2iPBtgQ9IGnlSS7prkKwOk=", 
		"answer": "25e9eoTx0Avjt7AuWxH8hf7+Jm6QSzNI9S/KEu40QGPmVarAYui+wIQxKVOdzVo74nfUt+X/8RMbh60byoGRYzYKap57wd+Hm6TcwWJAJcdKm4525do9dPVSzSmkNNfaM/suhj/ZcBa5J3T9NGJxlTzUhnkWq4K1tSW+FNs6xRs2k4M4790ofNmQzeia/F74hAeR1XjRTrhlBUGLsN3kq2+1g8I3s42kvzbS9bT6m+vWsJZaO1EH9sYyI2uukqkE+iY9EcGnKBML4eXCdRTiJmi3Lwtd2sTtxWBg0pc9VGY6thRBObVBR7MwZizcgWPDf7s=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avn5MUhQBv/xOn8PW7UQ2AQsHqHEqx6MGXrUefRZ+rwwJF4JF2Hjl47/XCGt631t2MdiqlW64KaMCMQPo9q29Ob3ubywDFDKoZAk4Z04YgacuAAxTOpfcLSJOtvwn3CAMAnOyP0YgVUNc6SWfH+uw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "LIC of India case (1995),Preamble is a part of the Constitution", 
		"option_b": "Kesavananda Bharati case (1973),Preamble can be amended but not its basic features", 
		"option_c": "Berubari Union case (1960) - Preamble is not a part of the Constitution", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040139", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7mzfi/F27CFmAQsXbDZ619f3+jV6bRa622mM4ndxXFzUxz82KGtKTjt0cHiuho/J6NdS8GPqhg3cKdkPe3zX9IJ89FlsB99JMRdftOjC+oc9XJJPdgyS6UL0CwdC28EGVn1D7QymhercOL5yK6Wdg7xUpwLO2acnhCQww4HJ49v/21ig==", 
		"answer": "24WqbZD+0xXvt4wzEhD90b3+dXvREXZRrHnDRqtxMFLsWrTWZ/nr3Z5+KR56one24OVMpTNJIvrxXGL1", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIX71FnI8pc1UB/gzL3KO2LfDSISomyGHuNgeHSjZ7LSfOjzzNdSKEmbmRtp93XJpKv57VYLz7xT7M6MeSUNd41my9GH1OG3y3cBJ85B2rBg4ZsSfvhFjD+4YJTIMPttx2iJJET8ayD9C2B9mjTSymheqZf74S++FOolxRQ/lIt9rcEvfNmQzeiSqF25lBLC033RXLVhUXeWu9284leJtIs3u4/F32Oq63z0sZXeLSYQqHFW", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Preamble is a part of the Constitution", 
		"option_b": "Preamble is not a part of the Constitution", 
		"option_c": "Preamble can be amended under Article 368", 
		"option_d": "Preamble is a source of legislative power", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040140", 
		"question": "25y2KIX71FnB8pYhRB/8xPP7NCvyC2MDomuKEqB1Y3SjHPabOb63hddmL12dzV9y9jbSq6CwxEYfna1W7M68fzcRastsx96K2/HzwTFAMclRjsBm7J9fb+BB2Ci+NNvdYOpmyy6wNUDxajuxAS82YtWHdg7X6C/ckdPM3fBk2Q==", 
		"answer": "24WqbZD+0xXvt4wzEh/8hfTxIW7XEWMd42+CQLc0f3ejQK/HLs7xx4RlLkicmVJ0/DS+feExF/zV0eWFsqGY+YPo", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIX71FnB8pYhRB/8xPP7NCvyC2MDomuKEqB1Y3SvFLPKa63N3IdjIlGMzXh052TS47f1/VYMm61fqYeLY2IGf5ljwdWbl+vnzX9IPMgEm452pJIacPAA2DWsYJTPKPsu/nyFJkjyazz9DWM0lXHGi25C6Iy9tTOzUZoUzxshgo5s+Nw1M9nf8LzT7UCojgeR1WGUTP1wGVHZvMO45FGIoYw7sI2Ct3LJ8fX9k/bUsN8FZkhbsZJ6cUuukrwA9i14RcCxKDFE//fEaED4NCGsKU4U94vv33Nh0sImWykg/BoGlIpFa899lp38rCA1LN5vEXOzrQRUz5E8bwWTdbC63G2mq19GNnsollZeY5IaPG3g1Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Preamble is not significant to the Constitution", 
		"option_b": "Preamble is not enforceable in courts of law", 
		"option_c": "Preamble is non-justiciable", 
		"option_d": "Preamble is an integral part of the Constitution", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040141", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0hbk84w0WxH8hfn2MSvEC2dRkGqTQKZ5dTHAW7LQeq3tzIMxIVObzVp293jCqqv3t0cHiuhr+4uefSAPe8t6xtSMxaTW1mVIMMpB2tMkvMVd3icQTCCJb6+X6a1dUNyTOA==", 
		"answer": "25u3KJD+1Bfu+oAuRl7hzfLqOW+QAm4Fpm3DRqtxMHPiR67BLuv7yINkNVmazVR9smLOpuXT+F0cm6FP/JqWfyxDfYRh3NGA2eHzhHhPc9JMn8BC9p8ecfZMyX/DD9Y3IUnkVoA9iq5V/EzC", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIX71FnB8pYhRB/8xPP7NCvyC2MDomuKEqB1Y3SvFLPKa63N3IdjIlGMzXh052TS4631+1dPm6Ba/c6LeCdDTplqyd2L2+G3zWIBMoZUm5JmpJUZPOBIyX2Oe9rINPd623qJKEuwZje5RHN1mnHUjzxXpYa18SK/FM85xBAg1qZq+cE/MNLfiv7LqGW3kQOU2WndCLRwUUeJsM2h7UqZpMIsvcyZ8TzUtPX0n/bX/dsFdkhBt4lqb1/8lqQd/Th4RcCxKBBK4u3TIVHhJSWmKRoOucTxlnJ8yIYoUGw64B5KwoVTY9RmxJ33/D02f9liEHOZrEpT051oSgOfe7P40Xuk41oxYXsia49p/CQ74RuULRROiG6dQS5dkcJd+RmDemjI8H4G29WtL9No", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Any amendment to the Preamble is allowed", 
		"option_b": "The Preamble cannot be amended", 
		"option_c": "No amendment should alter the basic features of the Constitution contained in the Preamble", 
		"option_d": "The Preamble can be amended without any restrictions", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040142", 
		"question": "2523f9H+0Bfzt5EpXxvhhfX+JivEC2dRk22GU652fHSjW6GCeuX7ib5/I1WIgxtY/XjVt6zk4kcGgKYb64uafmICc45hzNWNl+X5wDFWO8dQ2pd39p9faPxFjDypcN3PKfFg3S6NJkH1JzCzRGR8kXHXh3lYrI6++zPkFvT8U8yBGMr1NIc5V14X7mg=", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHDwxzr+ocsV176xO6/N27VDSIQrnqNVqZwMH7tV6KCZ+O+mM4mcRDJjF9/+3jB47H48hMYgLpf+s6jMhEMfYJuxNmaw6jLhjF9cfVBmZV+5YhTQLYAzTOpNOiZCfB6y2mSLlHpJQndr9rYilEr/wIvqylRCVA=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHDwxzr+ocsV17lxO6/NGbVDWYUpz+BS+NgeHSjAPXMaq3dxpliM1WdmE9y/XjHr+XR+lYBi6Ve55rfUSEXPoJhiIHQgLK38HlIIIZFl4V84JcacuAAzTmpcdCbNPZ8y2vAKUDnJy6yFnRn1EKWtj5lp4Cy9CuyR857/FdyqsVL6MspMNaNlZTRqEy2gka+nlKfXLhjA12NrPLqqzDctI14ocWI8QLJ8fX0mPTWsl4lC1q/uvL0EHLJdAk/fUA=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "The Preamble has never been amended", 
		"option_b": "The Preamble has been amended once in 1976, adding the words \"Socialist,\" \"Secular,\" and \"Integrity", 
		"option_c": "The Preamble was amended in 1995", 
		"option_d": "The Preamble was amended in 1980", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040143", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg37wvP2M2LTAmwSpj+MVONgeHSjQKLQY6252phnIk6MhFx1tTbHsOXl5FYLz6FVqZqXdWIzbI5uxdKF0ru1++V0Buor86Y8gxHSwN3b8w==", 
		"answer": "25y2bJjykRD5t4QuEhf8wfjvMGXUBmwF42yXU7dxMGbqQK+CYOK+yIJlL1ObhE9isnfErLP1t1obzUXdp8gsxhw8tgfBek/5VSY=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt8IzXQj31/j2MmWXQ2sf42uLV+NEYnTiWaXOa63twJB/LlqAiEg75n7Ht+XZ+VcGjuhS+s6RfzZDa4VrzcLJw+zyhHBUJ85LiIlm/doQbrRDwzO5ZtvXYPFojm+OPgX/czG4FjB6lSXfhXIWgZf7/DT7VdR3yRs2k5d948w5MsPfyryS/Ej4kQ+W1DuFQLgkF0acsMqn5gOIr8I7usOJpDHPtP3tibja/soOcAZTs8Z+bV/8krAd/Tg2UMT0aRRN8O3CchZYRtE5/x4jnJOtRloH+41l", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "India is a part of a larger confederation", 
		"option_b": "India is an independent state with no authority above it", 
		"option_c": "India is a colony of another nation", 
		"option_d": "India is a republic governed by multiple rulers", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040144", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhPzzPO/MWLDF2sfoGuKXa00cnT3Q6LHYK25zZJ8KF+bjE9y8TbVrKb59l8GnKUcqY+RdGJEfYRixcWH3vfjzXIBIMlHk4F+7YkSO6sCKyfxL3qwqDtwQB2jTT8XZw==", 
		"answer": "25G9ZZ7wwxj+/oZgQRHxzPzzPHjdQ2sftXCPRKZnMHCjWa7aa+m+zJR+KVOElBc75X7Pr6Cw9FwCgr1V4J2LeSFDbYRswdGF3vf6hHBIPtUEnI9gpJkQceRMySmoNNraNPdhwG+MLl/xczCyCjKWrDjEFvoU+IPMljU0S/Nd", 
		"explanation": "25G9ZZ7wwxj+/oZgQRHxzPzzPHjdQ2oer3uQEqV1eWXrFK7MLuy+xJ5pIljJiFh0/HnLuuXn/1YdiuhZ5pqXMDIWfIdmy5CI2eC31GNIJcdQn8Bh4ZkLc+ZTjD6icczSM+ou7WGNKlD+biqpDXM0hz7Vg31aoZC2tS61QtU71hAh1pNw6IgyPcOW1qaS5ESihxKL03XRR7skEFiV9cOt6k2P4I0+9d2fvjbO9+DwlfaT8dAPIhxausZ+YVSwnrwA9yR4Xs70eABC5+XEZBT9MiezIhwJ4IkAVK8UcqfG34/YDT9NmOuL", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Democratic socialism is based on capitalism", 
		"option_b": "Communistic socialism promotes individual ownership of property", 
		"option_c": "Democratic socialism involves a mixed economy, while communistic socialism aims for complete nationalization", 
		"option_d": "Communistic socialism supports a market-based economy", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040145", 
		"question": "2523f9H33hz5t5EoV17mwO/ydSzDDGEYonOKQbczMGPmWKbWa63qxtdYKViAjBxosnfWs7f/9lAHz7xUqZ6QZicRapIvyd6Nl+35wWBUMspNjpktpu0goxpLsOja66iXr7j7K2U=", 
		"answer": "25ysKJD63Aqq44pgVxD2he3wI27CF3td43aEXKxmcX/gUeuCauTtzJZiIhDJjFV/sn/IprTl9l8Gm7Eb5ojffzITcZl73d6Aw/21dht5iLKyXIMITd2CwRIqfw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt8IzXR37xPH2Jn+XQ2MC43KGXLd9f3/mUOfLYK3qwZIxF06MjFZ5/nOGsaD2+1YMm7sbwICbeSNEbctsx92E3vD6wX9Vc9JL2oF24Igab+dJwjrtZ9vYKf9ijm+OIwX1ZDazC319l3HSg29GqZGy4S6+R5oDyBBypZJo/80xOZe81r2B/A2rkgeW2WjRXLVlBRSdsMOn6FGdtIs79d6Csjva+P3ql7jS+dMYIhxd/4Nzala1makd/WooXt6xegZSvaTZZlriMimtJAtRuc/qxXFo1YdlHWg68F9PjIZHd8F/34z9/D02f8J6BTyot1FOzoBlHdbBUfndqv8fNqyIN0AwGD4=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "It supports the complete nationalization of industries", 
		"option_b": "It emphasizes individual economic freedom", 
		"option_c": "It aims to end poverty, ignorance, disease, and inequality of opportunity", 
		"option_d": "It promotes private ownership of resources", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040146", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQnl+4w0Wx3zyb32MW7fD20WqnqQEqt1ZnSjXanEYvj7x5R0Ixygg19y83iGsKrz/lIDhrtWpc6eY2IHe5hs2tmL0uC3zX8BJ85B2pBz94kee/EfjlRyZaCgST4kn/jQZyAbspc=", 
		"answer": "25i5eon6whSq9oskEjnzy/n3PGreQ3EeoHaCXqpnfTP5bCN8GIBPkyRIbRRBF7+3", 
		"explanation": "25y2bJjy31n5+IYpUxL71vC/PHiQCmwXr2qGXKBxdDHhTefDLu/yzJl1Z1OPzXZ64G7PsKiw9l0Lz49a54qXeSMNPphgy9mI2+3kyTFoJ4ZIn4F899oSc+ZFjCmiY9XJJO0u6W+OI035Zjf9F393nTDag29b6IK18We6XdckgAE91oZ75cE5KtLf2OjU+0K7jweO1WiFQb4kAVWNocu65QOTpsIrus6EtCbCs7Ttkurc5dkDIgxXsol8cVqonqtJ9S85X9v25QRN7hR3g1BbwBGqZxv0xQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Capitalism and totalitarianism", 
		"option_b": "Marxism and Gandhian socialism", 
		"option_c": "Feudalism and aristocracy", 
		"option_d": "Fascism and monarchy", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040147", 
		"question": "25SqepD91hyq440lEhj9yfHwImLeBCICt36XV65xfmXwFLPNLuz9yoJjJkiMgUI74HPWsaDj8l0bz7xT7M6cfywAe5t7iN+Pl/f4x3hAP89Xl8B76toLdPEA5TOpfdXVYN1hwH2ULlHlczCyCio01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EYj0KFILsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8H1fWNP34kCikoBV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcbWURoIhuvtMWmwdmbXsAk3CgkTCIiWSDdYDuq4nyxfz4pflK/KcuKE/AFlPWRZkVcabULmh8iuCITaccMZNiGSamMtNu0TjrOJ+H0nkM3t1gCHbp8CKQgcC5eWm/spzwgNM2HLoBINjJ8Iujv0vGcyfyYVqSaM/8UAn+D2/30AdkuxE2xR0eyiuYIYd7/CwD3m2/Sk1lni7zYTykm65U65GHZYsik+Hk2HIemeBxkJX22BQmRhCygnEDvYLfTlBDjVnTH8MUhAYoTKQTG5LE8XmfmniQSnIJP8r/EryVyi5dzur+gC09rJkDXICPPlnPhZ413BalBL1qWmTkqYrwLvEpBEdluoZ5z62Iuc6ydP3kLncrYR73VukZ4JpSYQN3GBjQRS1cILeoQpgQAfJK1HDYhQJMB2tGRVvfu6wNUAupuMXcZ2mecL4fBx/uaqAIX47vRk7MPbG52j/ECauZhge/H0ksVj+ZYbUO6gn/d5WyMxqnmyhn9sT9O0JPQY0UOWf8ciupsKGPAgV6fiIhaJpVc1HUXxVkhzvAM/Z1npsOVFFtdaCiWVMZmBJKjyqSAV4Fo0MdVqShSUAqaqBLYE8ZyHecH6QWXRKKpTUEnUKV1jf4IPVFcUgqdnfTm0Ognp5vkvbng5qESsTtO7gJxpRPaLJSV5/XDF5Q2vrj4e7yEGI6AyE3L/bMHuvftV7jA8T9ttqayloLxq4YOU0vMDeCnYabTmRDyQGOtzrNYfQ3eVmWkw==", 
		"answer": "25b1SdzXnDuoXvd1JdY3A4XY6KYuQvDugw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eh/g1/zxMm7dBmwF422GQrFxY3TtQLSCeuX7iZR+KV+MnU87/XCGsKrz/lIDhrtWqYeRMDYLe8tGxtSA1uq3535PINJNjpVm7ZURPPVDzyi/dcDeLOcu/XqBM0D9YjepRFM0kSLCi35aoZCz8DT7QNIygBM9g4l87Nw1M9nf1q7TwUO8jweMnGieS7RlHV2KuI6p+AOYpY83tt+MpTvYtOf2mfHS/NcYb0hFtpJ3I1r8mqER/S54VMu7Zh1G6KTjdVX5JSWmKRpd2Ivlw2Z9zoc7HWw49R1JkIJCZ9Mz2ZakqDo5LI1oGTa0pwRC3tR5Ugeeda6xymHq5xUrfX9rbIRrsDgwrwyZaFt42kydQihZnYFlvsMWlg1icWZTkTbTlj6fhWiKcoejz8D5nfj8obBt4eMzIUTAMlPZWp5carWANGhxw+iXBLVRc5ZpVzbuOJUH8j3wIZjU3DYDxNw4OzfU4CuNl8DwN3H6kdLwnZR/GrwPJMPA6t/3sU+HaDehNm+caMz4QEjjWnv/1h1xpFgryTUZ52zZBIBl9DkEkXDwWk1pmyvhfjy1mf5P/oOaes4i3Pbl3D4Zi/k034z/3R40Bwe0g2tRs4CWTEhcjUDeG40Gxx07DbhBEJPc/W6ElGLZSDwecM3/AKSO0DgI2/PhnG58vJhOXILOBRffg99kUU/hrekNw7GPVDPHWwoD8Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "A-B-C-D", 
		"option_b": "C-A-D-B", 
		"option_c": "A-D-B-C", 
		"option_d": "B-D-C-A", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040148", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fLfa39xoVjIl+dzVp053TS47b/9FoOg6FI5M6SdSwXd4RhzdTJ3uq30HlEc/ZWn4F/5pYaPPtGjCmlcZTyLvpnz2DABEr+dC20EGVgnT7Y1TwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EYj0KFILsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpDCkA/BoGq41Sa8F9lpr2vTw0f8JsVSC1oE1By51vUlefZ/281WXr40c+YXMoJZlivyQ0rQaPJRQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LwCXPPNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyYFs1cJeGADnMyw/rbDOZeP5ppE2LpO5UD/SvhKYWZnzgD1JkHLnnj/COKn435PGS0upz+ztxzFakJOsiF/cSgsU7DcmPmIHOXbsL1V0jjQH/x0gJspBVnJKP1BM35ltZVF1ciM+H52g==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzgFnr+YFgAFzg8zjTQ4/C3MLdV1iB1uLE", 
		"explanation": "25e3fJmzwg3r44AtVxDm1r3+J26QAG0DsXqARuN2dXLiQbTHNK3KwZIxDlKNhFp1snTUoqv0t1wJz7tU6oeefCsQc8tm25CN0un4x2NAJ89H2pN955MecP1TwXHtY9zSI/Yu3WeHKUz2bjyuRHE0mTjOj3gWrYC0+yi2TZogyQE61oR36NA1L8Oa16uWqEK+xhaX3neYS/1lH1DZpdyh/UKIpcIrsM6ZviDIyPrQjrja454KIg5HrI9wbRuzkegk+TggWNu5KBNF9aT3YFrpKCGwKkJd7sL33jRohpE9T2Y68xpUwopYYcx62JnwtT0+f9llAjKop1cA4JVyWx+fdbP4wHrt7lY2ZXYudspium0mpAOaZUZ7lmKdQi9U1IFl+pAKmgdqfGMAlmPzljaIhScwNo6CE9Nm7qH/UDg0tG9k", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only 1", 
		"option_b": "Only 2", 
		"option_c": "Both 1 and 2", 
		"option_d": "Neither 1 nor 2", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040149", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbk8sUvVF7mzfi/M2TcD20GqnGEErBgcWXmWaLMev6+yphjNVmKmVdisnLDsKbi/lEKnOhP4YvfVi0WbJ9niOOK3+Hz0X1Ec8lC2pR64do8c/pT2DS5YcDSL/AuwWjADkv0bjjiRDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGoDA5jkPC8LvqTrMwS9cRXhbWeQBQwWX9eIoE0iILyOhA==", 
		"answer": "25ysKJD/3Rbp9pElQV7hwPzrJivZDSIFq3rDcaxhfnLqWOfNaK3N3ZZlIk/LNmies4M4FAf7RXQwZ4Enrg==", 
		"explanation": "25O3fYPn2Vn59I0lVgv+wL3+OWffAGMFpmzDQaZ1ZGKjXamCeuX7ibR+MlKKhFc7/XCGkLHx41Ycs6ZS7M6tcSgaf8tcydKB1qS/8WFRNtQEso9n959fc/IA/Dy/eN3aLftg2ifC8e0UgaPAPOBMYMn8N3/R/A==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "It contains the scheme of the distribution of powers between the Union and the States", 
		"option_b": "It contains the languages listed in the Constitution", 
		"option_c": "It contains the provisions regarding the administration of tribal areas", 
		"option_d": "It allocates seats in the Council of States", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040150", 
		"question": "24GwbdHDwxzr+ocsV17myr3rPW6QIG0fsGuKRrZgeX7tFKjELsTwzZ5wZ1WazRtAoCaU8+ihyhHcrYPfeAWuGdGjMVcsFZCN", 
		"answer": "25T4eJDhxVnl8cU0Whuy5vLxJn/ZF3cFqnCNEqFhZDHrVbSCYOK+xZJ2JlDJiF1993XS46z+81YfiqZf7ICLfDtDcY0vx8SB0va31HBTJ9UGbjF2ToOICyfjn859zFMxkA==", 
		"explanation": "25STKLb8wRjm9otgRA2y9un+IW6QDGRRjn6HQKJnMDmyDfKSJ7e++oJhNVmEiGd10XnTsbGw5UYDiqwb/YaeZGIzbI5uxdKF0qT+1zFPPNIEn45064gcefVCwDjtfdqbIb5twXuSMwX/YQWzCHFjqD/0j25DqoKp/GeNR5oCzhw9mMcwvJFqbJ7FmZuG+F+9iwPC/3SEWqkkA0GVsMro/0udtL42hd+IsD/Z+PG5k+uT/tEfIgkSr4dtdxuzkegd8C94eMawYRNFscffb0f5KTy2MwcS94vr2WNs0Ic7ESkI+hZSwotTbtBglpHq/Ds+K8h4BSG/t0VUzptyHxiQNKmw1Sjn7FQqZn84JYVr/Dk9pE+/J1ptjmKIWThYm44rwt4ykBdrfHlBknfuhj7Lom2Obofqq5bvxdvkoa1msqwhaWqFJ13UV81UNOqXdC4y+fyLH6NRNqNpNC3zL8Fu7iz1JZLUyzEMxJk0J3KnxDick8D3NWD6uoG5j5RmFa0Udt7Dqd+/tRzubyfoIHPTWsXXVgbjW3XsxhpsuBYZxhUY7SLbB4R9/CMImj61T0JhkTOgY3rhgrZZqtHOdZs11Pjp0yYD2Px5jNv10RgyBxCzjGsDt5KaQRxzw0DeEdgAzEk6BLFBJITU82CUmXOQQm9Nfo7mALqTgyNOmvf5iyFesJ4dQYWaOQ3ShdBqiBWkFb1wQSfku7r3M/MBSmEi/L1jyeigtca+NfqqbGRqbBWiS/sZ/JMRZANsUSPSEiFZZariFokWRKB/wHDLmgVEQkNHDV/A67tIVArqq9fLa3jKYrgSBxDlI6cNFo7uR1TGOv/pxzaJEreZ1WSxUVcxRy6INbkC60fxdIiyGB27lmZn/I2lO19fQZMSMiP2en+1vO/DAhJ6dj9lJoVJN03AWAQtlzfCJfViz+t8kpyG0KIhMKtNnVEwbY0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A part of the Constitution but has no legal effect", 
		"option_b": "Not a part of the Constitution and has no legal effect either", 
		"option_c": "A part of the Constitution and has the same legal effect as any other part", 
		"option_d": "A part of the Constitution but has no legal effect independently of other parts", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040151", 
		"question": "25q2bdHw3hTn+ItgUxngwPjyMGXEQ2AUt2iGV600V3DtUK/LfeC+yJl1Z3GIn0Ny4XuGqrawtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRc+80QwTU5PPq5Rhpv8w51XjC8VyqHt2hXw==", 
		"answer": "24GwbdH12Bfr+8UnXR/+hfL5dWqQEHYQt3qPV7BnMGLsV67HevS86RVr6YsEdyaBXvsDju5M/Q==", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Rz55MUTXR37wOnmbyvxQ3EeoHaGRro0Z3nqV6+CYuz9woQxIVObgFp3znjPrbbk/kcam6FU553ffyRDeYR5zcKH2uH50E1PFMdKnoh77pNfdecAzX29fN3XL+1h3maJJET8JzizBWJ3nDjFnjx3poKp9i+yR853yQZymYl9rd80M5ej16GAqEKolgmR2X/RXLIkFEKcp9fo/1qMpcI3s42epTPP8a+5vfnd9NYCYwYSjYdycVq2jqlJ8TkEX9y8aQYL+PCQaEetIWiwIgIbtNnm0WFlx5YgU2505wZVloZbItd704rh/DcmOt9zGj2/401Th5tyWm6FSLO3x2ak8kAzcGgXa6dsrjU8sgLcOlFolWeKST8RlcBo8tEKhghmbnwAj3njizqfmSWOcpej+JT9ke38papwsrAoKkiFIUWYaoM3ZKHMZ0pz2PHbBadYc491EibvPsEr+HntKJeAny0F1ZkwPXjr8T6YgMT0LXb6pJv1gpRiFbQFdtLK59+lv1D7byznYWmbY4vnTQnkSjz53QolpwoqzDQT/GvXBsU/4SUI0j60TFdwgCj5LH2tmv5f5oOdbLI/1/zq2zcCnfp7moi31RM4Bwe3jGxQ8oWRW11IwlrfDcAUiEkvArBBEp/f82GajDbCTm8Yc9r/D6/HyiII5u3lhmQ9x4cHQYSLPhDVjZ4H3xaoQfJ/FXPlrcbKKf0BDx1szrpk2aHho8K+NfaqKCU4agmiVfsZ5JxdZD51Ew6dBGRcdLm6U5EbUvMPwXrJngJcXkNHMVLZ6ORISgHqqcXGLmPQZb4OA172a7IRU8z3Wk+PEvCnzDjARvncuEasRwQkRzeYJfAL6hXMdL/mJQe2n2136oH2PVJSQZcOfqqcHsUVYFaRz9x3uBL2HNo=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "The final goal of a stateless society", 
		"option_b": "Class struggle", 
		"option_c": "Abolition of private property", 
		"option_d": "Economic determinism", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040152", 
		"question": "25y2KIX71Fns+IksXQn7y/q/JH7fF2MFqnCNHuNIMkbGFJPqS63O7LhBC3nJon0721jiioS8t1sOmaFV7s6Mfy4Gc4Vj0ZCb0vf4yGdEN4ZQlcBx65QMaP1U2SmoNP3VJPdvjmeOM0qwZnmOC2ZxhjTfjXIWm4y4/Ca3XckjgCY3lZJ07Np8GNKS1quB6VmxhUaw2WuESrFtEhSYu8ro/0zcs4c7oN+I8SbUtPX1lrja5M1LYQFGtpx6bUjm14I8yx4Rcu34KAFE8u3RbRitJSusKQEQ8Mij13pthpImUWAg/RxHjtgWTulR86rQhXI/OY1+HTyvpExUi9R5RweEca6r2WfqrBU9cHYiYIwtuiw8tQfcKVp62nyTXj9ZnZAwvvUooCVPVFt53HnmwiyfgXGab9Pi5YS8iu6wr6lz/bEzPE+JIUWCFowSYfPUKCdi2OaWArJZc55qGCzhfcEm+TS5IZqYhHkr4vgUCkXJ3R6g0szmKnCoupz+zsB+Ef8EP9bL4N+u8FPBITfpJD2aaM/9TwH0Wn30kw9rs1gxwCRQ/WzRHJA/9CMJ3mq4TARtnDPla26ogqcc5YTOa4Y0k9vtyTsflrRRkdv4wQ98ZAu1nmtKppGaQUgP7EfFG8AFyBBuGLwIB9aWyirWkXmQQ3kfeszvQamDzDxclqP0gGB+q9APW4jOKxDNj54yx1e+FO9qUGv7rZW5KfQcGSQP9bxi3uS1ot6yev2YbilqKCLwGfxN8ptVe0J9HhmHRWQPIPjuFt1eAaAPkjWK10cIBz9yVAOVrJVKv0vc82tbL6o4Rf45WHS31Q==", 
		"answer": "26GvbZ/nyFT5/p00Wl72xOS/Om2QLW0HpnKBV7E4MCC6AP6APoQ5fQNiIevKHakF0/ET8w==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rwr7yvO/Om2QKmwVqn7DRaJnMHTtVaTWa+m+xpkxCVOfzQktvjb6rfSpowpPjb1PqYeLMDUCbctsx92E0ur0wXUBPMgEsIF8pMhJMKUZmW3vDwKW89rYIxRVWSi8j9UBOQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "twenty-sixth day of January, 1950", 
		"option_b": "twenty-sixth day of November, 1949", 
		"option_c": "twenty-sixth day of January, 1949", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "040153", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbk8sUvVF7mzfi/M2TcD20GqnGEEqx2enTgQK7Ua/6+wIQxKVOdzV528HnCqqD0t1oBz7xT7M6vYicCc4ljzZCd2KTjzHQBEMlKiZR78I8LdftOjDKrNP3VJPdvkS67dRWhMHTsOTKCFnIMtWSrhU2bzgL44PXD", 
		"answer": "25C7Z5/83BDpt4kpUBvg0eS9NJCKTNMJC+0VVJa5HWZewQ==", 
		"explanation": "24e9aZWzxRHvt5UyVx//x/H6dWzZFWcf43aNEqJ6aTHwV6/NYeG+3ZJpM16GglAhznj64ZL1uxMbh60b+YuQYC4GPoRpiPmH0+32iF1oEeN2rrky65xfaPxP2TqlYJibHPBr1n6SIlbjbjazSDB2kT3fj3oa6IW6/DOzFNs5xFUlmZVr5cEsAJWs1uTT1A+aukTC1WjRXLVhLVqYu92/7lHe2d1eRwLHFK1HGj+j2/MUcg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Preamble of the Constitution", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Liberty of thought", 
		"option_b": "Economic liberty", 
		"option_c": "Liberty of expression", 
		"option_d": "Liberty of belief", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050101", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t0cKnaUb1cyqfisMcMtgzpC6w+XjwWJ9cYZNlMBm7J9fVfpExTyjNPfULu16x3qVM0z/aXmuDXd6nTffj28WvIu64WeSWt4+wVU7hcd5rc45ONKN2Lya50P4iQDCz2+QXLh3XRSKvMOh50KO4JY39dmFtHL6+fHrk/vS/p4tZwxXrYdralSyq6Y67CssVMWxZgYL2M2KXVrMIyusNQoU98yjwnsp4pBpf1t01RJEh4ddY9I/lozsuXIgN99rBjb6nwZ1yZ1zUVeZcv2LxGnw5UYDNzo8ZJktvyU6sgqSaFton3nccG53kYRu7NENnAttPWBG3EX0gyuOk1nNPJHm6IHplu2wtLFmsoopLUiBdVXLFoMTcfOAJWZhz+3bAqgcMpEnFiX0ONAj+TftYJeZ0DcKkM0oKjf04CuNl97JN1m0hJrwjdw2G7lAItnAqdijsUjCbCbvNW7TYcLiXAawTn73xQslvgtqyTMVqGHXGpt69jlPVmkbmA4TbXbwQz5YgfIRgg==", 
		"answer": "25yRKJ793QCoM596CAFrxx3aStwiPM62Ow==", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhfTxNmTCEWcStz+BV6B1ZWLmFLPKa63L+rYxLk/JjFU7+3jCprbk5UYMm6FZ5YvfZSwKcYUvx9bJ3urzwWJVIdNHjolw6J9fb+BB2Di+OJTVJfd6xmuSZ1H4YnmICnl7mnHVi3IWrIao4TW0TZo2zgxypZN5+c1wfNmQy+iH4Ej4tRKDyH7RS7xqUVCcptq65FrctIo99fiDuD3VtJ/FlMTdw8oKdg1fuohrI3KV16EauCk3Q9qxawYL8PeQRUatAhrjBgMf/M/o12Yp1pAsW2wm5hpCwpdeZ4Bn04rp/A5yCsNjGj36rEIA9IB9SxKFSP/4337h8hUDN1wuYY9/vTk8rgHcJ1I+qX+dWClCqMIr/NUalBFweC9UlHOgqzGPiWSBPLXm74XuhPz5r7cj+7BnJ06UdV2YRIgPcL/UZ2h0iuiVTadbIZpiGifoKZUv8Tb3J9aHyzgZ1cpsb3bp8GqNmsi1KnG7p5fqztB5VLEPIpHN6N2y8EjPZGPzKHqbcovgVkjjSn/91wslsQoqxWEE4GeYDox78D8Mine/RwahYEWOY+t590LBVz8zHJeb", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050102", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t0MdgL5S+oeQfjFDcY0v3NiMl835wHhAPYZnlY5h8JMLaeBJwzPtYNzaNL5v3n6MPgXkaHmpDHU0hyXXnnlF6IKp8Ge1W853wQUimo577MowOZeW1+iH4Ej4lQeP2TucSbNqFEbZocHo/0uZ4Jc2vMKD8Sbe5ubwjvfB+dsYXgZhq4drZla5mbxJ0QNibcaAYBcL5eHCc135Lzq6ZwEbueLt0n1ohosnXmUh8BpVwo1ZdoB82JT9/CY4Oo15ATKuplcAxYFoHxaaZ7L4xWbt71t/YX85d4N5sz88pBzcKVp62n+ZXj5YgI9599UK1RBrfHsAkXf5wj2OwGSMbYbq+YX4xerp4K1r9+MAJleFJ1LVU4MIJbzGZ058zuCaTa9Sc4tvEmLgKME77jzFLqqa6DEE09FgIHGn4CKc0t7hOHG/vpf3msc2E7YWM9+F6Mm4plmHaDCuIG+WJsj7Sxr1TGi6VYojUnfp5L0Gj0kymLMVxA==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz4g3r44AtVxDmiNS/NGXUQ1EFomuGX6Z6ZDzKfefDfOi+yphjNVmKmRt6/HKGkLHx41YCiqZPpKe2MCsQPoVg3JCd3+G3x35TIcNHjsB3/IoTffpB2DSiepTdL+wu/XqBM0D9YjepSVk2RRW3USlgFsPeQTI3JyI/Aw==", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhf7wJ3nVAHZRomzDRqtxMFjtUK7DYK3dxpliM1WdmE9y/XiGt63x4xMOn7hX8M6Lf2IXdo4v28SIw+HkhHBTNoZKlZQy6p8ceedTzS+keM2bIe5+wmeDJkf8Ynm0CjBgnDSWmX1brcO29Cm1Uch31Bpygo99rd0yNdiRmbyW+l+xkgmQ1X6CBP1lAhSNvcuxq0KOpcI8vN+IsibX7bT4nvXa/tcYdg1AuoI/YUL8g6AMuAk9X9ymaR4L9uvGZEbjLS2tM05dxcXf2Ed9x5YsUGw64F9vq8NfcYBy2ovr/DE/Ld9vFif6oVFUh5pzS1eVe6+q1Wvw7Ex/cGI7aYtksm03pAydPUd72n+USWwpoIV57NkNmhZ6PWBG3F/uhjaK+SWGb9Piq5f1ge3i4Lx74rEiOlKJOlKYQoUda/PUL2IystyVBKlSc5BhVwvoOdwvhXn7JZWVyioIkM0oKjfr9T6Nl9+1MGu5v4f9i8c2G7EML5HW/cqjtU+HdivoLXjTcsPxGQ7/XXH9wU5suRsp3SUV+yLWB50/+iMBhz6kQUEkgTPheHmy2v5e/5bOfoIi3LX50zsflrRsmonl3QkzVQ2+nj9CvIDfW1ld313CEd8OwRpuGLwAANbc83TWl3OQSn8casfkBKzHwTUIzuv0zkZyqZUcW4GLIg2bhdhm4Rm1CPw5VHOtqYjgffoAHnE+//Jlw+Ck9W/koKc3h8C3+FvzOgaY1Ds=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_b": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is not the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_c": "Statement-I is correct but Statement-II is incorrect", 
		"option_d": "Statement-I is incorrect but\n Statement-II is correct", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050103", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDx3upey9iu+FIh3zxNygo99reEyON6e1+iw50Orkg+WyW+YR7MkFFmJutmt+VDctIo99f2Moz7S9fn8lOyT5NFLYwxftpI/alWomOgd8C94ZMa9ZxwL/uKQSFrpKSnvKBxduc7wwnVryos6VSV0+hpRwpBCY9R2xdjrsnIjKs5iVSe/sUkAxpp4HxSZermxxGHr7kY+Zjoiccp5tCQ7qhzcLl1q3VeSDB5UlZNk8JBRp005PVNOvWT0izyHhSXcPJzlq5T0gKjZrr1q861nCk6OJkjRQpgIbLzOZ2N3y+WITbFVJ5cnAyrjfdQq8TDqM5+b0XkCwpklPGPm9iaQgcX4PGuu853/ztpzA/8TItDR7Nj3pFTGdWPgM3jTaMTgGRjxXWi43AgloxAgiBQe4W3WSIZ5tQQDmnexCzr00owarrfJTn4Q4YXRIIc=", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/IXnFBi5RoWqXErd8dTHxUabRYeO+wIQxIV2Fnl45oLDgcbBIQ1kx++Pbe7CGMA==", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+cUpQV7m1+j6dWrDQ0MDt3aAXqY0IjHsUufWZui+4Jl1Ll2HzXh0/GXSqrHl41oAgehf5ouMMCsNeo5qzJCM2vT403RTc9JMn8BC5YgTdfVNyTO5NMDUYP9qw2eUZ0z+czb9EHhx1ATYg3NY6Iy9tQ61UNM2gBs3gcdr+ckoOcTf1rrT7V6shwSO1WiZCLNhBhSKoc+87lDcr4x4ocifvCGb9fr92vvc/toCdgFdsZU/Ykj8nrxJ/C89XNv0bhtfsdjeXVrfJSmwKABd8Nij0HVl1YdpX2w39QpVh8N3cNR61ZTh/GFwMMsqATu/421Ow519UVe1e7OrxGHw9UE2enRrYY9ssD51tgaIIBRqkm7cSiNDmYF/998X1QtlPWBS3HXogzGMhXbPdZ2j/4j5xe3oqap3+60gaVKUNEjdRc0TY/PUL2Iy/+eSAqgcPJknPiziNNRivBjrNJ+X0zxNg5ksLm70tC6WhcO1LXK185H2gNB/ALYPOMKF4MX3pFTOcmPzJHqSdM+uGQf+SjC40k5nvhQpiCIf5nbdBZlz9DkEkHnwXUxh0ibiY2qk1r1U64yJep1x0PTinTAV2P12i4n40Ag/QgD7hHEDpoyaD2xO31jfH8ACyh1uA7oNDdbG+3me1WLYTjwdbcf5E+iVxi9H1+70gGV8q5kBW8yBKlnPgttm+AW0EvR9UGn588b4M/hVHnMjtvJzz+uupc/7Z/anI2gnahSzUOFes4FZbUJ5GAfRSWRbaL3uZo8bUulL13ve1w9JVD9dChre/q4NT0S+osGIfWvTZvEIAV72a7ZFANr5WkKPOfSuwSPFB6uJh0L+XEsrTT+PL7UJpQH/aMz3PAOhlnt38M/iclhPV8MBNSLkZyuurLeLAgh6fmw2OI9Ec0HcThRkhDvRLvZjz763v0/WO8G1VPMhHVOP6HI=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050104", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDfOi+3YVkIhybiFx64HLPraKw41sKz6tU542aYDZDcY0v9JK82e34yjFONYZ3joFm4YkjPrRJwn25fNGbCfBqx2+OZ2b/aSqpDWRhgDjZhCNqpr+11Gr7YNIygAE3hIo40YoJMt6Q1+ic7g2LkgeW2WitCv1zEEfZtsan+EaS4JY39ciAoTra5/3jn7jH+N8fIiFcu49+I1Kv16lJ/i88VNq1fBtE/6TfZxT+NCm3Ih0h9+muljRdzodpaGc9+xEGpYxAZ9J9253qqHIzPsMqETapt1ZP3tRoVxLWZ6m5xG33oEI3cGguZJktqCUw4RyIKUB72myTWilDmo1u8MQK1Qdic2FPiDbkhyyfkmqWPIfr7sDJi+H/rvlf/IBqaQG0PVmYRZkdcbbTZ258isCVCa9dc5dmASemKd0rvCvwJ56Any0CkMolLHLj8WqfgML4eXGyttL/i9BzBr4UP97L1cWT/RyHVSvkYWmWdMa0ZUrFQXX33U5qsVgW3CAE7XHkSsl6+y4Ck26xWldhgWfuY2jhmbBQ88Kda48l1uas3ycE2PV0jJS3wRM1SAr7mXpRoI2LQE5GyEeWH8MDhAgtHaEIBpPVsnmTh2TZX3MfdsvlPaa7zQRHzaP8j29k/58IFZiGKVnInt8yzRq0D+k2RifqoZD8M7wUCGs6//J42aKgpc/7dvy2PmApe0X1xFw3W/ZEMSqTvQj1//cIQQ==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25T4YYKz2Bfp+JcyVx3mhf/6NmrFEGdRgm2XW6B4dTGyFKPHfe7swJV0NBygg19y8zqGt63x4xMGnOQby4aeYiMXPop8iNHJr9H5zX5Pc8lC2rNm5Y4ab40A3jy5fNHJYOpmz2DAJgWIQTy5AWJ1gDjZhDxZrsOI4SavUclOgCE6n5Q4/dozKt6M0KedqEm9hwqRnGyYXLUkBUOW9dqg4k2bs9h4usOI/XLV9fn82vfVsMoDZ0hRsJNxd0mlzOgI9i54Rd+7JFJf6PTVIVvrYDisKwcJ4Ivf2Ehn5MIgTik3+w1Uh4BCIsJ21ZnxrzdwC8VvVQa0qktOh7NzSRKEerC93nyk41QxNX4udp5/szR1tQeZaEdqm3+ZX2xGnIV5+9EK1RBreC9TiHf0h3+Mj3OKbp3u7o7olqjzobdt/bdnLUSTIU7XT80IbbaAEml7xefbJKgcBqxGW2LpM5U69Dy5L4Kc2itN2NguKzun4CKc0tnwK3ezp53rh9V6VLYOItTC+8KjqRzIc2PiLnOHb8XhXAywSmTxwBpguRsgiC4WqGOYG51+4ShNl23wTlFlgCbueHmkkv5e88Kad4tx8PriziYZjOFslpT5lCEyewqYzXZQ8o2RTFNd31HVCo0FwQovGacEVLfS8WKEkX/eTDwZcI7SE+il8Wxp1+H0imp8rdxOQYSLbAnTmN81zVfJNPNwWmmtp4C5DugUHmE/g/J5y/7htc++e7O0PmAsagilXOsZ55oRECR+FQ7PBDBGb7buWZtecvROxnDZ7kdOSG0JEU3Du7oNXBelpNeSLmXQZv1cGhbnI5oLF8f5QAfpMPWs2jHdD7CS1U6tH0oqWnqJKbVN9wLjb4DmZBy102lqucDiIFReSYYZKGfyeWS3ouOXAwN6bDgkPI9UOkvcQBVkgDbGerlGgKISeRssT+iBHFQThBBbljHcVRhEvkheS7KiDBMzIqwFM08Q2TKmUageShmKiDVKnF+byjasPfULIkwgfmCWz0rylJ8mi/fswoiEDtHwLKkS3YM/JopVYNrfDBsdluDrr+LvA348BXk3LP3LX/fCtQ/CCs20tsbIyBx3i4sGP1A1ZTaNyazN8S5oPJkNL3lE/WcRqYr7bAKj2IYZ9l9mQ0Hl4VTwSGgv9gN2aJb5eZ3SJY/l/15TD2TTWPlXkPk4zjjlIdrCJBgqEyM0nRSfNtvExDiWOanogLgHDBesl43OV5hk+Edrx9mhg01Or3thim7wAmLVcO7o+15AKn1sC7meAx1fg1cj1iuk10HtOc+onuYdhrUB/7oF5B75ryR4mx6DSQrnbXfj37aXuSbStkJhz793SXSmGRc2zSY3CzIUepodAr9vWM0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "all Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050105", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDbOLr3ddQNUiAjld+siSGoqv0t3Idm6FY5YvfI2IMeMt7wNXJ/urzzXBPc+VLlJNm7Y4KaP1Pwn2sZtGbNOx7yzG8KXn+RnT9JWJgnTLajzwE6Ia25SisUcgkgAE6k8dI7NowNdaS3KaHqFm3xgeG0XKFCLNhBhSKoc+87lDcqYwsuo2ZuTebwfrwlfaT/9hLSwZWtodDbXnx1+go6j4xUsSxKEEL9eHRbUetNyG3L04e8crt0XF6hosnHX088V9DmopFdsl90dj3qDMkOt4qGjX6t0xFh6FyVhiYNLK+kEHq5Fw+SXQIKMotnT8hqAyQLRQs2m+ZTSBC1Jdi6thZkBd3fG1MlWXojzqFlCWAetPt7pe8lvzxtLxwzq0DZAHAFE7MX44QYPOTZ2N3y+WITbFVJ5cnAyrjfdwg6DzrLpeYnysIndgkJWL04CecnNm1NmP6p5frnN1iG60JM8KHKhstK31hCqpeCuvyqDuH7A==", 
		"answer": "25T0KLO/kTqq9oskEjqwwNsiClI665YbD0Io+R14+A==", 
		"explanation": "25T4aZ/3kTqq9pclEl7xyu/tMGjEQ0MDt3aAXqY0IjHmWbfNeejs2tdlL1nJvVpp/n/HrqD+4xMbgOgj6IqSeTZDd4V7x5Cd3+G38X9IPMgElYYyzZQbdfUMjDK/NNHINP9swmeTLwmwaTyqRGNglSXTmTxZpsOo4CSzFM4y0hgh1oZ26Yg/M9mb0Lya50OrxgeRnHKFCKlsGFqSpo6u4lfl4LYwoN7B8RPJ4P36lv2Top4McAlcq5U/d0yz17gG7y8qQoigZ1Jf+eGQUVX/LCGiKgsT7ZGjnnUghpYhWCkk+whDkMNCbYBy0pXtqHI5MdllVSeypgR1yZ1zUVeZcv2R3mzt4RUxcG1rdp5sqCgm+k+dJlA+0mnVDDhZkcB78ccch0R3ci9Fj2LhgDOCk23Pcpb0q5PohPz1s4Vtzq0FaUCOMRz8FowOYPPDKHVgz+qPTadPc751AyvlMdBur3W5L5jUyzEIkNY0J3L1tCKYnMm5eXe/v5Pti8c2ALBAItnAqc24olHGdSruLz2cYIv7S0jzR3321At29xEriDUY7SLdEIBs4SQDmT6jXUVwlzSgY3rhgrZZqreAdoE/k/rqnRsenP1537L5lBIoTwGpzWhMoICMAxxu30DfHcEChFpuCLEAGIWR5WSCnTbEQ3lNdsDiBLqJwiAIyOa8j2V3qoMaWImAOFnShMoj2leiBL12Uyf5oIO5KfkHGG049aB4z/7huMz7YfuhbGYlYQmjUPtM9ptFKBFvEB/YFmRAZvi6XphedO5G3XuKmAEIbnFNDFuOnTOnxiYPh+NtI/aNAtJfuA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "B, C and D only", 
		"option_b": "A, B, C and D", 
		"option_c": "B and C only", 
		"option_d": "A  and C only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050106", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQBW0StmzDXaU0UWP3XaTOa62tiZh3Z0iBiBtS/HLPoquw1FwBnLxS/ZuLeS0NIckXJNqeg37QQCYLcy0O5PR9", 
		"answer": "25awaZ/01Aqq/otgRhb3hfjnPHjECmwW42yXU7dxYzHsUufWZui+/Jl4KFLJgl0723jCqqSyV1bMJBaWAx+/c9HxDaaCGQ==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpMUkVx/+1r3oPH/YQ2EZonGEV7A0eX+jQK/HLu/x3Jl1Jk6AiEg3snjHrqDjuxMOgawb5pqXdTBDf5h/zdOdxKT4wjFVO8MEn5h7944WcvMA3ymsYNHIYPFojnqIIgXFaTCyCjB7knH/hHhfqcOS4We9W9ki0xAh1oh2rdo5M8WY2Kaa8kS2gUaNzjuQRKlhA12Xso6840bcs5YqoM6ZpCDetPv/2uzb9Z4KbhpXvoJmI16vg6kL9CMrWc2wKAFf8PDVchYGH9nyVozYCcR+s7/G5Rvg", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Changes in the existing states of the Union of India", 
		"option_b": "Admission of new states into the Union of India", 
		"option_c": "Establishing autonomous regions within states", 
		"option_d": "power to establish new states", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050107", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRj444wjXhuyyvu/IWPVQ0sfp3aCXONXf3/wQK7We/n3xpkxIlGZgkx+4GWGt631t2MOnaRS6IOafjZDaoQvydSE3vC3ynRWc9VQm5R399oWcuBPjCmlcZTuLvdhwC6PIQXZaT20BS82MuR+NCgsnhnYbiu9NglorQ==", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpccBiAaT3Fa4aztG1WFkiWom", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpcUvVF7mzfi/HGXUCmMf41yMXLBgeWX2QK7NYK3525Z/M0/JmVN+skbHsan59l4Kgbwb/YaaMDIMaY59iMSGl+XzyXhVc8hBjcBh8JsLeecAxTO5e5TPKPsu+2CJKEuwaD/9LX5wnTCWvnRfu8O6+Su0Q8l3xhog1pNw6Ig1MtSTzLua50P4iQDC0n6GCK5wEECcpo6840KI4JU9p8jNvz3PtPvrk//a/t8HbhESr4dtdxuzkegd8C94ZMa9ZxwJAutMnJY1YqODL9cnodpw2w==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Article 3", 
		"option_b": "Article 2", 
		"option_c": "Article 1", 
		"option_d": "Article 4", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050108", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQAWMCqmzDVKxmMGXrUefQa+LszpZ/LkaImVJ0/DbJpeXZ+VcGjqYb+pqeZCcQPop8iMKM1Ov6yXRPN8NA2oJrpI4XebRz2Dy5ccebEvth3GmBKUzjZi20C340tz7bh3VFu4q0+3j5e5QY/sxnHMv+3UTTuOkKtw==", 
		"answer": "25mxZpbm2Ar+/oZgUxD2hf7qOX/FEWMd43eMX6xzdX/mXbPbLLPGIthBt/3TodsREKT8F40=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHAxRj+8pZgYBv91/r+O2LDAnYYrHHDcax5fXjwR67NYK3szJR+KlGMg19+9jbSq6Cw5VYAna9a54eFcTYKcYUvx9bJxPD20HRSc8RFiYV2pJURPPhJwjq4fcfPKf0uz2CEZ0blay2oFnF41DnZh3NRrY2+/DOiGJo2zRo8kcd3+cA5LpeZ2KuH51+rxBuwzBh+hrhWHQgkwTDz2AU=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Administrative convenience", 
		"option_b": "Linguistic and cultural homogeneity", 
		"option_c": "Economic considerations", 
		"option_d": "Preservation of princely states", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050109", 
		"question": "24GwbdHn1Avnt7liZxD7yvO/Om2QMHYQt3qQbuE0Z3DwFKTKYf77x9d4KRydhV4723jCqqT+t3AAgbtP4JqKZCsMcMt7x5CA2eD+x3BVNoZQkoUy26UgQ8t/8wKSS+ubL/gu52CELkSwcDG0CHU0hjTVhXtYoZmy+yD7QNIygBE7gIJq/s18NdOa17ya/ES9lUaN2juYXK4kEluXptqh/1aZrpZ4ptmMpTfItkc1lJ2Hk6hnEmqLrWMzgOw=", 
		"answer": "26C2YYXqk84cDEmNEqEu2byz2vjrcLc=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt7liZxD7yvO/Om2QMHYQt3qQbuE0Z3DwFLTHYuj93ZJ1Z0iGzVNy9X7KqqL44xMbh60b/ICWZDtDcY0v4d6N3uW3xWIBMoZXk4516J9fcvVUxTKjOJTMKPdiyy6BK1b/Jzi+D357gz3TjntfpoT74S++FN4+0wE7mIRsrcs0PcWe2ryW+kSrkg+BzzuQRrkkGFCcu9qh/0qZs8I3s42ZuTeb/fr9k+7a9MsKbkhBq4drZkj8gKEd8CM2Edy8bVJI/vHedUb0Yk+8/53THkorrg/+9LQmdlI=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "un,it,y", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050110", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sU0Vwz/1r32OyvzDG4ErnHDc+NjeWXrFLPKa+TsiZR+NU6Mjk879nPVoLf550cGgKZIqYeRMAEMcp5ixpCrlcq7iOpGjn+tMRlRlqBBp0M=", 
		"answer": "24C2YZ79kS3v5ZcpRhHgzPjseH/VEXAYt3CRW6ZnMHXqRqLBeuHniZZ1KlWHhEhv92TDp+Xy7hMsiqZP+4+TMCUMaI59xt2M2fC7hFBTJ89HloUyttc6ceRP2zi/Z5TrIexix2+NIkvkJy2yRHFwmTjCynJTv8Oo4SavUcl7gDQggo574c18b5q73Kmf+w2vjxKKnHiZSbNjFEfZvMDo7luVs5Yxu8rNoiba4PHq3bjR/8sFZglAtoNsLxuJmaEd4Wo5X8z0QRxf9OPCaED0bQGtIwccucLwlnpm0sIoHXsx5wpKlsNZZIBy2NjluyA1OsBvGyf6oklPyZM8TAOXYLirkmlQjUi3OAAvdz9m1hBQ3H8=", 
		"explanation": "24C2YZ79kS3v5ZcpRhHgzPjsdWrCBiIFpm2RW7d7YnjmR+fGZ//7yoN9PhyIiVZy/H/Vt6Di8ldPjbEb/YaaMAEGcJ99ydzJ0OvhwWNPPsNKjsBO6qYRXeZUxT6hcZSJYPtj3mGXIlfjJy21ATBElSPag31brY2vtTO0FNszzRwm1ol9+ogvKNaL3LvT4UOsiUaW1H7RfbNtHlrZusjowk2YqYMEu/GDkCDP/ff1n7iAsNoOYwRB/5F2d1P8lKAI9i09Qoi9ZlJf+eGQY1v4LiyiNQcY6ovi2HApyZYhWHt09QxWh4BCcYB80NjhpDsjK8RkEnOpt0VUwoc8SB6CfLS2kHzs5RUKe3Mka8pium0crwuVKWhwpmWpQiVFjcBq8NRZvAp3eGhSlWL5wjCNwEyBeJriq4nvxemwo7Zt8aY3PQGUPV3MFogRdbvBNG5oz/rbGa5Zc5ZpEyvwNMYn/jX8YJiVyywf1ZkvKTfz/C/ZnMzhMGq085P3ipR/AKxAJsPA+s6lpl3TaCzvYXmWddv9TQ2wW3T9kwpsoR032ygE8SLXDsls4SwZm23yDMdEvz6sxANbGROrL7qUxg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Article 2,Empowers Parliament to admit new states", 
		"option_b": "Unity and Integrity,India is not a result of an agreement among states", 
		"option_c": "Union Territories,territories directly administered by Central government", 
		"option_d": "Article 3,Deals with changes in existing states' boundaries", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050111", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3AAgbtP4JqKZCsMcMtgzpCg2eD+xTFGJsdWm45m4Z8MPOBIyX25ccbJKeph3GeBKwX5aS24A2J9gCiWi3JS6IC0+zOyWs8yxFU3jo5r+c0yP9Lf1q7T7Vu9lB/Cz2+QXLgkBl2Nvcemq1eUpcIRu8mEsDybwfrwlfbv/u0fYxxXsoNxdxuVvvI19h4wVIiXZxxY5e3EdEDkLybjKAhd7cPmlkFnz5YsWSkH4B5Sh5AWZdVyxJnqqDc1LI1+HTKu41BIwtR6WhOTZry0kG/r9lAte3cua54tvyw7rwCIaFVyjm6ODDhZkcBp8cIdkBZwPWBG3HP4iyyfiWuIPID36pT5lqjnqa1r/bYzaVWIMBzbWYMPYL3UZ2h0iv2TCOZfPJFkEjDoONFu7y34NJOH4zcx3u4oJnTvtCWf0tn9PCWpp5Pti9lzGqsTdtbM/8658F3FbjXkYXSAKcrmXEjzQG7q1g1x9dfdWgMbzbzu6MCTrmrO4UQ=", 
		"answer": "25yRKJ793QCoM596CAFrxx3aStwiPM62Ow==", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhfTxNmTCEWcStz+BV6B1ZWLmFJfDfOH3yJp0KUjJhVposmLOpuXg+EQKnehP5s6ZfzAOPoVq35Caw+XjwWINc8dIjoVgpJgQafpEzS+kcceXYP9gyi6DL0T+YDz9F2R1gDSWhH1brZD74i6vXNUi1FUmnoI47scyL9KRzeic7g2sjgPCz2+QXLh3UV2Xo8Gk/UaY4L42icOiv3LP/PG5lezb9cxLaglcu8o/cE+9g60E/SQsEeGdKBtYseffc0boIzzjJh1d7cPmlldmyJE9VH0h4BZJjMNZZIBn3p2kiTw5K8huVQCuolBF1NR5UQSDZrirkHzs5RUrcGg5bJ5iriQ0rU+VJkB7nXmVWDURlY5vvtMWmxBqc3pFmDblmjaYlGCBf5aj5Ia8lvzxtLxwsrQuPUmJOxzMXohcZrzVKXNg06XbDLUcJ5diVyTjOdA8/TW5J5mC2isD3dwuOzfk9SSXndm1OGmutoC5ncB3ALpANN7X7c6loxzQaDfpLmiHJt/8XEjjW33s1h0i9xsqxjIV5naaOamG9gx5JtShs6cVIah4yg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050112", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t2MdirtS7YuRZGIMeMtGxtSA1qT+1zFTNtdRk5J34NoLc7RBzyntfdqbIf1twXyEJkvzYnmqDWR81CXejzxAoYas5me+TMolxQYhk4M479F8KN+amauc5k69lAiH2DuCXLxwFBSVsMmh+E+dtJcqsI2auTfVtOb8mffe/dsFZgFcuMZ+I1m1m6RJ6i80UNyxbFJf/qTEaVGtISS3Ihwc7cLs2DRmwMI6SWgg8V9EjZZYZsFh3533/Cc+O8h4VRKot01Dy5E8DFeZcv2s2G2kw1oxZm4icZ95tSI7nQGvPFVqn2aZQjgRvakxwt5ZoQxmPV9BjnrpgzKOjnHPc5Wjwo74jOmwrrxm9rBnPU7AOl7MV4QSJafIIidxxeeICKhIc5BhVzbuOJUt8zf6JYSa2j1Nw80hO3Kn+C+em975OHGvoZe5jNFwG60FdtjL/dm4tEnEaC3mYXzTZML4VUjiSnD5xwth9wwqiDUY7SLZBJ165ywZl3G+CUti0jT0bWik1rBd54edP5s/1/D+nRMCjP17k563h10zQUSvhXoDkYuRXEhG2UHCF8IJ+AcSAoMJHZXZsmKQ1WLYTjwea8/iBKWCzThbmuT4mGRz/5EMWpqLbBDIxd80zVeyDu9rUGT56kygbOOKd3MZJ8Wz0K7bGu0=", 
		"answer": "25u9YYX71Auq3sUuXQyy7NS9O9OCNxOLPx49360zHrMDNg==", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhfv+OXjVQ2AUoH6WQaY0ZHnmFJfQa/73zZJ/MxuazUl+8XnLrqD+81IbhqdVqYiQYmICPolmxNzJ1Ov50HRMI8pFjol849ocdPVOyzi+NMHVJPt8jk+SM0zzazz9VzB9h3HYhWgWqoyu+yP7VsN31B031pFx6N8vfNiZmbyb7Q27iQiB2WmfTbkkAkCYocvo50abqZE0tNmYozeXtPX3nrjH+NtLUhpXrI97ZlWo16sI9mo5UsuxeAYL/vaQc1HnJSu3ZxoV9tjmlmJgw5U6HVU6yBF1loJCZ8122IyklRtwNt4qFD+prARGxphvWleUcb65xXvhoHswNXslfMp/uTwgqB2ZJVFwjiuaQz4Rm4J//9kXnApkPXtImTbjjTGYhWubPJzlq5T0gKjzr7dg97EpLEXAJkjZQohcabbHLnR+y/2OH6McMZphGDDjfdwg6Cv2JIOX1jcKkNhgLX7r+GqLl8H0LWC+84b2zsB+Ef8BOsXA+8qjuVPJISznYW6HZ9/xGQbxQnnrkwxgsRc3zWEC7WHXBYR6+ykEkHnwXUxh0iXpYHDt1qpU78K+bYsi2vHp0yZQkPVr34/4lA85QQGpzWtLt8SMTlFKjUDZXtkPwUk9GLUVEdbd92qfhnrRX2kfeo71DqaExj5G3+exiG5v/5UWRZ6LPwrShNlmwQOiQetwUHD+6JHwKfQcBCQtuqFhz+6oscO+cbO0KXcjYB71n40Fgyr3pSPBsuSuKbrfKA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050113", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb75SisUch3zxNygo99reEyON6e1+ij6V+0jweP2XWFCKlrUVWVocu6q1eUpcI6utiDtTPJ/fHq2vfVsNsTaxtGtoh4I0iolrwM62oxQoi6ZwYL4vHSa1HuNGi3KE4J8c6j1Xtn1YcnSSk78l9SioYWY8Z105vwuTZwLNlrATapn0oA9ZF9TBiYNPWKmTKk3Ft/VGg/bIlhuW1m4QCaaEB2nyu1QihYlY4r3d8XhhBqaXpUlXnuwjqGkGqYeYHwq5T0gKjAoatv+6IqLE+UdUjXFoAdbraAJG9zxO6eHuZIPN90AyPyOJUs8yz3JJeG1jwekM4pO3/o4T7ZgMjkLGyoupz+zsB+Ef8DOd/W7MWj8FPBITfpJD2AcsrgXBuwRnLu3AJzshxnvOjaqYXmMQbBKhlM2d+XFQ==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFgjO8rPV+nXo8G+gZITEyovIU=", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+cUpQV7m1+j6dWrDQ3YZpj+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+yIJlL1ObhEh+4TbSq6Cwx1Idg6Fa5IuRZGIXcctpx8KEl+ry0zFSJ8dQn5My64hfffhUyS/tYNzeYP98y2+TawXyaCyzAHFmnTTFynNE6I26+CKoFNUxgAE6k8d99cEvKN6R3uiA/EysgxXCy3KFQLJxBRSNvcuh+QOfr4wrsMOZjTzn+sb8m+vc/p4CcUhTs5VwI0+ugq1J+SQ8Ecu7egBO8vDceBToODivJgcTucrwllV70osqUWx0p19Hl5debdJ6xZ33/CY4Oo1aFCG2qkVNwppoHwOZNP2+33rpoFR/e388JZl5vTkw4Q2FaEd7imqOTThYm44r8dZZgQFxb2ZUk2T5wjmZj2jPfZ36q5PohPz14LZxsqE+aVSOPEjRWIpccaTPZ2hgiuSUH6McIItmAyf1fdo8vCn4MoKHnzYLkMo0LmPi52qWgI33ICWvvZvth9pxVL4OL5HR7NmluUjIczqhNXLTZ4vkWBrkD3P+kw9rrlg23CAE7TmajCfPdeY+kwlbU/4L1/Xyyw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050114", 
		"question": "25y2KIX71Fnp+Is0VwbmhfL5dX/YBiIBrGiGQONgfzHnXarLYOTtwddlL1nJjEl+82WGrKOw9hMcm6lP7M7XZSwHe5kv6cKd3uf7wTESc8lC2pR64do2cvBJzTPtV9vVM+pn2nuULkr+LnX9E3h9lzmWhXoWvIu+tSG0WNY41xw8kcdr+ckoOdqa17yAqEyqg0aB02mDTb5wUVaYpsusq0yS4JYwsI2+pCLJ8fn82tvc5cwfJRsSrZNzalW7hPc19hY2AIiAYBcL4evHZEatLy7jFw8P9cLi23Fn0sIgU2o44RtDkcNCasUz143wtD0iNtlzVSe140dFw5E8dhmSfby2kHzh8kc2YXU5fMp5s2004QmTOlF3nWXcTyNEmpR555AMmwBmby9hjmLpgTOOwDazcsGjwo74jOn+4K1m4LEuPU6SLBzbV4Ncar3MPidwz6mYCKJZN99zGGLnfdMh7jzwJ5jUzC0MxNxgO3/1+z+emo30eWa1vYHth8BjALYPONDJqcq6tVLDbCbvNT2GaM/xS0jRXWjx0AJg90tzkB0euyLrDZ1r+SgAm3CkCUti0iagbnO0mLpd+JvOe4ciw+D42HISneBvmp75lDQyQw26zX5NtsSeQVNbxVHEXs4I0Qc6Hq1BBpPA52SEkGWQSjwOcMDlFaGT1jhB1e3wgiF8spUAUYGLIg3nhIpm/B+0QaRtXSfOp4jqKfUBH3Al9bxwxq2Aus+1cf6hInFqThmjGacIqsMBIUJsEBidACpOY6yrUt0KTqBbwHTEhAFNVT9rAEjZ+akaVESfpM3HYCrKbPEsDxXrcKcEHfL2cknnOubpxTHHH/+TkweqV0FlXS6cNbUA4AnkNZ+yIxqllmYk+MPqJFQbTZBYPTX2NGi2t7GGCBJlPdWbOmKF6OzMQQcdH3sbxo8=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "2+T4YYKz2Bfp+JcyVx3mhf/6NmrFEGdRl3eGErBgcWXmWaLMeq2+wIQxLlKKgklp93XS44Tjt0MKnehP4YvfQzcTbI5izZCq2PHl0DZSc9RRlol849ZfaPxFjC2iY9HJYPFojl6BNUn5ZjS4CmQ0gT/Sj24WiZGv/CS3UZpkgBE9k5Q448cofNKR2qee+EyrlUaW1H7RSahwGVuLvNqxq1eT4IE9scjNmDzf/fX32uzW4swCdgdApsZrbBu9164G6i8xVsb0ax1e//DCeBTRLhStdU4U6ovg2WZ7w4E9HWgntAtOh8Nld9Bh05Xh/BE/Kt9+VTy8421Ow519HwSXfbn4xGDl9BUWe34iZIQtqCgnswaIJ0Zn2midQmxemoxyvtIc1QdmeWpE3GLvwj7LhmqdeZrk5cDvkenkpfl3+rEoPEaIdV2YVYISdqfJM3Jmw+aVDKocMpJiGSbrONs6vCz3JJOGnxgfxNAjI3Knp3zBrsPJNzb6uoG5h9p1G60SM9LRqcmys13SciahNXWWJvjhSRr1Qnm48AFwpQxlwS9QuTuOUclt4CEImj6kQUVw3mfzaWi1mrtR74yaP4E3k/Ss3z0FlvB5jYK30BQvVxGviD9Bt5CISllBjX3YGsQGhAggCPQAGpnF+miE1XXfXnIZbde2BaeC0GxG1fexnGRsqpkcUMyPbBrUhM0ywQOkFfR2W2bh6If0OPIRB2Ei7vJY3q2itsT7d/bkKGokalq1QK9c65BSfRZyBw6dBCdbabegFpwNAelbknHFkhQISXBdRVPC7acESwHqqcHbfWPRbfETCF7LbbcMEsC4WkLdJ/i9xyLQRquT1Ub+WUs3SzOaL/AO6hL+bp7rGB2PnTwk8NKlMV5JVoYUKGfyZyu4o7eGGUYJXGs2aI9fakvUQh4hkH7XKLlzhaJAQAooUqGjHF5WhBRJmizXAFtA8ABeH5GlRRN+PqEFA1Qf3iO8BbULVRPEhzZKr1uZzCbhLPRfcWggbyTb3hW2y9smiP76wouPC9f2KLlbxoJDPKRaSonQGklcuPb2+uPhA2V5M2N+IfaISu2RgE79C9vgo82YddAe4O0+Pw6HAzEyHefSfA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "all Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050115", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fQa+r/25N4KVvJmVN+smbJtKDit1wJz7xT7M6vYicQd49qxsTJ1urzhGVJNoZXjoFm4doTefNJ3zGsYMHJJb5nwC6BK1H1dTCzAzBngDDCjzxUp5a18SapXd8kgBQgk8d57sspLtaL3Pev5nG210vCnE+ZTf1UA1GKvMqt5Vfco4M29cmEoiDe8/XrnrjH+NtLdAFXqJU/ZkOsha0a6y88EcqtKAZD9KTDdVX5JWivIgkU6sfiwmF7w8I+VWA48V9PjJdEbcRm1ZHqu3Ixf89jGT/6sUFMxoB5W1eCe/253Hzh8lwxcjo4cYt5uW03rhqSLFVsk26PcCID2cArytgc1Rd3fHtF3HrlhTaYjGSbaYHmrJO8k+H1t6oj87EiaQGSME3NX58ZYfPCImF92OzbBKhIIZBjAiHvM9Ju/Xn7KZqYny0CkNooLnng8WqNmsi1N2S3ttL2iJR3VKwUN8XA1cXk/RyHVSvkYU2BY9j9XQ3+WzvrkxxgtBcoxSQe7GPMAYZxtSQe3nC1SkF3gSbydTyjk7hT+IfOdoAlwfroyDEZlvM4ntv13REwBxC0zX5PpoGND09bzEDTXs8I0QcqDaYIEYXt/FGYon7ZSHRNcMi2FaCCgz9c2/f0g2Rzq4NOUoWYKRebi9wp3hLxCO42VHXo6IX2L+4QCXBzuNCSBCuERcOvt1rObh5ZZ4Y=", 
		"answer": "2+T0KMOz0Bfut9ZiRz4kF8FvpqiOhWACS0JvmQ==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpMUsUwfhhfnwImWQF3Ue43yMXKd9ZHjsWrSCZ+O+3Z94NBybiFx64HKc46r+8h9PjuhZ4IKTMCEMcJ9qxcCF1vD+ynYBJ85B2oFw64waPPdIzTOqccebI/9gjmyFZ0z+cyuyAGV3kTWWg3IWvIu+tRe6RtY+wRg3mJM44sYwJZeI0LybqFmwg0aSznKeWv12FFeWuMOt5UedtIs3u42Ct3LP/PG5qurW49cPZwZG5MZ+bV/8g78GtGo6VM67ehcL4+HTblngJSanLgAaud/r0zRrz44lESkg/BoGspFTccl305bw/DoxLI1+GnOopkJF1dRoVxLWZ7y11Sjw7xUrfX9rdp5sqCh1rQqbIUdym3+JXikRl49l/dULmwFnPWlPjjblmi+ZhXacdZ3kq4nolqjmqbx04eMwIFWIPFKYV80PdbbDLmF7z+3bHaNOOpBjVxbuOJUe7jzqKZKR0S1NmNYyb0fm5iaQk8DwN3Hz85vqztp5AP8COcTL7Yu1qRzTaSahN3SWcdi0Vg6wW3T9kx1xtgwgiC0V72vLBIhr4D8I3n++TQRpkz6gaXW1nrtOqoONfIshx7Xjz3ICnf59nI+3wBU5Skj7iGlGvMSWSRxbxVGWCMQC0xpuDaYEVITU8Wifg3PUC3UDP9r/DK3Fu7xRQCWjkMdQWbg7qiqz5g==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1, 2 and 3", 
		"option_b": "1 only", 
		"option_c": "1 and 2 only", 
		"option_d": "1 and 3 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050116", 
		"question": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f43uGQapzfnD3UbSCeuX7iadjIk+AiV515jHV47f19FwCgq1V7Y+LeS0NPop8iNHJx/by1nRQJs9Xk5R3pJwQbrRJwim/e9DOI/dgyS6BZ0f5azX9FnV4lSXTjjxCp8O6+TO+RtM5x1UhgoZs6Ig+M8KR3amB4UirykaD0n/RXLVhUWSLsN2h70aStMIxpo2Dviab+vH6n+vA8cwCbhESvYlqbV/8lbFJ7CI9Ed69bQVYsevWIUDlJRecGDEixvTc6TRlw4UgTmU14ApUh8FTSPzlgDG2iEtnrwHi/8iB", 
		"answer": "26asaYX2k4L0M9Wlq9GgEV/HgoLTeUA=", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHDwxz5/oElXAq11r3tMGjfDm8UrXuCRqp7fjHqR+fMa+772oRwNUXJj159/WTD46z+40EAi71Y4ICYMCNDfIJjxJCb0uj20HRFc9JL2oF+8J8NdfpHjC65dcDeYPxh22CEJlf5Yir9ImVmgDnTmHFZuob3tTOzUZoH0hAhn4N949x8NcTf16eHqE+3kwiGnHmICKlsFBSPvMu/+AOZuJIqsN6etDab9u25jvDWsM0fYxxX/4p6ZFKvm6kd7Tg9E4APMVQuebKGiNxX9yEf8UM=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "st,at,e", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050117", 
		"question": "26KwYZL7kTj444wjXhuyyvu/IWPVQ0sfp3aCXONXf3/wQK7We/n3xpkxJkmdhVRp+2zDsOXk/1ZPv6lJ5YeefScNast7x5CI2/Dy1jFSJ8dQn8Bw648RePVSxTi+K5Ypei1uS2P3A8Jzvj0cYp/x", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpMfN395poHWcSVTHmJ7agc5c", 
		"explanation": "26esYZL/1Fm5t4Q1Rhb91/TsMHiQF2oU40+CQK99cXzmWrOCeuK+iZF+NVHJjBt192GGsLHx41ZPjbEb+ouPcTACaoJgxpCG0aTjwWNTOtJLiJky4ogQcbRBwiTtZ8DaNPsuwXzAJVzMaSyzDWR9mjaWnmtZ6IyptSq0Rt930wEzgoJrrccufMeey7yAqEK+xhWW3W+UW/1rAxSbrI695UqIqYw/9cyDqHLP8ebrk+zc4sdLdgcSvsZvYkmo16cPuCs2SIinfBNf9KT5dRThITGwZwoS7sWjwmNmhoEmU2094BZJjJAWa84zwpDtr3IiOsprBzfg40tOwtg8XleUfbG0kGvr7kE6eGonZJ5ksip1tQeZaFV8lX2ZDC9ZlY5s+8NZlgVtPW1F3H/uli2EhHCMeZej4o68keD14Ili4K8uKEyFO0iYWYMQfPPXLnN6iv2TCOZMIZZoBWL0ONYh8TT8LpKVyzAC3pkvKTfz/C/Zot/wKmy+tpzt1Zad6fOegygaBlj54sgKb1vq", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Article 2", 
		"option_b": "Article 4", 
		"option_c": "Article 5", 
		"option_d": "Article 3", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050118", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRonyXW6x6YzHqR+fsQdm+yphnIk6MiRt56zbSq6Cw51wYirob5ojfQCMRcoJuxdWHw6TiynVEIYZliJR755YaPKcAwzvtYNzeYNdgymeBKQXTaDeuEHlggSXfhXIJ6hBhK8T5mx4AkyTJlSn+b48=", 
		"answer": "25a9e4L63heq+INgexD2zPzxdX/VEXAYt3CRS+NgfzHiFKHNfOj3zpkxJFOcg09p6zTiFwWg4DBPEmeIFGgsde0U", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHAxAn48oglEj390O/rdWPVD2ZRt3eCRuNgeHSjRKjVa/++xpExF12bgVJ6/3PIt+Xk+BMLhqVS54eMeGIXdo4vycKM1qT4wjFAc9VQm5R3pNIKcvBF3n2MZsDSI/Jrjj3JZ0H/Yir9Cn9g1DLZnHlE6IC+5jSyW9R3zxNyv4l85MkyfMOay7qa/EKqn0aW0zuQCLtrA1GQssDo6EyJrpYqrI9Smh+2Nunmy8bhNUBuODYI", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Altering state boundaries", 
		"option_b": "Cession of Indian territory to a foreign country", 
		"option_c": "Changing state names", 
		"option_d": "Increasing state area", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050119", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1gzr5YQuRhv31r3rPW6QF2cDsXaXXbF9cX2jXanWa+rswINoZ12HiRt4/XjSqqvl8ldPirBS+pqafiEGPoRpiMOd1vDy1zFWOtJMk44y8JIaPMFOxSmocJToNP96y33AKEOwRjS4Fnl3lX2Wi28Wq4y25SapUd531Bpyv4l85Mljfj8y9nRdAmde/jWS6HoAamQ=", 
		"answer": "25a3ZoLn2A3/44wvXF79w73rPW6QNmwYt3qHEpBgcWXmR+WTV92ER7MFMh6OOaUWTLnu", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHS3Bz4/oYhXF7RyvPsIWLEFnYYrHHDVbZ1YnDtQKLHfa3qwZIxM1mbn1Jv/WTPoqmw/l0biq9J4JqGMCMNestsx96d3uriwXUBNt5NiZR36pkaPPtGjC65dcDeM7Iuw2+LLkv3JzCpRHF61A2Ug3JSrZCv5zK4QNM1zBByg4lx4sZ8M9Hf0KaX7V6slBOByHKTRLgkAkCYocu7qWqbhC9SRxmNf6mruPBoHUM=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Constitution of India", 
		"option_b": "Constitution of the United States", 
		"option_c": "State governments' consent", 
		"option_d": "Amendment process", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050120", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sU0Vwz/1r32OyvzDG4ErnHDc+NjeWXrFLPKa+TsiZR+NU6Mjk879nPVoLf550cGgKZIqYeRMAEMcp5ixpCrlcq7iOpGjn+tMRlRlqBBp0M=", 
		"answer": "24W3f5Thwlnl8cU0Whuy7PP7PGreQ3IQsXOKU65xfmWuZKjVa/++3ZgxJlCdiEk74WLHt6Cw9Vwagaxa+4eaY25DS4Vm3NWNl9fjxWVEIIZLnMBT6Z8NdfdBgTyjNN3VJPt92nyVJFH5ZTW4RGV6nT7YynNQ6Iq18SKoQMgiwwE7lIt9rdsoPcOayuTTyV+sjwWO2TvFBZlhEliYp8u7q0+dt5F4s8Kf8TTU5vnwlP+T/tscIhtGvpJ6cBu9hOgH9yR1UMWxZhZG9OrEchitATq3Lg0R/Iuwm1Vlyo0+TikE9Q1Ki4JbZ85nlozr/Cc+NtlvVSCuolBF1NRzTVeXeKm9wijw6FA2Zzopap9juCwnqAqPat6b7iup9b/K/++/WlvkEMM=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpN9gcxL+yursdVvREW4YonKGXLc0ZH6jQanLeui+2oNwM1mazVRpsnfKt6Dit0cHiqFJqYyQZSwHf5lmzcO12dj55WNVOsVIn8Amvto7efdMzS+oZ5TXIel9jmiPNQX2aCuwDX5z1D/TnTxFvIKv8DT7Vcl3zho824Z16MY4MdKRzbuv5nG2rwiG1XrRQa4kA12evdqk8gOYpZE7p8SPtDab9ee54vndsNcFZg1Bq5RqYE+1laQMuD82WMe6KB1NseDVckD/NSu3LgwR/IvwwnV9w5FQHV088V9zjIpZbIBU2Y7hrjw9OsN+VTC7rQREwodoTRiPNKmw1Sj39FQrcGlrcoJorig0sk+IIFE+iX+dWCkRk499+8IXmAFtaXwAn3fujDCfwGGKb4fx5Jm8keD14Ixt+6wpaWiOdWnrd8Fcar2AM293iuaPBaNOc5dmGSaqfcEm+XntJYSG1i0CwtAhIzfu+j6cld/8LXz6vIC5jdt4ALYOI9TBqc6vuU/TZC3iJD2cYIv1GRvkTmj9kwd29x8wyTMR5nbdDY0/9zRNina1CWdrnDT0ZWi0grdT5MDXUbhJeHbv8pnnhW46n1pi", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Article 3,Allows Parliament to unite states or alter their boundaries", 
		"option_b": "Article 4,Declares laws for forming new states as non-amendments", 
		"option_c": "Powers of the Indian parliament,Power to alter state boundaries", 
		"option_d": "United States of America,an indestructible union of indestructible states", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050121", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3oBi6FapKueYzZDTopkwcOd1uq3yHBPN4ZGlZV84JsNZbRXzS7tfdrSNPdvwmKZZ0H1czyvCXl6kTWWiH1FrYf7+in7QNIygCczkoR05M46OZe+zqmB7A23gEbThS/GdLNXBVWNsMOt5VfciatiicO5uTeb8P3qiu3H9c1LYxpbrI9xZBu6hacEuD4wVIikeh1d+PfZblr+YCelZxoV/IvR13BqyosvW2x01QhHkIcWdcVh09jxsCY5Msx+ED+j41dF04BwWhPWYLWq333j6BUrfX9rS49lrjh4jwCTJhRfnXmZSSFUmpQr8dZZxF02JVNOoHjXijaIiCWAetP344W8lvzxtLxu960zOgGHPErdWM0dZ7zWIid72aaaH6McMJB1BSflKZfwQAt3YMUwg6gxEYwS1GnG", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz+Fnr+YFgezewDbm4SXZFF7HmzNz7mUMRzw==", 
		"explanation": "26asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhf7wJ3nVAHZRomzDRqtxMFjtUK7DI8j/2oMxF12ChEhv83iGr6T+8xMNgL1V7Y+NaWIUf5gvwd6N0uHzhHVEJ8NWl4l84Z5fffdDwy+pfdrcYOphjnqIIgXCZj2+CHlykjSWq2tXuof7+iH7BYNjl1UOmLt23tw9KNKS3KaHqGSRxg+RnHqdW7IkEluLp8ur/wOds8IcvN6dpCbe57T4iPfA9Z4EdxwSsIA/cFSxkugZ6iUuWNu9ZxxYse3eIUDlJWiRJgoe9cLl0HEp55UoT214tAhOi4BeItd2xJ2krz0lOMV+VSe140ZFh4Z5TBiaYri8kHzs8loqcnJrcYJo/A80pgiZaHVpm3mYDCNX1NEyq4BZtApsaWdFjjblhDmEknHPa5Lwq439ge2wtLYj4aYzPU2FdUjQU54ZJbfJNHdn3uyITaRFc4tvEmLION086XTXL5manxgKwtwlInLp4GqWlI2kYDDi8Vcv6Kob8NH54YwEqR7kt04=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050122", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb7pHfrQNJ34xo8hZNx+d0oNdiR2KTTyUC9iAKP2XWFCJxnBRTR5575vgrcpoM7vMGEpTPP8fC5jvDWsNsTYQBTsYF6I1S617wM6jgxRcemYRdYsebVdUPoJSbjDgAZ8Mqj13pthqAoU2449RtDkYsaXs4z5J3lrz0+f4VYXGn6n0oA85x5HzmTfK+tnUbr71t/VH05YI9guSMh4QCaaAUnzzPcXzlSl4V47dYMmQh6PX1Fj3nslDqPwGSDcNPn4pPskPz1s/lx968mPUSEdUjXFpkUYPPMJml2iuuUGKhYMo1+VyDjKcIr+Te5CZiQ1jhN0dckb1Xm+i2Vk8nwKm342ozq+1MTRrfXAt5KYLJydA==", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/IXnFBi5RoWqXErd8dTHxUabRYeO+wIQxIV2Fnl45oLDgcbBIQ1kx++Pbe7CGMA==", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+cUpQV7m1+j6dWrDQzNB82uLEoB7fmL3XbPXeuTxx5Z9Z32EiFV//3PIt+XR9EdPx/oLuNvWMDUCbctqxtGKw+HzhGVOc8FNjIUy4ZwZefdUjCmiNMDTJb5vzX+VLlf5aT79C3Y0lzTEnn1fpsOv8DWpXc440hw3hcd69IgVMtOW2OiS5kn4khSD0miXTa8kHlLZtsu6/0KVrsI3ocWIo3LP8ebrk+zc4tcOcUhGsMZdYlW7m6kN/TkwEcG6KAJe4/fFYFruJWisIU4J8c6j13N7w4ckWGcgtB5IhsNfdtMzxorrqD0zMMEqED2uplZFw9R1UQOZNL+9xH/h5Vt/YXIuJa1iqignrwKZJkBt2mSaDAVfkIlqvtEXkURBfGFHkHfkhyyDvGuzcqHm6pPzi6j5s/ll8680LAGCMF/ZQ54ZJYfIIidbxO2SDOt5MoxzVxLnNtw96Dj3YJqV0T1N0tY1IXPm5jPZhczmeWG/p5frg914EbtAN8KF+c6l8EjPZGPTIHmQasLyXw2wbmv5wQoluB5lmXhEvyL8AZpv4DkIjT6xW0t3l2fveWjhmbgc+Y2Des4hwfr61CEZl/pr35L5lAk0QkSJjHtAvo2ZSVkP7EPXDMlLhB4mBbcJVIHU4GjWhnnFTHQZP9r5QaqCgz5Nyez9mGR5/4QGR4ObKxGbntYjiDWwBvp8FUb6qZT9ffMTSjV1r+Ix6+Ouo8K+Z7OhKmMlfQ73Tu5Ks5hQbAc7BQSdFiFbdLSrFokWRPNKknHDhBddU3paRVjVu7wAWESEr8zaeyfwbL4STj/lcbYAHsv2WgfAM7H4kWWRRP1DHwnNcjaIC/9NMaGMDY4=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050123", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDfOi+3YVkIhybiFx64HLPraKw41sKz61D6oaefiUGPoRpiMSMxfb+0H5TOsNX2oJ38I0aefoA5TOpfdWbIfBqjkyBKUL8Zj24F3g0ljDFj3gWp4374S++FN0+1hA81pd5/ts9O9LA5aav5mz1xkar0n+YSf1wA1WXpsit+VGZpMJt5I2IvzHX9eL8ibjH/54pYwZVs4d7Zki0q6YrtWp4Efy8bVJl9OzCdBnDLyetZy8a687m23Fn0sImWyllrUoewpBDYcN2xYviqT48Jo14ECC1r1JFw9R9UxvWdrKq1G32oFE2Zmo+cY9+/C8wtRiZLVo+s2WYRS0RlY5vvvIYmwNvfGtFj37cjBzGwCW7dJajutCskeCwg7Zt4bcuPVSUPFPWV4FcRL7FKWN/z+ePTYdfJ98vRXK3aJxu+jj6KZqdyzgZ1d1gO3/itC+BkcX0N2K/853/zsBzBq0JIt7X4M6k8F3JZWPsLnmaYML3WBz5QHK43Aglpwoq3igD4W3WG8l2+20ZlnvwaktqgTPpeGm1n7FSrZHOWYcjwOGs7jEYnfBtk57L2jlxB0SPhXoDnoWRSxxtwkHYGswV3UkPC6YEEZvU/HnWl3PEXHkIcY7fD6yOwmxJ1OexrGBzuJwPUYmdJFWbmdchxhK1QfR3FTa0/9K1fesUGSQ++6Z4zOSks4qsfOesI3A+LwiySPpQ4Zxfb0J6USjSCzdbaay7QpQRT+FDklTHkglMSnpHERhjpVVC5rE7ZRpwPwXkmTrh", 
		"answer": "25b4Z5//yFuVTJoxWHUjzKCRF56cCic3", 
		"explanation": "25y2bJjykQ349oszVBvg1/j7dTqBUiIUrXyPU7VxYzH3W+fgb+P5xZZ1Ik+BwRts+n/KpuXS9l0Ig6lf7J2XMDYRf4V8ztWbxeHzhCQQc8NKmYxz8p8MPOBPjBSjcN3aYMJg8mC0L0CwSTy1FmU5uj7ZhDx3r5G+8Cq+Ws53zxNyx94ttYg9KMOa1LiH7Un4kgnCzn6CR7FyFBSbutys7lHcpIsrpdiZtCGXtPbsjrja5J4PawwSsYlrI0iplKsM6zk+RMS4cVJK9eDCZEf+YCmvK04J8c6j32d604c6ESkI+iNItotTIpEjhozs/BE/Md5+HCevt01PyZVwHzabcbO83W3q9BUedm5rLdg97Xh84RidOxR7lGqfWClV1JRkvtcQgwEjeGlGmXX0wiuEwHGHedPi6JHpjPr5rr4j/aVnKkSSIV3RWM0IYKHSLnN92OCeHuZeKt9OGSbvPJUv8j25NISV0SoL1ctgIHGn9y+Lhsz8NyW1p5r8nJRiEa0SP8XK+8KyoxzTbmPDIHOUasrwXBv4D2jw1k5kuh0rzCwV5naYBYZ7/CsEm3rwXUxh0jfyY2qohbdT5JHObYs90uHl0zVQjPs4i5PylAk5VRaymXBRu4GMD1NJjVLZC99H1x0vGLESVN7w4X6XmDqQfHkea47UBKaAwiAEms70iWl8s5EXVMyPIh2bvswv2AKjALQ5XGmtvI78fdocGHc4uoFywuilosa+NfyibHEialqUVuFK55xFfRZyHgXhCxhBVLCrFrEfT+QP8HrfmQNJVWYJJF3e/q0FWAq+6svOLjuHNOVcGR/xI70KB47qT1PGM/iszHDNE7rcgUj+S0wgDjSYJLRN4wjiOo2yBxy9gHxt7dTxO15VRY9XHSr2em+0oK2XSwA1bWwmLZhTe07bCwQhhizKM/Z1hKYMMAw/QKa0H1UEhV0NA5aDOdj2YE82Hwm8Ofl1jg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "B, C and D only", 
		"option_b": "C only", 
		"option_c": "B and C only", 
		"option_d": "A  and C only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050124", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTrl+ZY0Wwrn0fTwO2rcQ0McpnGHX6Z6ZDHCV7OCaOz9wJt4M12diF875n7D46Do9FsOga9eqYGZMDYGbJlm3N+b3uHkhHNEJ9FBn44yzZQbdfUAzTOpNPbaLvliz2qFNE2vJdyYOz0b+ZC/3st4sayA32o=", 
		"answer": "2+ToOIX7kTrl+ZY0Wwrn0fTwO2rcQ0McpnGHX6Z6ZDHCV7OCJr+umMI4ZYbEuj8LZZ+tlO6A/xF9HXs=", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdGigUn+/8UDXRDh0fTrIH/ZDGwQrz+iX6Z6dHzmWrOCT+7qid8jdw3cxBt64TbSq6Cw+1YIhrtX6JqWfyxDaoNu3JCP1uf+yHhVMtJBnsBm7J9feexDxDyjc9GbL/gu2muSNUzkaCu0AWM0ljTCnXlTpsOS+yOyVZo2zhFytIZ26sQ9ONKM0eqUrrHkqtrka1q7YCCH1QoI", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "90th Constitutional Amendment Act", 
		"option_b": "100th Constitutional Amendment Act (2015)", 
		"option_c": "95th Constitutional Amendment Act", 
		"option_d": "105th Constitutional Amendment Act", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050125", 
		"question": "24KwcdHw3gzm84tnRl7mzfi/FmTeEHYYt2qXW6x6MDm6QK+CT+D7x5N8IlKdxBta8WKK4/SpoQNPja0b7ICZfzAAe48vzt+bl/D/wTFVNtRWk5R99pMab7RJwn2re8bWJewu62+TMwXAZjK0F2R1mnGemm5Tu4a14SuiFPg2zhI+l4N9/sB1Y5WklcpyuRPPEGrgaRPKwtt9", 
		"answer": "25a3ZoX63wzl4pZgXhfmzPr+IWLfDSIQrXvDQqx4eWXqV6bOLun735J9KEyEiFVv4TS6n8ZyKJ/IvtRWYYmnpH8h", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eh/81ur6JyvZECIS6j+gXa1geX/2W7LRLuH33Z52JkiAglU783jC47X/+1obhqta5c6bdTQGcoR/xdWHw/e38HlEc+dHjsBx648TeLROwyntdtGbJfBowXyDIkGwbjf9EHhx1CXTmG5fvIyp/CKoFNUxgBM9hIp9/4gZPcSLmZiS40SrkgeMnH+ETf1wHhSWu8mn4k2b4I49ssyB8TbS5+Tsjv3AsN8FZkhRt4dxZFKykOgZ9yYxRcG3aR4L8u3CYkHgMzyiKQ0Y6oviwjR9zoM9HX09+RoEL6n3EYhs0SsABD/SmBilNw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Lack of political will", 
		"option_b": "Violent protests", 
		"option_c": "Continuous litigation and political developments", 
		"option_d": "International intervention", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050126", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTDk84whXF7h0fzrMHiQFGcDpj+HW7Fxc2XvTefDaOv7yoN0IxyLlBtv+nOGpr3z/1IBiK0b5ojfZCcRbIJ7x8KA0ve303hVO4Zmm4516JsbeedIjDyud9vJJPdgyS6UKAXkbzz9FHFnhzDRjyMUwBdQb70zGGvOxtaQw6YY1w==", 
		"answer": "25Sre5D+nVnd8pY0Ejz3y/r+OSeQLmcWq36PU7p1PDHXRq7Se///i2khmxJtSCZ8ZB729Z8tYtM=", 
		"explanation": "25a3eoP20g2wt7EoV17ixO7sNGzVQ3EFomuGQeNgeHD3FLPKa63qzIVjLkiGn1J+4TbJpeXR5EAOguQb3ouMZGIhe4VoydzFl8nyw3lAP8ddm8wy5ZQbPMBSxS24ZtWbN/t8yy6NKEH5YTC4ADB9mnHCgnkWjoqp5jP7Z9k/xREnmoI44s58KN+amYuc5l6sjxKXyHKeRv1gBFHZocHo/0uZ4JY9p9+EpT3J/fX12v3L89YKbA9X/bovGG3OCWnlPelSNHWii18=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Uttar Pradesh, Bihar, Assam", 
		"option_b": "Assam, West Bengal, Meghalaya, Tripura", 
		"option_c": "Odisha, Tripura", 
		"option_d": "Assam, Utter pradesh", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050127", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrI45H48hMjhqZc/IeMZCsAPrt9x8aA2efy1zFiPMtJk5Nh7ZURPOFOyDi/NOfwYNpmz3zANUDzaDSwAX5wkTWWmHlZuoS6+y6hXdQwgAYml5N9/ogzMpeL0a3T6kyrjxXC033RSblpGFqQptq66leVtod4tsKDpzfV/fH3mf2T4t8fag1A/5J3YlX8m6EH/z8xQty9a1JN8OfEbkb+HCaQMw8J/Mbm2GAp76tzYWcA/BoGqLVmIuN825XtqCY1OoEqFjy0sE1T051yWFeZcv2W1WD29Rl/RXs/YIYh/Cw7pU+vIUB/iGqRTTVIlcwr7NUTkAd3eGsAkHfuhSqKh2DPfYCj/4j5xerxs7BwsqUoOwGSMFPKUYwSbKnJKWAy2f2aGaNPD5FbGRXuNNYmvDb/YIKc2nkexNg0Knri+j6K0sr8L2C085P7gcJzVLYTedDX7Iu0v07VZCD1Y8Hbre7CsmWNSfGlWYyvQc8=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz+Fnr+YFgezewDbm4SXZFF7HmzNz7mUMRzw==", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHf2Bft4owzRhfxhc3tOn3ZDWEUsD+gXa55eWLwXajMLvjwzZJjZ2+izX9z82SGsaDz+F4CiqZf7IrfYicMbIxuxtmT3urwhGJVMtJBicB96toLdPEAzjy+fcebL/guz2qNLkv5dC2vBWR9gjSWiXNYvoa1/CK1V9930hQmnoJqrdw0Pdnf1aGd71ixlRKL3zuXSb5wHkaKocatq2mqkMIbusCAuCbP8fG5iP3Z9d0fZwwSs4dxZE69kK1J+Tl4RcCxKBBK4u3DIVLiMmixIgEP/srt325gyIVpTn014BpVwGVjVYBpaZAH9dGLODME+0E=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050128", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t2Abjrxe+s6tdS0ReYphwcOIw+34yjFgMNIElYYytcNKKrRSyS64eMDeJL5nwC6UL0CwajyvA3Vm1D7QykxXupf71Ge6Wt538BQggsdardsoPcOayuia5lm3xgfCz3KfT7FhUVeYocuv5FGFnIwLocyZtD/e+uC5s9GJzNA/ag0SmYdlbxudm6FJ2yU1XMGnextE/6TDdFPqJTu3Igpd7cPmlnd7w4M9VGY6tBBAwtIAItNn14zhr3IxMckqRnO5pkpU1ZVwUw7Wdbm12Wbt80E6Z38vJZ5orj88tQCOIVFtpmWgQhtZnYNjvt8f1RBreC9TiHf0hzKOjnGcPJTq/YXyxenyr69msqo0ZkCSMBzbWZ8OYLDUZb5aNR2Nrb3SjctQQeZyZzs=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz4g3r44AtVxDmiNS/NGXUQ1EFomuGX6Z6ZDzKfefDfOi+yphjNVmKmRt6/HKGkLHx41YCiqZPpKe2MCsQPp9nzZCK2PblwXJVc8Ncioxz6psLdftOjDuiZpToNP96y2OFKVG9Tnv85374Gzy7JCDE0gWedv89", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhf7wJ3nVAHZRomzDcLo0ZHnmFJTWb/n72tdDIlObilp1+2XHt6z/+RMujLwbod/GJXRKPophzJCd3+G3k2VJc+VLlJNm7Y4KaP1PwjyhNPXWJfBqw2uOMwXRZC39TCEtwWefxjxCoIb78S6oQNM5wwE7mYk4780oK9Ka1+ij6V+sxifC3XWVCI1lA0DZl467/0KIpZF4osye8TbU+vG5m+/S6Z4caxxa/4dxZxuMlroduAl4Qty1fBdYsfPVc1GtISqsKwcO8c7nlkhn+owaSWgg8RJDjJcWS+kz34ukvz0iLchpAXO4tlAAxJtuTRKVYLGhkG388Fk+fHRrZ49uvTgmpE+6KU5y2kqQRWxym41m98MKnAttPXxVm3HlkSuOhCWbdJaj6oLzieHkqbZtsqwhaVWIMBzeWZgOKLXPK2MyyeWaHrVVNZZkFjbvMttu8z+5M4KVyzwekNguKzfz8TiLm9n6K2y/oNLsgNBzBv8UPtSF5tm+t1XJYC+hAnKddd/9TR3kRnP2kw9rs1gm2iQR/GvXBslw821cyD6jXUVwlzSgbXKl1u0c6YeAa5ww3/n1nTMUlf12lojj0Q85Q0SviG1Ru5CQXVVK3haot8viK3AdtwuHd+iYgwQr", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_b": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is not the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_c": "Statement-I is correct but Statement-II is incorrect", 
		"option_d": "Statement-I is incorrect but\n Statement-II is correct", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050129", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIkKz7/FoCz6pe6o+SdWICcMtu28OG1O320HQBINJFjoUy65xfaPxFjBSjcN3aLr5bwGePKQXlaT24FjBgnDSW2SlCoMOY+imoQNMj1QE7mYl54YgdMdKR3aWW5ln4pwWW4HWiXLxwFFmcu9rowmrGnIwLvMaGuD+b4/Xq2vTS5NsZIg5Hs4pmI1Kyg60O6issVMz0YRxf/qTEaVGtCSanLg8Tuf7t33tnhoAwHX088V8V1JdeIuN82IvwtSYlK8RlGzK242VNwpp4UhKYYP2Z03yooEI3fHkjJZhorCg0rQqYaEB2nyuMXiNHnZNi8d4K1QtlPXtImTaz1yuDwESCeZ3n5oXykdT+nLdU+qokIQGPMxzMXohcdqfBM2J/z+ePHuZbOoliGWLnP9o4+XnwM9mVzTxN09YyPXLk4GiWtQNC0pWEFU/k8p9Avy6l", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz+Fnr+YFgezewDbm4SXZFF7HmzNz7mUMRzw==", 
		"explanation": "27e3fJmzwg3r44AtVxDm1r3+J26QAG0DsXqARuNIfk3tYK7OYq2vkMMmaxy6hFBw+3uGtKTjt1IBz4FV7YeefmITbIJhy9WFzqTk0HBVNoZWj4x34NodZbRjxDKqbdXXYNdgjj/ZcxK8Jzi7EHVm1CXejzxaqZOo8Ge0UpoV0hwmn5Rwrdg9LtaS1r2d/E6hykax1XCaQbAkE1GatMOtq0Lc2JIqutmIsibU5vXtn4GT/9hLSwZWtoc/UFK3nKEEuCg9Usm5bVJK/6TRckfiIyGiMwtd6t/iwnEpyYRpSWExtDZIhopXbIBG2JHrsnIlMclvB3Ouq0EAlMFoV1e1e7OrxGHw9UE2enQqacpMsSg7pQKZJkA+u2iIDB9Yn4ti85AOlBcjcW5UmWSghCqHjHzPdZ337ofuhPz1pPlq/LcoaVWIMBzxWIkVZL2AEml7xefbD78cJ5diV3GwKd1u3zb3M4KdyywZ2dYuLnun1SecnMn4PGuu87P6mpg2A7cJNdmF+86ntV3LZCehNXWWJtvmVh75XHX33R0luB5l3CkVqDGNHIE/1CAIkHq9TEpw0P05gJpCP1/AUY8IjCEc0Ug=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050130", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDwWnIu+tQuyWt0iyQYmn4Q43dozKt6R2q2AqG63iwuLz2iYR7MkA1GausOl7k2YpYZ4p8iCozXa+v3jk/bUsM0fYxxXrMZ9Yki5k+gG9mo5VcW9ZhtY5fbRdV37JWigKAAL/MXq03pqw8I7XH088Q0GlotXbIB/35bjqTsjK8RpVTW7oFBP1YdAUVekcbyr32akqGd2LzoXa8pBvSMytA6bLRl8m3iZSGxDkY95+dEXnB5iaWZPkjb3jSqHhCWHfYXmq4z5gajkr/lg568zPFOBORzQWYATYrbOIm5m06maAKlSNN9zHyemLsEv6DzqYu2zVVldGOZXvO2RHMkFjfE=", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/IXnFBi5RoWqXErd8dTHxUabRYeO+wIQxIV2Fnl45oLDgcbBIQ1kx++Pbe7CGMA==", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+cUpQV7m1+j6dSvEC2dRj3aNVbZ9Y2XqV+fyfOLowJlyIk/JrlR2/3/VsKz/+RMGgaxe7IrfYicAcYZizd6N0uC31nROIcFFlIlo7ZQYPOdUzSmoZ5TZIe1ryi6PKQXxYzS0CnlngCPXnnVArcO4+imtUdQ+xRsxk7t20cYuOdaM1qbT4V74gAeOz37RCKlsFBSausOl4lCPqY029d+IuzfY4PH92vTS/tkeYw9X/4dsI0+0kuga9yY9Ecq1extYseXeZRToLTirJh0U487nlnt9zoc7HW819wtJkJAWbsl409jxsjskJo1rGzf6sEFD0oZ1Sw7aNLux3mnq41w+eToqa44tvSk4qAGVO0Bsm3+VWikRl49l7dkdkBZiaWZPkmWswjqfgycKdjWOlVGrjnNSmUIkRF3y", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050131", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb79jW+Vc4+zxtymYE4480rfMSL2LyW+w25iALCyXWYR7MkBVGLp8e85FGVpZF4vMPNmDzf/fW5kvnAsJ4JZw1c/8ZzalW7gqEa7CM7Ecu7ZgFC9eHCYEDkLyawGwBdy87ixXtnhsobFDN0yBEGropYZdV6xYztv3I4MMBlEja0pk1U3tR1TFeXev29w3vh7kE2dHZrY4tuqCIn4QmTOhRzm2KSWC1Ymoll+ZAYkQlqc2ZTiGThljadhSWKepXq6In5i+vp4ouKDI1IiLL6k27FLlx0Iqg=", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/IXnFBi5RoWqXErd8dTHxUabRYeO+wIQxIV2Fnl45oLDgcbBIQ1kx++Pbe7CGMA==", 
		"explanation": "24KwYZ32kRXj+YI1Ww3mzP6/NmTeEGsVpm2CRqp7fmKjXKbUa638zJJ/Z13JnlJ8/H/Aqqbx+UdPialY/YGNMCsNPoh9zdGd3urwhH9EJIZXjoFm4YlfffpEjCijfdvVYOpr3HyJM0ribjyuSDBgnDTPynRXvob7+yivFNgyxRtygo99rdszMNLf26mA4V74sQ6L0H7RRLRqFkGQptqh6AOUr483ssiDtDvP7bT6m/aT89EFdhpbvZNrZhuomOgI/CcxX8GnfABK5e3GZBToJi6qJAcY98j6mjRg0sIgTik6+wsGlotTIs992oGkuSEjOsN+HDK240JBxIBzTVeQe6/43Wnt7kE+fHQia40tvSk4qAGVO0Bsm3+VWikRkYZt99MQkApgZC0ZulGeZXvBO1bZC0HeaCBI", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050132", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRpX6ARqxmYzH0UbXHLu7xx4R4I1mbiF878G+Gt631t3UOlaQbyIKWMAEMc4Zm28OA2Oq3zX8BIcNHlY1/4ZQbdfpHjCmlcZTJJfF8yW+OLl/xczCyCjB7knHFnn1CrZDkySmHWvt6gCUgk5R9/949KN6Q1+ic7g2sjgPCyXWYXKQkEFqd9d2t6FaOqZYh9cKL8SbT8bT6le3d5MwSXgZw8sY/T1KykL0A6z4xUoi1ZhYL8vHcdUH/ISTjLwEQ9szm2HFg0psVU0p5tF8Gp4BZbM9+35ukvz0+LMRuECG7t01PyYdAUTPbNP2U0Wbj9VQ4cDoqdsp5tCh1sgCQLRR8m3iVX2xXm5Ir7NUWhwNic2ZanWLpjTHJOlZhSRw+5rQMpVlmUd1gpg==", 
		"answer": "25T0KLOz0Bfut6ZiZgS7snuJDJaCUqGFoNYd0w==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHV0APmt6QsW17RyvDyPHjDCm0f43yMXLB9dHTxUaOCfv/72pJjMV2dhFR1snnA47D+/kcWz6lV7c6MdSEWbIJ70ZzJ2+35w2RIINJNmcBz6p5ff+FM2Ci/ddibKPFjwWmFKUD5cyDxRHV3mz/Zh3VV6IC0+zSyUN8lwQE7mYlroYg9MtPfybqc5UKsjwmMnHSXCKphHVKYp8vo30uZ4IE3uMCEoiHS+/q5iP3Z9d0fZwwSq456I1Wzg6EG9mo3V4ihextF9qTcYFrqNSmkIk4c6ov33nEp1Y0lWCk29QxPkcNQbdIzxJ3rrjUxMcRwFCezrEoCa7wVCdRPKz5dbXkqVR0TsQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "B, C and D only", 
		"option_b": "A, B and C", 
		"option_c": "B and C only", 
		"option_d": "A  and C only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050133", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDbe7r25ZlIlCQzV9+4XXUqqf1t0cHiuhY+4ueZCsMcMtgzpCaw+XjwWIBMshA2pV87ZURPOBF3i+kYNvJKft9kVKOG0vRKnn9N3l/nzjbymtXu8O/8DSyU9Q21BA21oZrrckyfNaMyqeQ4Uysg0aRyHqFTf1xH1Ccp46840bc89csvY2uvjzI4P3tj+za/9AKbkhzsoNxZ1a5mbxJ2SksbcaWJVIL3+XXYFjsLizjMA8OucjixGJswsImSH10+xkGlotTItNn14zh/D02f+x5BjK341BPh5V4WwWTZ674xGDhoHs+cntraIV7uSAwrxugJncz2iu7Qy0d1KRq89EX2URic2sAuH/1wiiOkmDPfZDy/onugOywpqts/+MzIUTABVPKQpgbcLbTIidmwvuUGKFUc49oGyvlOJUv/y3wL5io0R1AkJkELnrm+mqYnMm1HWyv84X8nNE2F60FN8XA7Yu2oxzUZDPgM3yHY4vhVwH/QTzs1hx3vgwq2igV+yLZDp16520ZlnvwRU1mlzXheHWumP5T7MKpcI9zcrO90GvvE2PI8dG5fdmPmg==", 
		"answer": "25T0KLO/kTqq9oskEjqwwNsiClI665YbD0Io+R14+A==", 
		"explanation": "24axY5r63Fno8oYhXxuyxPO/NHjDDGEYomuGErBgcWXmFLLMaujsiYN5Ihza2E9zslfLpqv0+lYBm+h66prfcSwHPodu3NWbl/P21zFHJspIg8B76o4ae+ZB2DipNN3VNPEu2maFZ2z+YzC8CjBBmjjZhDxUscOv/SL7B4wjyFUTm4J26cU5MsPf+KuHqsYQvsLE6Vln/zHJGZqvTr0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "B, C and D only", 
		"option_b": "A, B, C and D", 
		"option_c": "B and C only", 
		"option_d": "A  and C only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050134", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQr+9pElQV7lwO/6dWjCBmMFpnvDULo0cnjlQbXBb/n3xpkxKE7JiVJt+2XPrKuw8UEAguh55oOdcTtDbZ9u3NXW6+rLylAMc+tFkoFg5YkXaOZB8DOPOZT8NfRv3G+UG0vTKnn9KXFwnCjXykxEqYe+5i+HWv56gFUTmINq7IgMLtab3Lub1EOEiC6NyzucSbN9UVuf9dqg7gOPtIMssMCIvyaU57T+k+7W/p4KYAdEusZ2cBS9ha1J+yUqQ823fE0Jyyer+M0ABvVgOk/NzEKZ5Q==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25q2ZIiz8Fnr+YFgcF7z1/i/NmTCEWcStz+/XJ96WX+jBf6UPqG+3Z90Z16AgVJ19WPHr+Xj41IbiuhU7869fy8Bf5Iv39Gal+D+0nhFNsIc2ol88JVfaONPjC6oZNXJIeprjn2UJlH1dEqQBXh1hjDFgmhEqcO9+jX7edslwQE6n8dr/c09N96R3uiD7UKoigPC3XWVCJpxG1WLtNro7UyO4KUtv8yfsCbStOfpn/nY+dAMIhhXsJZzZhubgqII6issEd+1e1JO4vDRY1jkMyCmI04c6ov33nEpl9c9VSkn4B5Sh8NZZIBn3p2klTw0NsxkVQa0qktOhZ0Nsk5NCNaZRTnf/HHdRBI=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "all Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050135", 
		"question": "24GwbdHf2Bft4owzRhfxhc3tOn3ZDWEUsD+gXa55eWLwXajMIq39wZZ4NVmNzVliskXt44H49kFDz7pe6oGSfScNeo5riMKM2PbwxX9IKc9KncBh8JsLeecAzjy+cdCbL/Au8VG/GHrPWAaCO09Lqw7pym5XvIu+52evXNs5gBk7mIBt5NsoNdTf36mQ/EKqlUSHFzxoIZBBE5v4vpv8pxV/", 
		"answer": "27S8ZZj92Ar+5YQ0Wwj3hf7wO33VDWsUrXyGED6cHoyvmhaDiwQW/JLd11U=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHf2Bft4owzRhfxhc3tOn3ZDWEUsD+gXa55eWLwXajMLvjwzZJjZ2+izX9z82SGsLD38FYcm61fqZqXcTZDbZ9u3NWal/f/y2RNN4ZGn8Bg4ZUNe/VOxSeocJTZIe1ryi6PKQXxYzS0CnlngCPXnnVArcO4+imtUdQ+xRsxk8dq7Nw0OcXfzaCS5g20jwiFyXKCXLRnUVKYttqn+VDeuMRtnJ4QSyNcSFsStIPHdA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "ad,mi,ni,st,ra,ti,ve, co,nv,en,ie,nc,e", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050136", 
		"question": "24GwbdHAxRj+8pZgYBv91/r+O2LDAnYYrHHDc6BgMH7lFPabO7u+yJV+K1WahV5/smLOpuX0/kAbhqZY/YeQfmIBe594zdWHl9T21mUBEoZFlIQy1JsNaLRijC65dcDeM75vwGrAJFf1Zi24ADB6kSaWmWhXvIaotSa1UJoizhw9mMds6NouNcOQy6GW+w26hxWH2DueRv1wGVHZp8ur5E6RpYw8tNmEvjzItPv/2uzb9Z40XTdtgLlAXGSDqJc2xxV68mwlYMCeG3D1AwCBJRyp2w==", 
		"answer": "25O5cp2z8BXjt6YvXxP71u72OmWSyXQ8igx3FIA7UYs5C7nSDw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHV0APmt6QsW17RyvDyPHjDCm0f422GUax5fXTtUKLGLvn2zNdjIlObilp1+2zHt6z/+RMAiehI/Y+LdTFDf4VriMSB0qT01nRAJ89LlMB94toReeMA3ymsYNHIYP9gyi6VKUz/aXmpAWJmnSXZmHVTu8O59DS+UJo4zlUhk5F9/8kwfNGe2ryc+l7667amwmgmQ3w7EZb/36gD0g==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Fa,zl, Al,i, Co,mm,is,si,on", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050137", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRrl+ogpQQ37yvO/J27TDG8cpnGHV6c0YnTsRqDDYOTkwJl2Z0+djE9+4TbEorb18xMAgeha7YOWfisQaplu3Nmf0qT0y39XNshNn45x4doNfeBIyS/tYNzaLr5ix2CHMkzjczC+RHZ1lyXZmG8J6smTkIIIKS3iPwIQbftb01w=", 
		"answer": "25GwaYOz8hbn+owzQRf9y7/ERXhGRUr5bWYXiDArU34u", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHf2Bft4owzRhfxhc3tOn3ZDWEUsD+gXa55eWLwXajMLvjwzZJjZ2+izX9z82SGsLD38FYcm61fqZyafzAEf4Vm0tmH0KTk0HBVNtUElY4y5Z4SdfpJ3ym/dcDSNvsuzWGOMUD+bjyzB3U41D/ZnjxCoIb70yahWJoWzBxytYh14MEvL96Q1+rScWgccM78jhLY4Q8Mz5ii", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Fazl Ali Commission", 
		"option_b": "States Reorganization Commission", 
		"option_c": "Dhar Commission", 
		"option_d": "JVP Committee", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050138", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5EoV17m0vK/NmTeB2sFqnCNQeN4cXjnFKPNeeO+y44xBk6dhFh39zaV46r2t0cHiuhy54qWcSxDXYRh28SAw/HjzX5Pc9RBnYFg4JMRe7RUxDjtfdrPMvFq222ULkr+Jza7RHE0ljjahjxQp5H79i+6Wt0y01Ugk4t5+c04fMOQmbyb7Q2+iRSP3W+YR7MkHlLZptqp/0aP4I0q9diDuD3VtOD8iOra5NEZaw1B4MTe0eaCfC9nnxGxKuIYDWP+", 
		"answer": "24WqYZ7hkQvv9IotXxv8wfzrPGTeQ20X42uLV+NEYnTwXaPHYPm+yJl1Z0iBiBtt+3PRsOX/8RMbh60b+pqeZCdDco5owcOF1vDi1nQDYAtptRsz6XrD/4T9yk4wMw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eh/81ur6JyvZECIT6j+zQKp7YjHxUaTNY+D7x5NwM1WGgxt09DbSq6Cwx0EKnKFf7ICLMCMNest7wNXJwe3y02IBPMAEjoh3pIkLfeBFjDGoc93ILP9623yFZ2TiczC+CHU0x3HEj21DoZG+5mevXNsjgBRylI504Yg6M8Xf2qCS5kq9lUaQ2XeQXLhgUUCW9d286leZs8I3p42YvzvU+rTtn+rB+coEcAFXrMZydkio16AI7i94RcCxKCJZ9PfZZVHjNG+wZx4P8MTxlmZsxY0kUGw68B5Si4xYIsF90tj3tD0lM8kqFzb6sUFGwoZuWhPWYLL4xGDhoFYwe3kud4RouG0mtQ6ILRRyn2yVXyBQgJV5+5AfmhYjaWdFlWSglDaOl3bN84HM1fbW7PTcJmfAzTPXhQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Prior approval of the Prime Minister and state legislature's consent", 
		"option_b": "Prior recommendation of the President and the views of the state legislature", 
		"option_c": "Consent of the state's Chief Minister and the approval of the Lok Sabha", 
		"option_d": "Prior consent of the Rajya Sabha and the Governor's recommendation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050139", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQzk/oouEgr31+/2IWTCGiIGomzDW619ZHjiWKvbLuz6xJ5/Lk+diEl+9jbHsOXx+RNIjqtK/IeNdSZDao592tmd2PbugzFDNsBLiIUy5p8WcvMAwTypcZTaYOtgx2GOZ1H1dSu0EH9mjXHUkzxX6KC0+zSvXc4i1Bw9mIZ0rekxOdmb1K2d/A2ZhRLdnvk/SQFs2h2/CicOddXuU1M=", 
		"answer": "24WtbITw2Rz45ZxiOBopAOl5hwJv6qnBbAMUMA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHVwxzk9I1gWh/8wfj7dWTGBnBRt3eKQeNgdWPxXbPNfPS+3ZgxDlKNhFo7+3iG8vyloxM8mqpI7J+KdSwXcpIjiNmdl/P21zFAN8tNlIlh8J8NefAAzS7tddqbWP9t33uJNUD0Jy24FmJ9gD7EkwUa6Jey+Sv7BYNhklUlnoJ2rcEofMCeyuie6Um9xgfCyXWYR7MkBVGLp8e85FGF4IAh9dmFtHKKoODx2tvc/s0faxxHq49wbVqw14kE/SQ8XM26fFJq8vCSg3w6e3hwf7MSV/QBkmW7Hw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Lakshadweep", 
		"option_b": "Daman and Diu", 
		"option_c": "Chandigarh", 
		"option_d": "Puducherry", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050140", 
		"question": "24KwbZ+z2A2q9IotVw2y0fK/M2TCDmsfpD+CEq1xZzHwQKbWa63x29dkKVWGgxtv92TUqrH/5UpPjbEb/ICWZCsNectuiMCIxfC3y3cBMshd2pNm5Y4aPPtSjCijfdvVYOpr3HyJM0rifnX9E3h1gHHXn2hep5Gy4T77UNUy01UmnoI43do5L96b3KaHqAW3lEay3WmdQbxpFFqN/I6g5E+Y4IM7tsKftTvV87TtlbjH+NtLSwZWtodxI3izmbsd8T4tRcG7Zk0JkNuFFCLrfGiJmjurkBWtPA==", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHDwxz5/oElXAqyjfLtdVvREW4YonKGXLc9MHjwFKnNeq38xoJ/IxyLlBtv+nOGtaz14EBPgK4b/YaaMDEXf59qiNyM0O3kyHBVJtRB2oF84NocffoAzT6uccTPYPF8jnyFLUDzc3mpDHV51npLutvOoAviRkheIW2vTk0=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3gv48oY0Eh/81ur6JyvZECIT6j+3WqY0QGPmR67Ga+Pqid9+NRy5jEl3+3fLpqvkvhMGnOhV5prfci0WcI8vysnJw+zyhGdINtFX2o90pI4XebRT2Dy5cZTXJfln3WKBM1DiYnm8CnQ0lzDYyn1Vq4ar4We0RpolxR83lZM4+cA5MZer0a3TwUO8jweMnFieRq5wGECMocen5QObsoM2od7NpTretMTrn+va9NsFdkgasJQ/U1qum6EI9S82RYH0fBpOseXFdVziMiG3Pk4J9ovu139shoYsXmAn/RBIkcNEZ8dyxJztsjVwK8VvVTW1sUlB051zUVeZcv221X+k80E+YX84JYV//Dg7qACSaEB7iHmVWCNDnYV4spALkANib2tMmWXzwjCNwHGHedPw/4HogKj8pb5q4a8mPVSSMBvLFpsVYKTTZffpB1jlyB9qwq8M63PQTnY=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "The President (or Parliament) must always accept the views of the state legislature", 
		"option_b": "The President (or Parliament) is not bound by the views of the state legislature and can accept or reject them", 
		"option_c": "The President (or Parliament) can only proceed if the state legislature unanimously agrees", 
		"option_d": "The President (or Parliament) can proceed without considering the state legislature's views", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050141", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskXDt7H88l4Kgbwb5ojfcWIBcZ5hzNGbzqTzzWJRJtJB2oJ38I0aefoA5TOpfdWbIfBqjm+OKFH4Yiv9B39hmiXEkzxErZKu/DW+R5o2gBY9mJRs5NwpKN6Q16mfqEy1gwiG0X6fXP1xH1Ccp46J+VeVo4499Z7b6Q7VyPrKjvnH9dMObBwSlq8lI2+0kug67ToqVMWxKDFE5PbEIUb4LC2nZwcTuZq6gC0p0oooSSk1tB1Jl41SY9JqlpztryIlK8gqBzaprEhV051zUVeBfamwkGnq70E3cGhrZoV4sjknuE+fKVo+mG7cTS9ZnYV9+9RZgQxxcnpHlDblmjqIlXGGapaj6oPojOf+4Lht9uMjJkSTdVLXQs0SYLDFNHR73uiPCOZdc5xoGTHyNME76DD2LpeYnzgA1dckInLp4BaXrsPJN1KyupHxzttwVKsIM5HW/cqjtVHCbzfyYXqacM76GQnyQGr9kwd2+Bk3zWET53DKDYprtzIjb5koD3GxsCTAt87UA5o=", 
		"answer": "25yRKJ793QCoM596CAFrxx3aStwiPM62Ow==", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhfv+OXjVQ2AEtz+qe+N9YzH3RrLHUuPCx5RyKE6NhFV8smLJ47H48hM8mrhJ7IOaMAEMa5l7j8PJxfH7zX9Gc89K2tErssNTPOdF2CmhcdneLuouwWjAJgXyaCyzAHFmjXHSg29GvZe+tSW+QM0yxRtyv4l85Ml8Pdmbmamd51mwgxTC33SERql2CBSdusu7q02TtMIqsNyYuCDetPW5mffd48oCdh1GtolxYlf8lqUM9i41VMagKCZD9KTCZFX+LybjLh1d78rv33ApxIcqXHwn8V9SioYWUdVjxJ3puXITMNh4AXO/sFBBxZh1TB+TcP2s2GnwoFAncHk+cYN7uW00ohuVJ1o+mWqSDC5U1JV4+9RZkwtxPX1Fj3nslDaFhyWcaZDrq4T1lvjltLxwvuMmOgGJIRzcWYgPJb3PMyd7xP+UAbBZc4tvEmLlOMY99Tb3YJmSnxAD1NAhITfz8TiLm9n6K3z6p525j5RwG60FP9bLqci4pVLTczqjV30VRMM+Q4Y/kuZdegpz8Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050142", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQr+9pElEgnz1r35OnndBmZRoWbDRqJ/eX/kFLPKa63QyJBwZ3SAgVdosnfIp+XE4lYBnKlV7s6eYicCPoR63JCG0aTW12JAPpkGDkm/W2UOhW89E81m1ZQLHQ==", 
		"answer": "25u5b5D/0BfutdGJg1mtvHrHoARD40ZfGV8=", 
		"explanation": "25y2KMCqh0qmt5EoV17B0fzrMCvfBSI/oniCXqJ6dDH0VbSCaOLsxJJ1dgzJj0I75nfNqqv3t0cHiuh16ImeMAoKcod8iNGH06TD0XRPIMdKncBz9p8ePPtV2H2icpTPKPsu3XqBM0CwaD/9JWNnlTyWvnRfu8Os9DT7UNU5xVUmmcdr7Nw1L9GGmbyb7Q21iRCH0X6fXP1rFxSNvcvo40yPtIs0sI2jsDXa57ZVDF59LlKJthlS+X51S5Ba", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Manipur", 
		"option_b": "Mizoram", 
		"option_c": "Tripura", 
		"option_d": "Nagaland", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050143", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQvv8IwvXF79w73WO2/ZAiIGqmuNV7BndXWjVefPb+fx29dyL12Hil47+3iGqrHjt0MAg6FP4I2efGIOf5svwd7Jhr2gljFWOtJM2pR64docbvFB2DSiepTUJr5gy3nANFHxczyuRHF6kHHDhHVZpsOv8DWpXc440hw3hdg6VMTV+zWfJ4WYH23WHFlkQg==", 
		"answer": "25u3eoX71Bj548UJXBr7xL9qcyK5+Se9rz45Qhy5BrKt", 
		"explanation": "25u3eoX71Bj548UJXBr7xL3sNHyQAiIconWMQON3eHDtU6KCZ+O+wINiZ0yGgVJv+3XHr+X99kNPhqYbuNfIIm5DaYJ7wJCH0vO312VAJ8NX2oF84NoKcv1Pwn25ccbJKeph3GeFNAXyYjCzAzB3hjTXnnlS6ulnz41y4jTEHyFy5ym7WNI=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Central India", 
		"option_b": "Western India", 
		"option_c": "Southern India", 
		"option_d": "Northeast India", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050144", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV17gwO7qOX+QDGRRt3eGEol1fXz2FKbMaq3VyIR5KlWbzWl+/WTBoqv55FIbhqdVqa+cZG5DLNs+kY/LIWbpyX2DoVO1Gs8FlBSjIQ==", 
		"answer": "25aqbZDn2Bbkt4omEgrlyr3qO2LfDSIFpm2RW7d7YnjmR+XbIejl14Sl48bj5xByjI5g", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHZ0BTn4sUhXBqy7vzsPWbZESIjpnCRVaJ6eWLiQK7NYK3fyoM9Zw7Z3AI3snTPpbDi9FIbiqwb/YaaMCcRbZ94wNmF0qTE0HBVNoZLnMBY5ZcSabRBwjntX9XIKPNn3C6JKVH/Jy2qCzBnkSHXmH1CrcOu+y60WpojxQcgn5N3/8E5L5vf16me7UGhykaW1H7RXbNtHlrZocu6+UqIr5Ah9cKL8Rja+fns2r6T298YagVbrcZ+bV/8g6AMuD82WMe6KAZO4/bZdVv/OWisIU4x+M/i3Xwrcq1w80EtPyCTgmXcMPJybA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Conversion of Ladakh into a state", 
		"option_b": "Creation of two states", 
		"option_c": "Merger of Jammu & Kashmir with Himachal Pradesh", 
		"option_d": "Creation of two union territories", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050145", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskLOpuXg+EQKnehU786vcTAPd4pizd6dl/D4hHVIPs9Kk5N6pI4XebRB3jisZ5TUJr5vjn2UJlH1J3GoCnRxhnH3mGhfq4++tXTyFNM5wxknkoJrrdw0OZeP1r+W+g2siUaB2X+UCJRqFV2Yu4687lGOqZY3p9TNpT2b9bT/lerW+dkFIgtdqohrcUKAmZQHyz45Rc25bRxfsc35O2DlJWiQMh4P/Mbmlldm05A9Gnp08BpFi5Bfbc4z35ak7Wtmb41/BTu/r0AA05x9S1e3Zqmx02ThoAZ/enxrcYJo/AQ7pQadJhRdlWWPWCVFgZRi8d5ZkQtmbi9Ok2Kgwj6HjGqYPKPi+Yz1hOX1rq0j5qxnKkSEMBzxWIkVZL2AM2Jg2OCPArRFc4toVyOmO9o8+TD+LtaX0CwDxMs5b2Du4CKWh9m1Omq0oIbwmsFiHbAON92F6MayvljKZC31YWidYs7mGQniW3X73wsl5E599C8s5l7WP4F29iVNkXC1CUti0jPoaTynmbJQ5ZWHcYlx2uas3j0CivF7i9v+2l0uQheriHxX8ouZD0hHyBTXHMIRwUk9GLUVEZvU/HmFyjR3jxOwmiUxoFlpdpSdnQ8V", 
		"answer": "24asaYX23Bzk48gJEhfhhfTxNmTCEWcStz+BR7dIfjHQQKbWa+D7x4M8DnXJhEg78XnUsaDz4xHRAuuJ73D4+2Q+RYj/3dDh", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHgxRj+8oglXAqy7L32JivWAm4Cpj+CXKc0Y2XiQKLPa+Pqib5YZ1WazU9p53OGorawt2cHiuho/J6NdS8GPqhg3cKdm6T+yjFIJ9UEnoVx7YkWc/oAxTPtJY2NcL58y2mBNUH5aT79EHhx1DLTmW9fp437+iH7dt8l1RczhI442MY1M9nfzafT2EyzjxWW3XXdCL5oFFWLudfo40aQpMIsvcyZ8SbT8bTple/W4p4EZEhivpRzalqxkqYduD43Ecy9ZRtF+PfYIUDlJWiiNQscucTllnUp1ZYoSWx04RFCh5EWQ9Jn35vouXJjf8llECD6rUtUh5dzSRKENKmw1Sjn5UYsfHUlJYVr/AQ7pQadJhRqn3mORThehpkr6t9ZlERlcn1FlXHuwjyElWubboqj34j5xev/tat3srEyJUSEdUjQV5lcZrbTNG59xKmUC+Z1PZtuFiymKdA87jDtL4SNny0CkNhgKXj18SOenI3mLWSuttL6j9o2G7EML5HH7Iuzv1LCITfpM3KGYcO0WEjzQHLrxwdxogwsxy8R5CLZBYxx8SAIkGrwXEpglzWgTW61n71Q78LdKdZz+mbSfaDZjuq3XOUgyQY0Mg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_b": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is not the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_c": "Statement-I is correct but Statement-II is incorrect", 
		"option_d": "Statement-I is incorrect but\n Statement-II is correct", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050146", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTrl+ZY0Wwrn0fTwO2rcQ0McpnGHX6Z6ZDHCV7OCZ+Pq25h1Ml+MiRtv+nOGoKr+9FYfm+hU786efmJEf5h8x9OA1vDyhGJVMtJB3d8w3ULGE4nl7rTpB03Rz1oBig==", 
		"answer": "2+btfJmxSfK3wRUv4cwusH/lc3ZWjw==", 
		"explanation": "25y2KMCqhk2mt7YpWRX7yL36LXvCBnECpnvDW7dnMHXmR67Qa634xoUxIE6MjE9+4DbHsLb/9FoOm6FU586IeTYLPqJhzNmIl8X0x35TN89KnYxrqNoLdPEAn2i5fJT4L/B92meUMlH5aDe8CDBVmTTYjnFTppf71CSvFJJmmUJm38dv7Nt8Odme2ryW7A26n0aW1H7RWLx2HV2YuMum/wOoqIsr9cyAtDzf+fH3jrja/soZbQxHvIN7I1r8ma0euCk0UNunKB1NsffEYEDoKCesI04I98/mxDR9zodpXmY65wtPlpZCa899lpr9/DE/MctvByGzrUMAyJo8bB6df7S1kHzs5RUsYXs/cJktsyt1oAHcUFVtiWSfRS1FkcB46tENkH0jcmkAiH7lwhaFhGyOctPW5Ynzi6rnn6WaEndnccZEarjOGZ8c", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "38th", 
		"option_b": "37th", 
		"option_c": "36th", 
		"option_d": "35th", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050147", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQzk/oouEgr31+/2IWTCGiIGomzDV69xZnD3UaOCeuK+3Z90Z0+djE9u4TbJpeXxt1Uag6Qb+pqeZCdDd4UvmYnehru1Gya8KrL7vmDxV8SXNUumyg==", 
		"answer": "252xZZDw2Rjmt7UyUxr31vW9NR3UYouyeH2xNm6ZLo2LPQ==", 
		"explanation": "25q2KIX71Fn48oYvXxP3y/n+IWLfDSIepT+XWqY0Q3niXOfhYeDzwIRiLlOHzRMqqyCQ6umw41sKz5hO54SecitObZtqyduA2eO3xWNEMtUEjYVg4docc/pT2DS5YcDeJL5nwHqPZ1H4YnmoCnl4nT/Rn31a6JCv9DO+FNUxgCUnmI1574R8KN+amYCa5kmxlRaH3XCYRrokEEactN3o/EaOpcI7usOepTvP4eD8nrja/soEIhxausZMd1qokugG/moQUNqtaRxKseXeZRT5KC3jLwcR9YvixHFo1cI+WHsxtBJDkIRTZoBk34zs/CY4Oo1rETm1qkpJyZM8Shmfe7P4xG328lwremgyJYVr/AU8rA6fIFVy2luOTShUh4gr195ZxF00LCMAiH7lwiqFiWqBPIfm+ZL1kefiufls9OMPIEyBNlTZWs0sd7LEInR6iv6aHuZZP5pxFjbjOYR8vC32YIKc2nkexNg0OmSn+yzZk43mLWSuttAFTtWhdgB5BsOXjQpsdth2", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Goa", 
		"option_b": "Jammu & Kashmir", 
		"option_c": "Haryana", 
		"option_d": "Himachal Pradesh", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050148", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQr+9pElEgnz1r38J27RF2cV432aEqB1YmfqWqCCYfjqiYN5Ihy9iFdu9WOLsLX19lgGga8b6JyacTFDcY0v4MmN0vb2xnBFc9VQm5R3pJsReLRNyS+qfdrcYOpmy2PAMEzkb3mpDHU0tT/Sgm5X6JCv9DO+C5i/3G3lSH4bjk6iHbvWresB", 
		"answer": "25S2bJnh0Fna5YQkVw36h+6J6pkOyXOhOo5/ZynA+1Y=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHAxRj+8pZgYBv91/r+O2LDAnYYrHHDc6BgMDmyDfKUJ63zzIV2IljJmVN+skLDr7D34h4cn61a4oeRd2ICbI5u25CG0aTf3XVEIcdGm4Qy944eaPEA2zS5fJTPKPsu72CEL1fxJyqpBWRx1CXZyn9ErYKv8GevXN93xRs+l5V/6Mx8Hdmb0bqSqH2qhwKHz3PRW6llBVHZgcatq0CdsIsstMHNvjSb4Pz82uvH8coOIh9TrMZsa1K6g60NuD43EeCtbBdZ8ObRZRYPtWaIPHSiJRQI1277pRG2", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Telangana", 
		"option_b": "Karnataka", 
		"option_c": "Maharashtra", 
		"option_d": "Andhra Pradesh", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050149", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV17i1/TyNHnJQ2QQoGuMQONgeHD3FKvHaq3qxtdlL1nJjkl+82LPrKuw+FVPm6BeqZuReS0NPp9q2sKAw+vl3TFONYZqm4dz6JsReKsCEaLUgzTFcbLisLEBHUl77w==", 
		"answer": "25S8bIP2wgrj+YJgRhb3hdP+MmqQDm0HpnKGXLc2sgiRUoUxvHi2V7K/COKIvw==", 
		"explanation": "25y2KMCqh0qmt5EoV17B0fzrMCvfBSI/oniCXqJ6dDH0VbSCaOLsxJJ1dgzJj0I75nfNqqv3t0cHiuh16ImeMAoKcod8iNGH06TD0XRPIMdKncBz9p8ePPtV2H2icpTPKPsu3XqBM0CwaD/9JWNnlTyWvnRfu8Os9DT7UNU5xVUmmcdr7Nw1L9GGmbyb7Q21iRCH0X6fXP1rFxSNvcvo40yPtIs0sI2jsDXa57TRle/W5tsZLkhQuoBwcV78kKEf8SQ/Eea1bxNH8OrUIUDlJWiwMw8J7Nij2XIp0oosHThi4BcGkZdXdsUz2Z6kqDo1f+RkETq7rQR1yZ1zUVvWfan4x2n3oEUzdHkuYcp4sikws0+IIFE+mWSSWD5emMBk+JAemhJmb2FPjjbvhH+qk3aOcdPq5cCt3L6h4jj2HZohvH27dG0e78492Mk=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Addressing the Naga movement", 
		"option_b": "Economic development", 
		"option_c": "Language diversity", 
		"option_d": "Addressing tribal conflicts", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050150", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sU0Vwz/1r32OyvzDG4ErnHDc+NjeWXrFLPKa+TsiZR+NU6Mjk879nPVoLf550cGgKZIqYeRMAEMcp5ixpCrlcq7iOpGjn+tMRlRlqBBp0M=", 
		"answer": "25K3adHX0BTr+cUhXBqy4fTqeFvfEXYEpGqGQaY4MEH2ULLBZujs2448AU6Mg1hzvjbnraHx+lIBz6lV7c6xeSEMfIp9iPma2+X5wGINc+RWk5R795JTVvVNwSjtMpTwIe1mw2eSamv/aTz/+fBiUDdPKZcmRdOBNVkwkA==", 
		"explanation": "25K3ad2z9Rjn9otgUxD2hdn2ICvHBnAU43yMXqx6eXTwFKjELvn2zNdBKE6dmFxu92XD45Xl80YMh61J+5ffZyMQPoovzt+b2uHlhFdTNshHksB3944efvhJ3zWgcdrPYN9gym+NJkuwZje5RF59lz7Ui24WgZC39Cm/R5ogxQc31pJ26c0ufPWN0Lya+0X4lBOO2TmGpfpgVwfu5snTxKP/mGMX", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Andaman and Nicobar Islands,British", 
		"option_b": "Jammu & Kashmir,None", 
		"option_c": "Puducherry,French", 
		"option_d": "Goa Daman and Diu,Portuguese", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050151", 
		"question": "25y+KJCz3xz9t5Y0Uwr3hfL5dX/YBiI4rXuKU600RX/qW6mCZ/6+3ZgxJVnJjkl+82LDp+mw4FsGjKAb5oCaMC0FPp9nzZCP2Oj7y2ZIPcEEiYN64Z4KcPFTjDKrNMDTJb5NwWCTM0zkci20C340mSTFnjxUrcO6+CK1UN8zn1UJxNcovPV+ImWM3I60Be8j0iH9m1cByA==", 
		"answer": "25OxeoLnky61co/dxocwOSPPfdBG9mk=", 
		"explanation": "25OxeoLnkQrp/4AkRxL3hf7wO3/RCmwC43GCX6ZnMH7lFLPKa63N3ZZlIk/JjFV/skPysOmw41sOm9FIqZmXaWIKast8wN+c2+C3xnQBMstBlIR34NZfdfIAzX2jccObM+pv2mvALlawZCu4BWRxkHPpHjec/9TZBruWG21A1CGK", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "First", 
		"option_b": "Second", 
		"option_c": "Third", 
		"option_d": "Fifth", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050152", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbk8sUvVF7mzfi/M2TcD20GqnGEErB3eHTnQavHfa3xz9dlL1nJpFV/+3fI44b/+UAbhrxO/YeQfmIPd5h725Cd3+G3ynBMNtUElYYy944eaPFTjDyjcJTIMPttx2iJIlawczG4DWI0gDTEmHVCp5Gy8DTkFOFlkEVhq8VOojTB3pbNhWdXpSgdjHzA", 
		"answer": "25OxeoLnky61co/dxocwOSPPfdBG9mk=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdG09xD45JFgYR36wPnqOW6XQ20X42uLV+N3f3/wQK7We/n3xpkxI1mIgUg75X/Sq+X8/kAbz6ddqb2LcTYGbctuxtTJ4ur+y38BB8NWiIlm64gWeecCVGFfFbx59D1LiI5tnaM5tw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "First", 
		"option_b": "Second", 
		"option_c": "Third", 
		"option_d": "Fourth", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "050153", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbk8sUvVF7mzfi/M2TcD20GqnGEErBgcWXmWaLMev6+yphjNVmKmVdisnLDsKbi/lEKnOhP4YvfVi0WbJ9niOOK3+Hz0X1Ec8lC2pR64do8c/pT2DS5YcDSL/AuwWjADkv0bjjiREsmxGGCtz66nOmgAnDUJUMHGdp2tcSG", 
		"answer": "25ysKJD/3Rbp9pElQV7hwPzrJivZDSIFq3rDcaxhfnLqWOfNaK3N3ZZlIk/LNmies4M4FAf7RXQwZ4Enrg==", 
		"explanation": "25O3fYPn2Vn59I0lVgv+wL3+OWffAGMFpmzDQaZ1ZGKjXamCeuX7ibR+MlKKhFc7/XCGkLHx41Ycz6FeqbyeejsCPrhuytiIl6zC1GFEIYZslZVh4doQerRwzS+hfdXWJfB6hyyEsRuapPsaXoIvXyNCY8X8", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Union and its Territory", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "It contains the scheme of the distribution of powers between the Union and the States", 
		"option_b": "It contains the languages listed in the Constitution", 
		"option_c": "It contains the provisions regarding the administration of tribal areas", 
		"option_d": "It allocates seats in the Council of States", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060101", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIgKzk/kkKgbsb5ojfWSwHd4ovzd6D2P231GNOJ8NHjol96toee/VJwi65NNXJMvt92i6BKUGwYzypAX5gnT7YxjxBoIq38Ge+Wt862VUzmo5949t8ONjf16eHqEW5kAPCyHOYW/10A1uNsM284kySnIwLocyZtD/e+uC5s9GJzNBLSwYSloh7alrw16lJ9issRNq1ZBtR9OCQYl35KTKmKU4U6ovm2n1uz4AlWCkg+19OjY9SItR709jrujQ5PMgqGjX6k1ZF1J14WhmCSLOE3l/s6VY3NXUtJZ5luW0mtQ6ILVl7lH+PDCtYgoVlvtEbmhJmPWZT03fyh3+Ij3edeZD3qQ5uuuodNnGdSWByVpw39Bk=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz+Fnr+YFgezewDbm4SXZFF7HmzNz7mUMRzw==", 
		"explanation": "27OqYZT91RXzt4QsWxv81r36O2HfGiISpm2XU6p6MGPqU6/Wfa3/x5MxN06GmV545n/Jrbaw/l1PpqZf4I/TMDULd4dqiNWH0unuhHBNOsNKicB65YwaPPhF3y6oZpTJKflm2n3MZ0T+Y3mpDHVt1DXZynJZvMO++y20TZon0homk4Rs5McyfNaY2KGd+1n4hxSQ2WiFCLxqFRSdsNqt5VeVr4x4ocWI8TfX/fPwmPHf+coSIgtAtpJ6cVK9164G6mosWc30ZxRN+OfVIVvrYBixIh0U/c7twjRgyMIAU2099V9PkcNVa9R6zJ3q/D02f+RkETq74Y5AZkGa2lhoVVqWRqFJNCs=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060102", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDx1oZey7yK1R5o4xlUbmINx7Ig0PcGambyb7Q2qjwGKyDuFR/1hAEGYuce88gOTpsI3pd2CoybO+v3tg7ja/p4bdwpetoU/Zlasm6cQ9S82RfS6KCBO8PffbxSlEmH5ZzITuf/r0zRKyYw6SWAg4QtPjY0WbcYz/5bgtTNwONhrBzK0t0FF1NR6ShmSdbC93nzl7BUtfH0jcZktqCJ1qBuPaFd3jmKGSSJC2MBi8NMVgABqc2gAiH7lwi2Ch22bPIfsq4XtkOn8qa16sqIpLQGFJEnZWs0Id7bBM2p3xP3bGKhYNo0nAyrjfdkv63sMgw74HQuTiuQJ9zGDGLA1", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFgjO8rPV+nXo8G+gZITEyovIU=", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rwr7yvO/Om2QKmwVqn7DVbZ1YnDtQKLHfa343Jl1JlGMg096/jbUqqL440BPm6cb4JqMMCEKaoJ1zd6am6T+ynJNJsJNlIcy8JIaPOZJyzW5NMDUYPt/22+MLlHpK3m0FzB1mCLZymhEvYb79Cm/FMolzwM7koJrrdw0OZec1rqB7U6sxgOazHeQRrxwGFuX9cin+QOLqJt4tsSZuCje+ue5kvnF9Z4fag0SrY94a0/8g6dJ/TstUMS9fAsL/uKQbkT9Lzq3MgAU7dKj33op1pcrUWA3tBpLko9Ze8122IymaFuL3XhJNdKh3J1eF2fsjg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060103", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsXaEWrdnMHDtUOfSfOTowJt0IFmazVpp9zbFrKv28kEdiqwb/J6QfmIAd59m0tWHxKT4wjFoPcJNm99O6qYRXbkA/jSqfMCbNPEuy3+VJkn5cyD9C3Y0myHGhW5CvY2y4T77XdR30AAwmo57rc0xLNuQwKWW5lmEiCTPnDujQbpsBRSNuo6p+FqQtY94s8Kf8TfV8fng2vnf+dsFcTRcnMs/I2m1kKAduD43Ed67fBcL+OqQZFjoIzyqKAAOud/slmBhw8IFUmJ0xx5EioIWY853lovwvSY1f8FvEjqpr0VUzoJ5HxaFZ7i10mT93FsbODprV4NqtDl1tQDcIFtyniuIRCkRm4Zt99Mc1QtlPV9SmWXphjqFlCWAbtPV4oP5yNjipapq9qYpPQGPMxzxWIkVZI/OG2laxf7bAKdSKt9oEWLyNdBu7y34NJOZ2jcZn8pgKH7x8STZk8/6L2D6uoG2j8ZzVLwPJMPA6t/o8ipVvwIYYSwIkHKKMk91JgM=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxRH48oBihNe0hfegvQArXU1qVizr0A==", 
		"explanation": "25q2ZIiz8FWq1MUhXBqy4b3+J26QAG0DsXqARp96TH/XXKKCTeLw2oN4M0mdhFR1snXJraP15UBPm6BeqYiQfC4MaYJhz5Cb3uP/0GIBMshA2pBg7YwWcPFHyS7te9qbNPZrjm2JM0zqYjeuRH9y1BjYjnVX6Mu6+yP7UN85yRAh1pNw6IgvPdqambycqEy0jwOMzzLLdLMkI12evdro/0zcpZMttMGEpSub+/K5lejD/8wfdwZbq58/alX8g6AMuCc5RdyxelJE96TAdFbhKSvjIgMN9cT623Fn0sJhfHsg/RxKh8MHNIlP2Irtuzokf9llVTKpukhVytR6UAXWcbO93XGk4Vk2cHQ4JYtuqDg0rQOFaFB3iWiJXz9Uh8B/9tVZmQ1udHtBiH/vjCzLgWuLPIHm75X/gOywsrBk+rc0aU6GdVnWU4AFJbLMLmJ82amfGLRVPZgnACP0Kdwj+Xm5HJim1j4FxJk0IDfx+z6c0sT7eWC2tpHth9t4B/8UOZHR4c73nFPMIRDgI3WSJsr6XUjjW33s1k5psh8s2y0R/GvODcl+5j4Ik3y8UHhqlyvpa3Wjn7JV/pvOa4Fx2/rg2XITneZsnpL5lA0pRQiyjj9MtIKWTFlcgRTfEM4L0Q0nArNBAJ7Usl2EkGXZT3kDa473D6zH9SVL367BnGRutpQLW5jOIx+bo9AiwRb9QfxqFWjjrcb2O7wBAmFs6Lt2wvmy98m0e/WhPncva1qiSeBXs5ZYfAthFAXOR5dr50GqbY2/32nA3z/1LcY=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "all Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060104", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq9sUkRwrrhen3NH+QAGsFqmWGXLA0f3ejfanGZ+y+xoB0Z0iGmlpp9mWGt631t3oBi6Fa586sZCMXe9QtijVKhMmkHH2840n7tpIwSw==", 
		"answer": "24W5cZj91ln+9p0lQVziROggi0kYgkZkLtcqtTJ+", 
		"explanation": "27axfJjp1Bf5t4o3V1720On2MHiQEHcSqz+CQeNkcWjqWqCCeuzmzIQ9Z06Mnkt+8WLPraKw41sKz6Za/YeQfiMPPo1jydfFl+X5wDFFNsBBlIR76p1faPxFjD6iYdrPMucs0Nyv8NeC2bt6cH+yJ3Ol5A==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Respecting foreign citizens", 
		"option_b": "Voting in all elections", 
		"option_c": "Paying taxes", 
		"option_d": "Supporting enemy aliens", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060105", 
		"question": "25y2KIb70A2q5Iw0Rx/mzPLxdW/fQ2cfpnKaEqJ4eXTtR+fLYK3Xx5N4JhyBjE1+smTDp7Dz8ldPnaFc4ZqMMCEMc5tu2tWNl/D4hHdTOsNKnoxrpJsTdfFO32LvmHoB4VsHMc2iAXK59e38TA==", 
		"answer": "24KwbZ+zxRHv/pdgURHny+ntLCvZECIQtz+UU7E0Z3j3XOfrYOn3yNXM4OYTeBmD85Mq2uCB0uhi", 
		"explanation": "25C2bZzqkRjm/oAuQV77y73WO2/ZAiIZommGErFxdGTgUaOCfOT5wYNiZ1+GgEt64HPC47H/t1Udhq1V7YKGMCMPd45h25Cax+H0zXdIMMdIlpky85IacrRUxDikZpTYL+tg2nyZZ0zjJzipRGd1hnHBg2he6Kq18S66FO4/yQZyko5r+cEyP8OW1qbT4V74iweG2TuVXa9tH1PZocel7lDcr4R4tsKDtz7S9+C74UcOL6jGrjsNzpBYtTq1BQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "During peace and harmony", 
		"option_b": "When their country is at war with India", 
		"option_c": "When they have criminal records", 
		"option_d": "When they enter India without proper documentation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060106", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhv+zPr2N2LcCnYI43yRW7dxYnjsWufEYf++wZh9I1WHihtv+nOGrKP2/lAKz6ddqb6NdTEKeo5h3JCG0aTeynVIMooEm5My55USbPVSyTntYNubNPZrjluOLlH1Y3mOEHFgkSKJyKxw3NV9uZHEVvzGtu6XRCI=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz0Fnp/pEpSBv8hf/mdWnZEXYZ436NVuN1MH/iQLLQb+H305J1Z1+AmVJh93iGorf1t1YDhq9S64KaMCsNPqJhzNmIlbXln3svupxVmhfEz3CCfNY=", 
		"explanation": "25y2KLj91RDrt4cvRhayxL38PH/ZGWcf432aEqF9YmXrFKbRLvr7xZsxJk/JjBt182LTsaT8/kAKi+hY4JqWaicNPop9zZCM2+3wzXNNNoZClZIy8JIaPPtGyjSucZTUJr5e3GuTLkH1aS39E3h9mDSWg3IWnbCauWe0WtYugBRylY5s5NI5MpedwOiR4V+sjkaD0n/RRrJwUVXZu8+8/lGdrIsrsMnNsjvP/e78lLja454ObgFVtoRzZhu6mLpJ7CI9EceybhtI9KTfZxTdMi2wLgoY99+hkg+5zG6j/aVS9Tex8k5XEQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only a citizen by birth is eligible in India", 
		"option_b": "Only a naturalized citizen is eligible in India", 
		"option_c": "Both a citizen by birth and a naturalized citizen are eligible in India", 
		"option_d": "None of above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060107", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3AAgbtP4JqKZCsMcMtgzpCg2eD+xTFCPMhQm4l899oacPVCwy+sYNGbMOxh2GeTLkr+dHmvAXd1hjXfhHsWvIu+tSa4Rc8+0xwmn4h2rckyOJeT1ruAqEK+xgWLyHKLTbN3GV2J9cin+QOer5Yw9d+Iojvf8frtibjS/tpLbR5XrZV6Ykj8vqYN8Ss2QvS6WwZK5eHdZFr5YAGKfTITzcPmlldg0oszWGcn/BZWwqJVdoB80Ni15Wdlf9prBnO/rUVD05F4HxWPNKmw1SjU4UczfHsmYIR5/CIz4SaSLF1/2n+TDC1VkJJu7cNZmAV3aWpSjzbyhzOKlGCLPIfsq4P1keHqpbdw+qo3ZQGJO1/UQ4kVa7SAJmRj3+CIBLJVPJEnFizifcEr7jTwLpeA1jYD7NccIUDv/SmR0sLzeXGyttLqmtViEbIFOMXWqcy+plnJISLjLmuWJsLnFgniSjz73Bx3shsxivnIvd5GLe//JGAb/N+UgrY=", 
		"answer": "25yRKJ793QCoM596CAFrxx3aStwiPM62Ow==", 
		"explanation": "25a3ZoLn2A3/44wvXF79w73WO2/ZAiIVpn6PQeNjeWXrFKTLeuTkzJliL1WZzV1p/XuGgrfk/lADirsbvM6Lf2JSL8tt3cTJ0+vy1zFPPNIEmY988JsWcrRFwDyve8baNPsu3nyPMUzjbjazFzBymyOWi39HvYqo/DOyW9R3wRs21ot3/tt8M9Hf2qGH4Ve9iBWK1WvReLx2HV2YuMum/wOUoZF4vMOJtDfftPH3m/vH9dpLdgBX/6V2d1KmkqYa8CMoEem3fFIDoL2FNB2tNCfjJgoZ687wxTR9zoc6WCk59QtSh5FFLoJN7KUqUkqq1zMIgUNdHtSF", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060108", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb71i6vXcAyzgY6n5c4zMsofJ/OgP3GoQ29igmAznqFTa4kEluXptqh/1aIqY02tMHNoSDU4v3qk/fd454NbRoSsodrd16uhOgb/SY5Rc2wKAZEsefZdV33JSawLwcNucLtll1nwosoYWd0xhpHkYxYIohBn8KkgDxwC8VvVRC1rVdUzoBpSx6Zev231ijN7lE2dDonZIlmr20xpBudIVh7niuMXiNHnZNi8d4K1QJsby9Bn2f1iyyClGyActPi5YS8iefjs/ls9OMkIFWJL1nWRYUVdfPBKWMyw+eIGaNdN99gBSPoKcZu6DH8YKaVzTUE0dQlIWOn4CKc0szgLW21oZvtl5RiG/8FONDG/Yu7sUvUISDuL36WdMX9Vw+wW3T9wAsluhkx3CQC+yBVb+vPuNEqB2O7ms2tdZ19", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFgjO8rPV+nXo8G+gZITEyovIU=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rwr7yvO/MW7RD3FRtHaXWuNgeHSjV67WZ/f7x4R5LkzJi0l0/zbnsbH59F8KnOgOqZqQMHNSPp5hzNWbl9T21mUBGu8Eso9l4YwabrgAxSntd9vVNP9nwH3AKUD5czG4FjB1miiWmnlEpYK18CmvFNQ40lUzmJ446MQ9PtiN2LyWqF2qiRCLz3KeRq4kGFrZocah+AOOpYU5p8nNmCab+/r1g7ja9NsFdgFUtoNsI0+0kugZ/TgrXsanKAVD/qTSZFfsLS3jJAcJ8NHm2GcpyYRpdGcw/R4Gg5cWa9RglpvrsT81Mc5vGDa0twQIzpEwHxiYNJe53n3l8kx/JyxnJds06X184SaIaFBxn3jcQiNF1IRu/9xZgg13dS9UlHOgki2EgmmKcdPs7cD9hvnlqapq5qooJwGPJxzUWZ4PJbzGZ2R73uCBCKhPO5Z3VzHzP8Yr7Sz8LoLUyzZN2c0zb3To+SecnM7wNGC0p9LQmpRzGa8PIdTX+oujuFmHUSLzLXSSa876TUjkQDz93Q9mo1gkiC0R/yLMB8lv5yIbl3q1CUJrgGfzeX+p1rNd/paLbZ1x0vvonTMegbR3i5Pyxl0xRhCviG0DoIGTTkhGw1OWCsJHxwA6Ba4EGoXZ+33UuPaoqPwAt19ETpoBIQKhlw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060109", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRoH6XV6R7YnjmR+fNaK3uzIViKFKazVl+8XfLpuXz/kcGla1V+s6QdmIqcI9myZCIw6T+0GIBMMlJl4V8558SefpUgH2kcZibL/Au5G+OMkTifnnvUjw0xWiD2jAWqYC4+jW/XdQwgAE91pNw6IgfM9mMzaGH/VmxiQjC033RYbNgGFXG9fKm10297cIZ9d2IoyHU+rT7lerdsNcFIiFcu49+X1We2uhJ2WooVNqnZxwL5uzfclGtMCmxIgAJ6ov002ZshoAmT2d0/REGq41Sa8FP2Lup/HIRf91vByC1rQRXz5s8Uh6RZrys1Wyk9Fp/RXsgbJl5vSN1oAmILUY+t2qOTyQRxcwrr4lNwkgjfGFE3GTlliqZjmCLPIfsq6nygeHxnLdHv+NnCAGQME7LWYNcarWADml2w+iVTalOOphuGWL0OMYn+DD3J9abyi0e2d0lb17p8COY0IeoKjS2JkDdxDN78avCaf8=", 
		"answer": "25T0KLOz0Bfut6ZiZgS7snuJDJaCUqGFoNYd0w==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbYL2kRrr44AnXQz7wO6/Om2QE2cDsHCNQeNjeH6jVqLBb+D7iZR4M1WTiFVosnnA44z+81oOz6lPqYeLY2IAcYZizd6K0unyymUBPMgEsIF88ZsNZbQSmnHtJY2OcLMu8mChZ1X1dSqyCjBjnD6WnX1F6IG05yn7XdR36Rs2n4ZE4+l8LNKNyqedqFqwiRWHnGuQWrhqBUfZosu67gOer5A29cSD8RvV8P34pvbysM4OcBtdscZoa1T8mqEO6issVMz0fB0LweXbaEf5ISbjJggJ/Nmj+3V7xYppDCV0pUYS1c8WY853lpTlqDcif99vASaorUFEh4BzHz6YcLS5kseRzAv+ce/cTu/r6GvPB04=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "B, C and D only", 
		"option_b": "A, B and C", 
		"option_c": "B and C only", 
		"option_d": "A  and C only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060110", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7mzfi/FmTeEHYYt2qXW6x6MH7lFI7MauT/hddwZ0yMn0h0/DbFoquw9VYMgKVeqY+RMAsNeoJuxpCK3vD+3nRPc89C2pR64YNfeuFMyjSheJTaLucuwWCFZ0r2Jy21ATBgnCPTjzxVp42//DOyW9QkmlUwk4526og+M8WRmaGdqGS2gg+DkDuZSattH1PZsMe840aO4I0+9dmFtDvJtOT4iP3d5M1LYAdAscZ2bRuVmawA+WZ4Xtr0ahdC/+OQbkbpKSaiNQcR4Ivx02dgwocnSSk9+l9vjIdfY4B12Yqkgw0PAPJVKgyF401NypF4VhaCcbGhkGrh5lotcDo/bY8tvyI4rAqSK1Fzn2WIDCNX1JRj+5A6mgpwaWZUiWLpjTHJqRcYmLTarU/xJBrxzMpC6w==", 
		"answer": "27OxfpSzyBzr5ZZib3wyz8CXPzM2bAEc5zmKEA==", 
		"explanation": "27T4eJThwhbkt4YhXF7wwP7wOG6QAmxRinGHW6J6MHLqQK7Ya+O+wJExM1SMlBt953rAqqn8t1IBluhU54vffyRDaoNqiMSBxeHyhHJOPcJNjol96olFPPZFxTOqNNbUMvAux2DADkv0bjjxRHh1gjjYjTxToZez8DX7W9x31B03n5U4/ckuOdmLyuiR51+2xg+MnFKfTLRlXRSWp46q7kqSp8I3p8mEvzPJ/fjg2urW49cPZwZG/49xI3Kyk6EIuCw3Q4iyYQROsf3VYEb+YCGuKgsZ8Mr303hwhoAsW2Ym8V9SioYWYc9+253qvzc9OsN+VTy841BIwtRfUBmFYLSsxXzt71t/PXMuKcpHvSMgoB2FaAYo1ivNFXkB3cKcgJ30PtnqEhNbNb7nYSpM", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "fi,ve, ye,ar,s", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060111", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7mzfi/FmTeEHYYt2qXW6x6MH7lFI7MauT/hddmL1WKhRt482LDpKri7hMAiehL7JyMfywQPolqy9GE0qTeynVIMsgEmYlm7YAacucAzSntfcDIYP1hw2OFKUb1ajyzEDB7mnH8i3JDqZGitXXtGJpmmUBiycVJVaItN5zIVFQSe+6OGC56", 
		"answer": "25T4eJThwhbkt4omEjf8wfT+OyvfEWsWqnHDQKZneXXqWqCCZ+O+4Jl1Ll3L+M9UXLTAQ4SzjitzDnnpRg==", 
		"explanation": "26W9eoL83wqq9YoyXF77y73WO2/ZAi5RtHeMQaY0YHDxUanWfa3pzIV0Z16Gn1U7+3iGiqv0/lJDz6dJqZmXf2IUe5lqiN+b0+35xWNIP98EiIVh7Z4acuAAxTPtXdrfKf8uyGGSZ0P5cTz9HXV1hiKWiHlVqY6+tQ61UNM2zlUxn5Nx980yL5eezeiH4Ej4hQmP0X6fS7hpFFqN9yfPSWuxxoGRIE38C5UaODw=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "A person who migrated to India from any foreign country", 
		"option_b": "A person of Indian origin residing in India", 
		"option_c": "A person who migrated to India after 1950", 
		"option_d": "A person who migrated to India from China", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060112", 
		"question": "24GwbdHQ2A3j7YAuQRb71b3eNn+QDGRR8ibWB+NjcWKjUanDbfn7zddlKAbLbn3u5PFNTT1enTOsBl/FPA==", 
		"answer": "25S8bIP2wgqq+oQ0Rhvg1r3tMGfRF2cV42uMEqB9ZHj5UanRZuTui26coYXT9aw1UcoTIca7Nh8=", 
		"explanation": "24W5ep360BTv+ZFgVxDzxun6MSvEC2dRgHaXW7lxfmLrXbeCT+7qid8gfgncxBtv/TbHp6Hi8kAcz6Va/ZqaYjFDbI5jycSM06TjyzFCOtJNgIV895IWbLgAzS7tcdnLL+lr3GuEZ0fpJy21ATBXmz/FnnVCvZey+in5sNBlN/alxmMQL9ZK3s8vPw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Address matters related to citizenship", 
		"option_b": "Abolish the concept of citizenship", 
		"option_c": "Define the concept of dual citizenship", 
		"option_d": "Establish the rules for immigration", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060113", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fQa+r/25N4KVvJpFV/+3fI46b541oViqZI4YePMCMRe8tsx8Kb0ufjhHNAIMNA2o98pNocc/pT2DS5YcDSL/Bvwi6QNUrmbiq0C35nyw3YtnJ34cOatTe+Rsk4zlUlnog45ckvfMGQ1b2d/EyqjwqbnHqSWahtA1Gd9dqg7gOfqZYxr8iDojrS5LT2nLjSsNgEcA1buIg/cE+9g61J+ys2EdugYR5HsebVIVWtIyG3LhQY94vs0DRAyIYgXFU61lYGp5VTcNkzxp32rz0+f9piGnOzsARP1dR1TFeScbi11Wyk9Fp/d39rZMputTk8uwqSaFt42kKSSCVQ1INq8JAVmhdmPXtImX/ywhaFhGyOctPg4pT1n+3+s7Fq4uMuLwGwNE7UX4wRYL3UZ3dz2fqeHuZdc4x3EiHvO9wtvDX4N6qa/HBN4NgyI37m+S+Xho39OHb6p5r8ztVjALcPJNjR8IujvxzKYCjkYW2Bad39SgH/QW+4wQtptgwgzGEE5yLMAIw/9C4ci3ejQFBtnSmgbXKl1qpZ+I+HcY8l2vrinT0W2Pdxi5Lt0RMvTw2rsXF/vKyQWBxCzFrPXsIBhB0mCfQSAJfF92CTm2KfWDwKdtjzD+iGwSNe36P4nS58rZVOVoOcPhzYnoFk3h3EahbirXr7sZOFHJhAiQ==", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UBEhfhhfTxNmTCEWcStz+BV6B1ZWLmFLPKa634wIViMxyKglVo5n/StrH5+F0Og+hL+4GJeTEKcYUviNWRx+j+x3hVP98EiZRz8J8MPOBIzSntetubMPt83WGOZ1b4ZjWxRHJx1DCWiXVCoZm++2e0UpoezhE7l8dx64goNNKGmaCS/kj4kAmOyXWFSa9tHU3ZtM25/kqOpYZ4ocWI8THS4P3jn/bA+NcbIgdU/4dxehu6mLoM8S02EdugaQZOsdjeXVreNCm3IgMY99+j9DRg1cIqUnsm8RxSwoJFIslw2Zb3qDskKtljGj36sFBB05FvHwOedan41X7h8kx/ZX85doVj/Do9rk+VOxRxiCuVX2xVkYVm+9RZgQsjf2oAnTbjiyuCmmCBPJzlq6nygeHx4Kpr868raUKPO0jRWJgZJafPZ2V3ivqODq4cMt9kHjbvJ9AgsHnqNZSe2joZkM0vb2Pv8WqJgMLjMHazvJzqzttwVL4OL5HJ6Nz3vV3DZGPjOD2jZ9n4UAn9SnLskzptvgtlxSQR5nGYHIF+4W09n2y8QEVplyn0LHSghf5I4ofOfpsl2/r+1CYJ2OB334v2xw58SwWsnj9XuoWLD19OwxTaG8wDhB0hTKAJEdbF93+bnHjRX3UCcY75B+iuzShB2+2xjWhptooLW5+GJQmbjNE0iBS0E+l4XGmtoYj9NOocDnEt9qFNxNGvhN66YfapKWs+Lzn3UPwZ8JpDegd4BUvcFmRMb7a9QpQKVPRG3XuKkBVJSWtaRWrN6aQBXAmvpNCIemLbI6ETGRvwI6cKU8P5RUKPJeOm3jnaD7CShgesWkgkWj+ZYaQCpRP4f8zzJwKmmntt7cjqPBFaSodXKCLheWK3pLeKBAh6cCplK4NTc13QRQMsnS6DJvdjzaYMfFgiVaCiCxAblwVbmizBTkpAvE0KWqHtVFxnKaBRKUEUwyS9GLBds7ShGSJtiO3iUI3j++RvDA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "All three", 
		"option_d": "None of above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060114", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIguXg8kEcgKYb64GNfmIKcMtGxtSA1qT4yjFOIYZFnJR39to1afhZjGzhNIWCeKkijmeTZ0b/aSq0AHVmkTWWizxVoZey7yK1FNUxgDw8ko55rcolfNWWy7ybqEK2ih/C1X3RSakkHVGYptro5E2Z4I0+9dmFtDvJtOT4iP3d5M1LaxsSvsZ8ak+1ja0HuCU+EeG6bBtKseXEIUDlJWi3LgMYucTllmBhw4s7HWs95gtOvo1ldsFn05XhsiZwFuQwKT2b40lJyZtuHxSefbG8kH/s7xU2ZjoqJYlkqCQvpAHcJ1I+s2WYRS0Rlpkr+tUKlgFtaS9BknKggzOYjyWOPJDq/4nmgOawr78j860oPUmFJxzbWZgScaHZZ2pn2f3bH6NSPIppFCemKd0rvDrwNJ+O2jce2NAwb3j1tCSYhsT6N2S2uobgzttwVKsIM5HK/cOyohzEbjbvNW+KJtz9TQD5QTzr2hYluhcr3CkDqG3eSIhr4SwEkHe+TgQ2w2f5aX2zhf5d7YfOa4FxwfD43Dse2N12m5L22l0/ThCyl3pNoYyWX2BB8VrhFsQEzEkhCvQVHJOR4XmXgXPdTnIZbI7xCL6CzWxJ2OzniyF0rN8PR4nOLxbJmNsl3FWw1uCa7wE6D4ivsKmhTFqE", 
		"answer": "25z4Z5//yFsMRG4z1CFI7DkSOmOoI7LK", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48UJEhfhhf7wJ3nVAHZRomzDU+NkdWPwW6mCbOLsx9d4KRygg19y8zbJreX/5RMOibxe+861ZS4aPtojiIHQj7O7hHhSc8VLlJN74J8NefAAzX2ufcDSOvtgjmGGZ2z+YzC8RHJt1DPfmGhe6Iq9tSKyQNIy0lU9kMds5c01LpeP2LqW5lmrxg+RnHrRS7RwGE6cu46n7QO1roYxtI2MpXLP/PG5jvHe9Z4EZEhGt4N2cRu+nrod8GoEX/S6WwZK5eHdZFr5YAGKZwcOucLt1Xt71IcqSSk1519Hwo5fbM9hlo/ss3I5LI1rVTCzt01awpo8UBHWXbO82Wmk4kx/Y3M5cZ9o/CIz4QuZO1d7lH/cTSJV1Il4vtEVhgsjfC9DlWLpmDqFwGqJPJLt8sDzkeD1svlg/bYpPVOZdU/QV4EQJbDFJnR3iv2UTaRZc54nFCvyNM8r8nn2Jta90T0E0ZkpKTfv8WqdncjmeWu1p9Lri9p5AbEDM5HR4c73s1XTaDnkL26bb9u0VhqwQX3s2gFrthQs3DhQ52SYCYdw4SUIjD6zRlFqhjX5LGuogrZV5MKddpZx3vriyToD2Pt+35P+x109UxC6hHFKvIPfSUlDwRTXGchFguwBEekVFrxgfLG+7i3tsA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060115", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3AGm6FB7ICMeCsTPqps3JCG0aSmnSQUc9ZWlZZ74J8MPPJP3n2sd8XOKe1n2mePKQXxaT39CH9nh3HZjDxVoZey7yK1R9I+0FU7mMdR48w1PeuR6ryS/Ei1gwiWnFK4EoFqMluUuMGm/EadrJYw9e6EpTvB8frqkvHDsMkKcUhbsYVzdl+5k+gA9mosWc30ZwBC9u3eYFitAyG3LhQY99jr32Qp54E9HWYytE4f19YaIsJmwtjtqHInPt4qBzaqpkVMwpA8XQ7WYLW9kEvt9FwlcHQ4bYN9/GUUrAqSLFl7lH/VDA1SgMBk+JBLxVQwQWF8kkHoizyDwGqJPIfr7sDvkenkpbRm/Lc0aUaJI1nWFoweaqXFZ25hheiJCOZfPI11EiHyf0pnKqIYhuOcApjq4s3sgX4=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz+Fnr+YFgezewDbm4SXZFF7HmzNz7mUMRzw==", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHQ2A3j7YAuQRb71b3eNn+QDGRR8ibWB+N3f2fmRrSCeuX7iYBwPk/Jgl0783XXtqzi/l0Iz6lV7c6TfzEKcIwvy9md3v7yymJJOtYEk44yzZQbdfUA8DORevvJKflnwG+MK1y8Jy21ATBXnSXfkHlYu4uy5WeaV853iERrw9IxrckwL9jfybqc/kS8gwLC2nSDCKlsFBS6usOl5E2LpYM0ocXNkjvP/e78lOvb+c5LQB1G88Zra1Kv17gb9zwxQsG7ZlJc8PeQc1H9JSmvIgpd+9KjwnxshqEgSWAu8RFViopGIohS253quD81MdkjVRK5twgAlcQsDFVtOT3L73bLeQ+Z8ga0g3x6", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060116", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb71iK1QMg2zFUVmZF9/8YxOdmLmaWS8Q2vhw+U2TuSTa9wEF2X9c2n5UeVtIs3u97Ntz3JtPr4ju3B8dICcQlGtolxI1Ky17wB/Wo7UNuxKB1NseXeIV3jJCG1LgoI+MejwXxmhoooTikm8RFCh5FTZoB334vwtTw3KsR5HTa+41dF1YJ1XBLWYLL4w2vt5Vs8cDZrdYJksCImrh+UMRg+m3mIAGxdnZRu7NENgBZmMS9Xk2Tshn+bhWSMed+j5JK8jf39obcj4rEoLlOFJk/kWM0uYLLTKGkygtvSV+ZgPd9THyemHtw69SP8LoWc1ilN8do0b3jhtHvAx5i1Pne7vYbqzsB+Ef8jM9/R+8q78HvIdybzL3CWaN+0TQD1D33txwZqpREx0WEE5yLdEIxy5TlNl3C0QFJtljLhYG/hkKxT58KNepwl0vzinTwRjOFqnpf+xxwoTgu1zXxMvICWW1VAw0eWHMwUwQ1uA7pBAJ7U+3/WlnneX24EfdviCKeJ0Gxc1aPnj3N0sIUdFYqHKRXfmZzzFOd/GqmFhc6oIb9wDKQe", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFgjO8rPV+nXo8G+gZITEyovIU=", 
		"explanation": "25K3fpTh3xTv+ZFgXRiy7PP7PGqQDmMI42iCW7VxMGLsWaKCYf++yJt9Z1OPzU9z9zbFrKv0/kcGgKZIqYiQYmINf5962tGF3vf20HhOPYZNlMBm7J9ff/VTyX2icpTaLr5nwGqJMUz0cjixRGd8m3Hei28Wuoa18SKpUd53xBwhgo526t01L9+a3eiA7V+ujwWHnG+eCLttFFidpo6k4kiZ4JE7vMiDsjeXtOTxk/Tc49EbahEe/4dtdxf8m6Ed/Tg5Rd2mbV4L5uvCbVCtMC2iJAtRucTxlnx8y4MnHXkm+xhUh5BFItV90p32/BE5K8RwED2pq01Qh7V/S1eZcv3piT2xot8tjk5YUj7qbYJW/v6zow8=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060117", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDbOLr3ddwJE2chEhy5n/JreX/8RMmgaxS6IDfcysXd5FqxsOB3vS3xWNEc8VLiJJ3545AQPp8whzgNPWbMPt83WGOZ0f/dTf9DX40vT/Sg30Wp437+jX7VdwjxQdyvJJ09IhtcJfOgPDEpA2xlUaDyW+eRbxwGFeYucKxq0Lco4ssvNeIv3LU8rTQlPza8Z4ZZw9TrYJzZkiv16cPuD4wVMGmKAJK4+HedUeqYCaiMwcS98rv32Bw+owLECl01V9Wh5FFbc4z1Jf2snI5MY1DGzezogRPydRzTVeXcqm9wijA5VY6eHgud8o+8G1n8V/IZBR9m2XcQyJdjcBp+5AY1QdqaWZamXigjTnLqWuLdZKj4oa8h+fkqPlz87EiJ1WTdV3KU801a7fJJmkyyeCPBLxZPYwnGDCmNNNu8zf8YIaVzTwDxJkpPDfm+mqwnMn8OGv6sJvth85zGv8BONWF/cOy8FPTaSbzYW2SdM76TUj5XDz23BolthZlwS0c7WXZBMly/Cofn3CkdUpH32egTTyxk6xP5YzOfYEj3bXjyCYDkfB937L50BQ9Bwu1zXBR8oWZW1ldjXDTHcgKxgw8TOVRWNaAqzTE2TbZWDwOcMDlCKyC0SlMmuKxjWhptooLW8yBKlnyhNovyVe4B718XHPlrZS5MvpVHmwp86Ax2uyzssSvZrOtPyUrLxm+TeZD9psRZwQ7OAXZDCUPYazuQpUbAfRG33CKmAEIU3dMDEiM+aEaSQyWpOCFLir/I6EZHA3tbfMHHNz2DkjaIeKgzDWJL7GYnEb+UEplQSjdILYZ4BWwXonxIR6xlnokqJGpcgACHdFbfCTyemW2seOCCBcvdj4gaKNJfk7URVAnnSrKPfxpnq8JYFgvWOijHEMVkx9b037XGF1L8EUYH6qjRRMoLOlRKF4Y33elELIaUgjZxjMZzleSggviLfNKPwkgcnCalUnu2Q/hz4fyyZ2VwML0wrBM7uE=", 
		"answer": "25f4aZ/3kTqq+IssS1yXEcmfLMPWNxL8cbGbgjyA", 
		"explanation": "25T4eJThwhbkt4cvQBCyzPO/HGXUCmNRrHHDXbE0cXf3UbWCRPjy0NcgaxzY1AMsvjbPsOXz+F0chqxe+4ubMCNDfYJ7wcqM2aT4wjFoPcJNm8B96pYGPP1GjDikYNzeMr5hyC6UL0D5dXmtBWJxmiXFynVF6IL79i6vXcAyzlU9kMdR48w1PZeezeiH4Ej4kg+P2TueTv1wGVGQp46q4lGIqMI59d2IoyHU+rT7lerdsNEedhtbu4M/SlW4nqlJ9yR4Xtr0aRRf9PaQRVHuJSWhIhxdqJuvliUwn9BlHWo1+l9HgZJDa9J2lrHquDsxMY1pHCezuUFO1Jx1T1eUbf281Xvn5VsrNW8lYY9//C4wsxudIVo+mWSSSCVFnY9l7ZLvubHKLM93GRbidczTGV4H", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "B, C and D only", 
		"option_b": "A only", 
		"option_c": "B and C only", 
		"option_d": "A  and C only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060118", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRoH6XV6R7YnjmR+fNaK33x5N4MVWNmFp34TbFoquw9lAemqFJ7M62fiYKf4Uvy9md3v7yymJJOtYEmJky9p8YdedU3jy5fdvVf75SwFKOBgiwRnmtAWJnmz+WhXoWgY2//Ca1FNUlyRI7mMdv5cd8NNaMmbqW+0S8gwLC1XXRYbNgGFXZs8G6q0LcrYs2vMCYvHLU8rTqn+7W/p4SZwlArLpxQRb814lJ6C8qQse6KAVD/qTZchTgITqxLgsZud/slnVnhqsnWWA1+l9Fi5dfeMV9lpnquHI4Pt4qBzapqkBFw9R1UVe/ermx0Sji70d/dG5raY9srzl1sgqKLVo+g26dXj9tmqMmvpA41RRmb3xPkjb3ijDLl2ScPJHs+Y68jOawtbdn+7UuLUSEdXXWUoQdJbzSZ2Yy3uyJH69IPI1+VzbuPMFu/jz6IZuRnykMws1gIHGn3SSdm8y1O2C8vID8zvVjE6oTIpGUvIf34QWTNh/vBTDTJuq0SQ3iXHP2kwFj9x4wxC1Q6WXdSIhx8W0On26xSk1wi2f3ZHPhgb9PqoePbYI41ues3HITkeBxhZ75lBI6Bw21iXpTt4qbSlJbjX3YGsQGhAggCPQJFYWR8GiTmzbCTm8Ee8f4BuiOzWxh1Of4jyF7sIJORoWWbBTUhMou21W5iTwbIcyI5K/JJZH64kVl", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "25q2ZIiz8Fnr+YFgcF7z1/i/NmTCEWcSt0ONbq1AeHSjd6LMev//xddWKEqMn1V293jS46jx7h9PgKYb6IDfcTITcoJsycSA2Oq7hGNENM9XjoVgpJsMPPUAzzS5fc7eLr5hyC6pKUH5Znm8Cmk0hDTEmXNY6Mu1+jP7Vt8+zhJyl4k45MQwOdCe1eie4UqqhwiWlTuYTv1sFBSbsMKn5USP4JY39cyDqHLU8rTtkv2T9tEHbgdFtoh4I1i9g60O9zgxVNv4KBxK/OHceA6gHCbrJkdducqjxnF71Y0nHWYytDZIhopXbIB8xJHjtTxwKMVlVTqp40tSw51yXgWfeKT4wm336VE6e25rbIQtlSMxqA7cLlts2niZWilf1Jlu/8IK1QZme2BSmTbtgzSCjmLPfZ2j6pDsieHzoa1q/a1nL06SdU7dUYQPcaHBM259xLKnA+5eet8nFmL2OMc98ze5N56bnzAekNQhPWXu8S7ZhsK1OCW5uobwlNF4VLAGdvjL7cK28F3JZWPoMj2cdM/9VwniRnDhkxxgpBEhzS8EqGvWSKBx8SQM3ni/WwR3lzHlYjy4k79O+cKMeog+wfCs0DMbkfp/35r5lBwsVwiyjn5Xu4uRD1pA3xTEG8oO1x08DaAIG5iKsPDboMWjdYWz9JI4jQEE/Xs=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "all Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060119", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRoHCNVqpgeX7tR+fPe/7qiZV0Z1qcgV1y/nrDp+X2+EFPjuhL7JyMfyxDaoQvytXJ0uj+w3hDP8MEnI9gpJQeaOFSzTGkZ9XPKfFgjm+TZ0T+JxCzAHl1mnHVg2hfsoa1qmeHWuY54Vhyoo99rdg5LsSQ1+ie/V6sxg6Dyn7RWrh3GFCcsY6h5QO1roYxtI2LviCb9eC5lv3S48pLdg1c/596Ykmvq6YrtWp4ZcCxKAJO4/ffbxTgNTu3Zx4S6tjmxWcpx4xpXG0x5QpHloYWac58wZThuDU1f8JsVTL6r0VOwIF9WBLWZ62902Hi6VA7NXMlJZ5luW0QqAiUPFw+qWiUSShEmIUr6t9ZgQxmPUxPkmX0iyuelGyAcq/tyM28seD14Klm4LAoJwGNIE/MFoUdc7aAJWJ3xKmSA+ZIO5onBCf0K9wt+Xn2JtaA1zxN+dckJnbptA2WhMjnN2i/vYa5iNtkVL5AO9jL4MaivRzIZ2PnKGuWJtLxWBrjc3Lcnk4lgxAgiDEV+nHXBsly4D4Z3mu+TUF2hibraTy1mf5O74yBaoAy1rX41TcZirR7lo/+zhgyVAyynT9MtMSeQVNbxVHEXs4I0Qc6Hq1BHZiR5mWT1XPGTnIZP8HwQbyPxiVamuLhnm10vJEaXIOAbB/UmJ4PxhO4APM5Vm75oZz8M+8dA3Rs+Ld4xOrhtsm4cOOwKWFoyvVw8cvkWxNLtd3e5+G7ZQ==", 
		"answer": "25f4aZ/3kT2q+IssS1xh9r120CzYsfMCS4rm5wg+", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHj1Av5+ItgXwvh0b33NH3VQ3AUsHaHV6c0eX+jfanGZ+y+xoUxJVmMgxty/DbSq6Cw5FYdmaFY7M6QdmIXdo4v4d6N3uX5hFZOJcNWlI136o5fevtSjDztd9HJNP9nwC6QIlf5aD39EH80ljSWj3Bfr4q5+SL7UtUlgERg1op349w0L5ee37yW+g25lhaO1XiQXLRrHxTZvMjo/0uZ4JI9p96Cv3LS57T42vva5NcRZwYSsIA/YlWzg6AM6mo7Xt26fABSvaTEaVH0YCW2NBpd7MXn02Z9x4ksHX07tA1DjIxDbMN2lozsuXIzNtljDza0sExJ19RzWVeCfLyskGvr9VsrZ2NrbIwtqCUwqB3cKURulmKfTThYm44r+N8L1S1teWZBkjbjiyuCmmCBb5vq+8D1lqjxo7pm4rciLQNkhy8SQGtCkcjN98c++vNl", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "B, C and D only", 
		"option_b": "A only", 
		"option_c": "B and D only", 
		"option_d": "A  and C only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060120", 
		"question": "25T4eJThwhbkt4omEjf8wfT+OyvfEWsWqnHDRat7MHjwFKjQauTwyIV4K0XJn15o+3LDrbGw/l1PpqZf4I/fdi0RPphq3tWHl/3yxWNSc8RBnI9g4doSff9JwjrtddqbIe5+wmeDJlH5aDf9An9m1CPTjXVFvJG64S60Wpo0wRtyl4Rp+MEuOZe216ya6UP4hQ+W1WGURq5sGETZt9fo1Hyjn70HivKyjnDB8rYiLDgBag5jp7Cx/Kcn", 
		"answer": "26e9b5jgxQvr44wvXFxPkkep8JnnNCh0yy3oAguj", 
		"explanation": "27T4eJThwhbkt4omEjf8wfT+OyvfEWsWqnHDRat7MHniR+fAa+jwiYV0NFWNhFV8sn/I44z+81oOz65U+86MdTQGcMt2zdGbxKT1wXdOIcMEm5Bi6IMWcvMAyjK/NMbeJ/d92nyBM0z/aXm+BX40lTLHn3VErcOS+yOyVdR3wxwmn51949s0NcffzaCB51i/jkaW1H7RWK9rElGKpo6n7QOOpYUxptmfsCbS+/q7HtWK7Hy3DQwBuVV9YXD4gA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "re,gi,st,ra,ti,on", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060121", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQn4+JMpQRf9y73oNHiQEWcBpn6PV6c0cmijQK/HLs733Z5rIlKahVJrsj7nrqD+814KgbwSqa+cZG5DLNs/m5zJ0fb4yTFVO8MElZJ745MRffgA7zS5fc7eLu1mx37ABkbkJ3HsXSUh3W6Uqxy4AlU7wmCB5PtBFUrMvA==", 
		"answer": "25a3ZZz83w7v9ok0Wl7RzOn2L27eEGoYsz2gHoCPvO++nmvAcLNk1nhb", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ2A3j7YAuQRb71b3eNn+QSzNI9irKErNmf2fqUKLRLuvx29dwJE2chEhy5n/JreXx+VdPg6dI+s6QdmIAd59m0tWHxOz+1DFANdJBiMBm7J9ff/tNwTijd9HWJfB6jmGGZ1H4YnmeC35ngDjCn2hfp4372jWyU9M5wRk+j8s4+cA5fPSWzaGJ7UOrjg+SnFqSXP0sQA3M4Ifo6k+Pr8Iop8KbuDbe8LT/leqT5NYOIitdsotwbUy5lqQd8GobWNy9chdF4uzZcRTPNTzvZxoV8NijxmZm0Is6VGY6tAhHkcNEZ9B215ThuHIyJo1+HTb6gE1Uzo55UQSefa34mEnp5Vs7eH8lccMtnS4h7U/OeAQt2Ig0l27m6GZIWnMlkR3jj1k=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Overseas Citizenship", 
		"option_b": "Naturalisation Criteria", 
		"option_c": "Commonwealth Citizenship", 
		"option_d": "Descent-based Citizenship", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060122", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhv+zPr2N2LcCnYI42+GQKp7dDHlW7WCb63uzIViKFLJmVQ78HOGrLf0/l0OnaFX8M6NdTEKeo5h3JCA2aTeynVIMoZGn4Z99p9ffeRQwCSketObJvF8jm2JM0zqYjeuDHlk1DPPym5Tr4qo4TW6QNM4zkpwk7jMyF8WVT4GG9zFxmZHIg==", 
		"answer": "2+L4cZTywwqou+YugqV7geccI1JkK+TWOw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ1Bf+5YQsEjn90/jtO2bVDXZRrn6aHuN7fjHiWufDfv3ywJRwM1WGgxc74HPBqrbk8kFPjrsb6M6ceTYKZI5hiN+Pl835wHhAc8dKg8Bi4YgMc/oAhDOiYJTZJfdgyS6BKQX5azW4A3F41DzfjW5XppfytS69FNIygBc3moh26tt8KNjf2KaKqEK+xhKK2TuXR7FoHkOQu8no6EKIpYU3p8SIon6b+vX0n/TKqpNLY0hCupRsbFX8mK5J0SQ8WMm6KB1Z+OPZbxT6KCfjLh1d9tnn33po1IslRCkm8QxPhoZYdoB62NjNsjY5Po1sGiH6sEFWwpo8RhKXZq740m3i70c6NXcqboNju200r0+dOERyk2idWCVemsBt8cJZhwFkdHxUjnf0izCFwv9ZrjkLrMbpHDqTGJdoN4U=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "5 years", 
		"option_b": "7 years", 
		"option_c": "10 years", 
		"option_d": "12 years", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060123", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq2aoUEl7mzfi/JXnZDmMDuj+AXa1weWXqW6mCaOLsiZYxN1mbnlR1smLJ46Tz5kYGna0bwICbeSMNPohm3NmT0urkzHhRc8Rd2o5z8I8NffhJ3zy5fdvVf7wNhiM9puI6joBd5akKwqPZ", 
		"answer": "25e9YZ/0kRiq5YAsUwr70/i/Om2QAmxRinGHW6J6MHLqQK7Ya+O8n5KSNm0kofzk7yXLlJqlbA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ1Bf+5YQsEjn90/jtO2bVDXZRrn6aHuN7fjHiWufDfv3ywJRwM1WGgxc79WTHrbGw9hMMirpP4IiWcyMXe8tgzpCH1vDi1nBNOtVFjol96toLc7RBwiTtZNHJM/FgjiaOKFGwZTy0Cnc0lT+Wg3BarYS6+We2Xd0lwRsm38dx64g0OZeP1ruA7V6rgxXCynqDQbJxAhSIoM+k4kWVo4MsvMKDonLZ4eC5mP3a/tlLY0hAuop+d1KqkugG/mo5X4idZhZC8OqQYl35KTKmKU4U6ovt2WApx8IsUW499hZKi5dPIsNh34zhrjsxfbtikGvE/zsL1rLCPF7X2xQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Adequate knowledge of Indian languages under 8th schedule", 
		"option_b": "Residence in India for a certain period", 
		"option_c": "Good character", 
		"option_d": "Being a relative of an Indian citizen", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060124", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsmqCXqpyeXLiQK7NYP6+yIV0Z06MnE5y4HPC46P/5RMbh60byouRZDACcstIx8aMxer6wX9Vc9JL2odg5ZQLPPUAzzi/YN3dKf1v2mvAKEOwaTipEWJ1mDjMi2hfp4374Sj7VZonxQchmYkn0cYAMobfmbiW+l63iEaPyWiFCLNrBRSbsI6pq0CVtIsisMPNvjSb9bT6le3d5MwSIh9aupR6I3Kyk6EI9mo7WNy9chdF4qTRc1GtMDqmMQsT7c7nlnJ7yY9pX2w3+xJPjIQWcdVx3J3nqCFwMN8qFjquql5FyYdAUUXWQLW9kHjh8kYwezomcJl5/D8wrwCJJld72n+USWxSnZRi5NUXhgxqbS9Pmjb0ijqCkiWMaYHx7o7oxev/tbd34LpnIEfAIVTdX59cZKPQK25xy/2SAqgcNZB1VwvoOdwv8nn6KYKdxTwDw9EpPzfu52qYkc7wKXG/t6733ZRCHLpAJtTX+sS58FHScjehKXyFY4vmXBv5S3n8kwdr9zErzCgRqG3KSIt68CNNl3DwXUxh0jTlfmqolbsc5YTOfs4W3OPpzzwdnfps35L5lDQyQw26zXlMoMSeWxxDyFXFCo0UzRFuAbsPAJ7Csn2EnHnCC2gCP9r+BOiG0zxE0+DwmmhysawAaYKmIw6bh98o0Ve+B71tXWKtu5L4KfkYD2o4taExzeS3ssT7dPGrOmBqZgn4WP1cs5ZeehB+Eh+CR7zwT1uwfsZ7PnCID6gBdFI=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIizxQ7ltfteHb8jHL21qHiBSINbQU0=", 
		"explanation": "24asaYX23Bzk48VxEhfhhf7wJ3nVAHZRomzDW7c0Y2HmV67EZ+jtiYN5JkjJmVN+smbDsbb/+RMCmrtPqYCQZGIBe8tuiNOAw+3twX8BPMAEm8Bx648RaOZZjCqlccbeYNdgymeBKQXzbi20HnV6h3HXmHkWuJG+4yK1QN8zgBMgmYo4780/M9qW16/T+1i6jAOByGjRR68kEl2NvNSt5VDcr4R4ocWMpXLY++H3jurKsNwSIgZTq5NtYle1jakd8SU2bcaHfBNf9OnVb0CtcmiqNE4e9tnx03d9hoM6HWAgtA1Dk5ZfcMVglozsuXIgOt95Gj36t0sA1ZFyUAKYd7j4xGDh6Ud/dm85d49jqG02qBuVMlFwiWOVXGxYksB/9tUQh0RibX9MlXXhljaEjiWJc4Gjwo74jOn+4Lpq5qo9LE+TPVXIFoQPJbLDJGJi3uyfT0Ye9kuaoOGg76iVL2wuzPc=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "All three", 
		"option_d": "None of above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060125", 
		"question": "24C2bJThkQ7i9pFgURfgxujyJn/RDWEUsD+AU600cTHzUbXRYeO+xZhiIhygg19y83iGoKzk/kkKgbtT4J7fcTcXcYZu3NmK1uj73S4DzeLtG+D+DEtp5Fb3KAa6mg==", 
		"answer": "24O3ZIT9xRj4/ok5Eh/x1Oj2J2LeBCIQrXCXWqZmMHLsQanWfPS52tdyLkiAl1514X7Ps+X04kEGga8b6M6IcTBBduzPtpxVkGHuQXDTv83OeA==", 
		"explanation": "25y+KJD9kTDk84whXF7xzOn2L27eQ3Qer2qNRqJmeX36FKbBf/j325JiZ0iBiBt4+2LPuaD+5FsGn+hU786efi0Xdo59iNOGwurj1mgBN9NWk451pJtfa/VSjDSjNMPTKf1mjkeOI0zxJzCuRHV6kzDRj3ga6Jez8C6pFPM5xBwzmMd75Nw1JtKRyqCa+A25kxKN0XqFQb5lHViA9dqt+U6VroMssN7PyuN+sXouZHQl6Tg2NVLxrw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Residing outside India for seven years", 
		"option_b": "Being imprisoned in any country for two years", 
		"option_c": "Voluntarily acquiring another country's citizenship during a war", 
		"option_d": "Failing to renounce other country's citizenship within a year", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060126", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEgz31Oj2J27dBmwF43mMQON1MHzqWqjQLu72wJt1Z0uBghty4TbH46b541oViqYb5ojfWSwHd4ovysnJ0+Hkx3RPJ4ZFlIQy7YlfffhTw32sNNfSNPd0y2DAKEOwZjeyEHhxhnHVhWlYvJGiqmXfFeE4/AGx1RUNJl0v7x7h", 
		"answer": "27G9a5j31Fn9/pEoWxCy1vTndWbfDXYZsD+MVON1ZGXiXanLYOq+z4J9KxyIil45FM4uR4QaCbzh1dSaYhx6lA==", 
		"explanation": "27T4ZZj93guq9I0pXhqy0vXwdWLDQ2NRoHaXW7lxfjHsUufrYOn3yNdzPhyNiEh493jS46T+8xMGnOha5Z2QMCNDfYJ7wcqM2aT4wjFAPd8ElZR64Yhff/tVwim/bZTIKP9iwi6DIkTjYnmpCzB2kXHXyn9fvIqh8Cn7W9x36Rs2n4Y45M58KN+awOiX5w22iRLCzn6fR6hqElHZocatq0CVtIsisMOeuTvLtPvr2vbS5NcEbAletpJmI1S617wB/Wo3RcCxelJI/vHedUb0YD+qMwYU94vw32wpy40nSWEntBBAwoJCdsF62JHqu3I2KsFmVTK9pgZWweJHW1fav7oD+xw5q4Su", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "decide within six months of attaining full age", 
		"option_b": "Apply for dual citizenship", 
		"option_c": "Renounce Indian citizenship", 
		"option_d": "Apply for naturalisation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060127", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7n1+3wJm6QDGRRt3eGErNmf2fqR67NYK3qxtdmJlWfiBt4/XjCqrH5+F0cz65U+86RcTYWbIpjwcOIw+34yjFIPYZQkoUy55sMebRPyn2pfcfPKfBp22eTL0D0Jyq4FmZ9lzSWnnMWq4ap4SayWpoxyRA+kpQnr+yhohQ5nc3w7FpnlPEKb44=", 
		"answer": "24e9a5703xDw8sUzWxn8zPv2NmreFyISrHGXQKp2ZWXqW6nRLvnxiYR+JFWMmUI51Y1FwcUS0N6w9IG14wRaOg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH03g/v5YstVxDmher+PH3VECISrHGHW7d9f3/wFKHNfK3wyINkNV2FhEh65n/JreXx5BMOz7pe6oGYfisXd4RhiN+Pl+35wHhXOsJRm4xhpI0Xc7RIzSuoNNnaJPsuymeTM0z+YCy0F3hxkHHVhXJCuoq54DOyW9QkgAE91oZq6MkvfNuW0q3T+06xgwiB2TfRWLVtHVuKut6g8g/coZAs+Y2BuCbe5vXtj+rWvJ4cbRpeu8ZvZlq/kuRJ9zh4Wd25aRwL4fbfZkboMzvhmzCX8haQrX+IYb+jKNLroA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Recognize significant contributions to society", 
		"option_b": "Encourage foreign nationals to apply for Indian citizenship", 
		"option_c": "Promote cultural diversity", 
		"option_d": "Reward economic investment in India", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060128", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sU0Vwz/1r32OyvzDG4ErnHDc+NjeWXrFLPKa+TsiZR+NU6Mjk879nPVoLf550cGgKZIqYeRMAEMcp5ixpCrlcq7iOpGjn+tMRlRlqBBp0M=", 
		"answer": "25ehKLX2whrv+ZFtcx3j0PTsPH/ZDGxRrHnDcapgeWvmWrTKZ/2yiaN0NVGAg1pv+3nI7on/5EBPi71eqZqQMBQMcp5h3NGbzqTWx2BUOtVNjol96toQerRmwy+ofdPVYN1n2meaIkvjbzCtSDBQkSHEg2pXvIq0+2qXW8kkgBEnk8ds4ogYNcST1rGS5FmhxhKNnG+ZTf1HHlqKoce8/leVr4x09f+IvyfV9/34jvHc/pMGYwNX/4c/Z16/m6kb+T4xXsb0ehdF/vHeYl3jJ2igLhoU487txXxg1sAC7Lbc+pSN8V1hOA0PUjCy", 
		"explanation": "25ehKLX2whrv+ZFtcx3j0PTsPH/ZDGxRrHnDcapgeWvmWrTKZ/2y9ZlFIk6EhFV65n/Jrejc+EAcz6xO7M6Lf2I1cYd6xsSIxf235XJQJs9Xk5R765Rfc/IA6jK/cd3cLr5Nx3qJPUD+dDG0FDxImhXTmm5fvoKv/Ci1GfY40wZykpJ9rdwzfPOWyqSc8Uy0kh/CyHTRXLVhUXeWu9284leJtIs3u4GxvwDe+uH3mfHS5NcEbEVfvo16I1r8k60K9CsqUNy9ZxwL4+HebkHjIyGtIE4e8N/qzHFn1YogTSsdFOPaQw3ZDCgsKuKmGcnC", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Termination,Loss due to Voluntary Acquisition of Foreign Citizenship", 
		"option_b": "Deprivation,Loss due to Disloyalty to the Constitution", 
		"option_c": "By Descent,Acquisition of Citizenship", 
		"option_d": "Renunciation,make a declaration renouncing citizenship", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060129", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3oBi6Fa5868fywQaoJ73cSA2Oq31GNOJc9An5My4pUNPPUA3yS+YNHWYPFojn2JKUL8Ynm+DWR9jjTYmXRfuL+1xjO6QN86xRsm1q5Rt/QyCN+amZ2d4Vm9gkaxyHqFTa4kHlLZlMOt+UqfocIwtN7NsDbU5OD8nrjSsM0ScRxXssZwZRu4gqkFuCkxRcGubRxY+e3AXVrRLh+rLg0VucTt0zRmwMI9VWx08hBKjoxBa850lpH3/DE/Ld9vFif6qkoA1ZFvTxKVYP231ijw6FB/dHgkc48trzk0tQqRLVpqiTTejrDyo4a5A5XeuGHYeycbNQ==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz4g3r44AtVxDmiNS/NGXUQ1EFomuGX6Z6ZDzKfefDfOi+yphjNVmKmRt6/HKGkLHx41YCiqZPpKe2MCsQPoVg3JCd3+G3x35TIcNHjsB3/IoTffpB2DSiepTdL+wu/XqBM0D9YjepSVk2RRW3USlgFsPeQTI3JyI/Aw==", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f42+RXbV9dHTwFKHNfK3xx5toZ13JnlJ19XrD46b541oViqZI4YePPGIXdop7iNmam6TeynVIMsgEmYlm7YAacudIxS3tQNzSM75jy2+ONAXkbzipRHF4mHHVg2hfsoa15meyWpoezhE7l8d3+s18PduT3K+a6UO7g0aN0neICKlrUUCRsI6d5UqTrsI5u8nNpTre5vG5k+uT/tFLcQ1CvpR+d178hLwI7C94UsGgYQhO//fYaETRLhStEwYYucT33nF7hoQsWWwm9RMGkZdXdsVglpTttzdwCv5LVTK0pwRz0J1oRRKEeLy21CSk71t/YXIuJYV5tCgn4QedJlAy2mqYQzxFkYQr6tgc1Rd6bntFkTbvhH+Pj3CNcJaj6InojPL1rqpr+7NnAE/AAG/5Gs0ZZLDIZ3d32PqUA+ZVIN9pGDamMtsi5Xn4YJWdyzAX1ddgIHGnwRm40s/gLSW7v4H2zttwVKsIM5HV6NmjuV/SbSLzYW6HZ9/xGRz/D2vw2g1t9xAgiCMV5G3WD5o9ITrZWDAuc57muMNkOASnFw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_b": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is not the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_c": "Statement-I is correct but Statement-II is incorrect", 
		"option_d": "Statement-I is incorrect but\n Statement-II is correct", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060130", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIiquw3l0LhqkXqY+TfGIAd59m0tWHxKi3zWNTNtVUn4Nm7YwaPPtGjCmlcZTINP96yy6UL0DpJzivATB2myPYynNE6JG+5i6/UZo+zllyk4ly4tF8KN+ambuS5Uj4lgmO1W+YS7xoUVWXsY6r4lWVrMIqvMqFpSGb+/K5mfHH+cQObBtatpY/Ylew16cf/Th4RcCxKBFE5OrEc02tFCCmNQtd8Nij2Hspwos6Xns9+RZIg5dfbc4z1J3wqzc1MY1pHCezuUFO1NR+XgSTcP233ijw6FA2Zzo4cYt5uW06p0+OLUd3nm6STyltmrN//8QcmAFtaS9ptSzcjAuDhSWmcpfq6o68puf+s61q5rYzIE6OdVjXU55cS5z0Z2N72eqJBKtVPZ5zEmLnOtQn8irtYJWdyzAX1dczb3jptD6Rl43yK2qvvZbqzttwVK0FJdjB7MW0tWDJXS3WKXSQbov7X0jkR3m4wBpkox0ozS8E+yLfAZ96+20MnHGmTARtgWjhfnnhlbFO+IeNa8wZ3FVPJnOOF1PP91rRuIDC", 
		"answer": "25u9YYX71Auq3sUuXQyy7NS9O9OCNxOLPx49360zHrMDNg==", 
		"explanation": "25y2KLj91RDru8UhXhKyxvTrPHHVDXFd43aRQKZnYHTgQK7Ua63xz9dlL1nJnk965nOGt6317hMOna0b64GNfmIMbMt9zcOA0+G3zX8Nc8NKkI9rpI4XebRTzTCoNMTULPd6x22BKwXxaT39B3linT2WmHVRoJeotSi9FNk+1Bwok4lr5cEsfNaT1eic/kiqxhKK2TuSR6hqBUaA9fqg7gO1roYxtMPNkj3V5+Dwju3H+dEFIgxdupU/bVSo17sZ/SkxV8G3aR5H6KTAc1vlKSqqM04Z8NjgxH1kz4woSWA7+l9Eg5BTZoB82Nj2uSE5O8hkFjbh401Uh4RuUB+fdrSswyjg6UY8Z3MmbIRsqCQ6r0+eKUd7niuTQmxDkYxi+dkWm0gjb25DmTqggT6YlGDDPIDm88y8ivqwsLVi8aZnJkfAN1XKQoVe1RfuoAMDz7JvPHTbRo0DNA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060131", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmIFbIRiiMSB0qT0y3VEIIZDk5Z36todefhP22eRepTnLr5P3X2FNVH5aDf9TFE9znHqhDxioIb73Cm/Xds5gDY9mJRs5NwpKN6Q1+iD+kKujwKHzzuXR68kEBSKrN287k7cr4R4psSDtj7etPfwjvHJ9dAYagFCg4g/UV69hKcHuGIKGJL0VBwLxezVIX3jJCGiKU4+9sXwwn1905YgUmd09RZLkcNCbYBjxJfpsyY1f8wqBja0sEEAyJI8WQWXYLiq3mHw+RU+e35rcIRkqDR1oAKTJlM+jmOZDDxUm5Bn+5AWk0RKc2tJnTQyCvNr+xg0IkCwPMKoepIg", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFgjO8rPV+nXo8G+gZITEyovIU=", 
		"explanation": "25y2bJjy31nJ+IszRhfm0On2OmWQBmwHqmyCVaZnMHCjR67MaeH7iZR4M1WTiFVo+n/W7+Xn/1Ydiuha5YLfcysXd5FqxsPJ2PPyhHBNP8NDk4F8559faPsA2DWoNOHVKfFggi6BKUGwczG4FnU0nSKWhHMWu4ar9DW6QN930wEzgoI47sEoNc2a17ub4V34sg6HnFKfTLRlHxS6usC7/0qItZYxusPNsDvW57TtlbjD4tEGbRxX/4c/cF6yhK1J9yx4V9q1fBdZ/+3EeBTsLizjMgAU7dKj13lmyIVpSWExtA9DjZNaZ4B80NjNsjY5Po8g45G+mzseKOrspdXXcKOD", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060132", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fQa+r/25N4KVvJpFV/+3fI46b541oViqZI4YePMCMNest9zcOA0+H5x3QBMtRB2oN99ogaf+AAkwGjSNr6bb4u+maFZ2z+YzC8CjBXmz/FnnVCvZey+in7VdY7zwIh1pRs7Nw5L5eL1uiU+ky2kkaRzH6SQbxoUVacu8uu4leP4I0q9d2ftDTe5vH3mf3AsMoEIhxauo9tI0m5hKEN/SQsQoi9ZlJI9PbEYF3jYCWiMxoY69jf2FYkhsIdVWx03RFCi4JYIuN82IvwtSYlK8RlG3OqsUtIzpZ1SwTWdbOhkG7r8lh/enxrYYN+vz88rAaSKUB3lWXcTStQnY546pAanBBqZ2pOjzbigyyOhCWActP344X1l6jipapq9qYpKkS8O3+VFs0obbaAZ1J8w/2eCeZvJ55zEjGmHtog7y3wNIOA1jYDkN8vI3vo4znZk43mIHautp+5gdI2B7YOMd3Aqci+pFXdZC3yKXSDWsXQFEiwe3T9kydrsxEkxmEz52zLHIBr4DkEkXDwT0tonij3fzyg1q1F+ZaLcs4+1bX/1DwXlPE4nJLj3Qc5SRezhG8BrrgDGj3WSZnEF4EVntAzSQ==", 
		"answer": "25T4aZ/3kT2q+IssS1y7dWt2EjU0PjdCxiCQ605r", 
		"explanation": "25q2ZIiz8Fnr+YFgdl7z1/i/NmTCEWcSt0ONbq1geHSjfanGZ+zwibR+KU+dhE9u5n/JreXg8kEChrxIqZ2LcTYGbct7x5CZxevhzXVEc9VUn4N75ZZffvFOyTukYMebL+wu3nyFIUDiYje+AWM0gD6WnnRToZH75yKoXd4yzgEh1o52rcU9KMOay7vT/EW5kkaE3XedCLJxBUeQscvo/0uZ4JItp9uEtCWb+/K5mffd48oCdh1GtolxYlf8haEO8D4rEfy8bVJi/+DZYFqtAyetNBoU7d7333tnhoQmUWU74wwGg8NFe9Nn05WkszRwLMRkEj+/40dJ051mWhmFfLSonCqkzf2agyCirqXXauKK/KpF", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "B, C and D only", 
		"option_b": "A and D only", 
		"option_c": "B and C only", 
		"option_d": "A  and C only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060133", 
		"question": "24GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f42+RXbV9dHTwFKHNfK3/iYRoNEiMgBt09Db5nJrPyGwwsJdkqY2WZCsZe4V8wNmZm6TgzHRTNoZFlowy55MLde5Fwi7te8PeYP9iwmuHLkT+ZDz9EH80gDnTyklYoYy1uWe6Wt531B03hII45Nt8Mtjfyq2D6V+5kgPCz2+QXLgkEl2NvNSt5VCUqZJ6JnqeD1eiCWweIHMQhWYrgQ==", 
		"answer": "26axZpb/1FtydtsB7sAoaPXeESgM5hf0", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHa3x3j9otgcRH81un2IX7ECm0f43qQRqJ2fHjwXKLRLuy+2o5iM1mEzVR9skqEsKz+8F8Ks+ob6oeLeTgGcJhnwcDFl/P/zXJJc8tBm45hpI4XfeAAzTGhNNfSNPd0y2CTZ0rnYnm8CHxxkzjXhH9T6Je0tTOzUZoCzhw9mMcw7s0yKMWe1eiU51u9lAiP2XWFAf1lH1DZocat+UbcqZF4u8LNojfL9eb4jv2T89cfaxJXsZV3akv8lrsa9ykxUNyxbFJc+PDYIV3jJCG1LgoI+MejxWBo0oc6H8clqORngEqfPfbhewI+zSk=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "si,ng,le", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060134", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQBG0Qrz+MVON9fmXxW6PXbeTwztdiLlKOgV478X/Sqr/1+UAHhrgb4IDfWSwHd4owivCG2YzDrO3F8LoH0pqk/NM=", 
		"answer": "25O3e4X2w1n/+Yw0S17zyPLxMivTCnYYuXqNQeGRDmGVHxQP5hKIe5kbJZ7N", 
		"explanation": "2729KJL6xRDw8oszEhf8hdTxMWLRQ20Gpj+CXq9xd3jiWqTHLuLwxY4xM1PJmVN+skPIqqr+t2cHirpeqYeMMCwMPphq2NGb1vDyhGJVMtJB2oN78JMFefpTxDS9NJTPKPsux2CUNUr0cjqpDX961D7Qym9fpoS38Ge4Xc4+2hA8hY9x/Yg1Mpe216ya6Q25jwuRnG+eCIEmAUaWuMG87gOIqId4s8iIvTvV87T2nLjV4t8fZxpctpJmI1qyk+gc9iMsSPT2KBNG/urXIUDlJWizIgEN9c6j2XIp0oosHWo74RFSkJoUMjgl5FmfrfCT3nEyqL44+A==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Ensure state autonomy", 
		"option_b": "Encourage regionalism", 
		"option_c": "Foster unity among citizens", 
		"option_d": "Promote religious diversity", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060135", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQn4+JMpQRf9y73oNHiQAmAer3aQWqZwMHjtFPWSP7SyiZJ/I1WHihtv+nOGsLX19FoOg+hI/Y+LZTFDcY0v4tGE2vG3xX9Fc+1FiYh/7YhAPoi7cnqKWaZcBYNJ32bXXM4=", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNBtc1z/WmQzlQjPqdrLxzYiFOOZ", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdHgwRzp/oQsEg3mxOnqJivfBSIFq3rDV7FnZGbrXavHLv7qyIN0Z1OPzXF6/3vT46T+8xMkjrtT5IeNMDUCbct9zcaG3OHzhHhPc5QUy9ky8JINc+FHxH2sNMTJJe1nymuOM0zxa3myFnRxhn2WnXRfq4v79CW0WNMkyBA21rs6zNooNdST3OjAvQCZukTCyHOQXP1lHViWosusq0eZpos2vMOK8SLe5vn4lP3d5J4ZZxtbu4Nxd0j8lqYNuCk3X86xegBC/+OQckToIyGiK04P8MzrwmcrqcYBtAwd+BsVn8hAjBKc4g==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Article 370", 
		"option_b": "Article 19", 
		"option_c": "Article 16", 
		"option_d": "Article 35-A", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060136", 
		"question": "24C2bJThkQ3i8sUJXBr7xPO/FmTeEHYYt2qXW6x6PDH0XKbWLu7/x9diM12diEg79nmGqquw41Ydgrsb5ojfdzACcJ9mxtfJ1eH5wXdIJ9UEjo8y8JIadeYA3ji+fdDeLup9kSxEe4D5Um9BcY1JPypuh6st", 
		"answer": "24WqZ4f61Ryq5JUlURfzyb39MGXVBWsFsD+KXON6f3+uV6jMffn33YJlLlOHjFc7/3fSt6Di5BEqpfBaC5I8Uqk82UkdlvEB", 
		"explanation": "26asaYX2wlnp9otgVQzzy+m/JnvVAGsQrz+BV61xdnj3R+fNfK3u25J3Ik6Mg1h+4TbSrOXk/1YGnehJ7J2WdCcNapgvwd7J2uXj0HRTIIZQkoFmpJwecPgAwyi5Z93fJb56xmvAN1DicTC4EzB7knHqyH9ZppCv/DOuQNM4zhQ+1pVx6sAoL+vdmbiB51uxggOGnHmICKlsFBS6usC7/0qItZYxusPP0w+dIQ+RIcnjx54bcQoEFQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Provide special benefits in non-constitutional matters", 
		"option_b": "Impose additional taxes", 
		"option_c": "Prohibit residents from moving", 
		"option_d": "Establish a separate legal system", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060137", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTj444wjXhuyyvu/HGXUCmMf43yMXLBgeWX2QK7LYeO+25JiM06Ajk9osmLOpuX9+EUKgq1V/c6efiZDbY573NyM2uH50DFONYZLj5Rh7Z4abucAxTPtYMbSIv9ijm+SIkTjJzCzRFl6kDjX1T4YEODQrP3MMDYEhTRpxxoo", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3Ryqptxitb+YxqqlFsmvtL5vF8sppw==", 
		"explanation": "26GwbdH1wxzv84otEhH0hfDwI27dBmwF436NVuNmdWLqUKLMbei+wJkxDlKNhFo7+2WGsLDy/VYMm+hP5s6LeCdDQsl/2t+d0ufjzX5Pc8lC2ol88J8NeedU332icpTII/ZrynuMIgXkdTC/AWM4qHOWnXRfq4v7+SK6UMl31BpyhIJr+do1P8OW1qaAqEK2xgmXyGiYTLh2AhSKsNq850qSp8Ixu42ZozvZ9fi5m+rW8c1JK/iQURukdZhmWD52lY5ZxQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Article 19", 
		"option_b": "Article 18", 
		"option_c": "Article 21", 
		"option_d": "Article 20", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060139", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sU0Vwz/1r32OyvzDG4ErnHDc+NjeWXrFLPKa+TsiZR+NU6Mjk879nPVoLf550cGgKZIqYeRMAEMcp5ixpCrmaacjJXvQNGro0UBtbyMYN0N", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNABH17AwOvwPm7UQ2sf4y3TA/o0cX/nFKbAYeH32p94KVvJnkt+8X/Hr+Xi/lQHm7sb6ICbMDIRd51mxNWO0ve3zX8BGcdJl5Uy5ZQbPN9B3zWgfcaXYN982meDK0CwNG7tSTBThjDYnm8Wu5e64SKoFM4/xVUimZB9/4goM5ePy62A61+xhAPCzn6CQblhH1ec9c+7q0Lco402scSZuD3VtPL2iLjA4NsIaw5bvMZ6bkuwmLEE/SQsQoi7elJK4fTfaFr5LS2tMx1Ruerxwn1qyodpDD95tC9UjYtfYMlnxdjgtSEzLcRnHD27t01PydRzUVeRZrKt3mz3oFo5NWguaYNqtSI74R2dK1E+mWqPWCkRh4Vzvt8L1RRvfGxF3Hnmwj2CknGHMNPC+ZT1huT14Og6v+MXO06UMF/MRc0IbbaALmlmz/ueHrJPc5BhVzHlNdAq6TX8YIKG1jsIw5kiNjf18TmNgMT2LWy0tNL0gcJzGboOIpHE58/3o1nTdS/kLHidcov9V0jkXXX60gIltgogyTJSihyHfX/WehRtNldjzJtetQ==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNBtc17lxO6/NGnfD2sCq3qHEqp6MCOzBf6OLszs3Z5yK1nJ3A07smbUrK359VobnOhf4J2cYisOd4Vu3NmG2aT4yjFVO8MEnZJ98ZQbb7RPyn2/cdjSJ/dhwCLANUTzYnX9B3FngDSaym9TsM/7+jX7RNY2wxBymYE478EuKN/RmZSd1EOZlBKL33eUCOwyXBS3uo6r4leVuoc29d6FsD7XuLT2lLjU4tEebAxB/4lxb0L8mK5J6i80WM+9ZxwHsfbRYlGhYCuiNBoYtYvw02wlhoYsTmox+gsKwpNaY8N2lpfi/DA5LdliWXOopldJw5FyXBLWe6/40Wb9oFo5NW4jYIch/C8w4QaSLVh3nWKeQCkRko95spAWh0RndHxDjn/tizGKlGCLPJLk6onylvywqbcj4KY0OUSDIRzXUMFcZL3ZZ2J/2uWUFKtZPYsnGDCmMtMo9Tr8YIOa2zwfkM0oKjfU4CuNl4PJN1m0koDth9d6Ef9TYYGF7tm2vkjUITD1IGmWdYvgUQ2wX3Pv1hwloxdl2DMV+2HKAYt6tT8IjXe0TEpnl2fhfzyg1r1T5IaHa4c+3bXq0iBQi+R9nJLx3R58QgmrgXBav4GRW08PwkaWH90XywAgGLkEGoKR8HiC1XjfXDwfesrjD6yGzTgGmt//sm9crYQHVoCLbEiCys40xwO0AulqFXPlrcbwM+gQGGE/7qExxevhpMmzcPexIGBqewi+W+pKs5dIKBB+Ah/PDCdbabapFpARV+VC13ve1wZGQz9aAE7Y960FWAq+6s3GLn7MarMdAl7jcbYEAIC6vAOEc14ojOULnQiIeRbcCQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Article 16,Prohibits discrimination on grounds of religion race caste sex or place of birth", 
		"option_b": "Article 35A,Revoked in 2019 and abolishing special rights and privileges in Jammu and Kashmir", 
		"option_c": "Article 19,Protects the interests of schedule tribes by restricting movement and settlement in tribal areas", 
		"option_d": "Article 370,Grants states the power to prescribe residence as a condition for specific employments or appointments", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060139", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3AGm6FB7ICMeCsTPsNOxdWH0+nyymUIc+dHjswytspPL7gAwTypcZTLMvF4x32JKEvjJz+yFjB1lyDDg29fvIq0+2f7ZN8l0xo8hcd364gVMtOW2KbTx1+xgQ+MnDOhYZJ3WBSfp8GlqxLK4JEosM6Etzve8LT6le3d5MwCZxtusbVrYk+5mq0H7GoReJKIZiZD9KT5b1DkISbjBAET6t/qwmF9z40nHWg4+BBRkcNQbdIz0o3lsHIzNtljDza0sExJ19R6UAXWfbO82X7t5EA+eWlrZ49hsyMyqAGbaEBx2miZXjhQnY4r7cAclg1ldGpE3HXvlzGfkmyKb6/t147LjeHzqPls/KZnJkfAIVTdFosTab/PMG58zamSHuZfPI11EiHyfdwgvCv8M4aR3C1N399gO3/itCubndvweXausob8g9F4AKxfdAuCuI2brcNkCeKQaPiejEI=", 
		"answer": "24asaYX23Bzk48gJEhfhhf7wJ3nVAHZRoWqXEpBgcWXmWaLMeqDX4Nd4NByAg1h04GTDoLGyOPYnZ8Zr/ohoIrHinRV95Q==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ2A3j7YAuQRb71b23FGbVDWYcpnGXG+NVc2WvFPWSPr6yiZ5/I1mMiRtr4HnQqqH18xMJgLob/YaaMCMAb55m29md3uv5hH5Hc+lSn5Jh4ZsMPNdJ2DS3cdrIKPd+jmGGZ2z+YzC8RDhbtxifyn5P6LO+5zS0Wsl3zxNyv4l85MkyfPiN0K+a5g3wti+tzzLRTq9rHBTI4467+0afqYQxsMnNsj3O+uDrk/3AsNEfag1A/5J3YlX8p6kC8TksUMb0aRxPscbRb1PhISymNAZdzcPmll1nwosoUykX+xFVlopCd9R62ZakuD01LI1kGif6okhMyIM8WRiENLmt0WSk41wrfGAua5lltT11rh3cLEF/liuSTThYm45q8tkNjEa21PlXQnf3X+7YFH6bnMPV", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_b": "Both Statement-I and Statement-II are correct and Statement-II is not the correct explanation for Statement-I", 
		"option_c": "Statement-I is correct but Statement-II is incorrect", 
		"option_d": "Statement-I is incorrect but\n Statement-II is correct", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060140", 
		"question": "27a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R5vMXfn/3ZJ8IlKdzXIhskrIl631t3AGm6FB7ICMeCsTPsNOxdWH0+nyymUIc+dHjswytspOKbgAxTO5ZtvfNf1ryi6UL0CwW3uSEnVmhzTXmTx1oZey7yK1FNUxgDw8ko55res9LtOX1qSX7V+ExEaR33OURbgkE03ZuMu67EqSp8IsvcjNgRv0tPf4iPyT490DZwVX/4dxZxuon61J1wkREcu1ehYL4ufYZFnoHCaQMw8J/Mbm2GAp76tzYWd0wBdDwqBfdslp05b3tDsgf4VLGDa0p0lFyYA1HzaVYPH4gji1tRl/cGI7ZIRpuSl1tQeZaEd9lXuZDCNX1K9I15ANmkRqc2xMiXLlwj6HjCWJc4Hm4ofyxebxtLBs/KIrOgGFLV/dRplccbvPNGIyzPuUAOZsMpRuBDbnM5Uv8j25Apea2DUM1NwzJ0vpyCSumsT2MSW1tdLthtE2B6sBItTI7MWjoxzAaDXkLz2SZMTiXEj5XDP5wQsltBc32iQT/CBsWCZlc6HnB2WLuULhr3V3", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz+Fnr+YFgezewDbm4SXZFF7HmzNz7mUMRzw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ2A3j7YAuQRb71b23FGbVDWYcpnGXG+NVc2WvFPWSP7iyiZp0NVuMiRtv+nOGk4zft1AOnawb+o2XdS8GPophzJCd3+G361Joc8VFiIQy95kXeflFjDSjYNubIb5gy3nANEb4YjS4RHN1mD3TjjxCoIb7yWWUQt8l0xAzhcdb5Nw1JtKRmaeVqGS2gg+DnFiQWrlsHlidsNyUqQOPo4o9uMjN8QbT8bTak+za6tsFcQBbr8Y3Qla5mawE/SQsGIiVawYHsbaAMAGhYCyqI04Y4dvi2HAp0oosHXo3+w9DwoxQItR709jLnxtwK8IqHD25r1FEwtRMWgWFe7OrkGfioHwxcXMqa8pCriQyqAHcYGRXtXjVDCpDm40r/9wV1QdsaGFUjn/lkX+OmGaKbIej24H3jPvkobcj860jaWOBO1vUV4kZdruMZ2ZhiuWUA6EcMownAyrjNMdu9Db0JdaX0CwDxMspKmSn9SaKnY30NWm1pJf9ztBjFbNANdjR4NGyvk/PaDOhNHOXY9m0TQD1Rm643wFmthRlxCAH+yDPU+xoUDWIJrJS+vIq3qSd", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "I only", 
		"option_b": "II only", 
		"option_c": "Both I and II", 
		"option_d": "Neither I nor II", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060141", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDbOLr3ddeMVmbnl564TblqrH57VYBz6ddqaeRdCsCPsNA6/nAl/fjxWVUIIZFiIUy8IgKeat8wgGjVZmbD91HjmaPK0H1dSr9DHFikXHQn3Ba6ICy4S6hUdQkyBwi1pVx6sAoL5eW1+i65kmxhzqM/jbRCIlsFBSausCr7lOI4I0+9cmYsD6b9/3tk+LW/s0DaxgStpU/cV6/mK8H8TA9VYihZhZO46T/Qn2tMzyiMxsOxcXAmzQp6aEAHWo15htOjY9SZ9Jglpn2uXI+MNkqED+zpE1Cy5E8SxjWYrKs1Sjt7hUWe34iZIQtuSEwohuVJ1ptpmW4AWwRoIhuvvMQgQ15eGFTlH/wwneqjWCBeJ7m5ZS1xcnztPUjoPN3eg3AJU7XQIQYYLeACERbivqPDLJJIN9zGGLWOMc98zfqYJmSnxAD1NAhITfI5iOem8O1cVWTnIGwztJkG7JAN93Jqci4pVLTcyrkMkGdWsXcVh+wQn32yk5qsVgxwCRQ+3bZHIxy8CMZ0W3wTk1ylymgbX6ugLsc45HBfpw0k/bjzyAVm+An3b+UDH3B+8zJMpeyOve3gDk=", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3hfvtQQBK6FoVpzvW6f7i+bSuw8=", 
		"explanation": "25q2ZIiz8lnj5MUjXQzgwP7rCWXsDU0yij+LXa9wdWPwFKPNLuPx3dd5JkqMzV1u/nqGoKzk/kkKgbtT4J7fYisEdp98iNmHl835wHhAc/JMn5ky5YgaPPNSzTO5cdCbI/t82m+JKQXibj61EGM0lT/SymxEoZWy+SK8Ucl7gBcngsds5c0lfNOQmaac/A2oiRWR2WiCCKlsFBSKtMOtq1GVp4ospo2MonLd4fj12tHd9NcKbEhRtpJ2eV6yhOg98C94csGgYQhO//fYaEStaAmuIgAZ9M7twj0p54E9ESlmpE8VzsNSa8Qzxorrqjs0Oo1FNhr6sFBB04FvE1eUYan42Xyk91QsNXYiaIN5uSl1tQDcGFFsiWSSX2xeksBC8NQQlAojUn1Jm3/uwne7qUqcNdPl+Y/xxfvgpbpq9KoiLQGDOknWQp8VYKCMZ2l93qmaAaocMJByGTb0NNA9vn46G03VoESrZ/DVSRYG1Bs=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only one", 
		"option_b": "Only two", 
		"option_c": "Only three", 
		"option_d": "all Four", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060142", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRqnGHW7V9dGTiWLSCb//7iZJ9LluAj1d+snDJseXf4VYdnK1a+s68eTYKZI5hiN+Pl835wHhAc45ruak7pIkLfeBV32KReujVAbMu7y6QIlfjaDf9C3Y0kj7Ej3VRpsO05y68XdR31x091o5rrcU9LsWW3KzT/EL4hwjC9XWVQbxqUVeQocey7k2grqB19Y2sv3LS+vDwjPHX5d8HIh9asMZoYkj8lugK8T4xS826KB1Nsc3eZV3sYCm3ZxoV/Iv333lsho0vHX088V9ljY1Fdslnw4ztszx3LI1pGj63pkpDwpl5UQOqep71kCjFoFg2e3U5JYlltSEx4RiUJ0d72mmTWCQRhIF5+94NhkRib2oAtXjkiz6FwGaGaJr57o7vuebU7fkj061nIE+EPErRUpgdafPXL2hhz6mcH6dSN49mBSfoKcZu6zzrJdaX1i0EytwuPDfo8mqpk8b8KnG7vdBwao8ihWEp82C1IqFS7kky", 
		"answer": "25T4aZ/3kTqq+IssS1xNkh+f7to6uNa8/BvtjnrV", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHgwRb/5IBgXRiyw/LtMGLXDSIesXaEW600f3ejVamCR+P6wJZ/Z1+AmVJh93iGqraw8l8GiKFZ5Yvfdi0RPqRM4ZCaw+Xj0WIBGshAk5Z74I8ecOcA2zWiZ9GbJ+xvwGqQJlf1aS2uRGdxhjSWiXVCoZm++zT7W9x38BQ5n5Rs7MZ8PcWamaac/A29ig+F1XmdTf1iHkbZmu2Bq1CIoZYtpo25uTeb8fjwnfHR+dICdhESvJR2d16unqlJ/TI7Xd2wbVJC/+DZd13pNSmvNE4K8N/rlnds1JYoVGd09RFFh5BCcMF/lpvrsjw1PNljGj2p41BPh4dsWhSfcrS91Cjn70AxYWgiYJktsCQ+pE+sKV93iX+dQmxQmoQr3NEXkghieWpTlDT4uqUXzG+M1hjMOh5NsP2i", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "B, C and D only", 
		"option_b": "A only", 
		"option_c": "B and C only", 
		"option_d": "A and C only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060143", 
		"question": "24GwbdHw3hfp8pU0EhH0hfnqNGeQAGsFqmWGXLB8eWGjXbSCYOLqiZZ9K1OeiF87+3iGiqv0/lJPi71eqZqQMAMRaoJsxNXJ6Nu3y3cBJ85B2ql84JMecrRjwzO+YN3PNepnwWDCQKce0eQ9R0r0vNnoYgLyTg==", 
		"answer": "wK7TKhP658JfT7o0OZ0B44E=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqrsUvVF7mzfi/HGXUCmMf41yMXLBgeWX2QK7NYK370Yd9Ll+AmVdismXSorH15BMbh6lPqY/fYCcRbYRhiMeB2KThy31UPdJFiIl+/doef+VVxS+oZ5TYKepn1GuONE35d3myAjB1miiWhWherZH79iiuWs4l2VU7hcd24tx8OduW3qGR5Ej4gAmQnFKfTLRlHxSavNqh8UaSs4oxpY25uTvItOTrle7a49cEbEhXuYB6YE+1ga0F4WooQ8e8YRBC5feQZUHsLGigLhoU487txXxg1sImTykw4R5Kwo1Xdsl82JnotSYpffWBMuI6+Fw4A+0BGzNPmlY=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": 9, 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060144", 
		"question": "24GwbdHQ2A3j7YAuQRb71b23FGbVDWYcpnGXG+NVc2WvFPWSP7iyiZp0NVuMiRtv+nOGk6Di5FwBz6ddqaeRdCsCcMtA2tmO3uq3jEFoHI8EmYFg4NoMf/xFwTjtddrfYOpmyy6vMUDidDy8FzBXnSXfkHlY6Iy9tQ61UNM2gF0dta4xrcs9LtPfyqub7UC9xhKNnHiDTbxwFBSNvcvo1wGjn70HivKyjg3kyLa5ifvb9dMOIF6mh0I0srVxTlaMNKpRRgw=", 
		"answer": "25qbQdHw0Avu/4osVhvgh5ImcBvp3PKiJN1d2ieGjio=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ2A3j7YAuQRb71b23FGbVDWYcpnGXG+NVc2WvFPWSP7iyiZ5/M06GiU5493KGouX+8kRPnKtT7IOaMCkNcZxhiNGal/D/wTF9celSn5Jh4ZsMPNdJ2DS3cdqbL/gu52CELkSwRDivAHh7mDXTmEAU6JC4/SK2UZoDyBwh1pR75c0xOZeI2LvT7kKqiwOGnHmICLBhA1OQu8no/0uZ4LIRmo2OsCDftOf6kv3e9Z4KbAwSq456I3SfvugK+Tg8Edu3YBdG9KTEbhT+KSWzKwcb4Iv33nEp1pAmXmwn519AjZEWa853347tuCcxM94qGjX6pUtSwp17UVeZZrS/2Wak91wrfToCa45kvSN1swCTPEc8KmBjeC19Ns4AFCZc1MWTwA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "OC,I, ca,rd,ho,ld,er", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060145", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQE3cDs3CQV+N7djH3XKKCQfv724R0Jk/JrlJv+2zDreX/8RMmgaxS6M7XXwEqN8t83NGdwveohgEnKLa9whnVv3y+5VWRQ00=", 
		"answer": "26G3KJnyxxyq9IAyRh/7y73tPGzYF3FRonGHErNmeWfqWKLFa/6+wJkxDlKNhFo5c8taxh3cmDGaPKW2sgB5Ag==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHc8jCq5JEhRgvhhfzzOWTHECIYrXuKRKpwZXDvR+fNaK34xoV0LluHzVRp+3HPreXn/kcHz4FV7YeefmIRcYR725Cd2KT/xWdEc8VBiJRz7ZRfbv1HxCm+NNXVJL5+3GeWLkn1YDyuRHl61BjYjnVX6JSy4S+0Qc53xwczmJNx4898OsKT1eiQ4VmxnAOMz3OYWP8Q/bXnJTjIg81uuIMzlZ3S", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "To grant full Indian citizenship rights", 
		"option_b": "To provide dual citizenship", 
		"option_c": "to have certain rights and privileges in India", 
		"option_d": "To enable voting in Indian elections", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060146", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRjp48UpXArgyvnqNm7UQ3YZpj+AXa13dWH3FKjELsLozIViIl2azXhy5n/cpquw+FVPpqZf4I/fOA0gV8Iv28SIw/HkmzMXcmjSwguD3NPyIhj9SLHM", 
		"answer": "25axfJjp1Bf5/4wwElbzyPjxMWbVDXZY416ARu80IiGzB+WKqXYX1h3L5N0YK1ron6+l", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ2A3j7YAuQRb71b23FGbVDWYcpnGXG+NVc2WvFPWSPr6yiZ5/M06GiU5493KGt631t1AAgate+ZrffyRDUahGiMOd1vDi1zFHPNQEqoVg95URb7RPyn2EetDSIfAu4XyJIEz+J3GNLV9n3XHQmHNb6JCr8CSyUtMyxFUxmZJ2+do1OcTdoKjw/KPOjYPF8lelxKWX4A==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Citizenship Act, 1955", 
		"option_b": "Citizenship (amendment) Act, 2003", 
		"option_c": "Citizenship (amendment) Act, 2015", 
		"option_d": "Citizenship (amendment) Act, 1980", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060147", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzwxDt/5FgWw2ywu/+O3/VByIFrD+sRKZmY3TiR+fhZ/n305J/Z1OPzXJ19n/H4+3f1HpGz6ta+4qXfy4He5l8l5JXr6x+H2p16uHpXPCMRVOC", 
		"answer": "24exb5nnkQ3lt5IvQBWyzPO/HGXUCmNTMJxTKO3JzlPmSkS7Ld5Kqw==", 
		"explanation": "25qbQdHw0Avu/4osVhvg1r3+J26QDW0F43qPW6R9cn3mFLPNLu/7iZJ9Il+diF8782WGt631t2MdirtS7YuRZGIMeMtGxtSA1qi30n5VNoZNlMBb6p4WffoAyTGod8DSL/B9gi6PNQXyYjqyCXU0viTSjXlF6Iy9tTOzUZoE1QUgk4p9reszKcWLmaeVqGS2gg+DnkBjBfdkB21M0RggOM9gyJI=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Right to work in India", 
		"option_b": "Right to vote in Indian elections", 
		"option_c": "Right to be elected as President", 
		"option_d": "Right to become Judge of Supreme Court", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060148", 
		"question": "24KwZ9H6wlnv+4wnWxz+wL35OnmQLEE442yXU7dhYzHqWufQa+H/3Z5+KRydghtr82TDrbHjsBMMhrxS84uRYyoKbtQtPTOSLgp7uWjzmtqr6pxavg==", 
		"answer": "25T4ZZj93guq9I0pXhqy0vTrPSvSDHYZ41aNVqp1fjHgXbPLdOjwiYdwNVmHmUg5CCS64vT7BZ7JIg+tHIJCOg==", 
		"explanation": "25T4eJThwhbku8U3WhGyzO6/NCvdCmwesT+AWqp4dD2jVanGLvr2xoR0Z16GmVM74nfUpqvk5BMOna0b6oeLeTgGcJgvx9bJ/urzzXABPNQElY53pJUZPOBIyX29dcbeLup9jmeTZ0SwZDCpDWpxmnHZjDx/poey9GeyR5oyzBw1n4V06Ig6M8Xf9ou6qF6shxKXzzl6F9RFkWqzwQkVigc6kg4S", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Children of Indian citizens only", 
		"option_b": "Children of non-Indian citizens only", 
		"option_c": "Children of mixed nationality parents", 
		"option_d": "A minor child with both Indian citizen parents", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060149", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sU0Vwz/1r32OyvzDG4ErnHDc+NjeWXrFLPKa+TsiZR+NU6Mjk879nPVoLf550cGgKZIqYeRMAEMcp5ixpCrlcq7iOpGjn+tMRlRlqBBp0M=", 
		"answer": "24C2YYX21VnZ44Q0Vw2/4PH2MmLSD2dRpXCREoxXWTHwQKbWe/6yibZkNEibjFdy8zvjr6z3/lEDiuhU54KGMCsFPp9nzdmbl+z4yXQBMMlRlJRg/doecPhP2y7tcMHaLL5tx3qJPUD+dDG0FDw0tjDYjXBXrIao/WqVW853xRk7kY564c18OtiNmYewwQ2rkgeWyWjdCI1lGl2Koc+mpmaQqYUxt8GI8TfD9/Hpjrja9p4fag1brcZ4cVqyk7gI6i82Rdv0fxdZ9KTTaEDkOi2tNE4S/4v33n16hoEmSGcg5gYE+60nyZiCbQ59lnuRDoPZgg==", 
		"explanation": "24C2YYX21VnZ44Q0Vw2ohc3WGniQBXAerj+XWqY0RX/qQKLGLt7qyIN0NByIn14793rPpKzy+1ZPiadJqaG8WWIQaop73cO12cXi12VTMspNm9oy1LMwb7RG3jKgNPXOM+p8z2KJJgXxdTz9AXx9kzjUhnkWroyptQiYfZok1BQmg5Q44sYwJZeW3+iH4EixlEaK03aUCL5rBFqNp9fo6k+Qr5Ur9cmYsD6b9/3tk+LW/s0DaxhusaV+bVq4lvJJyAMXQoiyeh1GscfRb1XpIWiiNQtd/Mfq0X1ryodpW2YmtDBlq8NFdsFnw4vYsgIxNMR5ATK0+QRw7rtvHwCee669kG/24Vs7ZXs5YIR5r20ipB2ZaFd3jmKGSSJC1I9tvuAYng1waW5O3Hfyh3+Fj3HPeZ/q7In+ie2wprZxsowEAAGTIV3MQ55eGog3/Dj2PPCsmVthczmtWg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "United States,Eligible for OCI status", 
		"option_b": "Pakistan,Eligible except if their grandparents were citizens of this country", 
		"option_c": "Australia,Eligible only if their home country allows dual citizenship", 
		"option_d": "Bangladesh,Not eligible for OCI status", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060150", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sU0Vwz/1r32OyvzDG4ErnHDc+NjeWXrFLPKa+TsiZR+NU6Mjk879nPVoLf550cGgKZIqYeRMAEMcp5ixpCrlcq7iOpGjn+tMRlRlqBBp0M=", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqosgDWwr73/jxJmPZEyIQtz+XWqY0c37uWaLMbejzzJllZ1OPzU9z9zblrKvj41obmrxS5oDTMAMRaoJsxNXJgKnFzXZJJ9UElYYy55MLde5Fwi6lfcSbL/guzWuSM0T5aXmwDXdmlT/CmTxCp8OL9CyyR842zllyt5Vs5MswOZfOieWw50OsjwiX3XWSTf1rFxSNvcvo+UqbqJYr9cKL8THS4P3jn/bA+NcbLkhzrZJ2YFe51/lYtRo5Q8S9aR9O//CQdVutMi2kMgIc7c6jwnxshpAgWmEgtBBAwoBfdslp05b3tDsgf89zVT+7tAY8GN0RZKFk06+MWA3MIzEJ", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqosUkVw3x1/T9MHiQIGsFqmWGXLB8eWGjVbOCeuX7iZR+KlGMg1h+/3PIt+X/8RMbh60byoGRYzYKap57wd+Hm6TLylBTJ89HloUys9oLffhL332sdtvONL5Nx3qJPUD+dDG0FDB1gHHCgnkWq4y2+CK1V986xRsm1oh+rdw0OZe81qaA/ESskxKL03XdCIFqMEaNvM2k7gPN8MIrtNSe8RHU+uDwlO3S/t0OIgdU/5J3Zhuunq8B7Dl4Xs70axtf+P7Vb0flKTjjZw8T/Yvf2FV70osqUWx0pU4GhopVd9Ng04uk/AIxLcFjFD6/rVAA05s8TRKRYbG5xG2k9F06NWgiYoJ5/CIz4QyVPF1kn2WPRCVB1IJyvtwYgkbSDbx8Tb8i2WrG5s3ErvsZ", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Article 7,Rights of citizenship of certain migrants to Pakistan", 
		"option_b": "Article 10,Continuance of the rights of citizenship", 
		"option_c": "Article 5,Citizenship at the commencement of the Constitution", 
		"option_d": "Article 11,Parliament to regulate the right of citizenship by law", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "060151", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/2CLtasmcckGmCHsVUqvzbnsbH59F8Kz/sMuK/fZC1DLdw+mZCe0vbyhHhPIMNWjoV2pJMRPOBIyX2Oe9rINPd623qJKEuwaD/9LX5wnTCWnnMWpYa+4WepUd0+zxszmsd86MU9MtOMmaeVqGO5gQeO3XWVBP1FAkeYuILoxkKSqZItp4HNkDzf/Ob42sjB8doOcQAe/7V2aFC1muRJ1SMiXtq1ZV4L0PbFb1flISTjFxwc/c7w3jRoyIZpemY1yBEUz8MWQc99xYztqCckNsJkVTy8421Ow519HxaYcP2s2G2k1Vs2YX8vJbl5vTkwsk+TLhRfl26ORS9Q1IVl6NkKlANmPW4AmGPhjn+bj2mGf4qjo7T0gKjFrrBs/OMmJ0XAIVTdFr4IZKfFNC4yyPyPTaccIJZpEC7jfdYn6DDtOpOazDEEwOUufDqn1WqXk9ngK2S2uoj8ipR1HasJLNTLqcSx8HXJZSrgYX6SaIv6XB71XTz61k5hsgg3wTcV7CLXDsl3/D5NnXekQF5hnDToZWydmIJS3YqHfIZx3POsyToV2Odsno/y2RgyUxf7inZVt4rfTl5A21GWF95IxRsrTLcOBoTU8XnJ11uZ5Qjq0ND2fKJboxj/MS8=", 
		"answer": "2+T4Z5//yFtqIB4th9O9apMH4n7ZyUrT", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNJxEj+y0fK/HCvUBmMdsD+UW7d8MGLzUaTLb+G+2YV+MVWahFR14TbSrOXe9lQOg6lV7cLfUTEQf4YjiP2I2e3n0WMNc+dKnohg5dovbvVEyS6lOJToKfVlx2PMZ2j5fTavBX041BDEn3JXq4u6+WeLRtszxQY61oZ26YgbM9bf7aCWqG63iBWW1W+EXLRrHxSWs46B5UeVocI9u9uEojPc8ee5m7jA+dAMbg0Sr4lzalil164G6mo6Xty8KCdF+OveIVXjJGi3Lwtdyt/iwnF6+owVU0h0+h5Sl5FXbslp05ykvzskNtdvG3OzsARPyZE8SB+ZNLy7wX3t8lAsNXkicYN3uSMmqQaMaFF3jmOZXmwRlpkr0NENgBZicWZanWLpjTHLj3fPfoqj2YX7jPvksrh3+6wpaXWIMEWYVYwSJbHFZ2N32vuSG6NYc5BhVyHvKdw0+TfqKJ+EnzALkM0oKm6n9SmIh8TnPGH6sJvth85zGqwIP8GF69L3pU/ObyShJ2+Sc8/hVQ3+Wzz11g9rpFrI6jlzSqudpEUQjiYEv8fZ", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Citizenship", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1,2 and 3", 
		"option_b": "l and 3", 
		"option_c": "3 only", 
		"option_d": "1 only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070101", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQBXcfoGuKXa00f3ejQK/HLt7r2YV0KlnJrlRu4GKGtKzk/xMdirtL7I2LMDYMPq16xtSI2uH50HBNc/RNnYhm99oWcrRpwjmkdYuZjzy6+cHyJQZwM0f8UHe9jQ==", 
		"answer": "24G3KILy1xzt4oQyVl7U0PP7NGbVDXYQrz+xW6R8ZGKhdoekUj9c/JzsYrY2H96VrQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjwxDn9pc5Egz9yfi/Om2QF2oU40yWQrFxfXSjd6jXfPm+wJkxDlKNhFo7+2WGt6qw5FIJiq9O6JybMCMNest62NiG2+C34mRPN8dJn45m5ZZfTv1HxCm+OJTVL+ou2mHAJkf/azCuDDBgnDTbxDx/vMO/+iKoFM4/yQZygo9q4t07NJeVzKya60S5ikaQ2W2YTaooUV2Kptuh5UTct5Axod7B8Tra+vD1k/bUsM4eYARbvMZ2bU+5ha0a7Go0WNy9bxNf+OveLRTkLjymNR4P/N/q2HMp1IsuVX0nuF9HjIcWYMF/15bntTw3f85lGCO/t01OwNR1UQOTZrirxHuk9102eX9rYIR+qT88rwjcPFx72niJXD5UmYFo55AWk0R3dWoAv3nukSuClHCbdZztpcIRdnoOus66nrBrHWW4ypBu", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "To enforce the Fundamental Rights", 
		"option_b": "To suspend Fundamental Rights", 
		"option_c": "To create new Fundamental Rights", 
		"option_d": "To safeguard Fundamental Rights", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070102", 
		"question": "25Gtepj91ln9/4wjWl7m3O36dWTWQ2ccpm2EV613aTHgVamCeuX7iadwNVCAjFZ+/GKGsLDj51YBi+hP4YvfYysbPplmz9idxKTw0XBTMshQn4V2pJgGPNVS2DSueNGbcacuwWjAM031JxqyCmNgnSXDnnVZptz5PWTzdGrSu2LHGdifWO1R0Q==", 
		"answer": "25u5fJj83xjmt6AtVwz1wPP8LCvUBmEdom2GVuN7fjH3XKKCaf/x3Jl1NByGixt+6mLDsavx+xMOiK9J7J2MeS0NPFQ8wJVb5nQRTvPoBdrvjkU=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHD0Avm/oQtVxDmhfL5dULeB2sQ43yCXONnZWLzUanGLvn2zNdiLkTJn1J8+mLV46Ll9kEOgbxe7IrfcjtDX5l7wdOF0qSmnTFONYZQkoUyx5URb+BJ2Ci5fdvVYPp73GeOIAXxJxe8EHl7mjDayllbrZG88Cm4TZojyBQm1o5rrcw5P9uey62XqEK2xhKK2TuWWrJxH1CK9cGuq3/epZossN+DsD6b9fP+iP3A49cEbEZu/cZLa1Kv17gG7y8qEcGnKBVZ8OrEZFCtNSanIhxd2Nn333dlw8J6CDF0+xkGlotTIul90pHlsnITMMN5ATqutlBJyJoyHyuYSLOcxXrt7lJ/Zm8obcpssm0wrAqOL1FwmXLQDDhZkcBs8cYchwpueGFU3H7hkX+fiGDPfYb344/ujPzp4K1ssrEiOlWSPF/MFoIOJaDVNHd3xO3bGa5Zc5xuAyv8ONs9u3nrKZGcy3kZ35kmPXLi8CWU0sLzeXaqtpf6hpR3GrtAM8nV+86ko1XIb2+hNXWWJtn9XgDkD2j3kw92pB0oyi0VqHLdCYp68zgBkmf8CVBsl2fyZXupgv5I5cKIcJw8k/T/zj0TkfVslpT5x10zVUSug3ZMvJfTD11ByRTZCsUC1kk8BbMJAIWR/2iYgX/fRXkJP8f4QYmV1yVL1uax3zgz/6wAaYKnOF7Iytcr2BijFfx3QSf5p8b3MugQSnAk+6Yx3uWopIqoYOC0KWs5ZhW5GeZKs4FUZRJ0AwrPHGRObrzuRZURVOxLknfP1xdaSG9GF07F9KYJUUS+pYTcZm+ecLgIGx/2arwLX475QEOPIfms2zWJFLabnVOtH0U3S3qcNKQC6Abkc4/zKB+q03ph78jzN1UbS40UOWfnfG75oK6GGQE/cS88aINUOkvcTQQhkHCB4RftVVCkDRndnWEc99/J7A==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "National Emergency declared on the grounds of external aggression", 
		"option_b": "National Emergency declared on the grounds of armed rebellion", 
		"option_c": "State Emergency declared on any ground", 
		"option_d": "Financial Emergency declared on any ground", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070103", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRj/440vQBfm3L38NGWQEWcCt22KUbc0f2OjVaXQYer/3ZIxM1SMzVpr4nrPoKTk/lwBz6ddqaiKfiYCc45h3NGFl9b+w3lVIIZClZIy6Z8SfvFS332icpTPKPsuz3yNIkGwYTavB3Vn1DDYjjxXpoK3+iC0Qcl30xAggI576NtjfujCJ61QObDjiCQ/ZVQ9yiU=", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHD0Avm/oQtVxDmhfL5dULeB2sQ4fq2cjKTRTCGvxdkgiYirv4=", 
		"explanation": "24C2bJThkTj444wjXhuylq6/Om2QF2oU41aNVqp1fjHAW6nReuTq3IN4KFLFzU9z9zb2orf8/lICiqZPqYaeY2IXdo4v2N+e0va30H4BPsdPn8B+5Y0MPOBIzSntZtHINOxnzXrAKFewZjuvC3d1gDSWnnRT6KWu+yO6Wd851BQ+1rVx6sAoL5fX1K2d/ES3iAOGnHKfCI1lA0DZnOeBq0ya4JYwsI2uvjzI4P3tj+za/9BCIg5drcZyZla+kroauCU+Edy8bVJK4+nVZRTrLzqgIh1RudvixHVkz44gSWgm7V9AjZFVZ9M/lojrsDszOoEqFD2+40tUz5FuHxaYdbG312fx8xUscGg9bIlor2N1nQGgJmB2k3jcRT8RkI9l+5AQm0R3dWoAlXj0hy2Ok3HPc5Wj/4j5xfv/trxx96ogJ1WZdV3WUs0Va6fFIHV73vDbAqAcGpFjHiOqfcEm+XnqJZWBzTAZyZkvKTfz/C/Zodn0LWD285P3ipRmAb0MP9KF5tmztU6JIQr1YXyfasTjSkjkR3m41AFzsgorxSQe/CLMB8l2+D0CjXvwSkF2hibpYjytn7NV/oOadoE/wLXj03IEkPE4moPyxh41VAH7gnkDlJGRS11CyFrCH8FH9gApBKASVJTIsmCTmHTVWW9NcMi2FaCC0CkIyebjmGh+uoNOQoSLIlnSnp4v21e1BPh0UGOtpoP6OO8GC3Y1urR+2K21v8/7dvyxInE4dl2kGetc9ZBfewc7EAXZRTdKY628X4kHD6Jn5COeUIP7IdlyBqaaELFG", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "The President", 
		"option_b": "The Supreme Court", 
		"option_c": "The Parliament of India", 
		"option_d": "The Prime Minister", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070104", 
		"question": "24C2bJThkQ7i9pFgURfgxujyJn/RDWEUsD+AU600ZHnmFLTBYf37iZh3Z1OZiEl65n/JreX/8RMpmqZf6IOafjYCcstdwdeBw/e3xnQBIcNXjpJ7544aeLRXxDShcZTWIex6x2+MZ0nxcHm0FzB9mnHQhW5VrcOy+2e6WsN3wQc3l9g6t+8VSZyqg1Dpy71OPIbnrA==", 
		"answer": "25Gtepj91lnv75ElQBDzyb3+MmzCBnECqnCNEDUeDnQXRqY942U12/tzaQY=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHg0hb68sUvVF791fjtNH/ZDGxRrHnDdLZ6dHDuUanWb+G++552L0iazVh6/DbEpuXi8kAbnaFY/YubMDULd4dqiN2IxfD+xX0BP8dT2olhpJMRPPJP3j6oNN3VYP9g1y6BNUDxJyyzAHVm1CXBhTxVoZG44CqoQNs5wxAhzLt20cYYKcWW16/T6Q2IlAmB0HqcSaltHlrZusjozk6ZsoU9u86U8TbO8bTtlbjvsvsTdg1AsYdzI3q7kLoM6zkxXsaIKkgLxOrUZEatATq3Lg0R/Iuwgy0pyYRpSWExtDZIhopXbIBQ2Zb3qDskKtljGj3241NIwpo8XlemZrK73Gnp4UE2enRraowtmSAwswiZJldn2mKPDCVf1IVt+NUagURnaGoAiHmghyefhXeBfZ+j6of7l+3js7Bs/O9nPUmFdWzKU54VYbbOMyd6y/rbGa5Zc55yAyrpL9w65XntL9adzCoY1ZkhITfo5i6cgI3hMWSu84HsncRzGrsTdsXN7IuyvlrIcyDkLHidcov7X0jkR3m49RtrsxkozS8E6W6YOoB4/Tke3nmlSFZlnDPlaXjhg7BY75DOXpwl2vbg2HJCyLR5kZ+39Q8oTge3iD8R48rfe1RG3hTFC94XwQc9BbsPVJfd/mKBhjbWRG5Nfo76CKWO1ylMmvH0nXVvtpMaXIOAbBbVysouzVe+EfhrVHPkp4i5MvpVHmwp6bcx2OSmv96oNfexPmwkaFqjUeoZ45BDYQ1/UQTbRTBHZfirW5gMRuVB0WyEqwl0SUhBAFSM9qkaSQ2rpoTEb32eaqJcChvhb7IXFsqiDm7BdeWhzXDMELqSgQexWQQoTyiJKLEBpQvxbczwIRq9lCht9NHqIVRfBIoZfCb9bSu4t6aCR0YcaiIhKYdCdFPUR1AWnTnLM+onjqYOMBooAbqiCkQEnxJbmjqSAUoFo1kNT6CjRFYjar5MNFMYw3ehGaELHB3YgztEznud0DblKPYLPUg0O22Az02giJtyiv79i4GPSsPqKK8ekoAKJL9PRYjPX1oJjvvr/ej0GGkqRnl2Jf2IXe3fpF35Doj7pIPZzEpCxf4JMlIyKzCYnY3Y5DNiIeVGYTBL/WEcq8PdbErq2IZdlVR9Qlzi8gH3VGQp9gV6Y5b4Jp3fI42s/BBNHyPPQ6oDmfJ8nSDtN9rDcBM6FCM4kB7QdNeKxCGRKa3yzKgNRQytl5TKTIR57UF3jtCz1AxBpT81gG7mDmSUIMr8JO/AW6tqzJYna0JtGx8=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "During national emergency", 
		"option_b": "During state emergency", 
		"option_c": "During external aggression", 
		"option_d": "During armed rebellion", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070105", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7T1+n2NmfVQzND7z+UWqp3eDHmWrPLeuT72tdwNVnJjlR14X/Cprf18xMfjrpPqYGZMDYLe8so+8SIw+GwhHdOIYZQkoUy9I8NbPtTyS7te9KbEP982i6pDmyvJeFgAPjJlxnY1a0btsWr3n0=", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNH811n+/4BgUxz90/i9nRQLEAOvQrYd8yxhqAOnaw==", 
		"explanation": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7T1+n2NmfVQzND43CFErd8dTHKWqPLb+O+6ph/NEiAmU5v+3nI7+Xk/1ZPm61J5M7YQzYCao4oiNaGxaTjzHQBI9NWio9h4Ylfc/IA/Dy/YJTyCdcuhkiVKUHxajyzEHF41APfjXRCu8r7/Cm4WM8zxQZygo99rc4zMNuQzqGd7w29iBKLyHKUW+dYH2iXgcatq2STtocqu8CIvyab+/K5s/bX+d9HIh9atoV3I0m5ka0b62osXoigYBcL9PzVYkH5KT6ma04R/MzqxXho0os/WCV09RFCwolDZslw35no/DAiPsNpHTap40tGh4B0WleVcbOswmnooFIwY385a4dosjl7nQGgJmB2nyu7QzpUho5m+94N1QtlPXtImTbTlj6fhXbDPITr4oP0xfr1prxx4eMzJgGUPVmYU5UZZqbULnF3hqmXCKFVIJNmAyvwOJlu/Tf9YJyB2zAO2dgsb3X19SSamsjmeWq884bxi5RlAL4UM5HC5t2yolLKZC31Mj2Eb9/8UAawZnL82g8rixYZxg0f62PUSIhq4SUCjHekQEF3yGfUZHWy1rdS6Y6be4sik/j50zsTkeR5k5Lj3RgvBwW1iT9Ts4qcR11WzEDFXoULywovAPQSEZrXv2qZg3PCRXEIcdq2A6eDyilbk6Pmh3V1tp5OQYSLbA3emMwv3BijGL12UyfEpoLwPLIpBFgi1aZ5z//htt+vffy2JXEjagntGc5L55xSZAc7QFmdBChcb/ivWpERVvMP1HrY1whcT3pbRV/C76EcVAG55oTBYCrfZ7UVGhftbfMRHI7sRkKPNPOm3jWFRquT1UW7H0cqQCmUJbUf4AOwe5+yNBKhhyhr/4HxOlQbA7ADPTP2Myuwo+OXAwMjPyEgLZ4HeULHXxEtmn7ANfBziLUJcVg/RKSmDVUS1gVA3z3dAExXv0BeXbztVFsiaq5KNl4DwzqwH7RfXRLOxi4CixaSwzb5O/8LPk9jb2yWhl6gnYdonOvgjYCSRJTWJbhb24MAJKNITZXYX1Qa2uDx7OmgFGItD3l+K+uIXePf8E3zQtvhoMnfxkgL3bFIOlo8JDXLgJHN9Sh9PaBbbmRDsn1ZrcTWIgWryo0Z2VF/Ev+K3OOxYzHFddBuhJ8tU9s=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Government of India only", 
		"option_b": "Municipalities and panchayats only", 
		"option_c": "Government of the States only", 
		"option_d": "All of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070106", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7mzfi/Bn7AEWccpj+gXbZmZD2jQ6/LbeW+zJllLkiAiEg7/3ff46T85FxPialX5c6KfiYGbMt7wNXJ0+HxzX9IJ89LlMB94tpYT+BB2DjqNMHVJPt8jk+SM0zzazz9VSIr1ikEGoL/dBvwy1aNCbFumTE=", 
		"answer": "25m3a5D/kRj/440vQBfmzPjsd86vKlNc+je8AvzLUZSKujI=", 
		"explanation": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7mzfi/Bn7AEWccpj+gXbZmZDHsUufrYOn3yNsxLlLJjF9/+2LPrKuw41xPm6BeqYuRZCsXd458iNWRx+j+x3hVP98El4V88JMQcvFEjDSjNPXJNPdtwmvAdhewaD/9EHhx1BjYjnVXpsOY+imoQNMj1QE7mYk4pcFyOZnTmbyb7Q2fiRCHznWcTbNwUVuf9eem70qd7MIsvcjNlj3N8eb3l/3d5J4EZEhGt4M/UE+9g60atGo5X8z0ZB1I8OiQYEH5KCexLhoU/NiqmjRm0oosTykx+gtPlopTcYB+14GkvT4jMI1sFD+241FOw5FuHwOecf281W7t7lwrfHUlJYVr/GoGtQ6ILRM+j2WYST4RtZJ/99MVkEQyLy9Jmjb0ijqSwGiKeYej6IXuken5rvlg4KozLFOJNBKYYoUZJbDSLnN32OCaTadONt9oETbjM5U8+TX4NJOQny0CkM0oKjfj8S2Ll8i1NmP6sJ33msZ5GP8FLtTX6sKktViHYzqhNXWWJsz7Tw3iQXH93RoluA4g2mEE4GfLDcl6+zkEine1WgRlnCOgeHSk1rBd/peces4+1bX41TcZirR+ipX0wBQzSRf1zUxMv4HfSkROwETaG95Hyw9uCboVHYLY937WgX7RXzwZd8u2Mr2X0SlF36PSgXRvq9AGVJ/OLxbVmdcizQW0Bb14RifrqYr1NPISSnEi/rdjivmpsoq/cPWtImw+ZhW5GeBfs9JifANvFEydECpLZarud48KSOND1zWbxUdBSXxFEF7JoZQGYQqZvsXce37RcahcLBHmarYWSY7bS1XbNPiniCPdB6uJgUisRgQnQT6UJKNN6hWwe5nmLByhmnxt/NKlJllaUMMHOTX1e3m05aSMHQMocSEgJp5GdgfTXh4ngDfMKeonjKkEMBk/ROi0EFcYnxdGnD/cGlRc8E8RUbG/T18rL60FL0lRyz67EK4cWRiKhCNKml6ZgiXjP/9ZP0QmdXDTgk3525Bj3+v7h4+VD9CiLK5blb4XKaJeA9rQEElcjvvhr/H1A3w2FWhkbvfOHsTEvkv3D836tsLWhW5CzrYcJRF7ETGOyZvc9yhoKuVAaTBJsn0NvsXeIgek3che2kZtQlvh8E/wAW4voB5/eJbmb9PIapK2sFEfHSHeF79Cm+h3z2ztO5/CcRk3R2cwhQKCe9vExiCKMqLojpEHORaF2I/OV4Rg6UZtjv+9zlxBpTJwnCaiLHnMZ/Xj5RtaNjx7RLmPG1NUgwRiwTKwyhPpL4rqj6MImLlNwfUQ7gLjsC56g1uID0XcI3z90POa92Tf/lMpzOpkU3CmSX1gywIwBPEl9jlvUihhWaRmurnnIbjKmSGpO5K72YUC60UUUq/LO/26r9C8ILDWKqv40IGPI2uh9px/AeehKNsLNHfBJDQR5LD1dpHWaEmePXLE07eLHWuMIGBY4Xd9k2aLRh1obWGgC45uCjdGlcU2NrcVodykkVhxdWnMH/E5i+81lWdXJV5KXu70lXRDDPluMJqVd0wt8FBcHecQKl6jaF5zPZxy02b0cDK/+SyxhvpNC8L5gVRxKRjazyGEfTXI4Opgai6qW8vA0deWEEWnruApVVhV5uhGmgWZRn8QZHd94xnRmKFoV0+JfB4hO/AGxtBVTcz5tREHmc80RgwUbTnZDz/5GJTLRNAHE9eh3LYprpkKyjQCE55Od57CRBnDh3yAFmJXeAJAfwSKmBW26pBrgMzAHB6B+22zh9qkHVacqHFcn8jiHo4TzxMrZp+FjdLrBu0gnvToGC0PVYAT4zEAl20fEWeXBlMtwPnhZGnFaAqs51ki2YPuyJFwhOHZxz2hOjFjWfMVCdIuw9pWype+8rASM8t+NBhERRYXuSFCMM9TmPbuXxE0L+6a+X3+ANAe3ZhiGvSv15IRHr9XnK6W", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Local authorities", 
		"option_b": "Non-statutory authorities", 
		"option_c": "Union government", 
		"option_d": "Private bodies working as instruments of the Stat", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070107", 
		"question": "25SqfJjw3RyqptZgXRiy0fX6dUjfDXEFqmuWRqp7fjHnUaTOb//72tdlL12dzVd65WWGqqvz+F0chrtP7ICLMDUKaoMv7sWH0+X6wX9VMsoEqIl17I4MPOdIzTGhNNbeYMFR8VG/GAfSxZJxbvG3YdHL3V6AyRqm", 
		"answer": "26O3YZWxirEyIwKdaCx/mQT5hWMJwg==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqptZgVhvxyfztMHiQF2oQtz+PU7RnMHjtV6jMfeTt3ZJ/MxyehE9zsnnU46z+t1cKnadc6JqWfyxDcY0vyd6Ql8LiynVAPsNKjoF+pKgWe/xU332+fNXXLL5syy6WKEz0JdLQhyoWCa0HYPdaNjCBaj4=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "vo,id,nu,ll", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070108", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7T1+n2NmfVQzNC7z+UWqp3eDHiQbPKYf/33Y4xLk/JiFZr/WHDsaD0t0cAz6xe6oKeYidDf8tjycfJwur0y39SJ89Qj5R765QecLRBwjntfdrNIfJnyjHCSRTh6ue4sM9CT+zSPOnDxA==", 
		"answer": "25+tbJjw2Bjmt4Q1Rhb91/TrLCn/NoRlsq4M1Y+WTEtXEgcQ", 
		"explanation": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7T1+n2NmfVQzNC43CFErd8dTHKWqPLb+O+6ph/NEiAmU5v+3nI7+Xk/1ZPjr1P4YGNeTYaPo5i2N+e0vbywDFVPIZAn4N+5YgaPPUAwDy6NMHVI/Fg3XqJM1DkbjazBXw0lT/SynVYvoK3/CP7Xcl31B031rs65904NdSW2KTT6VisjgmQ1W+IBIEmUUORvM2gq0qSo44tscie8SbT8bTzj/za89cKcBEe/5VvZli1kaEK+SY0SIigYBcLwvHAc1HgJWiAKBsP7Yvi2HAp7osuVSkX+wpUlpAWa84z/5bgtTN+f/liECC/40dP0oZoTFeedau9kHzs5RUvem0ud8pium0/tAuVK11/liuOSTpYkZcr/94d1Qdicy9EmXXsgy2OwGSBZdPv6pewxf/4pa1r97FnLE+BNkjdUs0efPPUL2IyyeyVGbRdP99gGDTjL9sj+TftYJmGnyoZ0c0lb3Do4i+LnMDwN3H285PqzsJ5HbtAP9eF4N/3uU+HZyz0L3nTcsS0Ww2wRnL73AB2vgsxzS8EqHXRHIE/+j9Nl3DwX01rnib0ZXOv1rFaqpaGes4Xxvvo3D8VluB5k9vF3Ro0Uxf7impCoIWRW1lKyRTUB40TzAxuL7sPB4LY5niCnHneBT58FeLcVLKvVFf15FAGbqAq", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "President", 
		"option_b": "Prime Minister", 
		"option_c": "Governor", 
		"option_d": "Judicial authority", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070109", 
		"question": "25y2KIX71Fnp+Is0VwbmhfL5dUrCF2sSr3rDA/A4MGbrXaTKLujw3Z5lLlmazV16/nqGtqv08kFPm6BeqYqadisNd59mx97J2OK3g0JVMtJB3d8wQQmeAjTda7dkst1NPfeCDQ==", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNH811n+/4BgUxz90/i9nRQLEAOvQrYd8yxhqAOnaw==", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIX71Fnp+Is0VwbmhfL5dUrCF2sSr3rDA/A0f3ejQK/HLsTwzZ5wKRyqglVo5n/StrH5+F1Dz7xT7M6LdTAOPsxc3NGd0qO3zHBSc8cEiZB355MZdfcAwTiset3VJ75vwGrALkvzayy5AWM0gDnTynpZpI+04i61U5oyzgE7go59/pIAMuuR7aCWqGq3kAOQ0naURqkkHlLZnMCs4kLQ4JUwvM6F8TfV9/v0ivnA49sYIhxausZ6e16/grwA7i90EcSxbxtY/eXEaELobGiiKQpd897n33dgx45pX3s1+hxOh5AWbcYzwpDh/DE1Mdl4FD/6pEtWwoZyUhKYYPOE3lTq1F06NV0kc49/siAwrxvcJ1I+jmOZDB9FlZRu7ZxZggxqfmcAlXjjjiqPhXbPaJvmq4XkgOvltLB19+9nJUSHPE/UV5kVc7aMZ2Z8zqmRGKJVMJZmG2LkL9Qg/zH8M9ab2XkZ2NxgPGPm4C/ZlcLjPHe0vpf3msc2A7YUPtjLqeK5tFXGLx/vHXO/acj1VUjxWmjw3BxsoxEg221Q+3fbAMl+5m0Ai3C5Sk10kyvpeHWkhf5d5IbOb48/0P3txDMEi7Qwk5T01RF8VAG3izJEvZKaXVJCyFrCXs8IwAArH/1BA5/F+mSY1WLYTjwZetzkCLyI0TUI1eWxp295tpFAaYKyIi3Tj80jiBK/FfRtXGL+5Mb4LrwRD2Il9Ld1iuSv9+upYfqnIGBqPkj3VukZ551UKCF0HxjJDDBadLGhWNFeQPJKknbFmRRBQ3pbAF6MvJscXBCv7YTOYXied7kZTg73caMKAMvrDkjJddC73DnKCrrcxBT+XkohDi6VJPAI6wH/aI/3KRa9hyhr/4HDJ19fRY4SMjPyeCuLrKSLHxV0PwUjaItJYwfaTVAwnDvQIrlig7MJZBEoUuiiF1EVggIPnn7eD08FpEQfS+WkUxMuJKpKLkgY3iOwH7RfSxXejnoFnBaVzGL6IPVHMF0qdGrTgEqgvYdom/7kh4CVC9iiH7Qc2pkQZPZSUNrVHlVcmPak6+TjHW0rA2k3OPfBWqLTqQ/iCs20qNbezF9CyKwRdkszNzaejpeZ5DJob7VdYHNPrmBZo8ySaBOu0ItQ1FwoQlD6/ETzDyVz4S5hpGUF2uW2gVFEFDGJ", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Government of India only", 
		"option_b": "Municipalities and panchayats only", 
		"option_c": "Statutory authorities only", 
		"option_d": "All of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070110", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MUBQAr7xvH6dTqDQ2sfoHOWVqY0eX+jXbPRLun7z55/LkiAglU7/XCGt631t0cKnaUbroKeZ2VcPCPiu+siRin/HoyCJNHn1hE=", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNH811n+/4BgUxz90/i9nRQLEAOvQrYd8yxhqAOnaw==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqptZgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+wJlyK0mNiEg78zbEsarx8xMLiq5S54eLeS0NPoRpiMSB0qTjwWNMc4FIm5c8o9o2aLRFwj6iecTaM+1r3S6OKFGwaDexHTB4lSbFymxXu5C+8We5TZojyBBymoJ/5NswPcOKy63ToE+3kg7C336fXK9lHRSYu8ro+FedtId4uciKuCHX9eDsiP3AuZ4JdxwSvopsbBuzg6AM6mo+Xtq5e1JE96TcZFPsLGiqKR0J697u03p91cIoU2109RxSi4xYcY4z4pDh/DY1OcRkHCezrEoAyJI8GBuXY/r42WakwUcrfHknYMo87208rwyQPVB7iTGgQhBfu5Jv994YmwdmbjUAsHf3kX+bkmqCaZ/k6pT5gajyufl3+qZnGVOFJlXcU4MIJbzGZ058zuCaTalOc4tvEmLBMsMr7jf2MoXU0D9Nw80hO3L0tD2Rl8O1LW2/84D8ncRzF6sJINSF5c6wuU/LYDfoN3jTZMTwUA3jD33q1k5ruAxlwS9Q+2fLG4Bw+2MxkEK+elBlhjL0Y2641pFO7oecbM4w3fGs7zcXjfh5i5L42g5mByW1lD9QpoWLWkhA302WEd8DwRs9QPQDDZrQ5X7a1WTFR3keM475E+iVxitd1uLlh25zrNADVIiLbBvCyt9mzxinBO93WGLjvMb4KOgdBXYl7qsxxf/htcW/bLOxImEvfVqjUeoZ8oBFYA1pGB/ERStJILnuWpwJAfBOwWbPk0dKXj9dDV+M960PVBemq9DdfG+QX78gAD33cKcKHo73XAf6JvCuzWqJJ7GF1USrTFAqQ3qSM/AY9gb3f8z6JQW6nW8k7cngcldUVoASfCj1NGe4su2/BTo0VTkhL4dCdFPGCxEqkH7nIvp1iKITKlgHVKyuGlkXmlFLmj3bHVFKvl9eXqupAFkyLq5IJVUF3nehGaELHB3Yg3oPgFCT0CHpKPhHNAkiaCSfjluup5xakcv7h4+VA9HxbbwV1s0iL6ReQZfTEU8PwLPQ/eThBWU8FS12IPyIX+XDtUr7B8bgsYPNzEhDibgHJFoyIjfLipDM/i5/JqBcL2RCvGdZpMvEZ0ao3I1XlVVwVVb54UTgAWU49gV7a9PbeNjPI5+g/kQfGSKHfrdHkf024SLYO/7ffVoeBHc8ngnQXtPczjqEfYD+x6wFRT2k0ZzIUdAtzUZgjtOmy0lS6zp2m3XtBTbVcKfp7R1dMXV3RfSXG0tUiBBiwTK0nlXnL4yvx6kPzrxAz/lT6AL0rjRyhlCLD0vKbnrk1+WKpWfSt1EkiaVxWGOxSDNswAhkQPUo+2pnTyMyB+P+1K/m5tA/Q73uC4uJb/1o", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Ordinances", 
		"option_b": "Statutory Orders and Regulations", 
		"option_c": "Judgments and Decrees", 
		"option_d": "All of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070111", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7mzfi/Bn7AEWccpj+gXbZmZDbwFLXXYuTwztd4KRydhV472XPVorPx+VIBi6kby4aeYiMXd8tsycOMm6TgzHRPc8VFlMBzpLkQcudUxSm4YN3ULv9ijm+NIkv0ajyzEDB2kXHVgn1apIa18iK/C5iDTA6s46BDicFUvMJVmsBV", 
		"answer": "24KwbZ+z2A2q4YwvXh/mwO6/NCvWFmwVonKGXLd1fDHxXaDKeq34xoV8LlKOzUt64GKGrKOw41sKz+9Z6J2Wc2IQapl6y8ScxeGwhs9a82mnYrMZ2pVlW6FLFGw=", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIX71Fnm9oskXx/gzr3UMHjRFWMfonGHU+NWeHDxVbPLLu7/2pIxbw3Q2ggyvjbSq6CwxEYfna1W7M68fzcRastgzpCg2eD+xTFTJspBnsBm7JsLPONIxTGoNMDTJb5ez3yMLkT9YjepRHh1h3HCgnkWuIys8DX7QNV3wRg3mIM4+cA5fPSQ17uH4Vmtkg+N0jfRXLVhA1HZvN3o6gOg4oA5psSO8SHP5uH6ju3B9eJJIgdU/5J3ZhufmKYa7CMsRNy9ZxwL5ezRdRTuISatKBpd+86j13h9w5AsWSk75l9Ch5BCcM9q05ykqDoiMNhtHXO7rkFOw5l5UQOFOv2M2G2k41oqZ25rbY9huG0hqQ6IaFU+uWSSXzhYgJV/998XlAgjfGJFknLthzGfwGaOctPh7sD/jen8rLxt9aYjaUiGdVXMFpsVar/BM2JhiuaJTbVZNpR0VzbpfdQi6DzrYIKc1ipN7JsiLmTu92qKht/gOnGvoZe3spZKGoMOAtnAqff1sl3UaCChMmmBc8jgTBr1cz641wFmowosxiRcqGPLSIxs4SwPknejQUFg0i7uLGipn60c6YOdesJx3vDt0yFQjPx5i9v00Q8oRg21zXlWvICeQllB2VXaXssCxR07HrESVJnXsnmekDbzRHIea8fiFLyOzCIEmvT5h2J1/5kAVoCbKBybjtsrxxSjAP5gGSf5oIO5L+kZDyQj/PJ9y/rt99m+duaoLXcjfBf7Gelc95BDaQ5yAgaRRTdKcLm8V4kXTu4P3XOKhwhfQm1aSRrN9axISQyv6tTaYX7bYKUVARCibLVFNdv2SkbCMP+9yTyJNLabnVOtEwQkXD/dI7UU6gn0Opj6IVOynm1q/cjrNRFLS5QSLmf8ciutrabDOwcocyUkJY9JbgmVah491B3MKepzhLMVZBEiT6mrWVEbkx9LkjvcGhhRuE0KH7OkT18mPqxWYFQDjTOwArQNUwXZxi4Ci0WZgiDtOvNIcU8menCGnUnz25Fnkb/rh86CAtXuIbgV1YgHaL9VBJnZCkkI2vL3r+PlGGI+Rnh5LffGTfbYpFriC8f6o8+Uh+/0dqJxCm5+Y56V3QRO+9U=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Only when it contradicts existing laws", 
		"option_b": "Only when it violates Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"option_c": "Only when it amends Article 13", 
		"option_d": "When it violates a fundamental right forming part of the 'basic structure'", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070112", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EYj0KFILsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8H1fWNP34kCikoBV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LwCXPPNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyYFs1cJfOAZycyiqnbTeYcc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbUn3lNkJlgbzentGrZ0o21eSX689K5zpQ2VP9AdpGFqYv38ByHIWOhYT3TJou0GUiwDzy4k04l91hliGFQqCKYSMk/tW1N3j7wCQQk0megLDzh1v4cqsLOP85xk7WsnXJQ2LQ439u3lF18B0T7zT8D8sTfbk9cyEbCF8IJnkluLaYVHZXd9y3HxjbAWXMbdsrzEuiTyykI3uzymnN0sZVOWorOJgzfg90vyRvxE/hvXGL65Mb4MfAaHW0i/fJlwujhhN+rZ/apKSUJYA+lTa9Y/ZERYAt8GUveCjFddKvuQpJeReVM3nTYkkdJB3NIEhrZ9asHUxe+o9DdemPRbbAQThfkI7oRU9jxQUvOIfS6iBbcCLudmEKwS0UpDgiUJrgZ9kewOsyyZFPz0ygkuYGlchEbBMNXfGezNCv55ePDS0Z6P2xlaMoHOgeVC1Bk1H6DZ7knzedAMFhtAejnWRBW1lEP336SThgF8AxeH+XtABNnaukFYBtRjXf1UeBfHFyKxnpKzhbcgmKsaboLcQljOyTTzwyg29Im37+pws7BSpSibf1bks1DaPYbBNqWXxtc2rOkr6GgUSx5Ri03briIHqKR8A+2Qoi04oOahRwLif5Idh97ZXnLyd+ZsHotb+UPLzAK/TNZ7IqSIkbqmbpc1ENnXg+stWD2VW4iuhQzP8Crb9DMJYyg4kMfAizCF4lCivBx3CHhO8uRcBV/Bm4wnwPQecCK1TGTOK33gKEIEgvi3pfISoR+5Vtty9Kmg1tJvzM1qWnsD3fXZ+n56RIUEHV/Q6CMWO9uTcqR+5FMVc0WFFFGRuE=", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmz8Ar58pc0WxH8hfzxMSviBmMCrHHDU7FxMHLsRrXHbfmyiZVkMxy7iFpo/XiGqraw+Vwbz7xT7M6cfzARe4h7iNWRx+j2ynBVOslK2oZ99to+b+dF3imke9qZ+Da8IXJN99VKhnbh5MeVfQ==", 
		"explanation": "25Sre5ThxRDl+cUpQV7xyu/tMGjEQ2AUoH6WQaY0UWP3XaTOa62vmtd+IRydhV4723jCqqT+t3AAgbtP4JqKZCsMcMt/2t+f3uDy1zFVO8MEno9x8IgWcvEAwzvtfsHfKf1nz2LANUDmbjyqSDBjnDjVgjxXpI+04jT7QNIygCYnhpV94M18H9iKy7zT6UO8xg6L23PRS7JxA0CK9dqnq0eZo445p8jNsHLX9eO5j/bQ/9AYdgFGqpJ2bFW9m+gA/moxRYiiYR1H8PDVchTLNSanJgMY99/i2jRbz4UhSXp6tCtOi5AWa9Mz3ZbrqzxwPt4qATu/41RP0JFuHxiQNLet1GHn6VQzNWguc4Noq2MJrzOSGlF/iWSSDCVC1IFn7d9Zlgtxb2pDiDbihzyKlXaKPLLx/4n/ie2w8eoroepnJkfAIVTdFqQSYbrBKSdRxeeIGa9IJotuGCymLsEv6DzqYIKc3i1N4NgyI37m+S+Xho32OGv6sp/8gNA2G61AJNTV7Mq78F3JeGPtIGrTcsP1TUj5XDzx3Q1quQss2zUV5naYH4Br/W0ri3C0SElhnDPhYDyTn7lU/pHAP6Y+xPD62CBc2OBwloi30BI5VES1gmsDv4GeQRxbxVXCXv8CxRohAvQIB9bF+mjWlnnCWXkOa47zGbiLwiJJzur+gCF7sIJOdJ+dKQvPg9Eohiu/PfNNXWKtq4nrL/kWHiQp4qJ9y+Ogo8O0e7OiI3dqTgmkXP1N+ppfKAtoUR/VBDAPQaq6X54SRKAegTXahQheTntMFhrY861ITQu9r9aIYWyeaaQYBx3rYr9FAcvuR0LYdeWmiCTBA/+vgFesWkkgDhmSNKIZpQb+fsz6LRS702tr7NPxIR0bU4sePy+zeW64q7DDHw47a2wxII9eOkTURVAgkT3PJutizaZAfBk6Ab2pGl8YhQVGiyvGB1dLsUBeVqPtSUdnPKBKLFoFyCT1N7URWB3HgzQej1rc8CvrIe5YfwkTenafhk3tnpxy3/zojM6AB9HsKf0UwM0RLaZeRZaWHhsQm+Sk++nhBSwwFS1zK/vEX/DUtA/jDMv7rNDOzEhe3bcHOF43ZTuSyYvR9XpeOrVdan1P/VAWudjGIgm4mYBQ0lgoU1r551X3DScjowUzZ4eradzSJJSxsF1eHSGHVvlPmes4ySTlIZ/Yd1o2CWA6nxSZZcbPySDDKqXvyO0vEBam1pTOS55s4AhLx9u6118AojU1m3TnS3DTcPT5qA5YI399CYN+PWWt/o0w3avnaYhYsGk=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both Assertion and Reason are correct, but Reason is not the correct explanation for Assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070113", 
		"question": "24C2bJThkTj444wjXhuylKmzdX/YBiISrHGAV7NgMH7lFODHf/j/xZ5lPhyLiF104HOGr6TnsBMGgrhX4IuMMDYLf58tBnSzk7Xv89DI/e1tBeYX1A==", 
		"answer": "25S0ZNH63x3j4YwkRx/+1r3+J26QF3AUomuGVuNxYWTiWKvbLu/niYN5IhyFjEw5cF4Y1JoBuAUjVXP2oyfePw==", 
		"explanation": "24C2bJThkTj444wjXhuylKm/Om2QF2oU41aNVqp1fjHAW6nReuTq3IN4KFLFzU9z9zbFrKvz8kMbz6ddqcmaYTcCcoJ70ZCL0uL41nQBP8dT3cB76YoTdfFTjCmldcCBHPBSwE+MKwX5aT20EnlwgTDamTAWv4u+4S++Rpo0yQE7jIJ2/ogzLpeR1qbe60SsjxyH0mjdCLx2FBScpNup5wOVrsIsvcjNtCve57T2nLjH+NtLbglF8bpxTVT8h60b6yU2Edu8aR5HsebVIVDkMyuxLgMU98r303Apx4UoVGcn4F9JjMNCasUz1Jn3tSFwMMsqBza2qkNJyJowHwWXd7j0kGvl80E6OTo4YJIh/D05oAyZaFt42mmVXjhZ2MBk7JAYmx0jcmkAiH7lkTrLhmSMaJzx+M7Ai9z4pflQ5qIzLAGTPV3UWs0SaqeAI2J806mPAuZdPYYnByf0LtogvDzoNZeY1i0UkNslKXj18WqNmsi1NWSt853rztFnAb4MdsHX5t+ys0jObi2hLnvTcsPxGQTxWG+4xAdxvxEriDUY7SLMDZtt/DkCjGfwRkIkuynkZX3vqrB15MKLbJ003fbpkXIxiuBxnJfylExoBwG1nmpRt5ffW1RO2RTCFshHyAg5TKATEZfF4S2XmXqQQnIJdtj/Bb2Gzz8I3/Lkj21xptAPW4jOPAvUgtckwQOiQflwRmT/oYvwM/0BA2siurBoivmpsoqIYfKwKStqRg7wSq9Ys5NEZgZ6HA7TESVDIKi8X5MdSPBD1zXFkUdCUmxdDFnJu6kGWUSsq83aYG/NcPEVAF72a7ZFH8v/T0uPJui63DXESv+Zm1SrTU0rSXqJKbEZpQLmf57rZAO2gXtr942lIFRcRZETMCLgZyu2o+OXAwMzbWwnKYlMfVXaXh4g1DHRZ/pvjLUBcwwoU6G0DVkVhV0Plz/BTl1UpU0SH6SuQ1Y0OelRLxsFxTL1HaUYXRCKlSMZmlORgiPiLbpbI0Y3fmeHhkPu251g3+vhh4eTSsbrKrUPwcNBUREu/pL/dj8qwYmCNTmGfA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "All individuals are treated equally by the law", 
		"option_b": "Some individuals may be treated differently based on their circumstances", 
		"option_c": "The government has the authority to discriminate as needed", 
		"option_d": "Fundamental Rights apply only to citizens", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070114", 
		"question": "24GwbdHw3hfp8pU0EhH0hbr6JH7RDyIBsXCXV6BgeX7tFKjELuH/3oQ2Z0mHiV5pslfUt6zz+1ZP3vwb4ICcfDcHe5gtYs5dqHYlLnuN1VAl38kaQQ==", 
		"answer": "24GqbZDn2Bftt4wuVhfkzPnqNGfDQ2YYpXmGQKZ6ZH36FKXDfej6iZh/Z0iBiFJpsnXPsabl+kAbjqZY7J3d8U+CDRbOk5zUqFc3WMRWBQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3hfp8pU0EhH0hbr6JH7RDyIBsXCXV6BgeX7tFKjELuH/3oQ2Z0mHiV5pslfUt6zz+1ZP3vwb5ojfZCoGPqJhzNmI2aTUy39SJ89Qj5R765RfePtF332je8CbLftvwC6UL0TkJzixCDB9mjXfnHVSvYK35me2QckjgBc31pNq6MkoOdPf0KbT7VW5hRKOxTuFQLgkAlWUsI6/6lrcqYx4tMGB8THS5vfsl+vH8dAIZxsc/69xcE+5lqxFuCMsEcG5eB5C9PeQdVzsNGiqKQoU78Lnw3Vl1cI+VWZ09Q1DwopYItN625HovSBwPMR4Fia3sFBByZd5TFeZZv25wm2k8FQtYTokY8p5tCh1sg6RLRR9lmqPX2xCnI9+8tRZlwEjaX1FnWLlhn+OkXCOcJ/6q4Llxfz4pflv87RpaWmPIlnOU59QJbrUZ2Z+2ebbH6NfPJhpHjjjLpU69DjtYJKd2T8IwtwuOzfu+i6QhMTxLGS2oNL2nJR1GL4TJdTWqcSx8FXJZSr3KHmGZ8fnGQXxVjzw0hhg9xwszicV+mfWHMlx8CgJjT6/WwRnmzXjeXGygr9S6YedP5o50uGsyjMCivV2i9vz3Q4oTgq4mT9XoIGeW1FKw0CWC8MDwRtuGLwEVJrQ5SPWoX7ZWDwdbcf4AqGXzykI2+/9gXZu/5YBR8ycKRjIhdAnyhu0Qf51VHT+oYDwPv0BA2si6fJwxOnhs8O9c/a2KWs+ZhujUOBXs5xfKBZzFEvcFTRDabuvQpQRT6BA1DXGlhBbCz9IFhrA9KYPHQW56tfdbWKeZ7gaCBvwZr0RGs/sR0jBdfi6iDLIFbqY1UiwH1YkWjOSL7EBpQb+fsz9Jhm2kHxt78SlMUNSUIYFNSazdWW95aqQSwg1a2wkOohOblXUWQlkmyyDI/B0jrUJfREjQLyoC0lYqh9zkRfcTl1Wo0kQXKDhABQiO7xELBsB3zihFKMLVRPExjUMzlqd1TGrafdOMEcwO3Cbjligj5pj3/Polc6SAtv3Iblb3IIXaLJSV5nEFlYVlPLw6qH3GHgxCXhjbvmISOPduUu2EM31sczUhV1Fzf4bPlAuKT3LnY3c8S4tJqtLZmZDuWYYoNmSZAejy4RAlVFmVBXp5FTtVWYjuggzbJL4b9mcJZXl5FhaHzaHRKlGm/V+1C+kJtbFcRsrDmw7gkeReNaKyTGGOb+1gIQdRRyt0oqLS4V5rEV4wNiz10kAvjV8iXPwBn/Oe6fk5l5AMHl5X7maFEkdhAI2lSiwylvtL8+shq8bgLVSy/US7wi3rC54wl+eTUPacXL4x7aasmXPrU4ux+duXW2qVXQtzBVkUPgusn5hVigzR6xxsqK3RRjTkfR6wt4MmS5Uls7WDA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Treating all individuals exactly the same way", 
		"option_b": "Treating individuals differently based on their circumstances", 
		"option_c": "Discriminating based on caste or religion", 
		"option_d": "Exempting certain groups from legal provisions", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070115", 
		"question": "25SqfJjw3RyqptBgQgz9zfT9PH/DQ2YYsHyRW659fnD3XajMLuLwiYN5IhyOn1Ru/HLV46r2tbmXYS10zeqGi3Q6RoBkV1I=", 
		"answer": "25a5e4X2kRjk88UyVxL7wvTwOykyOytpzmHR52MCEg2LpRQP", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqptBgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+2YV+L1WLhE9osnLPsKbi/l4GgalP4IGRMC0NPp9nzZCOxeviynVSc8lC2o598NoQcvhZjD6sZ8DeYP9gyi6SIkn5YDCyCjB2gSWWi3BFp8Op9CS+GJokxQ1+1oZ26YgsMNac3Oic7g26jxSW1DXRdLNYH32N9cum+FaOpZF4ocWMpXLP/PG5iezS5NtLcQBTs4o/bVSo16wA6ykqWMW9ZhNf9KTRZlXkLju3Zw8T4Ivg32Bg3IcnHWY6tAtOh5BTItNj05vtujszf8p4Gia0p1cA0Jx5UVefYP2732Xh8xUrejoqZolorz51tQDcOEF8lmKfDDxdlYNu7ZxZkAlzcWBZkXPulnPLgWuLPIfr7sDplu2wr78j4rYlJUiDdU7dRYIJd7DFNCky9uenA5JUNt9gGCPqfdw9vC32YIaG0DQCxNxgKmby9SaQhtS1OGu+84Lri8JzGqtAMtjW6tm+vVXJYDfoLnPTZMrnXAywQHK4xwZgpB1lziAT/G3KG8c9hpp6nKiY7gGRdv/PQNmnQA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Place of residence", 
		"option_b": "Caste and religion", 
		"option_c": "Occupation", 
		"option_d": "Marital status", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070116", 
		"question": "25Cga5TjxRDl+ZZgRhGy0fX6dWzVDWcDonPDQLZ4dTHsUufMYeOzzZ5iJE6AgFJ182LPrKuw4l0LirobyJyLeSEPe8s+nZCA2ef70XVEcUvot1kwVGqxuCm4aqmaoEg=", 
		"answer": "24e9e5Thxxj+/oouEhj91736NmTeDG8YoH6PXro0Z3TiX6LQLv77yoN4KFKaz08Ch3rMw+zFTdkeBSaFeLE=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqptBgUxL+yursdX/YBiICt36XV+NgfzHuVazHLv7uzJR4JlDJnUl05H/Vqqr+5BMJgLob/oGSdSxDf4VriNOB3ujz1nRPf4ZFlo9849oIdeBIjDK5fNHJYO1hzWeBK0npJzizADBxkCTVi2hfp426+SuiFNg2wx4ll5V8rcswPcSM3LvT50v4hQ+W1WGURq4qLVqlu8Gm7gOTpsIsvcjNtCrY8eTtk/fd454fbUhGt4M/ZF6ykroI9GoqRMSxKB1NserfbxnpKTugNQcQ8MXiwn1myMI8U20x5l9nkJdfYcx2lsmx/D02f9liEHOTrUBJxpo8fBiYZ6mxxH3w6VoxNXMlZoZ4uCgm4R2ZO1FsjGqIRSNf1IZk7JAclgttcmJJn3fsjibLl2COd5bxq5P5hvz5r7dwsqwhaVWIMBzLWY4VYKfZaSdT2P2SDqpZc84yX3SvfcIv73nwLoWRzS0I1JkpIWPotD6Rl43WNmupp5vtm8B/G7FAIt6F6Me7v0uHZyzzYW6GZcO0Sw3jSm7u0hpsuBY2hmEs5l7WIZ0/8CMMnHK1WgRwmiKgf2iggrsc/o3Ob5w+xfzo2HIDiPF7lpr7lA0uSBKynnZMvJffSVNdjUDeG40GwB8vArcEGZPf5i2ZkzbVSHMDcMP/AqmLzzUIzebwhWRv/4MLVpiHIxfIytEgiBS4FfRjUGn+5MbwL+4QGXQp+aZ43OjhuMz7YfuhJXdqbBukTeoZ/IcRaw56AhiRRTNGdLCnWN0KSeUP1XDEkhVJSz9KBE7J/KcaRErqnszBfSrbe7IZHgrrbL1FEsL0QVDcdfem2nDIALmVh0q/S00zS3qcIqQE6gmwboOyMQO/mm5wucTmPV9USYoUPSv/bSu9rLCCDxA7cTgkL49DOk7bTxkynTrWJvV0zagSMB8/Tr23ChABnhhDmn7fD1FLpE0XUayjRxMzIqwFMEkYwzS8AawaHBPMxjQFgBuYyzHvO/NGOEcib22cgQzvldJpi/fskM6GGNv3I7kIkoEKI7MbR5vFC15Q2uHh4+jnGGM3Si1lL/vNEqLCtVe6Qsn6poPKyV1IzP4HMB85LCufgdGburyFd/lLf017OzdJepJgrQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Reservation for economically weaker sections", 
		"option_b": "Reservation for Scheduled Castes", 
		"option_c": "Reservation for minorities", 
		"option_d": "Reservation for women", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070117", 
		"question": "25SqfJjw3RyqptNgVxDh0O/6JivVEncQr3aXS+N7djHsRLfNfPnrx55lPhyAgxt282LSprfjt1wJzVMCrnbTckAtmp75s/i1fn4=", 
		"answer": "25C1eJ38yBTv+ZFgXQyyxO3vOmLeF28UrWvBkClIBbi/KMPo4Av+yXXDsA==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqptNgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+zJliMk6Mnht+42PHr6zk7hMAiehU+Z6QYjYWcIJ70ZCA2aT6xWVVNtRX2o90pIoKfvhJz32oecTXL+djy2CUaQXZc3mtFn98nTPfnm8WrIqo9jWyWdM5wQE7mYk45MZ8LMKd1aGQqEi1lgqNxXaURqkkHlrZocatq0SOr5c2sd7NvjSb5vX6n7ST4tsHaw9bsIgzI1i9hLwMtGorVND4KBZO4ufVb0ChYDivJg0YucTllnZg1JYhESkm8QxPhoZYYcU/lpf2/DM+Jo1lE3Ouq0FNidRAUSuYXan4133l8lQxYX8udsporTg0rU+dK1d7iXjcWCMRk499+8IXmAFtaS9Kk3Tzwj6FhCWKcoD2+YXvxfz4oa0j87M3JkiOIVHdWJkPJafPZ3dnyOWSDuZMPIxuAyvpM8Zu/Sv8YJuV2zxN39dgO3/itCiYgcTmeWq885/8nN1iVL4OMpHU/Mq7uVrOYiL1KHKddYvmWBz4Sm64xwZkuVgjySIE53DLSIV2/ihNnX+jXUEo0jXlYHWmn7FSpsKBbc421vvo2CBe2MBwloi31Q8oTge3iD9ToIuSQEhK3hTQH8QVygw9H/QAGpKR93yDlHqQRGwdcNziFKaO1yVNyaP3gXM9vpwCFY+HOBDBj9A1iB6/Qfp2Q2L/pov8M+hVD2k89r1ox+ivo4T52Xz9VqjlgHjO1LVhamAy7Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Religion", 
		"option_b": "Employment or appointment", 
		"option_c": "Education", 
		"option_d": "Political representation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070118", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEh39y+7rPH/FF2serX6PEq51fnXiQKKCYeu+6IVlLl+FiBsqpSmE/I1sF2e7VfB82s1cuMfVOg==", 
		"answer": "24WqZ5n60xD+/oouEhH0hejxIWTFAGoQoXaPW7dtMn9+xLT+9DqEGd1AYjVPgFw=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3hf544w0Rwr7yvP+OSvdAmwVomuGEqxyMFDxQK7BYui+mMAxKFrJmVN+sl/Ip6zx+RMsgKZI/YeLZTYKcYUvwcPJw+u3xXNOP89XksBOpo8RaPtVzzWsdt3XKep38izAJkv0Jy2yRHZ7hjPfjjxfvJD75TW6V84+wxByn4k47MYlfNGQy6XdqHG2ugi30m+eXb5sEFaQuce88gOLoZF4tI2JtDfL+O25n/bH4tsFYQBXu8ZsbFi1lqRJ/TwxXYi9ZlJi/+DZYBitNyCmNQsf4Ivg02Z9x4snHWo7+RJTjIpCa8VglpnquHI5McljAzq+tkVM1NRrWgWTNK6t0mLh40E6cTo/asp+uTswswrcLF1tmXmVQSVflZRi8d5ZlApnPXxFm2TlhT6fiWqBPJHi+IX4xef+4K1r96o1aUKBJkjdGs0OYL3EInV7xO7bGa5ZPt9bVTfoKdo7/zH4IpqRzHdPYu4IlpDGr0We0tNxoWq7GA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Abolition of caste-based reservations", 
		"option_b": "Prohibition of untouchability", 
		"option_c": "Right to freedom of religion", 
		"option_d": "Right to education", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070119", 
		"question": "25SqfJjw3Ryqpt1gXRiy0fX6dUjfDXEFqmuWRqp7fjHzRqjKZ+/33YQxM1SMzUhv82LD46Pi+F5PjKdV74uNYisNecmrKb3O9IuNUceaI52Ii2wk", 
		"answer": "24GxfJ32wlnl+Yk5EhH8hf72IWLKBmwC4SOQeBQNoEtCcd2BVQtGkw8=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3Ryqpt1gXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+2YV+L1WLhE9osmLOpuXj41Ibiuhd+4GSMCEMcI1q2sKA2eO30HhVP8NX2o90pJQQfv1MxSm0OpTyNL592m+UIlawczG8EDB6m3HVg2hfsoa1tSi9FPM5xBwz1oR544g9P9SaybzT6UOhxhKLyHeUCLt2HlnZtMCxq0WTsocxssPNoiba4PG12vnd9J4FbUhCupRsbFX8n6cF/CM2Voi1ZgsL/uLWaFfoYCelZx4P9s3qwjRm1MI9T3wn4F9TjIdTcIBn3p2kryYxK8gqFjK040VDxJFsS1eXeqT4xGHw7FB/emhrbYVjsz91px2TJRR/lHLcSiNDkYls8JAKgQV3eC9XlWLojSqfwHGHedPg5I7vgObk4LZlsrcvLAGwJ1nLX4kZa6eAKGEy4+efBKcSD5FbGRHpcZUP7i3wI5qRn2hVkMkyIH/u9iONgY3hMWD6oIb4mtE2Eq0PO5HG5sWxtU7VaC3mYWmacsfxSkj/STz23AxsuxEx0W1Q6WzcSIBrtSwBjXHwWUhlkSLzLG6khapO44GadoE/wLXj03I5lvBxnpW31xQoTh6+g2wDoIGYTk5LxFrRXswExww+GL0PE9bF+3makGWQSnIJP8b5D6eV0GxOyOz8zmdyrZUHUoLOPw3ants1hlWQZGHQxVTN7NG/Ycl8c8Aj", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Titles only on foreigners", 
		"option_b": "Titles only on citizens", 
		"option_c": "Titles on citizens and foreigners", 
		"option_d": "Titles on individuals from scheduled castes", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070120", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTrl+ZY0Wwrn0fTwO2rcQ0McpnGHX6Z6ZDHqWrPQYenrypJ1Z06Mnl5p5HfSqqr+t1UAneh0/YaaYmIhf4hk39Gb06TUyHBSIMNX2shdxrkMNbRJwn2qe8LeMvBjy2CUZ0//ZSriRl1wCSP8ajgl26Vpu8U0bXo=", 
		"answer": "2+zrepWxyOe/qjumPg4WFmSTCtGePg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rwr7yvP+OSvxDmcfp3KGXLc0ZHniQOfLYPnsxpNkJFmNzUl+4XPUtaTk/lwBz65U+86wZCoGbMtNydOCwOXlwDFiP8dXiYVhpNIwXtdThX2kepTcL+hr3GCNIkvkJzOyBmM0nSKWnnRT6Nro5yP7ddcyzhE/k4lsrdwzfMOX3Oi65kmxhwjC/3SfW6ltBUGNvMGmpwOLqIs7vY2asCGb8fr4mezW9J4CbEgA79YqLRuAmZQHzCIxQoi1ZRdF9enVb0CtISSvKBkY/Yvl2WYp0oosHXkm+wlPkYpZbIB80Nj2uSE1LdtrATq1rVcAzpo8WhODd7ys2Wfq4Vl/fHQ4cYN5qTk8rgGPaFVwniubQzpUho5m+94N1Q5sf3wAmnnywhCpo3bDPJLt78D1kajxrKpssqopPVOPMUnbU4lcZPPOInAyyeWaGLVZf99GBTbvPtkrvGisaMPdk3kZ35klIXbl+C/ZhsXweXausob8zsB5VLIBPdSF+tuys1XGbWPxM3KFb9j9VgbjD3r3wU5xvx1lySUG6WzbDYR6+zlNkXjwSEp90jTvb3WgmrJFqoOAe8401+Dv3CYZl/p5k5fulB89RA+sjG1H8oeTTk9cgRTfEM4L0Q0nArNBO7Ty4SPUFCfw4iEU4PWvi+wciNltfw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "23rd", 
		"option_b": "27th", 
		"option_c": "42nd", 
		"option_d": "93rd", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070121", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTrl+ZY0Wwrn0fTwO2rcQ0McpnGHX6Z6ZDHiUKPHaq3qwZIxN06Gm1Jo+3nI46P/5RMdirte+5ieZCsMcMtpx8LJ8uf4yn5MOsVFloxrpK0aff9F3n2ecdfPKfFg3S7IAnLDdHD9DX40kz7Aj25YpYa14WexW9gkn1eqvqjVNFaHXNh0i+7Gch5S", 
		"answer": "2+ToO4P3k035r4sZL968vx74Ze/ju0s=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hf544w0Rwr7yvP+OSvxDmcfp3KGXLc0ZHniQOfDaun7zddlL1nJnUl05H/Vqqr+t1UAnehJ7J2aYjQCaoJgxpCP2Pa34XJOPclJk4Nz6JYGPMNFzTaoZpToJf16x2GONAW4Qg6OFzk0nT+WjXNArZG1+CK1QJo9zxch1o5rrdw0OZfOifuB7A2ZiwOM2HaURqkkBVvZocatq2qSpIs5u42uvjzI4P3tj+za/9BHIh9atoV3I0y9hOgM9is7Rc2wKBtFsbaAMA2jYBStGwAp8cLwlnVkw4wtUGw64F9PjJdEbcRm1Z3g/BMiK8RpGTb68hEIkd08XhmSNJyqxGHn7FB/JCxjM8Mh/Do9qAyUaFVylmSLSSgRko95vsQRkERxeHxFjmDhljaEjiWAetPw7oHolqj2r6sj96AoJ06NPF/ZWoEFJaTFJmx32KmICKVIOpBpBGLvM5Ur+Cz6IYKd0DcM3JkpIWTz/T6MhsT6N3b6spz9zt14VLgPINTX58ayvkiHayzjMjPRTjMK11NCEa9uLUJS+1yPfQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "73rd", 
		"option_b": "86th", 
		"option_c": "103rd", 
		"option_d": "122nd", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070122", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7mzfi/Bn7AEWccpj+gXbZmZDbwFLXXYuTwztsxI1PJo1pv+3nIoqmw1kQOnaxIqYKWeydDXINu2tGdl9b20H9Ac9BNlYxz8J9fXeZUxT6hcZSKeKEsCxvKvp8fIGNq5thLOOYMrA==", 
		"answer": "25u3JNHn2Rzzt4EvEhD90b3pPGTcAnYU416RRqp3fHSjBf+AMhYDw5LrUAdp7q11NHuRkA==", 
		"explanation": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7mzfi/Bn7AEWccpj+gXbZmZDHsUufrYOn3yNBiZ06cgVJ19TbPreXk/1ZPjKlI7M6QdmIhf4duwtnJ5eXwzHBXMsgEjM4y0ZQWc/oAwzvtXdrfKf8uhj/ZfhO5K3mTBWR9mz/Xhjx3v4Kp8TT7WNM8xVUmnoI4z8A9LtaLmZqS/EO5xgKNnHWeXP1yGFuVtNqtq2KOtIs7ucjN4Gqb+/K5jvDWsPcFZgFTscZcbFWvg6Ed7T4xXsb6VBx3/8XCdV3uLC3jdlZd9s2jwnxshqEmU3og/QtTlopZbIBjxJfstTA5K94qATu/41dUxoB5HxGEe7D402fq5lAtZ3MlYsp5tTk5pBzcJ1I+lGSeRSBYgJkr8cJZnQttcn0O3F/uwiuDhSWtfZ/i4Ym8t+n3qLh1861nKkCTMBCYQoUZJYDVN3V3x+zbLqlJIYsnHyfqOZU69DjtYLiVyzAC3tgsb1bw9TidgY3mLGay85PqzsB+Ef8iPtDX6N/3gl3TbyKhIHOXJt/8XEjATnj10k5EoBk3zDJQ6XDdSIdw4W0Zl2q8TFcknSGgYnOjn7JV/pvOcJxx2/ri0iBepPpEkdve2g4oQgW/wT9XuoGGD11dyBTXCcwVwBpuDboFVJLU8WKElGLZRHIeP9r+ALzH0SlL1eT/h3t4/5UWVomeOBDUhN8qiAS0E+twVmKtp5S5PP8dA2E6/790xPmy98iiNfqqKGw8Zh6iWONKs5xfKBR6AwLSEDcPZrGrWpkND6B72nDZkkdJUH5bAUmM/6dIUwu+6sfHYGzbcfEdAAeia7YXFsrxWkbdLLG52jnfD7OZkkKtH0s3DimNJLME5AuwaZjzMAag02dqudXtNxFJQYAeLC72en+q6eOCBQJ6ayQgMcpGaEKVRR8w1DvSMvBxjKsFfgxtVafnDUIXkhhbljHcD1QFpEUKU6C+AFwhaqdKIlIdxCOsX+IAxJInJ4csJxGFLlwm99/X", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Yes, they violate Article 18", 
		"option_b": "No, they do not violate Article 18", 
		"option_c": "They violate Article 17", 
		"option_d": "They violate Article 16", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070123", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhPzzPO/MWLDF2sfoGuKXa00cnT3Q6LHYK25zIZkJlCAmUI78HPArLf1t18OmO8b6ICbMGUGb55uxJCZxevjwXJVOslK2o90pJYea+cHk38q16w4x+v9Wv99vjd6HDA/", 
		"answer": "24axZZj/0Auq45clUwr/wPPrdX3DQ0MTsHqNUaY0f3ejRLXLeOTyzJB0NB4aC3uYpFkCjM1anPSUnVJT", 
		"explanation": "25CpfZD/2A3zt4clVBHgwL3zNHzsQSICqniNW6V9dWKjQK/Deq3/xZsxLlKNhE1y9mPHr7aw9kEKz61K/I+TfDtDbZ5twtWKw6TjyzFVO8MElZJ27ZQebu0AwDy6Z5TUJr56xmvAK0T+Y3X9AX1knDDFg2ZfpoT74S+6QJo5z1U9mII45Nt8PdWQz63T/EW9xgqDyzuQRrkkBVyYoY6i/lCIqYE99cSe8TPf+f33k+vH9cwOZkhbspZ+cU+1lqQF4WQEX/S6VFBu4PHRbRT9Mie3Ig0J8MTtlntvho4oSnoItl9Pj5Naa8VglozsvSZwNsNuHCWzp1FBy4c8VhnWZ7S12WTl8hUsfG4+ZJ5ksyMm4QCOaEN3jmPcXyVcnYxq7JAanQVxfGxUmWTpkSuCg3bPb5vs/oz4xer14K1x96IzLEXAME3NV4EQfPPVKWN32KmPBaMcP55wWWLPKZUp8zzqYJSRxjYD1JktKmXitCaclcz5eWCrppP1h8BvVL4OMpHI6MWzsUjCcmP1KXyHJt/8XEj3QGr9wQBoshYxiCAe7CLRHJo//CMeinekXFBtnSnzLGyzmahV7ofOep8k0vmsySAVmeB1mpXjlBwyQ0Srn3pVt4qLD1hG3lfEF8AOygg6BbsPVJTQ4WiS1XneC38Ibdr3CKbHwCRJyOLymmRvtoMaXI+dYlu2iJohjJwAhBda6CSHz5hv", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Absence of privileges vs Arbitrary treatment", 
		"option_b": "Similar treatment vs Arbitrary treatment", 
		"option_c": "Equal treatment vs Equal privileges", 
		"option_d": "Similar treatment vs Absence of privileges", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070124", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQn4+JMpQRf9y73+OWffFHFRt3eGErBgcWXmFLPNLuD/wpIxN06Gm1Jo+3nIsOX2+EFPm6BeqZyaYycRaIp7wd+Hl+vxhHBRI8lNlJR/4ZQLb7RP3n29e8fPM75nwC6GJlP/dXmyAjB1miiWj39Zpoy2/CS6WNYugAI3l4x9/4gvOdSL0Ked+w23gEaB1W+YUrhqAgvbcyJjPJyP5zZf8U4wXeqYLQ==", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqptNoBFewqy3/qfAuxPL0jGHZpdvRaQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjwxb8/pYpXRCy0fX+ISvRD24etGzDRqtxMGL3VbPHLvnxiZpwLFnJnUl05H/Vqqr+5BMJgLob/YaaMDAGbY593tGd3uv5hH5Hc8dUio976o4SefpU332iZpTLL+163S6JKQX2Zi+yFjB7knHXhGUWrYC0+yi2Xdk2zBkr1pB97MM5LpeM3KuH4UK2lUaN2juSQaltC1GXpo6h+AO9spYxtsGI8WONvKKw2vfVsMoDZ0h7sYJ2YlX8tKcH6z4xRd2gYR1Fv6Tsb2jjFCCqNE4N68T132dgyYxpSmgntBZIlpFZZtVw05ykvitwK8VvVWLq8FZEh7VxWhmSebi2xCjF40FzNSh7NNMh/Cw7pU+VPBR7lGqeQClC1JRj+5AKgQV3eC9UkzbwkDCdiWGKPIHm+IXuk+nkqbZt4eMhJlPAMF/XWIIRbLDBK2triv6eDK1ZId90EiHyNNog73mxBaGnlnkE3pknIGHi5iSUl8PheW+1sYG3zENb04Xeyub0brO1Up0oReo=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Article 16(1)", 
		"option_b": "Article 16(2)", 
		"option_c": "Article 16(3)", 
		"option_d": "Article 16(6)", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070125", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MUBQAr7xvH6dTqJQ20X42uLV+NXf3/wQK7We/n3xpkxIEmIn1p15nPD/Odpkf2LfXHMOdcaNTWPgk3O", 
		"answer": "24exb5nnkQ3lt4MyVxv2yvC/Om2QEHIUpnyLEqJ6dDHmTLfQa/7twJh/ZS5ouOGxDKRdpU3+e7+sHng=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqptxgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+zoJwNV2HmV5+4TbVqr2w8UYBi6lW7ICLcS5DeJlqzdSG2ve30H4BMM9Qk5p36olTPP1OzzG4cN3VJ75o3GuFI0r9Jza7RGNkkTTVgjAWqZCo8Cq5WMN7gBQhhYh75MkoNdiRleie51u9iwOMyDfRWrh3GFCcu82tpwOdroZ4ocWI8SDS8/zt2uzcsM4ZYwtGtoV6I1qyjugZ6iU+VNunYR1FsevCIVvuIz2zJhoU9sWtlkhn+owdVWwn8V9AkIZTZs9+xdjnvTxwPcgqBzapt1ZJxIB5W1efev2s2G2k6VsrcGgudp4tsyt1tw6OIVtriSuaTS9Fm5J4vtwQngEjc25UlXnugzPLk2CMaYHq/5m8hOb04Kl28K8uKgGPJ1jdRMNeB7e0WRFawMM6R0ydnkygxg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Right to freedom of speech and expression", 
		"option_b": "Right to property", 
		"option_c": "Right to education", 
		"option_d": "Right to religion", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070126", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQvj8I00Eh/+yfLoJivTCnYYuXqNQeNgfzHrW6vGLv3ry5t4JByEiF5v+3jBsOXx+VdPi61W5oCMZDACaoJgxsPWldv1dxKLmxVhU4K4K8Shl8U=", 
		"answer": "24exb5nnkQ3lt4QzQRv/x/H6dXvVAmEUon2PS+N1fnWjQ67WZuLr3ddwNVGaz4RVucMH/hwEpPY6pLq29ug=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHh2B7i48U0Wh/mhfzzOWTHECISqmuKSKZ6YzH3W+fKYeH6iYdkJVCAjht293PSqqv35BMOgawb7YuSfywQaplu3NmG2fe3zWIBJ85B2rwwwogaefBPwX25e5T6M+1rw2yMIgXAYji+AXZhmD3Ptj4WqZD78jK6Rts51BA3ksdt48w5Lpe+y7ya60G9xlfblCrYAL8tUVuf9dqg7gO1roYxtMPNkj3V5+Dwju3H+dEFLEhusbpxV1O1hOgP7SQ8UMWxZgZK/aTCaFPlNGimKQ8f9c7wlndg0oszWGcntAtJwoRXdsh2xNSkvSEjOsBoGTb240VOw9R4WhqZeq6swmnw5RUvcHsoYIx4sCEs7U+MOltok2+ZSGxCgYNjvtcYgQxmb2ZOm2Wggy2OwGuAct714o/wgObk4Lht9uMjJgGOOkiYUoQPd6bQMydi3+uXBKUcPI1jEjCof4GzckljuDx2jwPxRHWfth4=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Right to religion", 
		"option_b": "Right to education", 
		"option_c": "Right to privacy", 
		"option_d": "Right to assemble peaceably and without arms", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070127", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQE3cDs3CQV+N7djHzRqLUa+PqwIF0Z1iMmV515n/JrfqySTafRp1pdehHZUajM1ekfA==", 
		"answer": "24WqbYf23w3j+YJgU17iwO/sOmWQBXAerj+AXa55eWX3XanFLuzwiZh3IVmHjl47+3iGt631t10Kjrob75uLZTAGPO5HmH2xTLMChgBt9yAupdE=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjwxDn9pc5Eg7n1+3wJm6QDGRRs22GRKZ6ZHj1UefGa/n7x4N4KFLJhEg75nmGs7f14VYBm+haqZ6aYjEMcMtp2t+El+H5w3BGOshD2ol8pJscaP1WxSmkccebNPZv2i6BNUCwZDazF3lwkSPTjjxeqZG28zK3FM44gAE6k8dr6MspLt6LwOTT+Fi6ig+BnHSDTLh2XRSWp46l6kqStIc2tMOOtHLU8rTtkv2T48oKdg0c/69rI1Kv170a/S54Rcf0bBdf8O3eIV3jJCG1LgoI+Mfwln1vhpYhWHsxtBZVwoIWcMVyxZfqvTA8Oo1oED+zpkIAyIY8XgeGZriw1Wb36VoxNW4jZJ4tqCUwuE+RKU0+mWSRQSVF1INu7MQYnAojcmlGmXjzhyzLiWvPaJvmq4bpkf3ipfcjzq0bJ3GSMErdWJkVc7aAI2Jmz+ePBKlSc5Z0Vy3gKdAgvDz0MJqbxjwJkM0vb3bj8Dicgd61KmC5poDwms02F7AONdTX59j78EzVZDXkL2nTadnzWAb5VXn8kw13vhUghGEd6WvWHIh2+20di3y8QEcknTXkaW7t1rFOqpKccJo00OGsyToV2P12i57wxhQoXkS0iz9XuoHfXEhO2VGYXvEJ+AcHGPQIB9bF632flnfcR2VNfM/kE6GCx2xHz/exmWhpt58bQcyPbB/UmNMnxFelE/R4WSfspoK5NO9VGXEu8Ldy3q21uIq4cOGwLWwkLxayXu5Vs4ZQbgd8BArPATcPdLfuRo8bV+VBxjXDgxQISnZaEEnJu6kGWUSvpNfdfG+ed7kdGl72a7ZFF8vsT07BMPXp2DXbFbCS0lT+TU0iRi6OYbEf4EfgaIPmIRCnlmwqu+OIxaewv8QVItkoCyHaPcI=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Allowing unlimited detention without trial", 
		"option_b": "Punishing a person for past offences", 
		"option_c": "Preventing a person from committing an offence in the near future", 
		"option_d": "None of the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070128", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRjn8oskXxv80b37MGfVF2cV42uLV+NmeXbrQOfWYa3/yoZkLk6MwRtz/XrC7+Xx+VdPi6FI+YGMdWIMeMt/2t+Z0vbj3TFHIclJ2qFg8JMccPEAnWTyNsq4eRiByY21dZo68FgBkso=", 
		"answer": "2+HsfJmz8BTv+YEtVxDmhdz8ISvfBSJA+ijbEHZT5oUunNlSNcfh4H2ul8Y=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHh2B7i48U0XV7zxuzqPHnVTyIZrHOHHuN1fnWjUK7RfuLtzNd+IRyZn1Rr92TSuuXn9kBPi61X7JqadGIFbIRiiPGbw+30yHQBYp8ElYYy8JIaPN1OyDSsepT4L/B92meUMlH5aDf9Bmk0gDnTyigCvIv71Cq+Wt46xRsm1qZ7+YR8bY7IgebT3EWxlUaD0X6fTLBhH0DZp8ul5FWZpMIsvcjNozvc/OC5jveT4MwEcg1Aq58/Ykj8lugP7SQ8UMWxZgZK/aTCaFPlNGiiKQpd687g2nV61YsvVGwwtBZSwoJFIsEz2p3jvT5wLcRtHSf6tkpEwoY8fgWCfb601Si3sAUeOzoXa7ZjnT51oE+OLUdrln/QDDhZkcB599cRgUR3ci9Qjnnwhy2fmSWGb9Pt5MDwiub3pasj8+MhPE+ENFHdWJkdafPSLmB63qmSA+Z1PZtuFm6mPNk69DbsJ57U1i1Nw80pI3un8SSTndTmeWm/tJP1zsRkG6sFNcXM5sX58GjPaDChInWSaMzxGR/xXDz10gpg9wwqiDIE+mvTDcl+tS8Mkn++SkEkkCL0e3mkmP5V5IaHaYc1xvTgnSICl+R9jY/ulA81QAyvnj9CvIDfW1RKjVbEEcwDwRtuC7sAGNbe9C2FmnXZSnBNfsDyQa2EzCJH1+ryzmtorIQHVonAbvtxUDnVwMI6Qt/kJe4WcdQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "24th Amendment Act of 1971", 
		"option_b": "42nd Amendment Act of 1976", 
		"option_c": "86th Amendment Act of 2002", 
		"option_d": "44th Amendment Act of 1978", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070129", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsXaEWrdnMHjwFIntWq3uyIVlZ1OPzU9z9zbWsark8lAbhqdVqYmNcSwXe48v3d6N0va35WNVOsVIn8AgtsVdXitRgzKzoIQlnyPljqOV2w==", 
		"answer": "24exb5nnkQ3lt5clQgz31vjxIWrECm0f436EU6p6Y2WjUKLWa+PqwJh/ZSvSII1mAB0ESRjyq3ePg3k=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHh2B7i48U0Wh/mhfTsdUX/NyIBom2XEqxyMGXrUefSfOLqzJRlLlOHzVxp83jSpqGw4l0LirobyJyLeSEPe8s9mpCG0aTjzHQBGshAk4F8pLkQcudUxSm4YN3ULr5n3S6UL0CwW3uPDXd8gHHChTxErZOp8DS+Ws421Bw9mMd56sk1MsSLmayW/Ei2kg+N0jWtCoFqLVq4p9qh6E+Z4NBq9d2fuD/a5v31g7jD4tEdawxXrMZsYl25kL0I6i4rEdy7KBML4eHCclvjYD+rKE4V+Nij1HFsyMIoT3sx5wtDhsNXbMQz0p3wvTs+OskmVTq0oEhVw51yWFeCfLj4wmHj6EF/YXVrZ48ttSMzrh2RLVA+lW3cWCRU1Id58cUXkRcjcmkAnWTyhyyfzCWbdJaj+Yn7jfywtLYj8awpOlSMIRzZFoEZYrLMZ3dgy+qPBLJVPJFiBW6mPNsqvC3xJdaG1j4FxJk0IDfv9Sick961Omqoo4fqwJRCHLpAJNjC4d/3pFOHcybxM3iAY8XgWBz5QHK40glkvhY23GEU7XbdBp12+iNNl23wR0tw0iL4fG6kha1Q88KDeoAl2vri2DZQkfo4vonj3R4wQkTp3zEDjoqjQXRA2lHAG99LhAA6TL0SVJ/c4mGfkHKQTW4Cco7iCa3H0SVP0vexmm49vZVORZ6BKAzYj9pmyhK3Du98FWatpYf+NO8BGGU4//Jmw/mpvsT7J6fkJGo/fQn3VukZ8odDbRFvX0vqDSFBILnuRpgMUu9BknzZ1xdaSHtcBl/Iu6oNWwu4r4TJLmffZLgPGgzjd7ZJU9rwS16PPfC/zXDdDrrch065V1BlWjXdLLEG4EfxOp73NAG2gG1q7cDxO15VBIIQPS79Z3/5sauGAhR6eykxLYRTc0jbBVAQnDuDKvhghLQUYhk5ROiwEFwa1gVHmjCSCl1GuUgbH7KlRUcvL7sFL0lRwzihUbQQHA7Pij8LnVPc1irpaepOI1osdSScgQzimptq0b3XU+WkbgreLeSroLJbhhGN", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Right to be informed of grounds of arrest", 
		"option_b": "Right to consult a legal practitioner", 
		"option_c": "Right to habeas corpus", 
		"option_d": "Right to representation against detention", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070130", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRjn8oskXxv80b3+MW/VByIFq3rDQKpzeGWjQKiCa+nrypZlLlOHzV104DbFq6z880EKgeha7oubMDEKZst7x5CP2PHl0HREPYZdn4Fg98VdDNn/mllCjTN0sv3SujZYEQ==", 
		"answer": "2+3ufJmz8BTv+YEtVxDmhdz8ISvfBSJD8y/RECT54kNROk/Y9E5IYT3YtQ0=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHh2B7i48U0XV73wej8NH/ZDGxRpXCREqB8eX3nRqLMLuz5zJMxNFWRzU90snDJtrfk8lYBz7Fe6JyMMDUCbctuzNSM06TjyzFVO8MEs4527ZsRPNdPwi65fcDONPdhwC6CPgXkbzz9XCZgnHH3h3lYrI6++zP7ddkjjFVgxtcqo4gINN6Mmame7UO8iwOMyDuYRql2HlCMtsusq2KOtIs7ucjN42P6uLTukvHQ+J4MdwlAvohrZl6v17wB/WoqWM+8fFJf/qTWc1HoYCmtI04e9sbzw3h6yZAwHWww4RxHlopZbIBn2djlsD5wPMVjGTeopkoAzpo8Sx+TNK6o1Wvt5lw6cToqYo8tuz86tB/SaGhwpmW1WGxclYRuvtUdgAdiaWZPkjbhwjmejmGOcZbt/4Hwxfr5p7F3sqopaWiOMVXZGs0ZaKPIJnR70OCVCuZIO5onHi/2Msc6/Tf6Jdab2XkdwtY2JnPu+i3Zk872PHapupD1i5R3GrtAJ8TE5cKjqRzCZTbiIGmaacW0TQewSmr9wRcltBAsxCVeqiVjmdN5vbghc+Jw4vZ+Phc=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "99th Amendment Act of 2014", 
		"option_b": "76th Amendment Act of 1994", 
		"option_c": "93rd Amendment Act of 2005", 
		"option_d": "86th Amendment Act of 2002", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070131", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQvj8I00Ehr9wO6/FHnECmEdpj/RA+N7djH3XKKCTeLw2oN4M0mdhFR1smbUrLH19EdQze/oiCBWasq+udzpeKc3lCw=", 
		"answer": "24exb5nnkQ3lt4kpVBuyxPP7dXvVEXEerX6PEq99cnTxQL6AKlKVmYsoB/n+LIVJL8/Zjw==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpdRgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+2YV+M1mKmUg75n7D47f58Fsbz7xUqYKWdidDf4VriMCMxff4ynBNc8pNmIVg8INRPN1UjC65dcDeM756xm+UZ3mySTb9FHVmhz7Yym9eqY+3tSW+FN4y0Ac7gIJ8rcc6fN+Wyuif4Uu9xgmQnGuUWq5rH1WV9cKh6UaOtJt4sNWOtCLPtPX6mffB9NcFZUhGsMZvcVS/kqwc6i94VNugaRBH+PfYZFCtIjHjKw8Kt/ehlkhn+owdVWAntB5UlopVbsUz34ukvz0+LMRuECG/pwRPyZE8UBHWYLW9kGXr80F/c28lYYtguSMhoAPcKVp62m6PXylfgIlq8pALnANraXwAm2PhkD6FlGCKeNPh8sDoje2wibdn+6IpaWKPO0/MX5kJcbrPKSsyy+efTa9Ic5ppFC3rLdQ97zzqYICVzTACxcpgLmT38SmNgY3nPGm7p5f9zsB5VL4OdtjL7cKhuVjSYC+mMj2Bb8z8TUjkQDz02ghg9xkrzGEA7XDLB4d++W0LjHu1TUtp3GfcYkCvuahZ+MKad4txyvDtzyFc2OBwmtvEwQ0uQgm+zVxMp5aLD1NJjX3YGsQGhAEvH/QIGoLU4H2EkGLVTzwsbdr/AqSCg34ZmuHjgWB5s4lOQYPOJRfYhssizVe/Duk5WmnhscbtNflVGG0r8qYx3uLhu8O9cLOlImFqfx+lSuBX8pkRZAt5FBnJHGRNdazuV5ENTqBAxn3PhUdaQnNIEV/Iu7oBWgy+uYTbe2nWI7APTgrqZvMXGsnwWgfbOrGoiDTAAbGVk067WwQpRzyYbfAZ7QKwaIX1LAfzh2ck6dPsJFBYXc9XPSn3NH+xoOORAgEya2wxJ8pGOlfaRxwxgDfMKbRhn6IFMB0jV6G1Fl4bkx9b037TA1dLtwwRS62oUkBpaA9SqIQ10ijoqU42ztnRVoA=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Right to life and personal liberty", 
		"option_b": "Right to free speech", 
		"option_c": "Right to education", 
		"option_d": "Right to privacy", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070132", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV17B0O3tMGbVQ0Eetm2XFbA0dHTgXbTLYeO+25J2Jk6NhFV8smLOpuXi/lQHm+hP5s6MZDAKdY4v3d6N0va35WNVOsVIn8AjvcVdVwZDFd7tNg73hUeHTaS0LA==", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHh2B7i48U0XV7h0e/2Pm6QCnFRrXCXEqp6c332UKLGLuTwibZjM1WKgV47oy+ENDcFQpiOxkyne8wg7rIMzg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHAxAn48oglEj390O/rdWTWQ0sfp3aCEqt1YzHxUaTNaeP305J1Z0iBjE875n7D47f58Fsbz7xUqZ2LYisIe8tm25CH2PC3xX8BMsRXlYxn8J9feuFOyDygcdrPIfIu3GeHL1Gwcje5AWI0tSPCg39arcPqrGe0UpojyBByv4l85MkyfPSQ17uH4Vmtkg+N0jXRdLNYH2ORvMKtq2KOtIs7ucjN4Gub8+H4iPnd5NsOcUhRupRrYlKy164b/S88XsWnJFJC/+fcdFDkLi/jMwYYuc3x03FtyY9pUm905w9Dh4BeIsF90tjhpCIiOt55HDy040VOw9RoVxLWcq+91Wzr7RUrejoqdplosS85pE+MLVV9n2qeQDURlY5vvscQgQxsaHsAnWTtkXPLlG2KPIHq7Ijoxfz/4Kp34KosLAGBJhzZFosTd76AKGEy2vuUGaNPJ99oBWLnOtw6/S3wL5jU1ipN3tY0b3L/5CaQkcThNXz6vpf3mt15GroEdtDWqcr3tknJZSLsJHOHZ8e0SwH3R2i42gAloxAgiAIf5nHMAZ1q4SQCkDDy5aN44hq08Vbs79Eh+MLFSg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "The right to strike is protected under Article 18", 
		"option_b": "The right to strike is protected under Article 19", 
		"option_c": "The right to strike is not included in Article 19", 
		"option_d": "The right to strike can be limited by state governments", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070133", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRqmzDfIxAMHjtV6vXauj6iZ5/Z0iBiBt94HPDp6r95BMImqlJ6ICLdScHPp5hzNWbl8Xl0HhCP8MEy9ktppWU4xTxBy45tWe5RxyD8ro=", 
		"answer": "25OqbZT33hSq+INgRgzzwfi/NGXUQ2AEsHaNV7BnMuFrQAYmiGpbEp7c3xjvSbs=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH1wxzv84otEgr6xOm/PHiQLU0l43aNUa9hdHTnFK7MLvn2zNd3NVmMiVR24TbBtqTi9l0biq1fqZuRdCcRPqp93NmK2+G3lSgBPMAEjoh3pLMReP1Bwn2Oe9rINPd623qJKEuwbir9ODJShjTTjnNb6Iy9tTOpVd4ygBQ8ksd6+Ns1MtKMyuavqg2Pjg+O2TuwWqltElic9Z/xq0eTpZF4vMOOvSff8bTtkv2T9tEHbgdFtoh4I12ukq0N9ycrC/S6VBxt4+HVZVvgYCelZx0N/M7g3jRoyIZpWHEk5hpVkYpZbI5P2L72uTc0MMAqATz6oldTwpl+UxLWZLi5023l4lkmNXslYcp6tTk9rhqIaFVsl3jScCJ3hoVu+t8U1RBsPWlPjnuggyyYj2aGfYfq5I7vxefi4Kxt+6wpOg+8O3rKU4gYar6AM2gyx+aNCOZaIZpiGzumKd088yz+KJmBy3kk3t0pLjnb+gyLl8jxNmj6p525nNFlHbsFdtDL7YuktUjTbSahKHPTZ8XtGRjxXWi43AglnhYhwSBe1Gz+Gox68SIA3mq/CVR2kyT0ZX+k1r9S88KebYE31ub/1D0e1LR3nJjixBwoTgu1wT9XoIWbShAPwkaWHNgUzQcrH6dPKJjt/ESC0mWQQnEdcNziAKaTgzhHmu3+mmQ9q5gPQcyZJBDXj54H2gO4AvF8FTa06IHsPO4UBHAp/6Ex3uWkpM/7c+GhKWElYgn7GftR9owRaRB+URjIBy5KY6zuQpJeQuVdxnTDmUdaQn5aClTN+aQNHRavudDaZ2nKar4SHV7rbqMKAMv8DkXWdeWhzXDaEr6IkAe3UQQxRj/dKL4Z4BX1aZiyKxXzhWl28M7wIRFdRYADMzXgNHispqvDChV6bCMzLZhCc0DbXwlklTDHZ/BpmaIHYhE5WOioHxA/mBVGnnKSHk1HvEUdH6q/RFY1ZulELl9R2T+wUbMaXwnYjy4TzlmagjbkLLpYJUg3firRYjv9M2PUwhJ8heP7i2iK0w==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Freedom of movement", 
		"option_b": "Freedom of speech and expression", 
		"option_c": "Freedom of trade and business", 
		"option_d": "Freedom of occupation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070134", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ3z54BgXRiywfjrMGXECm0f43aQEqp6ZHTtUKLGLvnxiYdkKVWahRt6smbDsbb/+RMJgLob6M6PcTEXPoRpztWH1OG3xXdVNtQEjpJ75ZZfffpEjD6iesLSI+pnwWDfZchxpL23KdHjYysdey1Z/W4=", 
		"answer": "24WtZpjn2A/vt4ElRhv80fTwOylbNGH8oolgka98cWZg3qi2", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHnyAnvt4omEhr30fjxIWLfDSIYrWuGXKdxdDH3W+fSe+P32p8xJhyZiElo/XiGparit1JPn6lI/c6QdiQGcJhqiNGPw+HlhGVTOsdI2oF84Nocc/pWxT65fdvVYPd9jmWOKFL+JziuREw2hDTYi3AWrIav8CmvXdU5/FdymZU40YosKdmWzaGF7Q28gxKH0m+YR7MqLRbZicCU5XeUqZF4s8KfvHLU8rT9n+zW/soCbQYStpU/YFquhaEM/Go3RNz0aQEL8KTAYEb5YCelZxoV/IvgxH1kz4woUSk+4QxSi4BTItNqxYzhsXIxMckqHCD6ogRDyJpvWgaDcbO71Sjr5hU+NWoud5lism03pAaSLxR4lX6SSGxWgYln6slZmgIjfC9Djn/th3+fiHeAaZTrq4G8ie33obUj5rEuKE3OdWDWaoMobbaAN3Jg2uaICOZTNd93EiznMZUq+S38LoKd0DdN2cpgO3in/SeJnd7weWT6o4f3h8d+GboOIpHK54ujuFmHYizvN3SQcs7wGQH+S3Xu2gpwthRpiDYY4WHQSIR+7G0EkGi/RVJh0jTlfmqomLkc68KebYci3PuszjcejPF2nJ632w98RQGyg3gDoZGdRVlM2RTCEY0I0AErHvQHG4Tc4S2ZkzbcTnsMc47mFKaO0CRF3+3lzmBu/4MeUI+HKhDejp4k0Ve9AOo3F84w7y9W7yisGWqFd6FSD3g=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Preventive detention", 
		"option_b": "Compulsory detention", 
		"option_c": "Temporary detention", 
		"option_d": "Punitive detention", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070135", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R+fDYOm+2pJ9Il+dzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz6lV+pmaYmJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EYj0KFILsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8H1fWNP34kCikoBV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LwCXPPNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyYFs1cJfOAZycyiqnbTeYcc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbUn3lNkJlgbzentGrZ0o21eSX689K5zpQ2VP9AdpGFqYv38ByHIWOhYT3TJou0GUiwDzy4k04l91hliGFQqCKYSMk/tW1N3j7wCQQk0megLDzh1v4cqsLOP85xk7WsnXJQ2LQ439u3lF18B0T7zT8D8sTfbk9cyEbCF8IJnkkPHqAIF5rUsj/E1XnWC2gFeo7VDqaU1yVcz/f4gW89r4IBQ4WKKQqbmd8gzRCkAO99Rifrp5S5P/MBAiQ877x43uS3soq6e/fkPHcveR+5TeZP9tVVbRZ+Hx/UCioPXLaSWK8bQPNA3C+KpxVNUXpHEVPa/ugMWBCvpNDBYWSear8KARL0ZqBFF8vsT07BPP+uiDGJFrqOhkiwH1MsWjKSNKRN8RX5e4CyMBzzg3ph78TrJhFdUZcCLiKze22/oK2ADhV4JzNLRBDfihHjrxunpi4zhw==", 
		"answer": "25e3fJmzxRHvt4QzQRvg0fTwOyvRDWZRsXqCQax6MHDxUefWfPj7hddwKVjJmVN+smTDorb/+RMGnOhP4Yvfcy0RbI5s3JCMz/T7xX9AJ89LlMB94toLdPEAzS6+ccbPKfFgjO8rPV+nXo8G+gZITEyovIU=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHywgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/NmTCEWcStzHDc7FgeXLvUeeQPK3xz9dlL1nJpFV/+3fI44b/+UAbhrxO/YeQfmIKcI9qzdTJx/b40nhFNtUEiYF04Z0KfeZE332re8abIvF6xi6QMkv5czCrATA8lTfCj24WvJGy9Cv7VdQzgBY9mJFx7tw1M9nWmamd7A2olAOU2XWFQathURyOvNqg5FaI4JYqvMyB8SbUtOTrn+7W/spLZB1GqpR6I1S6ka0H6y8rGIiwbQZO//DZblqjHCafKToV/Ivx03V6yYxpVHp09RNVjcNVbdJh05vw8nIALch8ED2uqlJFh5B5SxKYYLS33ijt7kMweWwudsppuTk0qAGVJlM+myuMST5Cm44r6dkNnQt2aS9B3GLyiz6HzCWfbpru6pL1ifGwtLYj4rEiP0SOIRzMXogRJbXSKGoyz+ecDKFVPZgnHiymO8A66Sv8YJmS2TwDw9wzb3j1tCuahsTjMHGztoG5mtx3AP8BJNSF6sS5o1XDZDHkJT2bZ9n5Xx38D2j3kxptslg2zSIF+mvMEclw520di3y8QEcknTXkaW7v1O8N+m2zrJWCCfLF8Moro74=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both the assertion and reason are true, and the reason is the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_b": "Both the assertion and reason are true, but the reason is NOT the correct explanation of the assertion", 
		"option_c": "The assertion is true, but the reason is false", 
		"option_d": "The assertion is false, but the reason is true", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070136", 
		"question": "25SqfJjw3RyqpdRgVQvz1/zxIW7VECIFq3rDQrF7ZHTgQK7NYK3xz9dlL1nJn1J8+mKGt6qwyGwwsJdk1rHfcSwHPptq2sOG2eX7hH1IMcNWjpkwX4Ql+v7WVx8ApqqMWQuaOw==", 
		"answer": "25mxbpSxmj3xYqGdzenrjt1GAeXWBg==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpdRgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+zoJwNV2HmV5+4TbSq6Cw50EAm61Y/YeQfmIMeMt7wNXJxe3wzGUBJ8kEpsJ+7ZwaQLYAzTOpNMTeMu1hwG+MZ0n5ZTyvEGk61BjCym9CqZe+5mevXNsjgClwuIg4/c0uL9iRmbub6UG0xgSHnH+UWK9tB1Gd9cGuq0uVs8I0vMuI8T3JtOT8iOvc/t8HIgRbvYNtd0L8krAK/TosEcm3ax1Z9e3eZhT5L2izNQEe/M/2xHEpw5E9XGs4/QxOh4cWYNkz2pnz8g5yf/FkKT2Oq01Th5VuSx6VeLj42Xuk4RU5YHQvZIdosjk0rU+OIVN2jiuIRC1F1IVl7cULkBcjaWdF3GbyjSuOg3GGc52j5Ia8hOawqbdn+7UuLVSBORvLFp8VYrvUZ3N9iuWSC6McMpFjVzLjL8Yh8jj1YJCG2jwJ39Rsb2Ty9iCckdm1LWr6v5PuiMF6VK8SOdLA7d6ltU+JI+6vGSv73sFpoWP3Nm/TMj0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Li,fe,li,ne", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070137", 
		"question": "25SqfJjw3RyqpdZgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+2YV+L1WLhE9osmHOqqb4t1wJz7xT7M6Zfy4PcZxmxtfWlcZS4pJNWYm1S6xs6Iow5WI=", 
		"answer": "24GqaZf12Bqq/otgWgv/xPO/N27ZDWUC4STt1wcGqkGvyKzfMidFeX8=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpdZgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+2YV+L1WLhE9osmLOpuX2+F8DgL9S54nFTCw/cL99ydaP3ue3zX8BO9NJm44y5p8WcvNTln2ZfN3IYPNrz2CTZ1H4YnmtFnF3gDjVjzxZrsO54D6yWt13wRs21pR94cQ1MtDf0b2e6UP4hAOL0nyCCLx3UVeWuMOn70qIqYcr+Y2Ctybe+rTwlO7c/MgCbA8St5NyYlX8g7oI/iwxUsO9ZhUHseLfc1foJGivJgwS64ej2WYpwI07XmwwtA9UjZBCa9RmwpHrsnwMMfFkNza9olYah7Z5WBaENLSrkGmk5loteDokY8prsz82pAvcJ0Y+mWSRXDldh49555AVlAZsby9Jkjb3ijaIiCWGcpfq/Yn4kOn8s/li4KZnO0SRIFXKU4lccbyAMGhgwamMBLJUPIpzVzLnJNgr8i21YIKNzzAO0dUsNjfm52qY0sv6K2j6vJS5jdtzBrwJOd+F5tn3tUTXbSzoNXyHb8T6FzT+c3LZwRpstBQgiHNDqGvLSI165iQKkHu0CVBr0jfyaWqkmKoc64yKP54j3P3l3zsE2OBwmojylBgkVwi0hGtCpo2JShxOw1CWF8MP0QQvArFBBITQ8XmflnPDBzwdbcH7DryOzSsIzuv0zmV0uJ4HQZXOLRffytg0zRK1DvA5WmGtoYj9NOocDnEt9qE/iFTECcvkTXCmo+f1XdIxfI0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Right to privacy", 
		"option_b": "Freedom of speech", 
		"option_c": "Right to education", 
		"option_d": "Traffic in human beings", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070138", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq+oAhXAqyx+S/CSnWDHASpnvDXqJ2f2TxaOWCb/6+xJJ/M1WGg15/sn/I44Ti41oMg60bu93AMh5DpAVQBJJFjUFSlAZIIdU=", 
		"answer": "25a3ZYH23RXj+YJgRRHgzr3+MmrZDXEF42iKXq82r1GBLLPVvsUJ/P0/ty3q0Q==", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIX71Fnp+Is0VwbmhfL5dUrCF2sSr3rDAPA0f3ejQK/HLsTwzZ5wKRyqglVo5n/StrH5+F1Dz5QZ74GNcycHPoduyt+b66a31nRHNtRX2pR9pJtfb/1U2Ty5fdvVYPdgjnmILkb4JzizRHl6kDjAg3hDqY/7/DT7V9U60BA+moJ8rccufNSQ3LqQ7Un4kgnCy3SDQ/1lFlWQu928q1eUpYsq9dqEvT6VtMj3pvb65J4CbB5ds5B6cBuon61J7Tk9EceyKAJD6PfZYlXhYCexZx4O4Mjr2XhmwYsqXGV08hBUgYYaItR7xJ3lqCF8f8J4VTK0ugRP05x5TVeQe6+1kGfioFYwcGgobIVj/Dk64QKdI1E+myuMST5Cm44r6d8LnkR0dHtIk2P0wiuDhWydPJDs5ZP5i/y+4mr89ji2ADad5NHR2DNLbxk=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Voluntary work", 
		"option_b": "Compulsory education", 
		"option_c": "Compelling work against will", 
		"option_d": "Government employment", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070139", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTjp48UpQV73y/z8IW7UQ3Ye42+RXat9cnj3FK7PY+LsyJsxM06Ii11y8X3PraKw/l1PmKdW7IDfcSwHPohnwdyNxeH5iDFIPcVIj4R76p1fbOZP3ymkYMHPKfFgkSzbe/8fR7js7MwgIjUulel8", 
		"answer": "25y1ZZ7h0BWqw5chVBj7xr23BXnVFWcft3aMXOo0UXL3GOeTN7ioi4+pLT9ndMv+8jkMSd7rvHc=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHa3BTl5YQsEirgxPv5PGiQS1IDpmmGXLd9f3+qFIbBeqG+mM4kcRDJjlR2/3nIr7yw/F0AmKYb6J3fZCoGPqJb+PHFl+3khGVJNoZIn4d795YeaP1Pwn2oetXYNPtqjmeOZ2z+YzC8RGR71CHEhXRfqoqvtS62WdUlwRlygpV56841P9yW16/T4UP4kQmP2XXRSbNgUVeRvMKs+UaS7MIxu86BpDbS+vO5iurc48oCdh1GtolxLRuAmZQHzCIxQoi1awYL8O3dchT5L2igKAMf+N+j13pthpI7WH8x+gsGlotTItRh157itTE7NsNtVTy841RF1YdzUQTWcrKqkHzs5RUvYGg7aplo/CIz4RyZMEF/liuZVDxdm4l//8QQmgovPX9Sk2LlgSvLlG2KPIHq7Ijolqj/pvl1+6AzIEyTeRzZWIlcdbbOJmt70OzbGa5TIJonHizwMtk4+T25KZjUzCwO2JkhLGPu4iONm8jmdyWGva73p8A2FbMTOZHV+8ShuVjCcmPnLm/TcsPxGRr1R3362gJsoxkxwS4eqGPWDMls+i4En3LwW0FtnDPla26ggrdT5MKBec4n2vb41D8D2Pt+34/l1Rs6TgewhHFE/Ma8k40M361Dfzlf0+dPj9Rz", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Immoral Traffic (Prevention) Act, 1956", 
		"option_b": "Child Labour (Prohibition and Regulation) Act, 1986", 
		"option_c": "Factories Act, 1948", 
		"option_d": "Mines Act, 1952", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070140", 
		"question": "25SqfJjw3RyqpdFgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+2od0JFWPhFh6/nrf47Xi+FsGjaFP+s6LeCdDe4Z/xN+Q2uH50DFONYZHkol+4IgacrRJwn26fN3YKL56136FZ0r2Jzi+EHlinSXfj28J6i3E8PDfrZ9FJWq70Iui6VA=", 
		"answer": "2525cpDh1Rb/5MUhUQr70/TrPG7DQVt1EEGaeUdeL/BlOnQAIRM=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpdFgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+2od0JFWPhFh6/nrf47Xi+FsGjaFP+s6LeCdDe4Z/xN+Q2uH50DFONYZHkol+4IgacrRJwn2rddfPL+xny33MZ0j5aTyuSDB1mjWWhWherZH7/SahVcgzzwAh1oJ1/cQzJdqa17zdqGSsxhWW3W+UW/1wGVWN9fLqxUzco4oxucnNszfX++O5jvDWsN8MZ0hducZ5bE6ug60M9mohVMmme1JY+eXcbRTvJWimKh4R9tLm0jR9ycI+Uns/tBZIwoJYe4B115vwsyApf8J4VT6zrUEAyIY8WhmRdbq91Cjt7hU+e2Nrap5luT91qQ6GKUZ6lX6PDClchIxk590cmxAtQS18kkrutjeOwHWaboPs+IW8iu6wtLFq4eMkJk+TIVXMQ5kVar3BKydi2OaNBLVVPJEnHjGmKdpu7Cv2NJOXy3kZ2NxgPX7g/D6K0sz7PSWttp71w9ZzHbEHdt7Dqci/uVDDcybvYX+KJtvmXB71QWjx3QkloxAgwTNQ7XrIBIZ24SwZl3G+CUVqlmfldGyuhatO78KacM410vvr2CAfjec4kIm33BwuSgKugT9UvZaUD19Aw1DfCsQIyhpgTJ0VVITU9GGTlmLDC31NfMH7DKGTzilGzqPlgSFuvpYLUpmPPh3ShNlm3B+0QfV8VGv5oMb4M/hVGWUq/6ZoiuKn98mzfP+gPmAkLxu5Xa9c/YZEegt1FkvJDSVbIKymU4ReU+VM13zckkdJST9MAU/P+rwBUgrqq8rMLmXOc74OGgvsaqcMFt24SEjddeWhzTnbRruZg0KyUFQoSzSJb/ILU0YDqQOi7FcMqkifKZI5", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Harmless work", 
		"option_b": "Hazardous activities", 
		"option_c": "Agricultural work", 
		"option_d": "Artistic work", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070141", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV17RzfTzMSv8AmAetm3DGpNmf3nqVq7WZ+LwiZZ/Ixy7iFxu/nfSqqr+vhMugq1V7YOafjZDX4h7hJDbh7WhiDFTNshFl4Uy8JIaPMRSxTOufcTaLL5PzXrAJlavJcWAlUfpKkm7oOravazlFVc=", 
		"answer": "25awYZ33kRjk88UBVhH+wO78MGXEQ04QoXCWQOM8QGPsXK7AZ/n3xpkxJlKNzWl+9WPKorH5+F1Gz4lY/cLfIXtbKMk4EsySln6SHHYoQoGyv6Zf", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ2RDm88UMUxz90O+/fVvCDGoYoXaXW6x6MHDtUOfwa+rrxZZlLlOHxBta/3PIp6j1+UdPrqtPpc7NIHNVMst9zd6I2uHzhGVJNoZ0iIl855MPffgA7T65NNXIYOpmyy68ZWb4bjW5RHF6kHH3jnNarZC48CmvFPY2whonhMcw3dozNN6d0Lya50P4hwiGnEmUT6hoEECQusDhq2KftM545JTV53zntrTFlMTdxNYOIglfuoh7bl6yg+gM4Do5X8yxbFJf+eGQclfiMC3jKAhd7cPmlnhswYs6UWgg/RBIwpdZIsN8wJ32/DM0MMFvBjC/rVBTh9xsWgWFe7OrkGrh9EI6cHRrcYJo/CwypBzcJ1I+yz/cTSJV1NEzt5AYmwAjcG5EmTbjij6Fh2CcPIfsq5Pol+3+p61r961nPUmFdUzKWZsVdrrPKXQy2OyXDLJZN99zGGLyNdBu7Cv2KJ+W1i0E39dgLnnjtDicldj5OHGzvJy5gdI2F7cJOtWF5cq1v06HaC2hCHOXb8q6G85bh7WGxiAstfTrefo6cC4=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Child Labour (Prohibition and Regulation) Act, 1986", 
		"option_b": "Child Welfare Act, 1990", 
		"option_c": "Child Protection Act, 2000", 
		"option_d": "Child and Adolescent Labour (Prohibition and Regulation) Act, 1986", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070142", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MUBQAr7xvH6dTmFQ20X42uLV+NdfnXqVamCTeLw2oN4M0mdhFR1snPIsLDi8gxNvy0f8tee6Vm+fQJzcJ4DOw==", 
		"answer": "25OqbZT33hSq+INgURH81v72MGXTBiBrBybZCFJpWm8OeGXlFt6z", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpdBgVQvz1/zxIW7VECIXsXqGVqx5MH7lFKTNYP79wJJ/JFnJjFV/smLOpuXi/lQHm+hP5s6ZYicGcpIv2MKG0eHk1z0BI9RFmZR7559TPPVOyH29ZtvLIflv2mvANUD8bj60C340oDnfmTxTpoC0+De6R8ky01Ukl5Vx4t0vfNaMya2Q/F74iQDCzn6dQbptHkGK9cyt50qZppF4tMOJ8SLJ9fftk/vW4+IFXgZzrZJ2YFe51/pcuCMrEcn0bgdF9eXdZFr5ISTjNQca8d+jwnxo0sIsU3oh5hpVwpFTbsl035fxr3I2LchvETy340VOw9RoUBuTZry2022k6Vt/XHQvbIsh/Cw5rQCLIVp52mKSSCVHnYR+/9wK1RBsPWlPkHrvlX+KjmHPbIHi6JT1hu2wtLFmsrEiJUiHPFPWFoIaJafIIm5giuqTAq9fNt9wHyvqOJUv8Cr2YISRzCkI080pIXCn4CKc0sn8L2CooJvtl5R5Ev8SM93M7sK4pU+HYybtKHiVdYv9V0jkR3m40AFwuQw30W9Sg+4YClhwaV3T+noLVF3TpQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Freedom of personal choice", 
		"option_b": "Protection against discrimination", 
		"option_c": "Right to property", 
		"option_d": "Freedom of conscience", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070143", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MUBQAr7xvH6dTmFQ2Mdr3CUEqp6MGPmWKbWZ+LwiYN+Z0iBiBtr4HnWoqLx41oAgehU786NdS4KeYJgxo/LDAXTbTiwNH5Kyzcsxzkl4g==", 
		"answer": "25Gxe4L23BDk9pEpXRCyyvu/J27cCmUYrGqQEqFxfHjmUrSCb+P6iZJpN1OahE9y/XiGrKOw5VYDhq9S5puMMDYGcI5725J0g2BuCfoWkKIRWamDxdsw", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpdBgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+yJt9KEuazVJ19n/QqqHl9l8cz7xT7M6ZYicGeoRiiMSGl/Tly2FANMdQn8Bm7J8WbrRSyTGkc93ULrAu+maJNAX9YjizFzBgnDDCynVYrIqt/COuVdYkgB0zgII4+cA5fMWW3qCHqFm3xhWK3WmUCLxqFRSKpdyt6kfctIo9vN/NozfX/fPwle3AsNwObgFXuZUzI0uulqsd8Sk9QoT0aRxPsfDVYFflKSakNE4J9ovswnxs1JFlHWA69xNThopYZYBjxJf3uT4pK8RwHD2940VOw9R9SwOTea2s2WbjoEEwNXkka5xorjl1rhuULUZt2n+TDDhZkYl5vsIcmQ1kdGBO0jbIjSiOlmCdMNP344nvxfr5p7F3sqo0aVKVN1bdVZlccbyAJGJg3uiSA+ZONp50GCznP9krvCv8M4KG1joZ2dYuPDfz/CuN0sD0ICW4ttLwg8R5B7oEdtPcqd+/tRzUdSL1JD2aaIvgUQ2wRnLs1hxgpAxlxydQ+HfaBIB8tSIfmnuiBQRpnTXhYHW1j/Ic64yKP4Y00vn41Xwslsh2tpW30Q4vQgq4iDMDk5aLRl9DyBSES40A0Qg8DboVEZPCsnmekDbCQnsFa47iDuiUyy1a36PwgGU9r4IBWIOaKVnUhNth21ejBPFwUm7ipsq5P+kBSm04urZ+z/7hucWvNeO2I3Mjax/3WOEZ8pdCZw5uBQ6dBCpLIK2gRJgNVfJG0WHPk0daTnhBERrY9OgYTwu6q8PJem+ecbQQBxnrbL1JU8/rDk7bdfKoxnDLA/+OkECrU0UxSz7dNb9N9RX1bIn8MFOykHxt78jxO1RIBJcfPTOzeWqg5aeKGBQvbzhlOJ9Fdk7WCx82kDvRa7lqgrUBfBE5WOTnFkJWnhROkyraQBoBVJOiZosUau2F0JZV8ih3", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Conversion of individuals to any religion", 
		"option_b": "Right to hold private beliefs", 
		"option_c": "Forcible conversions", 
		"option_d": "Dissemination of religious beliefs and exposition of religious tenets", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070144", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7T1+n2NmfVQzBH43CFErd8dTHKWqPLb+O+6ph/NEiAmU5v+3nI7+Xn/1oMh+he55qWZCsGbctnycaMl/b+w3lVIIZWn4xz8J8bPOBPjC+oeN3cKfF73S6BIUPxbiuuWzISXCN72kq5+xRIGRv2O/Ab", 
		"answer": "24e9ZJj02Bb/5MUkVxD9yPTxNH/ZDGwC43CRErd8dXjxFLTHbfn3xpliZZbfFLvgzbOkcwPuCRrWYp0=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpdNgQBvxyvrxPHHVECIQrXvDQrF7ZHTgQLSCeuX7iZZkM1OHglZisnfIp+Xi/lQHm7sb5ojfYicPd4xmx8Wal+Dyyn5MOshFjol96olfffpEjDSjZ8DSNOt6x2GONAXkaHmwBX51kzSWnnRToZH75yK3Xd0+zwAh1oZ+68k1LsTf0KaX7V29iAKH0m+dUfEkAkGbv8ur/wOIr8I7sN+ZsDvVtOb8iezB+d0fawdcrMZ2bRuon61J8SQsVNqxewYL/uKQcUHvLCGgZwEP/c7xmjRkyZAoUWAg7VMGg41SIsh215TwtHwMMfFkNDC5rFZEzpp7HwOZNJyqxGHn7FB/JyxraowtqCUw4SaSLF1/lCu/QyJCgIl/68QQmgovPXtImTbljCuClGyKb9P344HoxeDxtrwj4KogIVWTdU7dWowIYLeAM2gy2OyXBKFVPIp0VyPgO9Qn7iq5IYSRhQUD7NcSKnvu8yOWh961PWC0vJ/wgNViHbAOJZHK+4ujuFnOc2PyJH6Hb8T6SjT+c3LR3QpsoREh3SAc+y6YAZtt8D4dm32kQFJh0ijmLGipk7dOqpCLc4c22vr5znISnfhxmp3kmF04SESzjGlG8oeaXUhOxFqWGNgJwAgjCboVFZqR4GSRnWLDC24Ic8/iBKzH1yMIyOb9h2Z0sJ5CFY6bOFn6mMovyxu0Qa8vFXT9rYXwO/UWC2gg4/JwzumzstmocODkOG0vLwi+XudN4NVebkJpFAfUAi1AdavuUpgQTu1G3HTenghGVD9GFxrY860BT0S5r8fcZ2XQcPEIAV7vYr0EFMu4Wk/KPOPpxyfHRq2ZmU65VkswXXqcJ7YM7BXjNMzbMFO3nG13uc/qJhFLQZEDPS79NH+25bGGBw89diMwO8pOdFTBQgQxgDfMKeongqFAcRQhAbqiFVkRnx5BjHKSD1ZB8EUKH6GiRUBnJKZRYFIf2zi5B6VfSBTPxikej0KZgiXjP/9ZP0QmdXDUnAzykpVui+ypi4DBHtzrPv0Y3YMXLa5PCtiK76Wo7S55F3YCm0Eo83Xm", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Individuals irrespective of their religious beliefs", 
		"option_b": "Religious institutions of all religions", 
		"option_c": "Religious denominations or their sections", 
		"option_d": "Only the State government", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070145", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MUBQAr7xvH6dTmHQ20X42uLV+NdfnXqVamCTeLw2oN4M0mdhFR1smbUrK359Vob0OqdAsUstw4sKbtvQBw/rjbw", 
		"answer": "25a3ZYH23RXj+YJgWxD2zOv2MX7RD3FRt3DDQqJtMGXiTKLRLuvx29dlL1nJnUl0/3nSqqr+t1wdz6Va4ICLdSwCcIhqiN+Pl+X53TFRMtRQk4Nn6JsNPOZFwDSqfdvVYifGd2GpEpnUOuGEVq8aEpE=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpdJgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+2YV+L1WLhE9osmLOpuXl5FZPgK4b+ZudfCsAPo16xtSal+L41jFVO8MEipJ96ZULdftOjDK/NNnaKfB6y2CBKUb1Jza7RHF6jXHGi25CoYCu+SapFMgyzBw1n4h2rccufMWa1aGU4UKtlUaG2XWeRbRqEECQusDmq2qI4JEstNmIomjn+sj3prr9/54bZxpBsIg/cFO9m6RJ+i94Use5eBdH/eHUIUDiYDiiPk4c99KjwnVxw5FlHX088V9WkIxVZ8V3xdjrunInN8RpHXO7sUEA1IR5XB6Qfb653GT9oFQvZWgkdZhkvTkwpU+VJhRum3KRSSJF1I9tvtUBhQFtbmpT3HDvkH+fiGDPbIHs5o/ojOf+4LZxsq4mIE+UMFLZWI4ZJbzGZ2Z806mLDLRIOpxyGyP0fccr8DD+KZmanzYfkMslI37g/SWMgY3xPGu1vpv3j8B/G7FOCpP55/e5mVKHZDDyJHOQY4e0eBrkRn/01k434FggxjIF+mfLSJ139DlNin+oWUV9lzXzLH2zk/5S5ZbOfIE8w/Dg0TcU2OB3353+2hwyRA26gXNa8peKX0xA30CWEd9H1BshAbsVEdbQ/HTWhmbVSHULds22E62LyitB1e2xgXM9rZUCXIuHIwzIyt8l3B6nCOlwUHStvI7rMukSAiQ48rd42K21ttL7ZfK9IWAkewn5GcZNs4BBYA13FRidESxKIKi8X5MdSPBD1zXFkUdbQnxcCVve8rsFHQWkroTYfG/IZr8IHV72a7ZFANr5WkKPM+OmxXDcFbaSkgeuSkYpRzndJ6UD4RSwfIPgZAG2n2Fj8M7wIRFLUZEHMzT2Zyu2t+OFChA1bSUrL8pGdF6VWxE2gDfAMvVmn+cSdRQkRqGoFx5U71aBT4hUs4rQU2FfCT4N1w==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Using public money for religious activities", 
		"option_b": "Imposing taxes on religious institutions", 
		"option_c": "Funding religious schools", 
		"option_d": "Compelling individuals to pay taxes for the promotion or maintenance of any particular religion", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070146", 
		"question": "24C2bJThkTj444wjXhuyl6WzdXzYAnZRqmzDRqtxMGL3VanBa63xx9djIlCAilJ052WGqqvj40EajLxS5oDfeSxDe496y9Gd3uv5xX0BOshXjolm8Y4Wc/pTjCqle9jXOb5jz2eOM0T5aTy5RHJt1CXejzxlvIKv8Hj5t2IQFCMMKQqIsT5ssiTZJA==", 
		"answer": "24e9ZJj02Bb/5MUpXA3m1+j8IWLfDSIYsD+TQKx8eXPqQKLGLuTwiZZ9KxyAg0hv+2LTt6z/+UBNMqrYdQmVHPkFwxH+KsUpCA==", 
		"explanation": "24C2bJThkTj444wjXhuyl6W/Om2QF2oU41aNVqp1fjHAW6nReuTq3IN4KFLFzUl+/n/Bqqrl5BMGgbtP+5ucZCsMcMtmxpCM0/H0xWVIPMhFlsB76okLdeBV2DSiesebNPZv2i6BNUCwcDGyCHxt1DzXg3JCqYq18CP7VsN31B031rRs7Nw5fN6MmbiB50WxhA+W2X/fCIlsFBSSsNfo+1GTtosrvMKDonLU8rTYiOza89IOIloK/4dtZhu9hOgP9yY0Xt+nMi5FzeriZFjkJyGsMh1d0MXwwmZ8xZYgUmdutDFJwpFTbsl035fxr3I5Md5+Bya5t01PydRvVxaaeP261Sj08lopfH4uYcpksm00rxbcLVBrmWqIRSNflYwr994KgQ13aHtJk3igljeKlCWGb9P044/wifGwrbhq/LcmIE+FMRzaT80IbbaAFHNz3uzVMahgPb5zAyfoOdQg/zy5IYLU7TwB2d4pIGL0tAOXgdnnLGauup331JRYG/8QM8PW5sX3sUjTZC3lKHOUJsr6QEj1S2n70hpsuBYkxGEZ5nHMAZ1q4SQCkD6iTEdrlSnpdnml1rxFqpaGes4Cx/T42HIfirRqmpjy3Qs1SQP7jHZH8ouKWxxAyxTlCswTwUkoGboFB9bC+myamTbSTjwfet/jCLqCx2xc1aPlj2p4/4APR5jOJRebi9A/iAW0DfR+XGj4u8bwM+8BGHEv7rt+xK2upYq6YeehImFqfR+7UOhQ/IBCKBV0AxjVDDQPd7G6XpILVaBb2nDDhUdLSHFaAFTYtZQGYQqDpITbe2fTYqMFQl7DcacMEML9DhWXdfSn2yXbA6zcgU+/SwQsQHqYJaUO5BP5dYLzKFO6nXtw8NXwJlhUSpBXKC/yYCu4t6bDDRM2czVlLp9JfkLRCxEqkH7OJvBpmaYJfh0pAaq+WUQek1F8iz/GCxQFokkSVqKkT0Y0aqBLM08D2DShGK8RHBXZxjQFmhaM0C36IP5ONQVjemqXz0Xun5twlvv8g4KSStfjI7MUxs0BLfZYS5fGGlcQn/ek++6gAW0rEmR0J+jJSueRuUG2EM34q8TTyklYib8LIlYtLC2CjIyZ/ygtJqtce2JfvmcQo8SSdQ++0YdMwRB8WFDl5wHnTmkysx9nINPfYtTPaou3/0ZWBS3IWflWiPR30Sj3dcvZYVovFWo7kg6AeteKyDLDLqn41aEIFxGx2tnKS44t/k11x9u7zFlT6zVwmmjwCnrTdv6t4RAUMWh5X7HSCEhTxhImwDmwylrnM46mx68HnaRIzKAH6AP5sW806gAOpxoPYWmOMkHUzGLv0A==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Religious instruction is mandatory", 
		"option_b": "Religious instruction is prohibited in all institutions", 
		"option_c": "Religious instruction is optional", 
		"option_d": "Religious instruction is completely prohibited", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070147", 
		"question": "24C2bJThkTj444wjXhuyl6SzdXzYDCIYsD+EQKJ6ZHTnFLPKa63swJB5Mxydght4/XjVprfm8hMLhrtP4ICcZGIPf4Vo3dGO0qi313JTOtZQ1sB99tocafhU2S+oK5ZJOhPoHE0e09DB331UwUjs", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz3RDk8JApQQr7xr3+O2+QEWcdqniKXbZnMHzqWqjQZ/n3zIQz7Fug7H4dE4uZvM8ROJ+jCA==", 
		"explanation": "24C2bJThkTj444wjXhuyl6S/Om2QF2oU41aNVqp1fjHAW6nReuTq3IN4KFLFzVZy/HnUqrH58kBDz79T7JqXdTBDfIp8zdTJ2Oq31nRNOsFNlY4y64hfcPVOyyisc9GXYP98yy6HNUT+czy5RGR8kXHEg3tevMOv+me4W9QkxQckk8ds5c01Lpeb0LuH4UO7kkaO3XWWXbxjFBjZps264lOI7MI3p42OpD7P4eb81Ljv/uIFVgBbrMZ+cU+1lKQMuDg9UsezZhtR9PeQdVzoYCGuNwEP7crt1XEpyYRpTXsx5xpUlIpYZYBy2JykrCA/MsJ+HD2941BIwtR/ShuCYa+53Cjl7lF/eXMlYp9krzk8ok+YIUJ7iHiVWDURm4Yr194dnAUjfGFE3HPukSqZhXbPaJvi/8DxjOb/srB36+MkJkyNIFLRQoQZdvPIJnF3iv2TCOZaIZpiEy3rfcEhvCnrL4KR3C1N0dckb2f18TmcgNvweXGytpvrzsF4Ha4VM5HN7Nm+pF3AZGPgL3nTb8/xVxz5W2W2kWO71HR4t5hse4zkC+PgOh8=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only linguistic and religious minorities", 
		"option_b": "Any section of citizens, including both minorities and the majority", 
		"option_c": "Only linguistic minorities", 
		"option_d": "Only religious minorities", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070148", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg3xyu36dWTWQ0MDt3aAXqY0IiijRLXNeuj93Z5+KRyIjlh04HLPraKw41xPm6Beqb2KYDAGc44v69+cxfCohlCjUU+vqyBX2DHI0Btlowk=", 
		"answer": "25C2a57+wRj55IAzEhz90fW/OGLeDHAYt3aGQeN1fnWjQK/HLuD/w5hjLkiQz8oCGgFtO8ih0Z4DvBMVGfA=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHg0hb68sUvVF7T1+n2NmfVQzBI42+RXbdxc2XqW6mOLuz9yphjI1WHihtv/TbSq6CwxEYfna1W7M68fzcRascvzd6K2OnnxWJSNtUEmI9m7NoSdfpP3jS5fdHIYP9gyi6UL0Cwaji3C2J9gCiYylVC6IqotSm0QJo7yRg7goJ8rdwzfNuW16+G4V6sjwXC0XKfR69tBV2cpo6n+QOOpZEsp8SOpTfftOD22uvD9d0CZAFR/5R6ZFKzmbtJ+j8sEcmkeB5C9PeQdVutISSvZx0Y+t/q2Xp6ho0vHXo79xZDlpoaIsV9xY32tTw3f9liEHOqsUFTwoZqXgOfe7P40WbgoEUtenckcYNism06p0+QKVp5j2qbSWARh4N598AN2URic2sAn2PsliqZhSWJc4Gj6Y/ojaj9qbds4KozIESTdV3WUs0IbbaAKmZ4xfuSGb8Sc6NpKyzHL8En/zX8YMTNnykf380lLGP0tD6Rl43nMGKyp4G5gdI2FbMMdtLK5MaivlXTaCbybT2BY8z1Swz8Sm/rkwFj9wwtzSgCqG7RBo5q/D4Zl33wRlYkgCLsZXuomatPqpGafpokwLmsyT1Qm/t2jJ7lwhh8Uwy+hG0Dto2MW1VBzkCWEswJwxwvC7FNVIXS4GSGgTqQSnIJP83jDbyS0SkGmOx47cJcTMsayI1SFaDUIi4=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Restricted to religious minorities", 
		"option_b": "Limited to linguistic minorities", 
		"option_c": "Restricted to specific regions", 
		"option_d": "Encompasses both minorities and the majority", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070149", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MUBQAr7xvH6dTiAQ2UDonGXErd7MHzqWqjQZ/n3zIQxb06MgVJ8+3nTsOX/5RMDhqZc/IeMZCsAN8tmxpCd3+G3x35PJ8NcjsB94toaeOFDzSmke9qEYtj79o/6XgdX/7LXjUPszpU=", 
		"answer": "24exb5nnkQ3lt4AzRh/wyfTsPSvRDWZRonuOW619Y2XmRufHavj9yIN4KFKIgRty/GXSqrHl41oAgbsb5ojfZCoGd5kvy9iG3ufyhmq+hhAvIXClARKwFNsXXRo=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNVgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+zoVwKUiazVZy/HnUqrH58kBDz79T7JqXdTBDfIp8zdTJ2Oq31nRNOsFNlY4y64hfcPVOyyisc9GXYOpmyy6SLkL4c3mpCzBxhyXXiHBfu4v79Cm/FNszzRw8n5Rs6Np8OdOK2qmH4UK2hwrC1XWCXLRwBECQusC7q0ya4JYwsMSf8THT+/36n7aTzNA3bDxatpU/c0mzgaEa8SU2Ec26ewdZ9PeQdVzsNGiuLgAS68L3zzRqyY8kSGc94BZDkcNeY9Z2lozsuXI2LchvETy341BPh5FvSxaUeLSr2Cjl7lF/eHslZI1o/Dk9pAaOaFtplCuZSDlSlZRi8d4YmURqc3xUlWL1ljaEjnbPa5vq54W8iOn5rq1i+60uJ0bAIVTdX59cZqbMM3Jgy+XbDKhYc5pjAiHnKdwh8jj1YJeByzYD39Q5YTfb+haXu9m1PWq/oNL3gcA2GroDM8LW6Nm+vEWHcTHuN3SXY4vySw31D3n8xg1koxEqxmEf+iLeAYd++y4En3LwSE1g0iX1eDynmb1J+YedP4E/k+Hk2HIRjeB3kZT6zV0zQUS2hHFMoI2LVhxKyUHVH9kOywcvAPQIGoXF+3mDgX/fRW9DPTseqB6vCRk/fEFMUGM7ZTM=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Right to free education for minority students", 
		"option_b": "Right to receive aid from the State", 
		"option_c": "Right to govern majority educational institutions", 
		"option_d": "Right to establish and administer educational institutions of their choice", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070150", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7mzfi/YT/ECyIwrnqNVq5xfmWjdaTWIq3pwZZlZ1iGiEg702TSqqb88hNc3+hI6IiadzcCbI8v2tWF1vDywDFVPIZUiI9i4YgLZbRBzyy4fcfSNPdhwDHCgCkoRxx2cHfJdrB3iPI+Qg==", 
		"answer": "24exb5nnkQ3lt4AzRh/wyfTsPSvZDXEFqmuWRqp7fmKjQ67WZuLr3ddhNVOZiElv6zTwb/ATLAs8IH95U1SBHNAP", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGnhQ3it6QtVxD2yPjxISvxAHZRp3aHEq17ZDHqWrPQYenrypIxJFSIg1x+4TbUpqnx41YLz7xUqZ6NfzIGbJ92iNGKxvH+13hVOslK2ol8pLsNaP1DwDjtJ4SbL/gu2maFZ2z+YzC8CjBXmz/FnnVCvZey+in1FOY5/BsThJNx7sQ5fITPmbiB4UC5lA+OxTuXR75xAlGK9cGmq1eUpcIqvMqFpXLU8rT0k/bc4tcfaw1B/5JwI16vg6kL9CMrWYi1ZhYL8ODdaFrkMzymNU4Y/d7g12BgyYwoUSk9+gxSi5dDdsl82IukszRwK8VvHCH6oExPzpd5EVe/YP283233oFswYTo4dY9utSs8og6QJE0+m2+YXilCh8B77N8JkBZ3ZC9Bn2f1iyyClGyActPs+cDoje2wsrBk+rdnPU7AJU7dQIgScfPDKGpi3+WIArRFc55kBjfvLtw69Tb3YJmSnykf38klPWP+umqlnPH7DW2/84Lrh9l3BqZAJsTX+cSktRzIZ2PAM2maZcfxGVugD3Xrkxpq9wg3xzUV63aYHIF6tSgJi32xXU1rnCbsLH2vkv5f/46aapww37XtyCYflvt1htv40l0xTgq0n3ZXq8ScQFFC2FrfCsQC10knAvQoGpLY8yPUG5O58XknoPDAlpmQ/75+lA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Right to prevent compulsory acquisition of property", 
		"option_b": "Right to receive aid for property maintenance", 
		"option_c": "Right to sell property without restrictions", 
		"option_d": "Right to establish institutions without property", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070151", 
		"question": "2523f9Hywxyq/oszRhfm0On2OmXDQ20X42uLV+NgeHjxUOfWd/37id9/IlWdhV5psmXDpq75+VRPna1Y5omReTYKcYUvxt+bl+X+wDgBIcNDj4xz8J8bPPZZjCmlcZTINP96yzHCHoUmcHI8RhmHhR0OnGb8qg==", 
		"answer": "24GwbYiz0Avvt5Y1UBT3xum/IWSQAm4d422GVbZ4cWXqW6nRLuzu2Zt4JF2LgV475nmGrLH48kFPhqZI/YeLZTYKcYV8ipE7Bcr7Dwc/GhWzRJUOJ+E=", 
		"explanation": "25y2e4X6xQz+/oouQV79w73rPW6QF2oYsXvDRrpkdT2jQ6/LbeW+yIV0Z1KMhE9z92SGsKD1/FoBiOhJ7I2QdywKaoJgxpCH2Pa3xXhFc8BWlY0y8JIaPOdUzSmoOJTaMvsuyWuOIlfxazWkRH57gHHFn35crYCvtTO0FN4+0hAxgsd/4t45LtmS3KaHqF+9gROO3W+YR7MkHkbZvMC87lGapZA9u86I8TvVtODxn/HBsNcFdg1AsYdzI1q6kakA6jl2Efy8bQFOse3eckDkND23LgET6oej2XJ9w4xpT2wy8Q1Uh4cWds8z14ukgHAlMcxjETa+nwYAyIY8Y1WGZrSu0XzhoEAxdHMvYI5R/m08rxyIIUBrjmKTQj8d1I97+8IYgQEjdGFEmWbljDuOjnGDZdPi5YS8hPr14Lds5uMhIE+BO1/RV4EQfPPTMndixfuPCKIcMYYnAyrjfdIh6jzrLpuR0S1D7NccIUDv/Sac0tn9PHz6u5Pvi5R3AasPON7I8Iu+vhzTaSboMz2SYsb9VwHjW275xwdquVgkxiVQ63fKGoB84CEYkzLwXUxhi2fhfnnhhapV5o7ObJsz2fDvyXIEl7R7monj1RQyBxa+impPs5CQXUUP3UbZCMQUzQYgH/QSAJff9myEkWWcC30De476AL+Ugz5N1uLli2U9q59OUIibLxjPg9EohFeyFO9rXGT4pJP0cbwUDmkl6aF4xeOy+4q9cPa3YCUrYR73VvtR9ocRaRFrFAjJFmRAZvirUogdQPRG3XvLm0dJQ3JAC1Pf77oJSQ2lpIqIWmLbI7QEGhvsd/MKFY7qS0DaOfC9wT/HRrKdjAeoXlY8Dj6YMbUD4Q7+fcz9KlOnm20k6tHgMVhdTYBXOSPmd2qtrKyNCgp6byMpIYlOf1SVSh4g1DLCMOongqFAZBAoAbuzGEQT1h5d3z3dG1ZRolVeVqvtV1suKaEFNFMUjT67ArQWSAnejzUEzlmMxzDtPf9YfwsXfsaMbvbemuXGm0YYaYU9", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "They are fully autonomous and not regulated", 
		"option_b": "They have complete exemption from laws", 
		"option_c": "They are subject to all regulations applicable to other institutions", 
		"option_d": "They are regulated only by educational laws", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "070152", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kRzr9I1gRhvgyL3oPH/YQ2sFsD+AXbFmdWLzW6nGZ+P5iZN0NF+bhEtv+3nI4+WwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EYj0KFILsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8H1fWNP34kCikoBV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LwCXPPNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyYFs1cJfOAZycyiqnbTeYcc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbUn3lNkJlgbzentGrZ0o21eSX689K5zpQ2VP9AdpGFqYv38ByHIWOhYT3TJou0GUiwDzy4k04l91hliGFQqCKYSMk/tW1N3j7wCQQk0megLDzh1v4cqsLOP85xk7WsnXJQ2LQ439u3lF18B0T7zT8D8sTfDxwPjRSWXo1HhEluTPRBVNaRsi3W1TaQCzxNP462QejHg2wImqOxziE9/9BOFczObFmbyp5miFfxQb05FSet6Ma5fbxVSiRsuvIxiq3h94r7NbPkbCVqL1r3Ga8Zs9URKEI7UUudRWQPIPjuFt1eAaAPkjWK10cIBz8JRRqMu+hIHUTq6oSILiqeI/FcTl6iI/NFU464DgePdbHpiHCJRv/c1Qf+HwRlDnrdYfBNpUewOsyyZFPz0ygkuYGlchEbBMNXfGezNCv55ePDS0Z6P2xlaMoHOgeVC1Bk1H6DZ7knzedAMFhtAejnWRBW1lEP336SThgF8AxeH+XtABNnaukFYBtRjXf1UeBfHFyKxnpKzhbcgmKsaboLcQljOyTTzwyg29Im37+pws7BSpSibf1bks1DaPYbBNqWXxtc2rOkr6GgUSx5Ri03briIHqKR8A+2Qoi04oOahRwLif5Idh97ZXnLyd+ZsHotb+UPLzAK/TNZ7IqSIkbqmcgZlRAoEBWstQGkASdh9lEzLtOrKp2catvlsBAfVmSHF/kD2Lw4nWykdZ+RJFp/RyN10UfQNpKKh3TDfey7gO1JRVjil9mLBcotrAg5jpzygwwA63s1zzyiSzaaIqetqF4UYjw4C/TfWh0dxldilXrxnhOofc/qx+ZJzvABmPVToUy34mE2zx7MDwqOIzOqnrbe9yaG/gdhieojHCbjGzMtjkxkBLBrsjkuAG1hCeE0/Pa1bPGE3iHvbtz4jcxNpRYUBueKb/37/ZW8ZeOFb+WsmcDDbzKhsdNFDea7aPdFN3/ZbH0zra3gIq3tL3BVnW5sNOwRAJwWKKz2doY=", 
		"answer": "24WqZ4X20g3j+ItgXRiy7PPrMHnVEHYC43CFEo59fn7xXbPLa/6+hNdQNUiAjld+siSf7+XC/lQHm+hU786yeSwMbIJ7wdWal/D4hFRSJ8dGlolh7NoecvAA7TmgfdrSM+pr3C6lI1DzZi20C351mHH/hG9CoZeu4S60Wsl3jVUThJNx7sQ5fITPleih4UqwkkaW0zuBWrJ0EFOYocvo+UaQqYUxusPN/HL65uDwmfTWsIxeLkhgtoF3dxuomOgI/CcxX8GnfBdZsfTCbkToMjy6ZwcTucrg1Xt7woMnXmx04xZSisNaY9czm9jFriY5PMFvVWHs7QY6fQGG3Wyr21gcUBpGhp6O", 
		"explanation": "24WqZ4X20g3j+ItgXRiy7PPrMHnVEHYC43CFEo59fn7xXbPLa/6+hNdQNUiAjld+siSf+Zn+y10unbxS6oKaMHBaPpt9x8SM1PDkhGVJNoZNlJR39p8MaOcAwzvted3VL+xn2meFNAXyfnm8CHx7gzjYjTxXppr75iK4QNM4zlU9kMd75Nw1JtKRyuiB7V6xgg+M2zuYRv1lH03Zpc+6/wOTpsIRu8mEsHLT9eLwlP+T8Z4PaxtGtoh8dxuwlqYO7Ss/VIT0exFZ+PTELRTiMmigMgIJ7Nnmlntvhos9Tik74xEKwpdZIsN82IvhriQ1f9liEHOpoklFidRIVx6FNK2q337t81wwezoua5l4rigm4RuUKUA+l2KSQz5YgIlu7ZAalAojfmBOj3PylDrLlG2KdYGj54Hygv3xp7wvsrAkO0iQIRCYWZ9cZqbMM3Jgz6mMBLJUPIpzVyvoKdA8+jzrJZiX2ncx3uspKH/ztCWf0uD8N2qouobwi8c2ALBAE8LR6Mm7uU/PISLvJT2yYsb9VwHjW3nqkythohsk3Cgf5mPUSKBx5jkEimukQEtqgWetLF2zgrdf5ofOLN5r7/vQ0xMCjP17k563h018QBa6g2tQ8omWQVNdxEDfG95LhB4mCaAJEYSR8GyFkHKQRHJNbcv6CK+OzCII1fGxgmBzuIUPUonCbA3Tj540wRC5Fb1tWifou5L4P/AcGWxs+7x1iuylusO1fOCwKXdqah6iWu5N+ppfaQ47GAXOES1bdaynWZMND6B72nCKpBNJU3oJFlLN96RIUwu+6sDBfWnMarwVAB/2ZvMEFM/xQFTbdeK8yziJD7GPgU6qSlAsQTSOb4wD1w73cpiyMBzzg3pr6cDiM0VeBJESMC70fWS35e7DKhQudi8pLcoVLx3pRSwqtSzXLvpriOdSJVg9U6exEFQThVFJkCySCEpAtUgRUuWiRhMkJadWI1IUwzSwUaERWFzejj9KnF+byjasPfULN1smfmiKz1zylJRjjOylwp6TC9f2JL4ens0CJrIbVIjZD1obm+fhr/PlHWU+D2J5YLj8VuvC8Er4Ed3mp9Ca0VROibcGMlYtLD2eiJOe43p/JqJHezBesjMJvsXCYwGrzY0Z2l5tF0as50ToSGAouQRgLpHuZtTZLIjl5F8fGTDPUqtQ1sB27yXjPcuRcBV/Bmc4mAmZZcbP1XSTL6Prxb8dHFir2dnKRoli/kx4wN+3g1tJvzM1g331SzuaQ/X54R1YJzwqHe6jFGFTpwU23Dm92xO6a8+6lakfh7REy/UB5AD+pSh5mk3MS0/AbH7j0PeKvmnIrQc1wa8jTm+kU2ct2gNkQeM/83tiST4pCaB6uPb4LbjKimCmINyxw58Z7EJBUq7FIa77u9ruZbHAI6zr0I+WPDLg/5cpB/2uN9cRIXTBYX0PsazkbZfBfkXTKGTE37qWEyyLZTRT63B82m2ZWlhtK2ayQttOXj9c0I93N60Utt2kv0wlbm/ME7Zh1q9F21pXCBBNRbzuj38BWPlhKJuVYFohv1cSDa8UbmC+Z0Nlc9lUm3OmTDeq+T2lw7NgRNbolhtrLAqUxCHIbnzI4KtgIinlU8PSjNetCgyx4OQyTkdZ5qFdnESICG8EZGB34wLMjfUvSlyAZxclMesBh9sHRMznpUUGl9ciRhkSbDnZCC62FZfJTpUfBdev0rYmrJ9e2zhHDoNOaomOThHEnHucWm9UekNLdFfekR7yrY9vis7LAw+G6j7+xKOTmWivUJiggic+Q0/xIKo=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part I", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Right of Minorities to Establish and Administer Educational Institutions,Article 30", 
		"option_b": "Right to administer property in accordance with law,Article 26", 
		"option_c": "Protection of Interests of Minorities,Article 29", 
		"option_d": "Right to propagate religion,Article 25", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080101", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7n1+3wJm6QDGRRgm2XW6B4dTGwBviAWwMgqVwtp3YSnOQbYYXwnA==", 
		"answer": "24G3KIHh3g/j84BgQBv/wPn2MHiQBW0D42mKXa91ZHjsWufNaK343Jl1JlGMg096/jbUqqL440BNJo6ul1NikjDYkEI/bnBq1Q==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNdgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+2pJjMVmazU9z9zbFsazk/lAOg+hL/JyPfzEGPoRpiMCb2PL+wHhPNIZNlIR78pMbafVM3326fcDTYP8uyHuOI0T9YjepBXw0hjjRgmgWvIz78S6pUdkjzAxyl5do/8c9P9/fzaCWqH6tlhSH0X7Ra7JxA0DZusjowk2YqYN4s8Kf8SbT8bT8lP7c4t0Obw1cq8ZwZRuon60A6mo+RMawaR9O//DRbRT/KS+rMx1Tufft6npA0sIgTik3+xFVi4dTcMV3lpfquXI/OY1+HTb6rktT09R1UgeZZqm53nyk4Vs7NWokco9/ujg54R2ZJVF6k26PDC1HlYln/9IVkER3ci9Qjnn0hzyfwGSBeNPm5Ybzl+v14L92/KcmJESOIV3UFp8VYrvUNCkwr/Eth2Bs2mfNcoJmhBlRNA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "To declare fundamental rights", 
		"option_b": "To provide remedies for violation of fundamental rights", 
		"option_c": "To establish the powers of the Supreme Court", 
		"option_d": "To define the role of Parliament", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080102", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRqmzDfIxAMHCjQ7XLeq3qwZZlZ0iBiBtI52bUpqj1t3AAmrpPqY2efmIKbZh6zZCP2Pa30HlEc8NKnI9g558SefpUjDKrNNLOLvpvw2uOM0T8Jyu0A3hgh26UvqX/EKwwcXjH8MbRipVYPA==", 
		"answer": "25qqbJj90Bfp8sfa3lF5Pfu+SSDczKYejYY+", 
		"explanation": "25qqbJj90Bfp8rliEhfhhdPQASvRQ3UDqmvDRqt1ZDH3XKKCXfju25J8Ihyqgk5p5jbFoquw/kAcmq0b74GNMDYLe8tqxtaGxefyyXRPJ4ZLnMB08ZQbfflFwimseJTJKflm2n3OZ3n+WzeJDHU0myXej24Wp5Ov/Ci1R64awRs2l4pt/oR8DMWQ0aGR4VmxiQjOnFiUWqltHkaYp8fkq0KSpMIQtM+IsCGb9/vriu3AhN8ZZ0hGt4M/YFSxmqcHuD0qWNynKAZD8PCQdVzoYBu2NxwY9M6j9Xt81JZpFWg68F9Oi4ReIsN8w4rwr3twPMxkVTqpsFFFh5JzTVeAda+x3333oEUqZ2okdo9+8G08rwyQPVB3lGzcWCRU1IVl+N8LlgFueGFU3HnmwjmejmGOcZbt/4Hwxfr5p7F34e1nFU+8O33WFrFeaqHELmlzxOqeMeQcJ4Z3HiHnMdk3vCv8JpOGzHkZ35khb3vi8yOKnszhMHO/85/8j8djBrpAP8LW/M6z8F7eITfpJD2jdM7nUAz1QWi43AglnhYhwSBQ53CYHIF6tQoCiHuiR0t20ijmLH3hhapd/ofOaoA11uesziIVm/1+lpi31xQuRBG2nmtCvIeaXBxOw1CWF95HygY6TLVBAI/B9y2ZkzbHWXUZP9vlBKzHwTUIzuv0zmJyqoIaRsyIIwubhtshyRvxE/h0UGPkrZW3f9KG1uujDX8TPP2zTt787y0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Habeas corpus", 
		"option_b": "Mandamus", 
		"option_c": "Prohibition", 
		"option_d": "Ordinance", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080103", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg37wvP2M2LTAmwSpj+MVONVYmXqV6vHLr6siZ5/Z0iBiBtY/XjVt6zk4kcGgKYEq78pNsNjrBvBu6KMAWPPhoU=", 
		"answer": "25ysKIHh3g3v9JEzEgr6wL35IGXUAm8UrWuCXuNmeXbrQLSCYeu+3Z90Z1+AmVJh93jV4cXOkKqteCMrfylvgrBFkiw=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNdgWw2yyvu/JWrCAm8etnGXEqp5YH7xQKbMbei+yIQxLkjJiFZr/WHDsbaw9FobhrJe553fZC1DbY5qw5CDwvfjzXJEf4ZUiI9m4ZkLb7RG2TOpddneLupvwi6SLkL4cyrxRHF6kHHDmnRZpIeotTOzUZol1Rk31oh+rcQ9K5ee16zT60K2lRKLyG6FQbJqEFjZpdyh5UCVsI49po2Ev3Ly+vDwm7aT2cpLcQ1AqYNsI1qv16lJ/j82Vcm5bRxf8OiQcV3hLCmxZwEbud/r0zRAyIYgXGd0+BpBg48Wcdlgwp3p/DM+O41uED61oFZB051/HxCZYriq3mnq41BxN66+kzE/mW+6Fb7IJeqEYx4=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "It protects the fundamental rights of the citizens", 
		"option_b": "It empowers the President", 
		"option_c": "It defines the powers of the high courts", 
		"option_d": "It protects non-fundamental constitutional rights", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080104", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRrl4pc0Ehbz1r3rPW6QAG0foGqRQKZ6ZDHpQbXLfen3yoN4KFLJmlJv+jbSq6CwxEYfna1W7M68fzcRastmxpCd3+G3wX9HPNRHn4136o5fc/IAyiijcNXWJfB6z2LANUz3by2uWzIQrMfQX0b3iOjV5SSvt7S5", 
		"answer": "252xb5mz0hb/5ZFigvD8sChOEQOnrkZXnacLqA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHb2B7it6YvRwzm1r32Oyv5DWYYoj+LU7VxMHLsWqTXfP/7x4MxLUmbhEh/+3XSqqr+t0QGm6Ab/YaaMBEWbplqxdXJ9Ovi1mUBOsgEjoh3pJ8RevtSzzigcdrPYPFojmiVKUHxajyzEHF41CPfjXRCu837ySmHWu4/yQZym4J549t8KN+ezeia5kmxkA+GyXqdW/1nEFrZtN64+Uydo4p4sMSZuTfJtODxn7jg5c4ZZwVX/6Vwdkmo16cbuD4wVIimbQFb9OfEaELoYACqIAZd2sT2xGApyYRpSWExtAxSg5dTItd704rh/CY4OsR4VTWvrUBBypFySxaaNK+x12Dw8xU+Z39rZIZhuSowpU+IJxR2m32ZDC5UkY4r6NkWmQV3eGsAmnnywi2OjWCLdZbwq4HygajipbVq96VnO0SMNEjdUs0IavPUL2Iy3OCUAadIOpBpVy3gfcEm+Sr8YISd2DEZw5dgE3nb+giWhsW1LW2/86HsnsZzGbpAFd7Q+9/3sVLDITfpJD27b8z8GSv/Wm7swE5ttg4giDUY7SLZHZ13+j8EimfwXUskmzTzeXnhgaxV/pHOeYEjk+Hk2HIVlvJ3jZjy2RgyU0S0iz9Fp4qbTlFKw0DXEo0VzQ4mGKdPVjOhXXABmVJJ0V1Qh8pn4Fg=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "District court", 
		"option_b": "Lower court", 
		"option_c": "High court", 
		"option_d": "Supreme Court", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080105", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEh39y/n2IWLfDSIXrG3DW61if3rqWqCCT//qwJR9Ihza3xt9/WSGsaD8/lYJ0OoHmjQxFvZY9Kg/ENXHapxJ", 
		"answer": "24OxZ53yxRDl+cUvVF700PP7NGbVDXYQrz+RW6R8ZGKhOs9SHvPTuzX3kglHd0xQkA==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNdgUR/8hf/6dWLeFW0apnvDXa14aTH0XKLMLvn2zNdnLlOFjE9y/XiGrKOw9hMJmqZf6IOafjYCcst9wdeBw6T/xWIBPMVHj5Jg4Z5dxWkhkVs/+553VDi18uhnCg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Availability of alternate remedy", 
		"option_b": "Violation of non-fundamental constitutional rights", 
		"option_c": "Violation of fundamental rights", 
		"option_d": "Violation of customary rights", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080106", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7gzPD+J3KQE3cDs3CQV+N7djHCRrPLbeH7icQjZ1OPzU9z9zbvraH59l1PrKdV+pqWZDcXd4Rhl5K0IDualdo671WXGE6ANa9f", 
		"answer": "24G3KJL83x/v5cU0Whuy1/T4PX+QF21RsXqOV6d9dWKjUqjQLvn2zNd0KVqGn1h+/3PIt+X/8RMJmqZf6IOafjYCcst9wdeBw/e1hVGyxuwcjkLaZ5YpbwLkSg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3hfu/pEpXRCyw/LtdWLeFW0aqnGEEoJmZHjgWKKCPb++z5hjZ06MgVJ+9DbPsOXk/1Ibz7xT7M6ZZSwHf4ZqxsSI26TlzXZJJ9UElYYy5ZRfdfpExSukcMHaLL5j232UZ0f1Jy+0C3x1gDTSynNE6IKp8GeuWt4y0lU7m4px480yKJeL0bqW6Vn4iQDC3n6YRrokB12Wuc+87kfS4L42icOsoybS9/j82quBsNsGcgdFupRsI1Kyk6Ef8S4tUMSnKAZEseDZc1HuNCS6Zw8N6dns13dhhpYhWCkH4Q9Uh45TIuN8w4rw/DQ/LY1+HTb6pkpGyIZ/WhqTeqn4326k9F06fGhrY59juCw4pAGIKVg+iGKbRDhC2MBp68RZgQxmZC9NiWX0wjuOjWqBb4fx6pT5xfz4oa0j5qsiIFPAM0nWUowRYL3UJmsy2OCcBbJPc5dmASemP9Ar8nnwLpCG1jcK1d1gOmfo+mqWgI30K2D6soa5nN1lH/8PMJHH7MK5txzRaCztIGmWYoW0ZQbMQUjw2h0lthQpxzYDqGvWDIBp/CkYn3KjCVBr0jTlaXfhhLtR74aHep1x0vvonSICl+B9nI/+2xN8QRa0gD9XuoHffElf31HbG40kyxw8GPQWHJPfsnmekH/CC38Ccd3iCLyS1yVH1OL9znN0uJgaRsyPPhybi8pm2wOwCvg3F2enY6iCponheMZLG2dexg4=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "To establish the Supreme Court's jurisdiction over all legal matters", 
		"option_b": "To define the powers of high courts in issuing writs", 
		"option_c": "To confer the right to remedies for the enforcement of fundamental rights", 
		"option_d": "To regulate the jurisdiction of both the Supreme Court and high courts", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080107", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRqmzDfIxAMHCjQL7Sa63xz9dmNVWdzU9z82KGoKT+t1EKz6FI+puadGIBZ8ttx8SBl/D/wTFyJtZWn413pLkQaeZUjDyjcJTTKflmjm2PMlfkdGb/fNPhkzwJ4fkO7JsacVmQGw==", 
		"answer": "25y2YoT90g3j+ItiVKdQM53rsTwirid1WUdpcA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHnyAnv5MUvVF7l1/TrJivEC2MF43yCXON2dTHqR7TXa+m+y44xJVOdhRtv+nOGkLDg5VYCiuh45puNZGICcI8vwNmO36T0y2RTJ9UEm5J3pLIefvFB332Oe8bLNe0ijkOBKUHxaiyuSDBEhj7eg35fvIq0+2v7d98l1Bw9hIZq5IR8PdmbmZmG5wCPhxSQ3XWFR/1YU32Xv9um6FeVr4wE942EonLV++C5lfbWsNENIhxaupV6I0yunrwaxCQEX/y8bVJ3s9PCaECtLy7jFhsSufzixGZoyJYmYSt0/QwGjIxCIsEzwoH0uXI/OY19Bzqu41BIxoA8XBaYNL+9kGH380A6cTopfMpvszk94RuULRRNj3uOSSFU1KNk68IN1QVteS9IlXHowjyElXebb92j3Ij1ie2wtLFmspAyOVOFOFmYdYIJd6eAJml2iuGSCq4cMJByBTb1fdYv8nnwM4WB2nke1c8lPXbrtCmWn8D6NyWuqoL8nZR5Ev8XJNjR+of3uVLEbTblKHOUJsP1Ww3xXDz73Bx1ogtpiCwR5mbZBZxsuW0djHG4QEZthi7vYjDhl7BYqoGLbZo43Oftzztc2OBwmtvLliouThD7gnkDg5GQD2tO30bXENkI+EtuBadBFdbD92GXgX/GTnAUP8LzErvHwCNF1+z/znZvtoRAaYKyIjibtpwR2h6lQfJ/FVb4p8bOPO4HC2o49Y4ziuSy99mrcPCtKmwpbha7QK9M4JBVKBZ0UQjVBChDZbapU90KSeUPwHzNnxMISG0JBE/Y86caVBCz6svOLmuec7QOHRHsI7sKH8rxQECPNLG53TLFD7zcmkG4VkcgDjWPYaAC9g7kc4P8ZAe8035h68jjKxFMTIYDNCLhNH+xoLrDAwcsemwxII8HdkLSShxkhSvCK/BhhKQBZBEiT7vnGF4S1hRBizfGAl1ItUIKH7GiAFsoJq0FNFMQ2Xe6F6YWXxmExhMezl+PgiOsPuhCJQk2aGGXz1jv24Nzmuz9i4GPSsDqKP0X14oKPL9WRZnPX1Qa2uDr4uTvH2l5DmJ7KvHGWaLBpU36C8u0rcXczF9Oh/wSKWq/1UPYcuqvgwC0j8ie", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Habeas Corpus", 
		"option_b": "Injunction", 
		"option_c": "Mandamus", 
		"option_d": "Certiorari", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080108", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7n1+3wJm6QDGRRt3eGErRmeWWjW6GCQ+zwzZZ8Mk/Wz8YY8j9CH5mWVy7ynMMnRpo=", 
		"answer": "24G3KJL83BTr+YFgU17i0P/zPGiQDGQXqnyKU680ZH6jRKLQaOLsxNdlL1mAnxt09HDPoKzx+xMLmrxS7J3dPb/kZCYMlzHcF0s4G1LtAQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjxAv6+JYlEhH0hen3MCvHEWsF43CFEo51fnXiWbLRLuTtiYN+Z1+GgEt+/jbH47Xl9V8GjOha/JqXfzAKapIjiNeGweHlynxEPdIElYZ07ZkWffgMjDK/NNjUN/t8jm2PMlfkJy2yRGBxhjfZmHEWqcO38CC6WJoz1QEr1ohqrdwzfMOe0q3T6Q2rlgOB1X2YS/1lEkCQusDo/0udtMIsvciU8TPJ8bT2mPTa998fZwwSq4k/c16ukacb9WotX8yxelJf+eGQbVX6bmiKM04U6ovilmN7z5ZpVHon4RpCwoFPIsEz3pHjtDcif85lACGu4wxT0pd0HxaFNKmw1SjX9UUtcHcuJaliqT8h4QCOaFU+kmKbRGxSm5V56plZgQsjfmBNkXfuhn+KwGmAa5bxq4PzkPrk7Plk/bUiO0+NMFLMFoIaY7rDInU+iuaJTbZJMZNuFGLnKMEm8yvwNI/UyzZN09gyPW6n+z+N0tn9PGyo85bsmt1zB/8PJJHD/MW0pFXIbzChKHPTZ4v4WB/2WnC40gBh9wg3xzEV+iLVCYdx8D9DonCMR21q0iLzf3mvlbsQqpaGes4mwfz4nT0W2Nl5kZ/22QgvBw2ozX4DoIGSSlhWjUHFG8lH0AZuCboSAYTUsnmelGKQTHMbetz4DK2J12xH3OX4jWh8s4NOVIKKbBDVmcov3AKlCPJ3RifsrI78L/lVHmts7rp0iv+0u8/7evXkIGQ9Lxu5Xa9f5plXYQ53UR/VAC1dILSrUZwSAe9N3nzNlhNBSHFaSxrl7+gBTkSr6snNb2TNI74aThvsZbwXEMf2SQfONvKm3T7dB72VmU6qRgQkQD7dMaII8wL+boX8I1O8lW5t+sjkPkIbQpEYMWfyd3+wq6TDCQMjcCIhaJ5Pf07HCxwhkz/PZ/hyma8PYhE5WOioCxAYkxZDmj3GB1ZC8FgWWqy/AEAzK71QNFQD1HexBLQWWQ+ExD1/KtL5MLSFurjyrpsliCg=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "To prevent a court from exceeding its jurisdiction", 
		"option_b": "To enquire into the legality of a person's claim to a public office", 
		"option_c": "To transfer a case from a lower court to a higher court", 
		"option_d": "To command a public official to perform their official duties", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080109", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRomqXWqxmeWXqUbSCbezwiYN5Ihyen1JvsnnA45Xi+FsGjaFP4IGRMCAGPoJ828WM06T2w3BIPdVQxcJ2FntFaEGmpLzoeDekIxVY", 
		"answer": "25+tbJjw2Bjmt4QuVl7j0PzsPCbaFmYYoHaCXuN1ZWXrW7XLeuT72tWlLjEtnUplEadhP/LMcKvs", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHkwxD+t4omEi7gyvX2N2LECm0f43yCXON2dTHqR7TXa+m+yJBwLlKamRtx53LPoKzx+xMOgawb+JueYytOdJ5rwdOA1ui3xWRVO8lWk5R74YlRPN1UjDS+NNWbLPtpz2LANUD9Yj2kRGVnkTWWnnMWuJG0/S65Xc53zBolk5U47scpLsOMleiH+kS6kwiD0GjdCLJ2UUWMtN2hpkmJpIs7vMyB8TDU8P38ibjV4tEGIg1KvIN6Z1KykOgd8C8xQ4i+fQBC4uDZYkDkLybjKBxd+Mj333puhoAsRGY68F9SioZfcIB/05/lsHIxKtliGiGzt10Oh71oHweEcau93nz3oEE3cGkuJYt4qCU6swaIIVFt2m2OQyERl49l6tkXgA1tei9XlWLowi+Zj2aKeZfq5Yfvxefi4LRi+aopLgGEMF/RRYQTa6CAM29z3qmaH6McMZp+GCzifcEm+XnqI5mE2nkC1pk0J3Lu5mqJndrwK3b6vIC5h9o2ArYPOtDR4MS58FPBIS/kJnyfJtvmUAbzRmz01h0rixYZxhUY7SLPGoBrtSIL3k6iRkxtkC70ZXOv1rdPqoyBa84lyuXl3jMclO04lojkwRg4BwW8jHZNoZDfQ1lIxEfaH9kO0gxuDrsFHZPCvi2XkXvZRXUea9z3FaGRxmxJz/f5gXN0q5kLRsDOIwubmswv3halBL1wW2Pkvo/9KP0ZGSQj6PJzxemostn1NdqwbGw5LwmnXOxQ9ZxSaQ53CEvcDClKZPivQt0TQOlBxnTDmQ5GQD9dDV+M8qYcWAO4o9DRLmXYI6UUC17odrcMEMf5QgffJ/6qzSPaRr6SkQe7UVcwXDOTJvAZ7QbkOobnIBqwmmlouc73ckBORZAecS3mcGK6rKKPSwcvayQqOoNTc0LGCx80kSzCM/wnmq4UeBEjAbyvHBAVmR9JljDXHRhKtgwKV6DtTFIwZOsNZdw+E4/c8I7HuUYYkJfF", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Judicial and quasi-judicial authorities", 
		"option_b": "Legislative bodies", 
		"option_c": "Administrative authorities", 
		"option_d": "Private individuals or bodies", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080110", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MU0Whuy0u/2ISvfBSIgtnDOZaJmYnDtQKiCb+TziYN+Z0ybiE1+/GKZ4eiq87P9uPl9sTidPL8EeI4=", 
		"answer": "24CrfYPj0A3j+ItgXRiy1ej9OWLTQ20XpXaAV+HTEwEM96J01BdW2tyfwpH+", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHkwxD+t4omEg/nyr3oNHnCAmwFrD+CW65nMGXsFLfQa/v7x4MxM1SMzU5o52TWorH5+F1PgK4b+ZudfCsAPoRpztmK0qq37WUBOtUEm8Be5Y4WcrRQxC+sZ9GbNPZv2i6NIkT+dHmBRnJt1Cbei2gWv4Kp5ya1QIULgltyv5M45Nt8PZeIy6GHqESrlROH2DuTUf1lUVeWoNy8q1eT4IN4pcifoj3VtOPxlbja454DbQRWtoh4I1r8h70L9CM7EceybhtI9KTHaEDlLz23Zx4P9tvmxDRo05YhUns94AYIwrdeZ4BkxJHw/CA1LthjBzap41BIwtRsWgWFe7P4xGek810wYjooZJ9+uW0iqRbcPFx7gyuPRCNEmIQr8N8N1QZmPX1FkXn2hzvLhneAcdPs7Yb1hu2+nLdf/JcvLAGXJ1XMFoIaJaLVKCdly/uJDKhIPN9uBGLzLtAqvC32YIaG2i8I3s1gP3Lo5Cac0svnNmj6u531it14E/8QI9PJ4Mj3v1rBaCDkYXSfas7zWAT8VjK4+holtBkriCMVqHfLDY0/4SJNnXaxRUhhnCDlLGipk/5d+pKBdoAl3vDiyXIfnrR534vyxg4zSUSvgj9C8pSKTVBGzhTZGMsOxwxiTLsTVILesm6elHrcTnIKeo7iCa3HwCNGzur/m2R5/4QLW5mcKVnUjJ4niAe0E+52WyfkpsbpKP4ZA2ds9bR3w+6k+Yi/RHaWrJ/loVqgWjAuWngI", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Arbitrary detention", 
		"option_b": "Violation of contractual obligations", 
		"option_c": "Usurpation of public office", 
		"option_d": "Excessive exercise of jurisdiction", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080111", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRj444wjXhuywPDvOnzVEXFRk36RXqp1fXTtQOfWYa3szIRlNVWKmRt04DbHobf/8FIbiuhd/ICbcS8GcJ9uxJCb3uP/0GIBNclW2oN39o4edfoAyy+iYcTIf7yeqB8Wh1OWE8nYN6ezx8ZM", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNZi16I4RHX6AeQnFS1kaVY1OQ==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNZgXRiy0fX6dULeB2sQrT+gXa1nZHj3QbPLYeO+zJphKEuMn0g7wnfUr6zx+lYBm+hP5s6NdTEXbIJs3JCGxaT2xmNONMdQn8B08ZQbfflFwimseJTJKflm2n3AIUriJzq4FmR1nT+WjW5ZvZOouWeoRN80yRM7lYZ04dF8MdKS262B+w23gEaW1H7RSa9pFFDZs8G66EaP7MIotN+MvDvX/eD4iOGT9tEZYQ1B88Z+bV/8h6cF8Sk9Ec67ehFO4qqQXVrRLhyrLh1d6dnswH16z40nHWg4+BBRkcNQbdIz2pHptSYxK8RlGyD6rEoA05x5HxKOca+72XvhoFo5NXw+a45ssSg7tQ6QaEZ3nWOIX2xTjcB/9tUKkERkb2BVjGWglTeOjiWbdJb6q4HugKjjpat1+60gaUiOdVPKFp0Zd7XPNWp7xO7bCbNIOpp0VyHpM9sr/y38JNaD1i0FkM0oKjfm5ieclo3zNne5toG5gcY2G6sIM8OF78Sls1nUITfpIGnTYMr4VUjlQXj9wU5xvx1lyTQE4G3KAZ1mtSIL3mq4TARnlyn0fn2t1rlT/IeccYM03eGinQYYnbR5lpa33Q58Uwv7iHFQp5aaD1hG3lffDsEOygxuDboFVJvQ+2OClH/eC2gFeo7zB66CwDhBzOb/i3Ju/58IFZiGKQreytgp2hS0ErM75uU3Zsb2uvFzMhHZyeNDvA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Article 32", 
		"option_b": "Article 35", 
		"option_c": "Article 33", 
		"option_d": "Article 44", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080112", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhHwz/j8IWLGBiITpneKXKc0d2PiWrPLYOq+3Z90Z0yGml5psmPIp6Dit3Idm6FY5YvfI3FDaoQv+NGb2+32yXRPJ5kGi9SDH6D9Ph89pCrL+pG+eA==", 
		"answer": "25C2e4Th1Fn65YowVwyywfTsNmPREWUU43CFEqdhZHjmR+fDYOm+xJZ4KUiMg1p18XOGrKOw81ocjKFL5YeRdWCWSDcLsaRgYleN2bJ7UCGb", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH80xPv9JEpRBuyx/j3PGXUQ2UDonGXW61zMGXrUefSYfr729dkKViMnxta4GLPoKn1twBcz7xUqb6eYi4Kf4ZqxsTJ3ve30H4BPsdNlJRz7ZRfeP1TzzS9eN3VJb5vwGrAIkvjciu4RGR8kXHTjHpTq5ey4yK1UckkgBo01pNw6Ig9Ltqa3eiV51+7gxXOnGuQWrxpGFiQoc+68gOar5A7sN7B8TPV8LTplfTa89tLZAdAvINsLRuAmZQH0T54Q823ZxVF+P7VchT5KCm3ZwcTucjmxGBoz4xpTmAg4R5Si4xYcYwzwpDh/CEkLcRpAXO7rUAAzplxWhOfdam9kGn08Fk2dns/bIVj/CIz4QmJJlB/l26SWC1d1JJi+dgNhkRufHYAnnOgizGIj2iffYfq6Yz5xf/5tLEj5qsiaVOFJEnRRIgRYL3UNCd9zKmWBKpVJ551DmLpL5U+/Sv4LZ+Y1i0MwsBgPHL14iOal436KyWqvJ7wjdE2EKoUL5/55/e5kkWHYC/tLmqaaMy0aQniQ3X53gtro1gxx2EC7XHMGoB84W0CjD6xS1ZrlSb0aTyng7BY64+LcZow37X+1DUYjOc4mZTllAk0Qhe+zXhRvZGPXBxL2EbfEMpH0AErBaZBB5PD5GSVkDqQX3QIP+35D7uTyjhdzur+gCFuupUFRsyaI1nInswvwxLxAL17VGvspoX8ff4QHnMp/7wxw+OlvtyycealICU4Zh2/TfwZ8ptVKBZzFEveCihDZbu6X4sbAelBxnDYkhRcVD9GAxrC+rwBUgqrpoTba2nLcbgIF17jbbdFA9v6Qk7Mdf67zDXbSP377c6GrxLxiBi2GD7nYxgs", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Protect fundamental rights", 
		"option_b": "Ensure proper discharge of duties and maintenance of discipline", 
		"option_c": "Enhance legal privileges", 
		"option_d": "Facilitate civilian oversight", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080113", 
		"question": "24KwZ9H70Aqq440lEg790vjtdX/fQ28QqHrDXqJjYzH2WqPHfK3f24N4JFCMzQgorTReRkUMMnrzn0SW7st5QS5L", 
		"answer": "24W5ep360BTv+ZFiWGPZDHsaPTaGwjqoTyEa9g==", 
		"explanation": "24C2bJThkTj444wjXhuylq6/Om2QF2oU41aNVqp1fjHAW6nReuTq3IN4KFLFzU9z9zbWrLL15RMbgOhW6IWaMC4CaZgv3N/JxeHk0GNIMNIElZIy5ZgNc/NB2DjtYNzeYPh7wGqBKkD+czixRGJ9kznCmTxZrsO28Cq5UcgkgBo01pNw6Ig9Ltqa3eiV51+7gxXOnGuQWrxpGFiQoc+68gOar5A7sN7B8TPV8LTplfTa89tLZAdAvINsI1+phaEH/2osWc29elJY9PbGaFfoYCSqIh1d7sL33jR9zodpbWgm+BZHj4ZYdoB80NjNsjY5PoMqKT2GrXRB1Zh1XhqTeqn42Gn3oEE3cDoqcJ5lsz88tRbcPFs+imqPX2xdkYdi7dwYgQ1scy9UlHf0wjiElmCdcoCj/4j5xe3otLxt5uMmJ0XAOF3WWIgOJbrOZ3B6w+qTTbJUNoxiVzDvOt0673n0IY/U3TxNwtwzO2Xu9z6clo36KyWppoHpi9pyEbtAMN7XqcayvV7CczChLnvTcsPxSg2wSXPq0At29xEriDUY7SLRBp165ygeij6/TwRgmzTjZWytn7BZqoOAe84l2/Cs2DQWnfdslo3ylBspSQevhHBNu4qYD1NJjUDeG94ChAY8C7UPHYzQ5mSZm2WeCRKoWa072uns4AOe0U8aQ8c=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "President", 
		"option_b": "Supreme Court", 
		"option_c": "Prime Minister", 
		"option_d": "Parliament", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080114", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MU0WhuywOXvJ27DEGserT/EX6Z5cnTxR+fNaK3qwZIxJk6EiF879HnUoKDjsBMMgL5e+9Hdph1TKo5P/0tPVoFE1IRcpA==", 
		"answer": "25u3Ztzw3hTo9pEhXAqywPDvOWTJBmcC43CFEqJmfXTnFKHNfO772tX91YoSFNHLPoumxltJKzMp", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH2yQn48pYzWxH8hbryMGbSBnAC43CFErd8dTHiRqrHaq34xoVyIk/OzUtp+3vHsaz87hMMgL5e+53feSwHd51mzMWI2/e303lOc8dWn8Bz544WavFM1X2+ccbNKfBpjmeOZ1H4Ynm8Fn1xkHHQhW5VrZD7+iH7VZo0zwA8gpVho4gINN6MmbyK+ES7hwqOxTuYRr5oBFCcpo6l4k+VtIMqrI2dtCDI+/r3n/ST59YEIglAusZvYkmo16cPuD4wVIimbRVe/eXCIVv/YDqmNAsP786j0Ht7xYc6HWg68F9HkIYWcdVx3J3nqHIkMI1nHD+zt0VS3tR4VgSVfa202WbhoFQxcTokd45orj574SaIaFFwmWSRXC1Ch4V4vtMWmAZiaW5OiDbwhy2Yj2uBeZ+vq4Hvxf/1rLUj87BnJ06OeF/XW48dcbLOMyd3x/mXAr9ZNownGCSmKd0rvDjrLZOQnz8CwtolPDun4yKW0sD0ICWqoZ3vh9BzVKkBJNjK/Nj3o0nXcSzzNT2Vc8X3TQH/QW+27wBZuTExiCUf7XGYBoZrtSoIkHuiSEhoi2fjY2qkhP5O75aHbYs1k+PpyTcCmfpr35TllB41UQ23hH5N8oeQQUhdzFfCEd8UhB4mA/QABpOR/GKC1XfTX3UbesLvQbuC0TpB1OSxh289q5gLFY2cIRzfytgp2hS0ErM5fWj6rZD8L7BVHmwpurdpy+6199m4euOhbGQka1q+V/tc4YVDbRZ6BQLSC2RAZvi6XpQNAfRKwHiKlAZGB2lIF0OM/boHUESlpMGIbWXLbaUOF1nxI78AFM/0DlTWJuWsxXDdCf+dm0iqV0E3AnqcL7RN9hf1eYX0LRDzn2lz6oHqIBFJQYQCMCbnfWS3tuOOCh96eykjIYRCOk7BCx0rhjuDN+tijq4TdRQ0D+qvFmZrCfGqqAQYSc8yODDP", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Non-combatant employees of armed forces", 
		"option_b": "Medical personnel", 
		"option_c": "Retired veterans", 
		"option_d": "Civilian contractors", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080115", 
		"question": "2523f9Hw0Beq9sUwUwz+zPzyMGXEAnAI43OCReNxfnDgQKLGLvjwzZJjZ32bmVJ4/nOG8Paw9lUJiqtPqY2QZTAXPoZu2sSA1ui3zmRTOtVAk4Nm7ZURI7av9vhNAnU/N1VajLEYCFa5", 
		"answer": "25Cga53m1Ryq9Io1QAqyyPztIWLRDyIXsXCOErRmeWWjXrLQZ/76wJRlLlOHzV104DbDraP/5VAKgq1V/c6QdmIla4Vryd2M2fD2yDFzOsFMjpMwZZks0tM3AXBKU4qXDlOOZg==", 
		"explanation": "25T4eJDh3RDr+oAuRh/g3L3zNHyQBmwQoGuGVuNhfnXmRufjfPn3ypt0Zw/azVh6/DbDu6b84lcKz6tU/JyLMC8CbJ9mydzJ0fb4yTFVO8MEjZJ78NoVaeZJ3zmkd8DSL/AuwWjAM031JwqoFGJxmTSWqXNDupf79Cm/FNI+xx1ylYht/9wvfMCWzaDT+ki/hxSGnG+eCKlsFBScu8in+UCZrYc2oY2Ct3L94fr9m/XW/soKbkhgtoF3d0j+sUtxtz6KLT9EVvXAwOF0Cw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Expand court martial jurisdiction", 
		"option_b": "Merge court martial with civilian courts", 
		"option_c": "Limit court martial powers", 
		"option_d": "Exclude court martial from writ jurisdiction for enforcement of Fundamental Rights", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080116", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MUBQAr7xvH6dTiEQ2ccs3CUV7E0ZHnmFJfDfOH3yJp0KUjJmVQ79nmGp7Di/l0Iz6Va+5qWcS5Dcop4l5Jdp1aNUOv5z8RDL8obetIy", 
		"answer": "25y2bJT+3xDs7sUnXQj31/PyMGXEQ3EUsWmCXLdnMHfsRufDbfntiYV0K12diF875nmGrLf08kFPgqlS55qafiMNfY4tMY92Gn71pb/kUlwXmMs3UQ==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNFgVxPiyur6J3iQF2oU40+CQK99cXzmWrOCeuK+wJl1IlGHhF1isnHJtaDi+V4Kgbwb+ouNZiMNapgvx8LJ1uruhGFEIdVLlMB064hfffdU332pe9reYPdgjm2PKUv1ZC20C340gzjCgjxCoIb7+CayWs4yzhQ8lYI44tp8LtKMzaeB6VmxiQjC033RR69gFEbZsdu64k2b4I85p9mEsD6b+PXu2Nuor4OxcHo0lZ0PmSEq+Sk=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Restrict fundamental rights", 
		"option_b": "Indemnify government servants for acts related to order maintenance", 
		"option_c": "Suspend martial law", 
		"option_d": "Challenge fundamental rights", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080117", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MU0WhuyxvLxNm7AFyIepT+OU7FgeXDvFKvDea33xId9PgPL4D/8QSgODlV6X7dYnrG6Tg==", 
		"answer": "24ate4H23wrj+ItgXRiyyu/7PGXREXtRr36UEqJ6dDHiUKrLYOTt3YVwM1WGgxt56zbLqqn541Idluha/JqXfzAKaoJq25LBJZGwGfLpiD9+s6cFxk/C", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3hfp8pU0EhH0hfD+J3/ZAm5Rr36UEqp5YH3qUbSCeuX7iYRkNEyMg0hy/XiGrKOw+EELhqZa+5fffCMUPophzJCd3+G3xXVMOshNiZRg5Y4Wc/oAwzvtd93NKfIuz2iGJkzidHm/HTB5nT3fnn1EscO64DOzW8g+1Bw3hcd57sszLtOW16/T/EL4kg6H1WnRR6pqUUaMucu7q0yJtJExscjNpTretPvrnvHd8cwSIgRXuIdzI12ulqUM7yUqWorSGWEr7jj64PiepKI+eUz3", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Suspension of ordinary law and administration by military authorities", 
		"option_b": "Establishment of new legal system", 
		"option_c": "Promotion of democratic governance", 
		"option_d": "Integration of civil and military law", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080118", 
		"question": "24C2bJThkQ7i9pFgVwbm1/zwJ2/ZDWMDuj+AW7F3ZXzwQKbMbejtiZRwKRyEjElv+3fK46nx4BMNiuhf7I2TcTAGetQtZsCJm/5t3CA1Rb9BM1oDgg==", 
		"answer": "24K5et2z2Bf89pYpXRC+hfTxJn7CEWcSt3aMXO80YnThUavOZ+LwhddjLlOdz0rLWdNCbslUyi0kbnzy7XY=", 
		"explanation": "25i5eoX60BWq+4Q3Eh3zy739MCvUBmEdom2GVuNhfnXmRufHdvnsyJhjI1WHjElisnXPsabl+kAbjqZY7J3fYzcAdstu25Ce1va7hHhPJcdXk498qNoWcudV3i+od8DSL/AijnyFJUD8azCyCjw0hjjZnjAWp5H74y60WN851FUgk5Rx/tw9MtSambycqEG5kURNTuOtXPxakofkFpdmETCC", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Natural disasters", 
		"option_b": "Economic crises", 
		"option_c": "Political campaigns", 
		"option_d": "War, invasion, insurrection, rebellion, riot", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080119", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7n1+3wJm6QDGRRgm2XW6B4dTGwAefLYK3szJtwM1WGgxtv/TbAtqv09l4Kgbxa5c6NeSULapgwivKTJcAFuLMCxKEm0BrEEyw=", 
		"answer": "25C2e4Th2Bftt5AuWxj91/D2IXKQCmxRt3eGEq11ZGTxUefNaK343Jl1JlGMg096/jbUqqL440BPjqZfqZ6KfisQdoZqxsTJ0evlhHhPNdRNlId36Z8RaLZ77xl+8j8k8pfaav7b3gGk", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNBgVxDh0O/6JivEC2MF43CNXro0ZHnmFJfDfOH3yJp0KUjJhVposmLOpuXg+EQKnehP5s6ScSkGPodu38PJw+u3w3hXNoZBnIZ3545faPsAzzi/YNXSLr5o22CEJkj1aS28CDBmnTbenm8a6ISu9DW6Ws4yxRw8kcdt48E6M8WS0LyKqES2xgCX0n+QRbhqBVWV9dyh7EuIs8I5u8nNoSfV/efxl/3d5M1LYwtAsJVsI3Kyk6EIujw3nhF9FiDZm0C/enJM3WQ=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Establishing new fundamental rights", 
		"option_b": "Defining state-specific fundamental rights", 
		"option_c": "Simplifying legal procedures", 
		"option_d": "Ensuring uniformity in the nature of fundamental rights and punishment for infringement", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080120", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRbst5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRrn6XRqZmYzHqR+fsQdm+zJphKEuMn15/smLJ46f1t18KiKFI5Y+LdSZDfJIv3NiMl/fjxWVEc8pBnYlh6JsLaeZF332sd9fUMvpnwGnAM0qwRiupDXN4kXGF3yMUKl2XZ068TevoMTP9klmUKw==", 
		"answer": "25C1eJ7k1Avj+YJgURHn1+nsdWTEC2cD42uLU600ZHnmFJTXfv/7xJIxBFOcn08783jC46358FtPjKdO+5qMMCQMbMtp3d6N1unyymVAP4ZWk4d68IlfefpGwy+ucdneLuospa9O1U/Xg2Hkland3kQptw==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNBgVQzzy+nsdX/YBiIhom2PW6J5dX/3FLPKa63uxoB0NRydght2833D46nx4EBPna1X6JqadGIXcctqxcCGwOHlzX9Gc8VLj5Jm99pXc+BIyS/tYNzaLr56xmvAFFDgdTywATBXmyTEnjxXpof7/S68XJo0zwAggpQxrdwzfN6Myr2WqEmxlAOByHKeRq4oUVuLscu6+A/coYw89dqfuCbItPL2iLjV5dAPYwVXsZJ+bxuunq8B7Dl4VMayZwBI9OnVb0CvGDAdf/oKwn10FfzlpzN2Jg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Prescribing residence for employment", 
		"option_b": "Restricting fundamental rights for armed forces", 
		"option_c": "Empowering courts other than the Supreme Court and high courts for fundamental rights enforcement", 
		"option_d": "Indemnifying during martial law", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080121", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEgz31Oj2J27dBmwF43mMQON4cWbwFK7MLuvx25R0Z12dzU9z9zbFrKj98l0MiqVe55rffyRDaoNqiPOG2ffjzWVUJ89LlMBn6p4abrRh3imkd9jeYK07kSy+AWTqZvZEl0SIUVAXDZDJ", 
		"answer": "24GwbYiz0hbk44wuRxuyzPO/M2TCAGdRtnGXW680cX33UbXHaqG+25JhIl2FiF83snnU46T98l0Liqwb65ffQCMRcoJuxdWHw6ZstVF7h8UjYdgQidiBZTFZ", 
		"explanation": "25m5f4Kz0hbk9IAyXBf8wr3rPW6QDmMFt3qRQeNnYHTgXaHLa+m+wJkxBk6dhFh39zaV9uXk/1Ibz6lJ7M6WfmIFcZlszZCIw6TjzHQBINJFiJQy65xfaPxFjB6iesfPKep72mePKQXzaDepDX5hkXHChTxUrcO+8yG+V84+1hByg4ls5MR8KN+amZiS+kGxhwuH0m/RRbxvFEfZtsap5USZs8Isuo2ZuTfWtODxiPfG99ZLYwRGupR+d1KzmbtFuDg9Qc21ZAEHsevCIVXgJSanKgsT7dihwQeUFFdXaBjUHjPLADe/Fw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "They continue in force until altered, repealed, or amended by Parliament", 
		"option_b": "They become part of the Constitution", 
		"option_c": "They are nullified by the judiciary", 
		"option_d": "They require state legislature approval", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080122", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t5EoV1791/T4PGXRDyICt36XR7A0f3ejQK/HLv/3zp9lZ0iGzUtp/WbDsbHpt1oBz7xT7M68fywQaoJ73cSA2Oq3y3cBGshAk4EtpnVxxQByr4WfffrM2hRw+ro=", 
		"answer": "25q2bdH811n+/4BgVAv8wfzyMGXEAm5RsXaEWrdnMGTtUKLQLt3/24MxDnWgzwgzB1e5ZZtnMCBrRDZ/UuQ=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH8wxDt/oshXl7h0fzrIHiQDGRRt3eGErF9d3n3FLPNLv3sxod0NUiQzVJ1smLOpuXT+F0cm6FP/JqWfyxDcY0v4d6N3uW303BSc9JMm5Qy7Y5fa/VTjDKjcZTUJr56xmvAIVD+YziwAX5glT2WmHVRoJeotTK1UN8lgCUzhJM4xOEVfNiZmbyb7Q2biQiRyHKFXaltHlrX9ee8q1Sds8I3p8SKuDza+Pjg2vHd89IeZg1W/4dsI1r8kb0H/Cs1VMagaR4L4+3XaUCtKSbjBhwJ8Mjv0zQ6l85pSmE99xcGhZZXcMF9wp3huHIkN8gqBzq9q1AA05s8XhSHYbSq1SSk6FozcTZrZIRp/Ck8sh+TO1E+lW3cXD5ehIV56slXqQpfc0dPi3P2hy3HwHGHedPx4of0kajkr/lz4Kw3LFOULBzNWIkZd6TFKXMy2eCcA69aOpxmGTamPt0v8j78M9aA1ysCxd4ob3To+jmNm9ngLWy1vZP1ztV7EbEEO9TL/dj58GjPZGO1dWmbJur5XAb0Qnn2x05EtAxpiHBJvzqUSItt+jgKlmrwSEZrhzOgbTysl7RT+MKPc5o0wfT41D0e2PZh34ny2RIqTgq8zWtLt8SNRltH2RTCEY0X1gY+CaYVDdbQ4S2X1XDFRXgMcsv4FamLgz5B3evlzmBzu9AcUI+CLQrIg9g/wRm2QfRtFWb+6Ie5MfkSC2hs6Lt2wvnv9/6zfODkLWgvYR66XOFNs5BXbgd4BQLLAChWIKqrRYkMSONb13GKgw9NB2xKCkrJu6cOHRCir4TaZ23Wd/EIAV7ycbwVFtzsVwuPMPy5wDHaD6WVm0D+S0wgDjOQMb8f8Qb+eYmyKxXzgGdn8MDpclBVQMMSPyj9e2awpuOMCQw/fDgsPo9UOkjDTgJknTDHLu9uibIBfFg9U6e3HEICj1FdljnaGksL8sx8RCLLgXaq4W9YgcQPjLY=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "One of the fundamental rights under Part III", 
		"option_b": "A constitutional amendment", 
		"option_c": "A legislative power", 
		"option_d": "A non-citizen's right", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080123", 
		"question": "2523f9H32B2q440lEkqm0fW/FGbVDWYcpnGXEoJ3ZDHsUueTN7qmiZZ3IVmKmRtv+nOGsaz3/0dPm6cb+ZyQYCcRapIwinC9D4KhPQQQ9CD15vmqyVg=", 
		"answer": "25S6Z536whHv88U0Whuy1/T4PX+QF21Rs22MQqZmZGijVbSCb6343Jl1JlGMg096/jbUqqL44xEp8NM4npTG8QsRbFkEEGIA", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGnhQ3it6QtVxD2yPjxISvxAHZRrHnDA/ojKDHiVqjOZ/72zJMxM1SMzUly9X7S47H/t0MdgLhe+5qGMCMQPoovzsWH0+X6wX9VMsoEiIl17I5fdfoA2DWoNP3VJPdvwC6jKEvjczCpEWR9mz+YykxEoYyptTO0FM4/yQZyl4p948wxOdmLleiH4Ej4lA+F1G/RXLIkAUaWpcu6/1rct4Mr9cKDtHLU8rTtkv2T9ssFZglfuohrYlf8haEO8D4rEc+haQBK//DVZFCtNSanIhxd2Nn333dlw8J6DCk78l9SioYWQc99xYztqCckNsJkW3OGrXhO75trWgGTZvH4xGDhoAFrYXJrRIdosik4pAGIaHV9jiuOSS9dlZN499YQkAAjaWdF3GTphTefwHGAPIPx5JD5l/zp4LhwsqJnJUSHNFCYRIQbbaeMZ2J0zOyYGa9KNpN+VzDjMNo49Tf+YJ+Anz8f39RgO3/itCaQgdm1NmP6tYf3itV7EbEUN92F+8KwuEjUL2PVKXSAJsr5XAb0Qnn2x053sgsx2igT/GfcSJ138G0enXGgTARrlGfwfnOxk6xI88Kcdok5x+as1DxQsfp8lpq31RM4BwG2nXdCoY2FSlgP2VzTXsQK1AY8GLUPF5OR/WvWhnnTQn0BP8/4BeiCwCNG1e74jSFyvZoLVpiHOhzIytEwzQXxCPN9XHHkrJP4MbwFGGs8/6Bl062zvs2zYeDqblllfMjXIJbuZgcxLazhSfI=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Abolished the right to property as a fundamental right", 
		"option_b": "Extended property rights to non-citizens", 
		"option_c": "Created new property regulations", 
		"option_d": "Established new exceptions to property laws", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080124", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5EoV177yO3zPGjRF2serWzDXaU0ZHnmFLXLaeXqiYN+Z0ybgkt+4GLf46Tjt1JPg61c6ILfYisEdp8wiuCVrhJaOcMiIo5gFnA5EzY=", 
		"answer": "25ysKJLy31no8sUyVxnnyfzrMG+QFGsFq3CWRuN1MHLsWrTWZ/nr3Z5+KV2FzVp293jCrqD+4xHt3Rc/dF/2t+UrzK9p07vd", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHh2B7i48U0XV7i1/LvMHnEGi5RomzDU+N4dXbiWOfQZ+r23dsxJF2HzVl+smTDpLD89kcKi+hP4ZyQZSULPoR9zNmH1vbuhH1ENM9XloFm7ZURPONJ2DWiYcCbIb5twWCTM0zkci20C351mHHXh3lYrI6++zP1FPMjgBwh1pdq4tw5P8Oa3eiS70yxiBWWnHqDSrRwA1WLrI6k7kSVs445ocSbtHLa9+DwlfbAsNwedkhWsINsI1Wzg+gO6is2RYiwYQBO8vCQYFfuJTuwZxoSud/r0zRa05I7WGQxtDxJl5FCIsZ8xNjhsjQ/Lc5vGDa0twoA+5pAUSOefa743G3j4Vl/Z3MsbZ4tvT0lrQaZOxRqlSueQzhZ1INi6tkDkApwPW5OmDbujTHGg2ybdYnm5ZOwxf/5tLEj4bMiKkiGPF+YRp8TdbbSM34/2OyXDLJZN99rFjX1fcMv7iDwLpHU3Tge1d1gIHmn3SSdm8z7eXe/tIf1j8B/G7ETdtDL7Yunv1DOYirkMjPRKt4DDWNBItNxpskANPSkhw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "It is protected against legislative action", 
		"option_b": "It grants direct access to the Supreme Court", 
		"option_c": "It can be regulated without a constitutional amendment", 
		"option_d": "It applies only to citizens", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080125", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ39+MUjUw331r3vJ2TGCmYU437DVbZ1YnDtQKLHaq3swJB5Mxydght4/XvWpqvj9kcGgKYb4IDfcyMQe8tgzpCI1PXizWJIJ89LlMB99toNeeVVxS6kYN3ULr5hyC6QNUzmZi24RGBmmyHTmGhP6IGitTOzUZok1BQmk9g6MChBSr/4/OcX8LmP1y2HvQ==", 
		"answer": "25S7eYT6whD+/oouEhH0hfD2O2TCCnYI43qHR6B1ZHjsWqbOLuTw2oN4M0mdhFR1tWWGs7f/51Ydm7Eb6ICbMC4CcI8v39md3+35hGJVMtJRjo9g/docef1MxTOqNNjSLfd63SwyYMOvCHX1L5n+hr+4ngNX", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHj0Ar59oIlEhP3y+n2OmXDQ3YZomvDUax5YHTtR6bWZ+LwiZ9wNBydght59zbWoqz0t1oBz7xM5s6ccTEGbdEv39iM2aTjzHQBINJFjoUy5ZkOaf1SyS7tYNzeYO58wX6FNVHpJza7RHE0mTjYhW5fvJr78COuV9sjyRo8l4s45MYvKN6LzLya50P4zieQyHKSRLgkQgTQ9c+m7wOLqIc29dmFtHLI4PXtn7jS888eaxpXrMZzYlW416AM9C54U9H0aVJb9PbDblqtNSanIhxd6c7xxXtnx45pXnw44BZQg5dfbc4zwZHwtDs+f95+FCevt0tS3tR/Wh6afbO/kGTt7VwrZjpjRJh5tS45pE/PeXU32KBwiZEZZ47hhBKiyfA+FCY=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Acquisition of agricultural land and urban property", 
		"option_b": "Acquisition of minority educational institution's property and land within statutory ceiling limits", 
		"option_c": "Acquisition of non-citizen's property", 
		"option_d": "Acquisition of commercial property", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080126", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kQ3i8sU0Vwz/1r32OyvzDG4ErnHDc+NjeWXrFLPKa+TsiZR+NU6Mjk879nPVoLf550cGgKZIqYeRMAEMcp5ixpCrlcq7iOpGjn+tMRlRlqBBp0M=", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNQBElOy9/jsMHnGBnFRr36UQeNyf2OjRLXHfeT6zJllLl2FzVh0/GXPp6Di9kcGgKYXqc6+YjYKfYdqiIPY9aS6hFRZNstUjpMy6JsIb7RG3jKgNNLOLvpvw2uOM0T8Jyu0A3hgh3HVgn1apIa18iKoGJoW0gE7lYt9rZttH5fSmZiB51m9hRKRnHiUWqllGFrZsce67kCIqZQ99d2fuDzY/eT1n+ufsPc5Iitduop3bBu/lrsMuGd4Y924bRYL8OPRaFr+NGihKw8T8s73ln1ky5cnVH0ttBlJkMN4a85n3tjXvzo1O9hmEHO2olNThVbZyZ0E6l1X8meLR6+YFvs=", 
		"explanation": "25T4e5j03xDs/oYhXAqyz+j7PGjZAm5RsWqPW61zMGPmWKbWa+m+3ZgxM1SMzXVy/GLO45bz/1YLmqReqYGZMDYLe8tGxtSA1uq3535PINJNjpVm7ZURNMZFyji/cdrYJb5Cz3aNLk7xaS39Bn97n2uWrGlYrIK28CmvVdZ38hw1npNrpIo0uVyyi+nwj7sv1SOQtBjf", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Article 31A,Reserves laws for presidential consideration", 
		"option_b": "Article 31B,Exempts laws from fundamental rights challenges", 
		"option_c": "Article 31C,Protects certain directive principles", 
		"option_d": "IR Coelho case ,Ruled against blanket immunity for Ninth Schedule laws", 
		"quiz_type": "match", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080127", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0hj+8oIvQBf31r3wMyvcAnUC436RV+NncWfmUOfEfOLziZR5JlCFiFV89zbTraH15RMunbxS6oKaMHFSX8tgzpCd3+G3535PINJNjpVm7ZURI7akYIBbKJrtC4DYm0Tt7F9Y", 
		"answer": "25m5f4Kzwxzm9pElVl7myr3zNGXUQ3AUpXCRX7A0cX/nFK7Mavjt3YVoZT0xSFdXKhgwErakFfRTpYc=", 
		"explanation": "24C2bJThkTj444wjXhuylqzedWTWQ3YZpj+qXKd9cX+jd6jMffn33YJlLlOHwRtv+nOGoKTk8lQAnaFe+s6QdmIPf5x8iMSB1vC3xWNEc9VFjIV2pJwNc/kAzzWseNjeLvlrjm+SIgXgdTCwBWJ9mCiWmHlaqZe+8WevW5o7wRs21pV968cuMcTf2KaXqE69lBKD1XXRW7JnGFWV9c+m7wOZo402usCEsnLW8fXqj+rW45BLVgBXrIM/alW/m70N/Wo0UN+nKABO/eXEZFCtNCf5GwAh9+rgx2Fg1Ys9VGY6tBBAwoZFdsFn04ukvTw0f99vGTKupkAA1Z17VwOFOP2x3mvo9VE2e31raYtjuG0npAmTOllt1FeSbylYmIll+ZAWm0Rien1Jn2PsliqZgWnPdJzv74nygvu+nLdW4KEmJwGMNFLcFo4ZbL/JKWAyy+efTbRZNIprFjbvMttgwDfVIYGHnzAAwNUlInLp4COXlY3RMHe/sIbwmNE2JK0JONLM+ceyoxzIZ2PSNXyHY4vEVgT5TGW0kx11shsszigT6W7UEcle5zkEnXK1CRc92iWpLH2vkv4U6cvCP5k52vbknSIViuB5lpW3wBJ8QhWuhGtCsIiaD1hG3kDEF88S0AAhAvQOEtbD936ZgGTTTm9NfsDyQbiVxjpN1Pf4gW89sJZOVoOALxzVnswn3B6+D712Uyf6rYf1KfRbSMe7acJjWKuARrynBo6MaK8=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Laws promoting personal liberties", 
		"option_b": "Laws related to land reforms and industry", 
		"option_c": "Laws related to international treaties", 
		"option_d": "Laws affecting religious practices", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080128", 
		"question": "24C2bJThkQ7i9pFgURH8wfTrPGTeQ2EQrT+CErBgcWXmFKvDea38zNd4KlGcg1479GTJruX64lcGjKFa5c6NdTQKe5wv3d6N0va35WNVOsVIn8AhtbtAPp3RWMjsMJ35MKS0cmprABo=", 
		"answer": "25y+KJjnkRHr5MUyVx33zOv6MSvAEWcCqnuGXLd9cX2jVbTRa+Pqi84PRWkHG7SZldVnRwIpvnA=", 
		"explanation": "25T4e4XyxRyq+4Q3Eh3zy739MCvZDm8ErXrDVLF7fTHpQaPLbeT/xddjIkqAiEw753jCprew1kEbhqtX7M7MIQNDd40vwcTJ3+XkhHNENsgEiIVh4YgJefAAyjK/NMDTJb5+3GuTLkH1aS36FzB3mz/Fg3hTuoKv/Ci1FNs5xFU6l5Q4/80/Od6J3KzT4ESrxgeRz36fXP8ZVTRGlyUisGwgIlvsdE2n", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "If it is supported by a citizens' referendum", 
		"option_b": "If it has been in effect for more than five years", 
		"option_c": "If it has received presidential assent", 
		"option_d": "If it is passed by a simple majority in the state legislature", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080129", 
		"question": "2523f9H33hz5t6QyRhfxyfi/ZjryQ2YYpXmGQONyYn7uFIbQeuT9xZIxdA2ozVJ1smLDsajjt1wJz7hJ5pqaczYKcYUwiqHsPja0KbcfJzLxOIwnF3c=", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNQCEh390/jtJivcAnUC43aNErd8dTHNXanWZq3Nyp90I0mFiBmDSvWwtUnLThF5ZHlZD4Mu", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNQCEhr7w/v6J3iQBXAerj+iQLd9c33mFPSTT633x9dlIk6Enht09DbWsark8lAbhqdVqYeRMDYLe8tpx9yF2PP+ynYBJMddwLx82JQ+buBJzzGoNIeKAr5twXiFNVawaziqFzB9mnHCgnkWhoq14S/7Z9k/xREnmoIirekuKN6c1a3TuxyaxhaQ022YTLh3UUSLutqt6FeVr4x4ocLNvTPM57TtkvnHsN8ZZ0hbsYVzdl+5k+gA9mosWc30RhtF5eyQUlflJSy2Kwtd9s2jwnxshqsnWWA1+l9ljY1Fdslnw4ztszx+f/liECC/40hB0Ic8XgWTNLS13X3q5RU5Z3UmJYllvSE5pAGbLUc+lWXcWCRU1Id58cUXkRcjcmkAin/vjj6fiWuIPJX25YT9iO3+tLhvsrEuLkmUJhLkWLESSr2AM293iuaPBaNOc5dmGSaqffQ86DD6LJPUjGgskMkyJnrm5iOVi43xPGS2oNLuh8B+VLMBIcKF+867sUjCZWP1Lj2fZ8XwGRr1SXPq3h0lthYhiCIV+nbZAYc/5iIOl3+8CUVqlmflb3OvmbNV6cKDeo8ixufpznIRlvA4j4n4whQ4Qhf7nW1MpoGcW1VAwxTXGcwOyho6TLcJFZrd92ORkGWQRHJNa8bzQa+VzDlG3vCxgWc9qZkBWY2aJRfcytgzxhOwDPh3QWbh6JTwOvQBGSpuknA12yeivU8R+vLMXIenJA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Article 31B covers laws in the Ninth Schedule", 
		"option_b": "Article 31B applies only to state laws", 
		"option_c": "Article 31B provides blanket immunity", 
		"option_d": "Article 31B includes only land reform laws", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080130", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2BT69oY0Ehr7wb3rPW6QVzAfpz+iX6Z6dHzmWrOCT+7qid8gfgvfxBtz82DD46r+t3Idm6FY5YvfI3MgIcnNiVbTdwVznLujN6u2wklx", 
		"answer": "24GwbdGngxfut6QtVxD2yPjxISvxAHZRpmeTU61wdXWjdbXWZ+7yzNcidn/Onht4/WDDsaT38hHOnV7wxxb30Zb2CacmeYdE", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGngxfut6QtVxD2yPjxISvxAHZRrHnDA/ojJjHmTLfDYOn7zddlL1nJnlh04nOGoqv0t1AAma1J6ImaMC0FPqp93NmK2+G3lyBifYZ4lLx8zY5ffuZPzTmoetHfYOpmyy6UPlX1dHmyAjB4lSbFymheqZf79iiuWN53whByhpV3+c0/KNKbmb2d7EiqxieQyHKSRLgkQgW69ci65E7ctIo3psjNozfX9eD8nrjH/54vaxpXvJJ2dV78p7oA9ikxQcSxe1JE96TjdVX5JWiTKAIU+tKjwnspx446Uik9+hxKl4dTIsxywYukrjc8PtlvEXOurARJyoRwWhqTeqmx3m+k81o8fHsnbJl5tS51pgCdJEc+m2WYDDxemIlo99UK1QVwPWBViHrpjDqPwGyBPIfr7sDMl+3xrbtv9+MoLwGUPVmYdYISdqfJM3Jmw+aVQ+Rzo9PVkR7pzok98ghT+iAl", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "The 42nd Amendment Act restricted Article 31C's scope", 
		"option_b": "The 42nd Amendment Act removed Article 31C's protective nature", 
		"option_c": "The 42nd Amendment Act introduced Article 31C", 
		"option_d": "The 42nd Amendment Act expanded Article 31C's coverage", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080131", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRrr5IBgWxDm1/L7IGjVByIFq3rDUax6c3TzQOfNaK25y5ZiLl/Jnk9p53XStrf1sBMAiehP4Yvfcy0NbZ9m3MWd3uv5hHBPN4ZNjpMy7ZcPffdUjDKjNN7OJPdtx2+MZ1f1cTC4Ey82AihlivwKwYbRQNAIX1a6SQ==", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHY1Arr4YQuUxD2xL3dPWrCAnYY41yCQaY2//G7QeW+2L4p5ama+BHOjA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHY1Arr4YQuUxD2xL3dPWrCAnYY41yCQaY0OCC6A/SLLuTw3YV+I0mKiF87tXTHsKzzt0Abnb1Y/ZuNdWVDf4VriNGF2+vgwXUBMM5Flox36p0ab7RUw32hdcPIYPdgjnqIIgXebjepDDBHlznTjmlarcOy82evXN8ugAM7mYt5+c04fNGK16yS5Ui2kgeOnGmYT7VwAhSWp46840bco402ptmEpSfP/fv33euTt9wKcQFR/5VrcU6/g70b/W16mX8+wOBK/8QsHHBuUtwPoQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "The Minerva Mills Case", 
		"option_b": "The Kesavananda Bharati Case", 
		"option_c": "The Coelho Case", 
		"option_d": "The Zamindari Case", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080132", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzwQvl4YwzWxH8hfL5dUrCF2sSr3rDAfJXMGbiR+fKa+H6iYJ/JFOHnk9y5mPSqqr+9l9PhqYb/YaaMAkGbYp5yd6I2eD2hFNJMtRFjoky55sMeasC+hcI/RFa6clXpr4nyHHglw==", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHg1Brl+YFgQgz90/TsPGTeQ3IDpmmGXLd9fnajWKbVLvzrzIRlLlOHhFV8sJ9sw4s6Pf8Q908/li6k2qc=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHg1Brl+YFgQgz90/TsPGTeQ20X416RRqp3fHSjB/bhIq3pwZ5yLxyZn15t93jSpqGw5kYKnLxS5oCWfiVDcY0vxNGexKTwzWdIPcEEn4Z04ZkLPOBPjD6oZsDaKfAu3mGMLkbpK3mqBWM0kDTVhn1ErYf74Cm4W9Qk1Bwmg5Nx4sY9MJX4hBsr7jpRO/kMlTg5pHIQ", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "The first provision protecting directive principles", 
		"option_b": "The extension of Article 31C's scope", 
		"option_c": "The second provision preventing law questioning", 
		"option_d": "The inclusion of Article 39(d) in Article 31C", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080133", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0gvj44wjWw3/hfnwdWjCCnYYoGzDUax5fX7tWL6CYujozJsxJluIhFVo5jbSq6Cw0UYBi6lW7ICLcS5DTIJowMSal+35hGVJNoZnlY5h8JMLaeBJwzPyNjrjfDq799xqKhn0XMnyKEM=", 
		"answer": "25Cga5TgwhD88sUsWxP70fzrPGTeECCLvu+IkXJrnfGh8S9x7RV3", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9pcnRxuy0fX+ISv2FmwVonKGXLd1fDHRXaDKev6+yph8IhyehE9zsnjTrqDi+EYcz61D6ouPZCsMcJgjiMKMxPDlzXJVOslKicwy9Y8ecP1GxT6sYN3ULu0ijm+OIwX1fymxBX51gDjZhG8a6I+y+C6vXdQwgAE6k45qrc06OtKczaGF7UO9lRXAusI8xZZAaiZnkwP3fsT4Ww==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "No social and economic rights", 
		"option_b": "Excessive limitations", 
		"option_c": "No permanency", 
		"option_d": "Suspension during Emergency", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080134", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRj554AjRl79w73rPW6QJXcfp36OV61gcX2jZq7FZvntiZt4NEjJhEg7/XDSpquw9EEGm6FY4JSadGIFcZkvwcSal+35x35MI9RBkoV895MddfhJ2CTyNm3tSQbwCIcnsq7tV6Cufm0=", 
		"answer": "24GwbdH/0Bft4oQnV17n1vj7dX/fQ2YUsHyRW6FxMGXrUefQZ+r23YQz1wFp1NPsnK+Q+we5jpkzkg==", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9pcnRxuy0fX+ISvEC2dRs3eRU7BxYzHiWqOCeeLszYQxMk+MiRtv/TbDu7Xi8kAcz45O54qefScNaopjiOKA0Ozj1zFAIcMEjIF18Z9fffpEjD6iecTXKf1v2muEawX9ZjK0Cnc0gDnThzxSoYW9/CSuWM53xhog1pNw6Ig/M9qS1qbT+EiqlQmMnG+eCKhqFVGLptqp5UfeQZzmXWjMJSeuUNkCbziBRg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "The lack of comprehensive political rights", 
		"option_b": "The absence of social and economic rights", 
		"option_c": "The language used to describe the rights", 
		"option_d": "The suspension during Emergency", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080135", 
		"question": "24KwcdH32B2q3YQzQh/mhc/wLCv7AnIerG3DQbZzd3TwQOfQa+P/xJ5/IBydhV478X7Hs7H15RMAgeh9/ICbcS8GcJ9uxJC73uP/0GIecXhKZ86aOVRFGt3t1eYrSk4=", 
		"answer": "24G3KIP21xXv9JFgRhb3hfT7MGqQDGRRr3aOW7d1ZHjsWrSCYeO+74J/I12EiFVv83qGkaz3/0cczX8fY07eSJCg4L2GVDbls0M=", 
		"explanation": "2565eJ78w175t5Y1VRn31un2OmWQEWcXr3qARrA0eHjwFLHLa/q+3Z9wMxydhV470XnIsLH540YbhqdVqYmNcSwXbctJ3d6N1unyymVAP4Z2k4d68Ilfa/xJwDjtddjIL75nw36PNEz+YHmxDX19gDDCg3NYu8O0+2evXN86gjbc7QgdPlPJ+q0CCwu7htE=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "To emphasize the importance of economic rights", 
		"option_b": "To highlight the role of the judiciary", 
		"option_c": "To clarify the provision for preventive detention", 
		"option_d": "To reflect the idea of limitations on Fundamental Rights", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080136", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz3xb+9ocsV17z1u36Nn+QDGRRhWqNVqJ5dX/3VauCXOT5wYNiZ1iGiEg75n7D4+L0+FAbnaFV7M6QdmIBf5hmy5Caw/bix2VUIcMD2oF24Igab+cfjltKih4JtTeOwpvCLCRZEsU=", 
		"answer": "25mxZZjn0A3j+ItgXRCy0fX6dWrFF2oesXaXS+N7djHTVbXOZ+zzzJllZQZl/g9WZbpQiOBsuNADfN4=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdG01Rbp45cpXBuyyvu/N2rDCmFRsGuRR6BgZWPmE+fDaunszIRiIk/JmVN+snrPrqzk9kcGgKYb5oDfZCoGPop63NiGxe3j3TFONYZ0m5J+7ZsSefpUjCmiNNXWJfBqjmGSZ0T8czyvRHNxhiXXg3IWrpa18Sa2UdQjwRlyl5Ro6MsoL5eQy+iV7UyskxSHzzueTv1wGVHZnMCs4kKS4KE3u96ZuCbO4P32lLbv/uIFIiFG/4NscF6yg6EI9CYhEcC7ZBZYsfDYYECtNyCqKwtdycrx2n1oy4cnSSk89QwGlotTItB8wZ32/CY/f8xnED2+41BIwtRfUBmFYLSsxXzt71tzNXM/JYlssiM6tU+dJEB7iCuVWD8RloF499NZhhBxaGxUiWTlzn+ciGyMdNPq5YPwkOz1s/l3+qZnL1SOMV3VU4MIZL+ANW51wv2ITadSN99zHyemOMY9+TftKZeYnz8f0dQlOHj1/2qWlI3hMWD6kJ33ncB/AKoUP97Lp4lEihnr8OEF61/VB9rBLpVK", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Limitation on the authority of Parliament", 
		"option_b": "The scope of preventive detention", 
		"option_c": "The expensive nature of legal processes", 
		"option_d": "The suspension of rights during Emergency", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080137", 
		"question": "24KwcdH33lnp5Yw0Wx3hhfv2O2+QBWMEr2vDRapgeDH3XKKCfv/x355iLlOHzV104DbWsaDm8l0bhr5eqYqaZCcNaoJgxpDB9vbjzXJNNoYWyMktpsLvO2MKBDWVNm1e5hM1xS8=", 
		"answer": "25ysKJL83x/v5ZZgUwzwzOntNHnJQ3IetHqRQeN7fjH3XKKCXfn/3ZIxJlKNzVJ19GTPraL15BMAgehS54qWZisHa4pjiNyA1eHl0GgDvkcIW0fpswVmxycGbvtiFw==", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9YAsWxvkwL3rPWrEQ3IDpmmGXLd9ZnSjUKLWa+PqwJh/Z1mEnVRs92TV47H48hM8m6lP7M6eYiAKaplu2tmFzqT2ynUBJshAn5J/7ZQab7RJwjmkYt3fNf9ijmiSIkD0aDT/7PSXSDULuEYIgGEz6C63+Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "It hinders the common man from getting rights enforced", 
		"option_b": "It benefits the rich section of society", 
		"option_c": "It lacks a consistent philosophical basis", 
		"option_d": "It confers arbitrary powers on the State and infringes on individual liberty", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080138", 
		"question": "2523f9H33hz5t5EoV17h0O7vMGXDCm0f43CFEoVhfnXiWaLMeuzyiaV4IFSdnht/52TPraKw9hMhjrxS5oCefGImc459z9WH1P23xXdHNsVQ2oNg7Y4Wf+cHjC2oZtfeMOpnwWDAKEOwczG4RGJ9kznCmSMURHfy1sTNJAfnT11or1471g==", 
		"answer": "25ysKIT91Rz4+owuVw2y0fX6dW7WBWsSonyaEqxyMFf2WqPDY+jw3ZZ9Z26AilNv4TbHraGw41sKz6xe5IGcYiMXd4gv28maw+H6hurK3/s2XrKGKuPNgKgRTXs=", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9pcnRxuy0fX+ISvDFnEBpnGHW61zMFf2WqPDY+jw3ZZ9Z26AilNv4TbCtrf5+VRPiqVe+4mafiEKe5gvzd6N1urwwWNSc9JMn8B24ZcQf+ZB2DSuNMfCM+prwy6BKUGwZDCpDWpxmiKRym5fr4uv5mVmITTQ6w+x6OQ6vTlW2vkN", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "It undermines the efficacy of Fundamental Rights and the democratic system", 
		"option_b": "It highlights the importance of judicial protection", 
		"option_c": "It enhances the role of the legislature", 
		"option_d": "It shows the balance between State and individual rights", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080139", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7x1/TrPGjDTyIGq3aAWuNzYn72ROfAa+P7z55lNBydhV47/3nVt+X25VwCz7xT7M6aaCsQaoJhz5CvwurzxXxEPdJFlsBA7Z0XaOcAyi+sedHML+xlkSy0dGy8qZE4bWWyUxfdO994", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHh2Brit5YlUQr7yvO/Om2QF2oU41aNVqp1fjHwW6TLa/nni1MnRR31DXisa7h5NZoI4yA=", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9pYzVwzmhen3NH+QB3cU42uMEqZsYHTtR67Ua63yzJBwKxyZn1R492XVpra8t0cHiuhJ4I2XMCAGcI5pwcTJ2uvlwTFHIclJ2qZn6p4ecfFO2DyhNObSJ/Z63Syin7tyZMfuw0mNJEvoO58s", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "The State and executive authorities", 
		"option_b": "The rich section of the Indian society", 
		"option_c": "The common citizens", 
		"option_d": "The poor and marginalized", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080140", 
		"question": "24KwcdH33hz5t7YpQF7b0/LtdUHVDWwYrXiQEqBmeWXqV67Ya63qwZIxJFSInU9+4DbJreXW4l0LjqVe55qefGIxd4xn3MPWlZUk2K34ZFa1Bgeb28ilYfY=", 
		"answer": "2529KJP23RDv4YAzEhfmhfH+NmDDQ2NRoHCNQapnZHTtQOfSZuTyxoR+N1SQz5lkGOsDvtqB4ut2Taawuq8=", 
		"explanation": "25+9Zp/63x75t4QyVQv31r3rPWrEQ3YZpj+lR61wcXzmWrPDYq3MwJB5M0/JhFU75n7D44z+81oOgeh45oCMZCsXa59mx97J2+X0zzFAc9NKk4Z74Z5fbPxJwDK+e8TTKf1vwi6CJlb5dHvgdVaD7WEDqq+zF7JvNMXw", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "He finds it overly restrictive", 
		"option_b": "He thinks it grants excessive liberties", 
		"option_c": "He believes it prioritizes social rights over political rights", 
		"option_d": "He believes it lacks a consistent philosophy", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080141", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RD544wuUQr70/jxMHjDQ2YepmzDRqtxMGHxW7HLfeTxx9d3KE7JnUl+5HPIt6zm8hMLirxe55qWfyxDdop5zZCe3vD/zX8BJ85B2oN96o4aZOAAwzvtc9jUIv9ijmqFKkrzdTipDXM0lz7DhGhEoYaoqmXjDjdwztq1tcj+3nl3WArb", 
		"answer": "25ysL4Kz0Beq/os0VxngxPG/JWrCFyIepT+qXKd9cTbwFITNYP7qwINkM1WGgxlGTehWk0O3f8S9VNVLzm8d", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjwxb8/pYpXRCyw/LtdXvCBnQUrWuKRKY0dHT3UanWZ+LwiZ5/Z3WHiVJ6tWWGgKr+5EcGm71P4IGRMCsQPo9m28SA2efjzWdEc89K2pR65Y5fdeAAxS7tddqbKfB6y2mSJkmwdzivEDB7knH/hHhfqcSotSu+U9s7gBMgl4p9+scuN5ee16zT4EyrxgSH2XXRQbNnHkaJutyp/0aY4JY39cyJtSDe5+e5iejW89cNawsSvI5+b1e5ma8M62oqVMS1fBdPsfDfIVrsNCGsKQ8Rudjm1WF7z5YwHWg68F9Wl4Faa8Mz2YrguSB+f/FkKT2Nq01MwtRsTRKAcbOs2X7hoFE6YX8lcYNism08sk+SJ0A+j2WVXTlU1JRkvvkXkQ1iMS9JiGWglyyKh2DPfZ3nq4z5gun84Klx/bUuOkiPO0+YVYwSJaXBNX4y2eCcA69aOpxmGTbqJJUv8Tb3J9aQ2jQC08shO37ktCSYhsT6N3b08YioXuj1/fkpmaGT57pejJU=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "It's a common practice among democratic nations", 
		"option_b": "It's a central component of rights protection", 
		"option_c": "It's limited to emergency situations", 
		"option_d": "It's an integral part of India's Constitution", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080142", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzwxbm8sUkXV7U0PP7NGbVDXYQrz+xW6R8ZGKjRKvDd633x9dlL1nJiV52/XXUorH59BMclrtP7IPffyRDaoNqiNOGwurj1mgecZPU+B6GX2NE0gssFs8SWFg=", 
		"answer": "24GwbYiz0hbk5JEpRgvmwL3rPW6QAWcVsXCAWeN7djH3XKKCaujzxpRjJkiAjhto62XSpqiyMuvm2odXJc8KWDCN16XQ9Q==", 
		"explanation": "25OtZpXy3Bzk44QsEiz7wvXrJivWDHAc42uLV+Nyf2TtUKbWZ+LwiZh3Z13JiV52/XXUorH59BMclrtP7IPTMCcNbZ59wd6Ol+35wHhXOsJRm4wy6JMdeeZUxTi+NNXVJL5r33uBK0zkfnvFj2U22BfeG++FRFr++/xP", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "They safeguard minority rights", 
		"option_b": "They establish rule of law", 
		"option_c": "They enhance government authority", 
		"option_d": "They constitute the bedrock of the democratic system", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080143", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxxjm4oAzEhr9hdvqO2/RDmcft36PEpF9d3n3R+fHffn/y5t4NFTJmlJv+n/I47b/9FoKm7EEqzx7lEonTyUkMwyLneFxWQw=", 
		"answer": "24a3a5jy3Vnv5pAhXhfm3L3+O2+QEG0Sqn6PEqlhY2XqV6KAHJYFJlsFbFD2lW6A7Orprg==", 
		"explanation": "25OtZpXy3Bzk44QsEiz7wvXrJieQAnFRpnGQWrF9fnTnFK7MLvn2zNdYKViAjFU70XnIsLH540YbhqdVpc6aYzYCfIdm29jJweX70XRSc9JMm5Qy9IgQcftUyX2+e9fSIfIuy3+VJkn5cyDxRGN7lzjXhjxcvZCv/CS+GJo2zhFyn4l85N41OMKe1eiV+ki9ggmPzzuGQalsGFrZpsGr4kaIucx4icOxvwXT/fj82uzb9cdLaglEusZ9cVS9k60buCM1QcS9axNf+OvechTvJTGsKQpd7cPqxTgp0oosVHt05A1Pj4JEe4B12Zvxr3I5LI1lG3OpokJFwIF9TROferr42Wbg6UM2cW8qacphtS8wsxuVLUc+m2WYDClfh5V5994e1QUjd3pTiDbhjDvLhXSadYfi6Yz5xfv/o7Bm5rppaXWIME/dFp8VYrvUNCdz2OzbCLVPNpFzHiPqfdMh7nnsMJ6b0z0E3t5gO3/itDqLm8P2MHW2toG5gdI2ELoNOdLX6Miu/BzVdC/kYXKVJsf1TkSwTnL8kwdrtBQw2ygG7WzdG5o//CNNnz60QFJhgDTlLH2vkv5M5pecfoI4wOHl3nIDl/dxmo/ulBE1TAH7pHFHu4XRDTRHJjA6a5e1Wx+hiB+1mks=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Economic prosperity", 
		"option_b": "Political dominance", 
		"option_c": "Religious", 
		"option_d": "Social equality and social justice", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080144", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxRz4+sUpQV7n1vj7dX/fQ3AUpXqRErd7MGPqU6/Wfa3qwZZlZ12biBt1/WKGqqvz+0YLiqwb4IDfQCMRastG4fnJ2OK30HlEc+VLlJNm7Y4KaP1PwmLvCsX8D9z6u9ssHEddToa+kQ==", 
		"answer": "25a3ZoLn2A3/44wvXB/+he/2MmPEECBica4e/9ViYsw0yT3+0IhA", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHh2B7i45ZgXQvm1vT7MCvgAnAF41aqe+N1YnSjX6nNeeO+yIQxJFOHnk9y5mPSqqr+9l9PnaFc4ZqMPGIPe4xuxJCb3uP/0GINc8lW2o596tcZafpEzTCoesDaLL58x2mIM1aywpnk/6kkKQ9sxj6IJucxjQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Constitutional rights", 
		"option_b": "Non-justiciable rights", 
		"option_c": "Fundamental rights", 
		"option_d": "Part IV rights", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080145", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQnr5ZFgXRiy0fX6dUjfDXEFqmuWRqp7fjHgW6nWb+Tw2tdlL1nJn1J8+mLV47f1+1Ibiqwb/YHfZCMbf59mx97J1urzhGFTPNZBiJRru9j0DG7j/yHtiPhRVCHcafaD", 
		"answer": "24W5eoWz6TDDtY+nkUHe6wH8pUoO1TjIBHc=", 
		"explanation": "24exb5nnwln48okhRhv2henwdX/RG2MFqnCNEqJ6dDHzRqjSa//q0Nd4KRydhV4723jCqqT+t3AAgbtP4JqKZCsMcMtu2tXJx/b+yXBTOspd2oN98p8NefAA2TOpccabEP982i64Dmy8Jy61DXN81DjFymhfvI++8WeHFvw+zhQ8lYI0rfguM8eay7yKpA2biQiWznqSXK4oUVWXsY6b/kqIs8wE9425uTvItOT4iOyT+dAIbh1WupU/QkmonqsF/Tl4RcC1fFJK9eDCZEf+YD6iNQcS7Nij12d5w4E9Tik78l9Sg5tXdsl82NSkrCA/L8h4ASr6sU1Hz4BvE1eXern41mHq4Vs8fHsnJYdsqDkwsxzSaH1q2mqQXyMRkY5o8d0JlBdweHwAjGTvlDaYiWqBb9Px7oz9ke304K1ssrcvLAGEPE/MRIQecKfJKGkyxe/bH6NKNpFyEjGmP9A66zz8LtaA1zxN5dcpIHmnvCmcnNnnOGn6tJ3vi8Z4GboOIpiF6MWz8EjPZGPyNXyHY9i4GQnjD2v93wIltgtl3CkVqHLXH4xt5m0MkHrwW0F3gijuf3Wjn7JV/ouLbM4+1bX63CAZl+Fr353+2hwyRA26gT9Cp5CXQE5G2V3TDYM7yjUgP6QEF5/X+27WlGTEQn8Bet22FqGTyyVGmtPwnHU9h7knGcydORrTyt81iDajFfR6WWL+6NSvaLwBBSR+ouM9iumktsb7YvqwJCU+bgK2TeZW/dkRfwpyHQ6dJDZbabuiU45eTelE1zWZx1dpB29MF07N8qZISQvqvszNLnjXZLkITgrtI6MXHN79XFPWe7GdwDnaRq+dh1P+UEJlWjKYYZMC6xTkc5jnMBq8nShr7NXpO19eV8MDNCKzeG6+pK/DDRQ7cikyJ5hMOkDaXRU2mjfNILlhhKkBfhskQKTnGF4S1gFdkC7XHExc/V4bU6S5RVdnJ6hRNF4D3ne8H+A2UhjDh3gxAzHiUXsinXtLTYGY3keL", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Part III", 
		"option_b": "Part XIII", 
		"option_c": "Part IV", 
		"option_d": "Part XII", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080146", 
		"question": "2523f9H33ln8/oosUwr7yvPsdWTWQ2EerWyXW7dhZHjsWqbOLv/3zp9lNByNhF1992SGpbf/+hMZhqdX6JqWfywQPoRpiPac2eD2yXRPJ8dI2rJ745ILb7RJwn25ccbWM75hyC6MIkLxa3mvAX1xkCiJyLb1VBmHB3ZQ80PUY2/nyY8=", 
		"answer": "25S/b4P61A/v88UwVwzhyvPsdWjRDSIcrGmGErd8dTHLXaDKLs7x3IVlZ0mHiV5pslfUt6zz+1ZP3foNq4IlCHFicF0pIu3WY+lelOw=", 
		"explanation": "24OxZ53yxRDl+ZZgXRiyxvLxJn/ZF3cFqnCNU680YnjkXLPRLunxiZl+MxyOn1p15jbSq6Cw81odiqtPqZyafScHZ8tgzpCE2PL+ynYBJ85B2rNn9IgacfEA7zK4ZsCbNfBqy3zABlfkbjqxATAnxn2WiGlC6Iq15jO+Vd57gBQ1kZVx6N45OJeW16ya/kS8kweOzzuSSbMkEESJp8Gp6EvctIo99eWEtjqb1/vsiOyT5NYZbR1Vt8ZwcV+1makb4WorRMGge1JE46TFb1DoMmiCNRoU+sfmliY7kMBjoldHijOF2z/8Xq90x7pY", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Aggrieved persons can directly move the Supreme Court under Article 32", 
		"option_b": "Aggrieved persons can move the High Court under Article 226", 
		"option_c": "Aggrieved persons can request the President's intervention", 
		"option_d": "Aggrieved persons can approach the District Court", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080147", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRj444wjXhuywuj+J2reF2cUsD+XWqY0dmPmUaPNY63xz9dlNV2NiBc78XnLrqDi9FZDz6lV7c6WfjYGbIhg3cKa0qTjzGNOJsFMlZVmpI4XebRUyS+/fcDUMucuwWjADkv0bjjiRukW50XiDT96e68PGIuA+wc=", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNVxEIJxGwXl6XvLu+A5240S754=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH1wxzv84otEhH0hentNG/VTyISrHKOV7F3dT2jVanGLuTw3ZJjJFOcn0h+smLOsarl8FsAmrwb/YaaMDYGbJlm3N+bzqT4wjFoPcJNm8B799oYafVSzTO5cdHfYOtgymuSZ2TiczC+CHU0x2GHynNQ6Jez8GeSWt4+wRtytYh2/tw1KMKL0Kedpg2EiDqM/WmFQb5oFBTK5Z/o+FedtIcr9dmFsCabyLbKj/rZ9d0fIhxd/5J3Zhuzg6AM6mooQ8eiYQFC/urDIVvrYDyrLh1dycrxwjgp0pAoWWx4tBxJj45TcMN2mtjlsjZwNsN+ECG5rFFS1JE8Sx+Ee6i/2Gfx9BUrfX9rcY9/riQhrh2FaFt42kKSSCVQ1JNj/9wV1QZmPWlSmXOuwI2jxa+rgctKZVCI376RqF0=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Article 265", 
		"option_b": "Article 301", 
		"option_c": "Article 32", 
		"option_d": "Article 300-A", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "080148", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhPzzPO/MWLWBWcDpnGAV+N2dWX0UaLMLvn2zNd0KVqGn1h+83TPr6zk7hMAieh9/ICbcS8GcJ9uxJC73uP/0GIBMshA2o9m7J8NPPdPwi65fcDONPdhwG+MZ1f5YDGpFy820BFA95heoQzac9P37glk4w==", 
		"answer": "25OtZpXy3Bzk44QsEiz7wvXrJivREWdRp3aRV6BgfGijUanEYf/9zJZzK1nJmVNp/WPBq+XR5UcGjKReqd3NMkIDZ69Le4F5US2BprScn5U=", 
		"explanation": "25OtZpXy3Bzk44QsEiz7wvXrJivTAmxRoXrDVqpmdXL3WL6Ca+P4xoVyIljJmVNp/WPBq+Xk/1ZPvL1L+4uSdWIgcZ593JCc2eDy1jFgIdJNmYx3pMlNPN1OjD6iesDJIe16gi6PM031dXm+C35ngDjCn2hfp426+WepXd0/1AZyl5V9rcYzKJea166c+k69hwSO2TuFQK9rBFOR9e+6/0qfrId45p/NsyfPtPf4lLjR9Z4KZgxAupVsZl/8g6Ab9z8/WYi7ehZC/+XCeBT+NSG3NE4S64vCxGBgxY4sHTtmol37arCtgFoZY2JhLrZ4oMg4", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Fundamental Rights Part II", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Fundamental Rights can only be enforced through executive action", 
		"option_b": "Fundamental Rights require Presidential approval", 
		"option_c": "Fundamental Rights are directly enforceable through Article 32", 
		"option_d": "Constitutional rights can be enforced through Article 32", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090101", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MU0Whuy0fjtOCuXJ2sDpnyXW7VxMEHxXanBZ/3yzIQxKFrJvk965nOGk6r8/lAWyOhJ7IiaYmIXcdQtuaZ9T+XLmU7XzFMfbOQiTw==", 
		"answer": "25a3ZoLn2A3/44wvXB/+hfTxJn/CFmEFqnCNQeN7YjHxUaTNY+D7x5NwM1WGg0g75nmGt631t2AbjrxeqxJ5FPBrf50Kwyc1WyFr1Kw=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHPkz3j5YAjRhfkwL3PJ2LeAGsBr3qQEqxyMEL3VbPHLt3xxZ5yPmDLzVJosneGt6Di+hMbh6lPqZyadicRbct7x5CIl/H5zWBUNoZCn4Fm8YgaPPtGjCmlcZT4L/B92meUMlH5aDf9C3Y0vT/Sg30Y6L+1ySmPXN8kxVUihI527sEsMNKMleiV51i2gkaL0juhSa9wUX2v9cGuq1eUpcIbusOepTvP4eDwlfaTuP8ZdgFRs4NsIwjq2v1YsWZ4UNqxKBVe+ODVbV3jJTvjKBxd687g2Xlkw4wtXH09+xFVwpdZItR709jnuTwkLcxmVTK0pwRT05VoWleRe6u9wmbp5VsrZjokY8pEsik8oEPcO0F5nW6PWCVfk8Bj8cdZgQxmZC9TlHn1jjvLj3WKbpL37sD1i6jkqLwj8bYrPVSSNFCUFogfar3PKm5xhqmaA6IcIJBkHiPqfcY+9DzrJYXUyzZN0dooJnLx8WqY0sfgKnH6oJ36h9FiDfFIBNTD7Nmyvl/CIS/gOXCabcr6WBywbXP32ENGv1gRwCRQzGvKDYpr/DsI3k6iQEpnmzfsaW/hmbgc2ZaPa4tx4/rg1DEJ0baZcaerF3qxKOLXxsKuzGdA", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Non-justiciable principles", 
		"option_b": "Constitutional instructions or recommendations to the State", 
		"option_c": "Local authorities' mandates", 
		"option_d": "State governments' regulations", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090102", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg37yPTzNHnZF3tRoXqXRaZxfjHHXbXHbfn335IxF06Ag1hy4nrDsOXx+VdPm6Beqcm2fjEXbJ5izd6dl+vxhFhPINJWj4Nm7ZURb7MAyi+ieZTPKPsu6WGWIlf+ajyzEDB7knH/hHhfqcOa9jP7W9x3kUxhw9g6sup9gG4RJu2Lm7EgGotGaA==", 
		"answer": "24GwbYiz0xb+/8UzVwzkwL3+JivZDXEFsWqARqp7fmKh16BSO9O0mg7Jyd00ejwULg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHPkz3j5YAjRhfkwL3PJ2LeAGsBr3qQEqxyMEL3VbPHLt3xxZ5yPmDLzVJ1smLOpuXT+F0cm6FP/JqWfyxDcY0v4d6N3uW3xX9Fc9JMn8BOprMRb+BS2TCoesCbL/gu52CTM1flZC20C35nqHOWiXNYvIKy+yK/FNM5gAE6k8df4t45LtmS3KaHqEK+xi+M2HKQCJxnBRSWs475shDJ4IA9tN/NsHLI/fnwlvnB+coSIgFc/5J3ZlKu16YI7D8qVIi1ZhYL4fHCcVv+JWbjGwAh9+nswnwp1Yc7S2x09QwGhZZfZsV/35bhr3I/LY14EDC1rklFyZB9Sx6Zeq74xGek9F06NX0kc49/siQ7pk+dPUB2lXmVWCVUh8Bk8JARmhMjaWdFhTbzijCejGHPc4Pm+YHogKa4krxl97EiJ0KFdVDZToAVbrLOJnMy6OaUBut/O99THyemGdw8+TrtKYCRnwkf2dcjJmfr8TnZncu1CnG7p5e5vtt6HbwZf5PC0TBrc8rSYCKKqormLRBJ", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "They both enforce Fundamental Rights", 
		"option_b": "They both serve as instructions", 
		"option_c": "They both create local authorities", 
		"option_d": "They both apply only to state governments", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090103", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Raq440lEjr71/j8IWLGBiIhsXaNUapkfHTwFKbLY63qxtd0NEiIj1dy4X6Gqquw41sKz6tU/ICLYjtEbctox8aMxer2ynJEbISXUv3j/WB0YUBHKaaFZDAe", 
		"answer": "25C7Z5/83BDpt4QuVl7hyv72NGeQB2ccrHyRU6BtMtUANfhPRffrd/CQhOZAxHQ=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHX2Avv9JEpRBuy9e/2O2jZE24UsD+MVONHZHD3UefyYeH3yo4xJlWEzU90qErIn6vD+FAGjqQbw5uMZCsAe9Ev7d6awvbyhHBPc8NVj4lm5ZgTebRTwz6kccDCYOln2mbAKUqwYzCuB2J9mTjYi2hfp4379yaoUd53zxtylYZr+c1wfMWa1aGU4UK2ykaNzjuWTbNgFEbXicCU5Wafr4w3uMSO8RjO5+Dwmf2JsP8PdAdRvpJ6I12zhegP+SMqEcy9ewZZ+ObFdV3iLmisIU4P/Njsw2Zqw5FpXGcwtAhDg49CaoBn2djmrjs0OMgqATu/40NB19R+WgOBcbi2kHrt411/dHQvJZpisz97nQGgJmRxlmKIRS9QmMBB68MNnAdmJy9niXfygzGfhWDPf5r34pr5i6jgoat3+6AuOUCUPFPWFoQSJafIIidixeWSGa9fMpMnBzDpPtA973n4LpLU2DYb1csuLnnk8Wqfnd+1OGm2/a73stpfGqsFJN/E/cK4vl3LIRPkIH6WPIvHTRr5WXm41QF39x8pxyMR5CLIDYh88G0MkHrwXFRsnSvkLHWvgrtO5IOadoE/0vms0TMH1sh2o5XA0RE6Rha+zUxXs5CaFRx731XYDcsI1gRuJboFHZeR+2OCmjbRC28ZftrzQbyPwjgI2+Dlh3d4s4lOUIKdOQvemZ4lwQO4G/h3FXDopIq0P/kcBGNixrxNxMivocOpev2pKWs+LyqlVvtc8IFYZwwhUTjcAyFIdbm8Ut0KSeUP13vcnhVHSXJMC06M+qYMHROjpsDEZ2zbLY0SMhDBdr8RBtz5QgfOO/Xp7TTcBb6InEiwXkhlfiiSLL8Z7Aj+IMzCNhynlmtwudXtNxFSSpcSLiLgYHj5qqXDHAM7dCk3aJlCeVPcRB431D/NI7l3n6ITdQo7ROiOF1Qfl1Zc3z3HAkxQok0SH62oUlozK65AbhMjyDGwA6URXxmKijsSg1+XwyztPbppPkYoNkebz3jontJClu3sgZqIHNGiHa8S3I4KOLpeV9rZGRsvjvLw6qHQHmAwBXQ+bM4x7LjKzD8lqcBBKytcZes=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Economic and social democracy", 
		"option_b": "Police state", 
		"option_c": "Dictatorial regime", 
		"option_d": "Religious orthodoxy", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090104", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhL3wvzzdWXRF3cDpj+MVONgeHSjcK7Qa+7qwIF0Z2ybhFV4+2bKpraw/l1Pm61J5J3ffyRDe4Vpx8KK0uX1zX1IJ98b2Eww2P+i5gqBeYoKYIQBNuU=", 
		"answer": "25u3Ztz5xAr+/oYpUxz+wL9NIh80WXLWrrAQM1F2Kres", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH/1B7r+8UuUwrn1/i/Om2QF2oU41uKQKZ3ZHj1UefyfOTwyp5hK1mazVR9skXSorH1t2MAg6FY8MLfeSxDao59xcPJ2OK3wX9HPNRHn4Fw7ZYWaO0MjDS+NMDTIeou2maFPgXxdTz9Cn962TvDmWhfq4q69yu+GpoDyBwh1op97MYvfMOX2LzT/EW9n0aDzn7RRrJwUVGXs8G66Eadoo499c+U8TPV7bT6le3B5J4EZEhevpExI2eyq6Yg/mosWc30bx1d9PbebFHjNGinKAsOucXswjRowoosT2x04BAGjZEWa81j2p3puTwkf9liECC/41RSzpp/Vgeaca70kGvt9FwlcHQ4JYlssiM6tU+dOERslWqfRGxFnIUr/d8MhxBwPXtP3HLljz6FhCWbdJbq+cD5i+7/srpm/6YpPQ/AAlTRWohccbvFZ0N72OyYGa9KNt9XBSvoPtw+8DzqYJ6b0z1Nw9AnIX7h/SmYnNm1NGqosp65j9pyVK8POtjR4Mi2vBzQZCrmKWnfJt/8XBGwS3O43QFx9xAk3iRQ/GrdSIV68iwB3ny5R0BtnCCganOzlbsc/oqPa84l2/Cs+ycenPV1mpXj1RF8dQ28hWtQ8pSQXE9K3keWF8NH0AErTJ0PEJ/Q/C21mnjDX3UZatr/DqbJix5N3Obji29+utACVJSDJRLahN8yiDW+DvY0dm+tnI78fdgcGGEv7rtnz62RpcO1dvq0IGA5LxWxGdxN8oFUKDJ0HQLeHG0N35ocH990wD9YDE8nKv29Mw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Justiciable", 
		"option_b": "Legally binding", 
		"option_c": "Non-justiciable", 
		"option_d": "Only applicable to local authorities", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090105", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRrm9pYzWxj7xvzrPGTeQ20X41uKQKZ3ZHj1UefyfOTwyp5hK1mazUl+9HrDoLHjt0cHiuhS7YuefDFDcY0v29+K3uX7zWJMbIRiYBdEZStL0w7O9mYrsFM6", 
		"answer": "24a3a5jy3RD544wjEi7gzPP8PHvcBnFTZMkVitq3EL+/QhQrrBeqfw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw3Rj55IwmWx3z0fTwOyvfBSI1qm2GUbd9ZnSjZLXLYO732Zt0NBydhVpvsmTDpan19Eccz7xT7M6WdCcCcpgvx9bJxOv0zXBNOtVJ2pB39o4edfpTjCmiNMDTJb5+3GeOJEzgazyuRGR8lSWWi3Vb6Je0tSKoQNs1zBwhnsd5rd85MNGey63T+1m5kgPC3XWVCK12HlmWocvo7kCTro01vM7NsDzftOf2mfHS/J4BdxtGtoV6LRuIn60a/Wo5Q830ZxRf9OqQdVH/LS2nZw8Oud/r0zRVhLEmXmA1+BZVlopVIvBh35bntSI8Ot5WV336n0p8yaB0Wg7WcbCo2Gn36U86NW4jYMp/uSkgohuVJ1o+lW3cXyNSnY8m+9MWmwtudGwAlXjlkyqKjGybdZbwp8D5lP35tLhh/qZnLUiTIU7RVJgIbLzOZ2h0ivueHqlJIZxiBG6mPNsqvDz3M4OG1jcKkM0oLmOn4CKc0sDwOGup853/zsRkG7sVNcXM5sX3sVLDISfoMmmBb8nhTQH/QTzr1hxzslgxwCRQ623VBYZxtSoCkXr+AXZhlCLyaXKik/5Q65qDdoUw3fT4nRAfl/81vJO34BU5ByCyn3pApo2JShx/313YHcQXyAw9TLsHVKXF83mT1UbfR3UOZoe0TI/RByEnHSvNRSwT51okCQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Gandhian Principles", 
		"option_b": "Socialistic Principles", 
		"option_c": "Fundamental Principles", 
		"option_d": "Non-justiciable Principles", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090106", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7T1+n2NmfVQzFJ7z+UWqJgMHjwFLPKa63xy510JEiAm147/XCGt631t0AbjrxeqYeRMDYGbIZ8iN+Pl/PyyHdAIcMb2Cs+hOhdhAcVdjXt1GzFv4o=", 
		"answer": "25ixZpj+2APvt4wuVw/nxPH2IWLVECIYrT+KXKB7fXSvFLTWb/nr2tsxIV2KhFdy5n/DsOmw9l0Lz6dL+YGNZDcNd59mzcPLTTV5g191eXvELfexxPVbbQ==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpN1gXRiy0fX6dUjfDXEFqmuWRqp7fjHsUufrYOn3yNsxMFSAjlM79HfKr7aw4l0Lirob/YaaMAYKbI5s3Nmf0qTH1nhPMM9UloVhpJUZPMdUzSmoNOTULPdt1yLAK0TpdHm5C2d61CXejzxFvIKv8GCoFNU1yhAxgo5u6IguOdCey6ya5kr4kQOO2nqDTfMkOEDZptqp/0aP+r42icOsoybS9/j82quLuI9COEhmt4M/UE+9g61J6yI5XcT0ewZZ+PLVIUDiYDixKAMS7c6jwnxshpUsUW815hoGjYUWdsh2lojhsyI8Oo1oDHOppkdV1Z1yWFeXern4wHrr9FA8YXMlYspsr20wpwmZK0B3jG6QVWxQh8Bi6pAUlB0jfC9Tk3XpgzPLj3eLeYGj4o68kuD5o7Ej+LY0PUiDMBCYRYIfbLLMayd3yeaVAqtVMNMnFizifcUh8DDtKZWV03VNw9EhI3un/SSfnd/4eWS2v9LthtE2HbETItjR/N++v1LUISznYWmbY4v6WBz5QHL5305pvh4ghh0e1Gz5Gp129iEI3i3oARYtyGfUZHnhpapd/ofObIYw3/mgnTse2OR5jY/+1wgwRhb3zWxXoI2JShxbwhTbF8MOyQA0CfQVHJOR+2OThGPRR3UZdsvlQaGJgyVG2ez8iy09vp4KFYmAKBzanNE0iAO+Qfh1XGrkpoftOLwcBGE977N9w/mostn7fP3kP3Erew+kFa9f8pZYZAtvGA7OSWRObrzuWY0OTvJbx3vDgw5NVDMJC1XYu6cGUR3qq8nHYG3Nd/EVABrrdboBBs/0XQfNIOXpyTzaCf+dmEiwWFcxDj2PLqUd9kf/fMziIRyjn20k68T2O1VSSoRXNSmzcGK/o6aRDgguPy03LYtUOkjHCxUqkz/EIv0nhKlAdBErR621HF4C1gdAnD/GB1dLowIiUZmjaV1nL7pWJVUSyHv1BagaHBPIjD8Jml+Kx2LjL7pfOUxjaHCSm0ms25NlnPD7hoePDZT2Iv06wJkKK7peBMmOUxsVibPw4KHwA2M0CXlybuzAW6LGtUPwA9rx4szchVVf2v4LP0syPzyFmt/b6XpoIbZafXlEujMY7MDHcRLqyoda3FFkEFr+8UT2AW4v9hB/YtP4etXZOJ62sF9ZVirGQ7BMlv10nSDtM9qRZRQ7R2Es0QaTYtvcwjiafbv00qYACx/iw5aLSINj5UVw1Nny0ENDojQ4in/tBXnXa+St4RBRM2l5R72LE1hOxhYv2jS2nlr8Ls+pjrIAlLVPy/sv7zD5ni9KgWKCelnLcU/k//WduHTCt0kmib5sHEexT3puwglkF6hnsm5mQTlhQLI0qL7wbL7GlGSsOpWuyMwC4xZATqKKPKm6qdC8LK2FO6D+1JPDIHSh5pZlAvS9IIE5LkrDWDM6qq3hcIGEZAeXNX2N1q6ZHmuCLCJe/G1nn3GyWih+Im28X8wdFzhGlZB4Iq0Yq8DlvAp1eWvDH41m6bMGj15aGBBURfL0lXRDDOteN6OVfFZg9kwZSeYbb3yiaEZ/c9VDyCO9TWem5Sqzjr8iRMT/lABsO0fawSWLcHnV/OJxOWDlXszBgpiJEgqwtOEuSEVZ8LtunCeFB2g2RlFYrTfHj+59XFCCaVA4Mb4z1cgcSNXy9lZW2oEzDghaZnvSGDmtEo7BF9oNSoOq1vg0v5sKynBLCdEafZ6PVFbClS6YH2JUfVBHJk2N0AT5t6NzudDjGBWG4iSqg5TtEVbNqWJVl8juH91S1V1iYYKSkMrjT6Mni/n1GTdGBsYd5ngYlnxWJ2DaUldjxbfqODnechur7FY5woOxxqt/tOOl3A+rAy0fQ7MiTNAu19ZWwIb38b9KMcQ1ciVRUEIw8W5cc+heyoLHSEUZJfCaujilWJcgezspVFwtmg/x5OW+/c5BWi/u+OY2ZXSGloLyp7gdkW8EC0p0aX2ITh6aLcc=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Ensure individual liberties", 
		"option_b": "Promote international peace", 
		"option_c": "Protect monuments", 
		"option_d": "Minimize inequalities in income, status, facilities, and opportunities", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090107", 
		"question": "25Sre5ThxRDl+d9gcwzmzP7zMCuEUEBRrHnDRqtxMFjtUK7DYK3dxpliM1WdmE9y/XiGparz4kAKnOhU586PYi0OcZ9mxtfJ1Ov41HRTMtJNjIUy95UcdfFUxTi+OujVHPBcy2+TKEuqJx68CnR8nTDYykxEoY24/De3Ucl3yRtygo99rcszMsOawbzT50v4og+Q2XiFQathUWSLvMCr4lOQpZF4tMSA8SbUtP30ivTW/dsFdkhGt4M/ZlizmacE8Sl4UMawKAFE8u3RbRTkJC2iNE4S/4vO13xo0o8oHU41+htOi80UcxvtLSy6MKGCiTxlDWaw4g==", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHSwgrv5ZEpXRCyzO6/IXnFBi5RoWqXErd8dTHRUabRYeO+wIQxKVOdzU9z9zbFrLfi8lAbz61D+YKefiMXd4RhiNaGxaTjzHQBEtVXn5Jm7ZURMrZ1EzV3ZPFiJJTuCmAIfmy5", 
		"explanation": "24KwYZ32kQ3i8sUBQQ331+n2OmWQCnFRt22WV+NgeHD3FIbQeuT9xZIxcw+rzVR9smLOpuXZ+VcGjqYbyoGRYzYKap57wd+Hl+L4x2RSNtUElY4y9IgQcftUxTOqNNfUL+5r3G+ULlP1JyqyB3lxgDjTmTAWvIu+tRW+Vck4zlU7hcd24tx8KN+amauc+l+9hRLC2WOBRLxqEECQusDo7UyO4JYwsI2soiHe5uDwlfadsOIFXgZzrZJ2YFe51/xa2mooQ8G5aQBC/f2QZVHsLDvjMAcJ8Yvg2Xt5w5AoSWAi8V9VjYBfZ9R604uo/DM+O419HTq2pgRnxpp4Vx6Xev2IwmHq41wveX84JYtksW0hrk+VJURyn2aZQjgRuYFj/8QUlEREfGFElH+nkX+Og2qBc57q6MD9i+yws7Zg+6IraUiEMF3LGs0IbbrTZ3R33qmUC+ZMIZZpFCv2MdA9vDDqYJiby3kJ2cslLGPr7WqLl8H0LWC+84b2zvVkALYDOtSFvZiV/hz7bx/vBnydYsP9WAawf27x3Q1spxQg22ET53TdGslp9D8EkWujCUV3giLjeG/t1rdS6Y6be4c/1LX41TdQl+Z/npX+zhwoTgu1zXBF8pKWQ1BOylGWDswJxwEvFbUVB9bQ/GnWgX7VC2wfcMP5FaGIzWxH3KPygXVpvpcLFYWAKAzInswvzQT9Qf9sQSf5oIPgff0HDyQi9aYx3uWk99mrcPCtKmwpLxi2SuZKs5NeekJaAx/UBihKIOz9dNNWc+VJ12fPmQRNB3NIHVfF8KkGXBDqiMvHZSf9a/EoBhuiR7oXFs3sR1HKdcG7wT7KD6+QkFT+UEJlfS6cNbVN1Qj8c4/rbVEeIQgxGp4sYzsT6CK+7cbp", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Both the Assertion and the Reason are true, and the Reason is the correct explanation for the Assertion.", 
		"option_b": "The Assertion is true, but the Reason is not the correct explanation for the Assertion.", 
		"option_c": "The Assertion is true, but the Reason is false.", 
		"option_d": "Both the Assertion and the Reason are false.", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090108", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YNHwmNlFL1nJjlpv93HJsbyw+FVPq6FJ7I2LeTQGPrt9wd6K3vT7wWIBNstUkoFh7YAWcvMAzX24et3dL+xjjm2JMUz8JzqyAHU0kjDahm8WvY2/8DX7E/02zhE6n4Z2rfguNdmc0Lif7V72wTqM4HXDBolsFBSNsNylq1aPpYZ4ocLNtTfI9+bwmP2T5NYOIixbrYN8d1Kqkug56iM2UsGkZBdYsfDYYECtISSqIABd7sL33jR6yYEgXGU95xIGi5AWJfN81ZHlsDsjK41aBzq0oE1Qy5FvEVCqeoG2gyajzFw9cGgqacpdriQ7ogaMJFFt3SuVX2xFnIUr6tULmER2bmpE3GLvwjuOk2addZHmq6T1l+3ztLB19+MXO0iONlXIWogPJafIJnMyy+WSCqgcJJZzH2LqNNcr7jj1KYWZkQUD7Nd0YVan4SSQlMLnNCW5uoTwgpR1G7sFdtjWqc66oFTGcir7JHnTc8XwXBqwCFDx0Qt3thRl+DMZ5mHRGIV65mNKonCMR3NsmyToLHOn1qpU78KPfYEn1rX/yTMEnfl9kY/klBwuQkS4gm1Rt4eLEB57lrXD+tK0bSjLVOA9BOk/", 
		"answer": "2+f4aZ/3kUqoTRikMfo2huO6iLkTw9A3OA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHw0A3v8IoyS179w73bPHnVAHYYtXrDYrF9fnLqRKvHfa37xId5Jk+Al1J19TbH47D+/lUAnaUb6oeJeS5DfYRrzZCP1uj71zFUPcJBiMA1w5sRePxJzTPtRMbSLv1n3mKFNAu3WzeBCll6lz7EmHlVvM37wS++FM85yRM9hIo47sEqNdvf2qeX7Q2xlUaF2XWUWrxoHU3ZtsGm+EqYpZA9sY2ZvnLd9fj12u3d9NsZIk9hsIV2Yle1hLxJyDgxX8u9eB5O4qqXXVrZKC3jMwsP9Iv2xXFthpYmHW0x5xxUi4FTItR709jAtSA1PNljAzb6k1ZJyZd1TxuTZ/2s2GnwoFQzfH0lJZ1kqCV1sgCfIVVyk3iRDCVC1MdY8dMQlAhqbnsArGTpjDyCkGmKb92k147Ai8v/sqtm8bdpaWWJJ1nbQoQKYPPwNW58yeCLAaNPc4tvFjamPNwjvD/2MtaH0DoE0dVgOHLr8iuLl430N2H6toPsj9h/AKZAMNDJ5YuivljCc2P1KXSAJsj1TQ33QG7hnTJr8DQsyiQC6W6YOJt2+y4EjnK1WgMkmzSgeHSk1qpZ+I/Oap0017X40nIUned7jZL10V0YTha+jmtKpIHff05Gw1ffDsEC10k6BLUVVJfd+2qY1WHZX3RNc8f0BLqGzyVb163NgF1znJ8cR4mNOFebvtYj2xLxEe9wW2TkuIr8LrwUGGFs+7t8z+nhtt77fP2gJXMjaw+2Va9V+pdUehZiUQrTAWRbaL3uRo8RTO9b23rE1whOB2xGBlPN9+gCSBe+o8fNIFbQQvEJABfkbKEIU83xWE7DdfKmzDWJD6zckEquV0U2RyCYJfAY6wP1aMy1CBqxlnpl9YHVIFhVR4oHMCLgOiyFq5+NIgg5cD43LYlTNAf0CwUqnTjMNfQnjq4WeRRtQqejHBAfhVFImjDXHFlJvFVeXKqjU1ojL7tAJBsFwnezEKwTHAnEgj8YzhGvzSHlKPZCIl1jS3aagU/pi55jjLGuyryEDNHwKLMY180PKa5WTZHXEVoI2tHr4OqtMmR5MmVybtzBTOfSpEbgB4jEsMrUxlVbxbsbdlA9ZQqfiIvcsApiI6xMdjkI9R20sgvE5elNtkJMRYK8HA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "1 and 2", 
		"option_b": "2 and 3", 
		"option_c": "1, 2 and 3", 
		"option_d": "All the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090109", 
		"question": "25S7a57h1RDk8MU0XV7T1+n2NmfVQzdA7z+UWqJgMHjwFLPKa63t3ZZlIhyNhEl+8WLDp+Xk+BMfnadW5pqaMCsNPp9q2t2al+vxhHhPJ8NWlIFm7ZURffgA3jihdcDSL/B9kSyFEwTTp2jIkZDRoP7y97Tk", 
		"answer": "25y2fJTh3xj+/oouUxKy1fj+Nm6QAmwV42yGUbZmeWX6FtdhweIcpDw98yBEUyQBeQs=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH2yRjp48U3XQz2zPP4dWTWQ0MDt3aAXqY0JSC5aKn+YNG8/Z90Z2+djE9+smXOoqn8t1YBi61a/4GKYmIXcf9TxpiInqTn1n5MPNJB2ol88J8NcvVUxTKjddibMPtvzWvAJkv0Jyq4B2VmnSXP0UBY4IHytSq6XdQjwRw81o1t/tx8PdmbmaCc5kKtlAeA0H7RWrhoEECQusC7q0GZtJU9sMPNvzPP/fv3iaPv/pYIK0hUsJVrZkn8ha0a6C87RYiyZwAL+OrEZEbjITyqKAAc9Yvv12Mpx4wtHX0m8R5Sm8NZYMx60ZnwtT0+LI1jG3Ouq0EAw5F9Ux6Yc674326k70c4dHQido9p/D0wrh+QLUc+jWKIRGxemoUr/94WgQxmbzQAnXjkvjHDhCzPeZ3g5JXuhO/14Kpm5rcrLEyFO0iYWYtcbL3UInV8y/2SAqhdP99jHjH2KMEr73n7OdaVzTsExMshO37o+mSl0PH7BWuTvdL8ncdzGrwFepHk+9++s1DCIXawYXiedsP1SgHqSm+4xwZko1gMxiUZ6SLLAIZq+SlNjWqiQFJh0iHvfjyxk79f74Sbc84w3fGs3j0fiPFqno/+whh8VQG3jGtKvYqMD0tG2VyWEdkPwRtuD7sUGoLD+2iF2TbFW3QCc8q2FaCCgzxa0+3yh3FxuoNOWorOJRfPj8woyQO4DvN4WSfhqZG1ff0bDiQ+/6F+xvuk98m0e/WoJWY+fFqjUf1W5pJZKBJ+EAjYAzFDILWrV5MND6h913PPhQJGRHoJCVvU9qEDXAqrvoTqYWXVLpIUTirqZvMhGtz9TVPGI/Tp+CLACLyVhUu7TAQqSHquNbEZ4EfAdYD7Jwr60WyGmrl7a1KSa9CdXiZqU9Q=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "International peace and security", 
		"option_b": "Economic development", 
		"option_c": "Environmental protection", 
		"option_d": "Artistic and historic preservation", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090110", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kRzr9I1gRhvgyL3oPH/YQ2sFsD+AXbFmdWLzW6nGZ+P5iZN0NF+bhEtv+3nI7eWwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EYj0KFILsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8H1fWNP34kCikoBV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LwCXPPNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyYFs1cJfOAZycyiqnbTeYcc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbUn3lNkJlgbzentGrZ0o21eSX689K5zpQ2VP9AdpGFqYv38ByHIWOhYT3TJou0GUiwDzy4k04l91hliGFQqCKYSMk/tW1N3j7wCQQk0megLDzh1v4cqsLOP85xk7WsnXJQ2LQ439u3lF18B0T7zT8D8sTfDxwPjRSWXo1HhEluTPRBVNaRsi3W1TaQCzxNP462QejHg2wImqOxziE9/9BOFczObFmbyp5miFfxQb05FSet6Ma5fbxVSiRsuvIxiq3h94r7NbPkbCVqL1r3Ga8Zs9URKEI7UUudRWQPIPjuFt1eAaAPkjWK10cIBz8JRRqMu+hIHUTq6oSILiqeI/FcTl6iI/NFU464DgePdbHpiHCJRv/c1Qf+HwRlDnrdYfBNpUewOsyyZFPz0ygkuYGlchEbBMNXfGezNCv55ePDS0Z6P2xlaMoHOgeVC1Bk1H6DZ7knzedAMFhtAejnWRBW1lEP336SThgF8AxeH+XtABNnaukFYBtRjXf1UeBfHFyKxnpKzhbcgmKsaboLcQljOyTTzwyg29Im37+pws7BSpSibf1bks1DaPYbBNqWXxtc2rOkr6GgUSx5Ri03briIHqKR8A+2Qoi04oOahRwLif5Idh97ZXnLyd+ZsHotb+UPLzAK/TNZ7IqSIkbqmcgZlRAoEBWstQGkASdh9lEzLtOrKp2catvlsBAfVmSHF/kD2Lw4nWykdZ+RJFp/RyN10UfQNpKKh3TDfey7gO1JRVjil9mLBcotrAg5jpzygwwA63s1zzyiSzaaIqetqF4UYjw4C/TfWh0dxldilXrxnhOofc/qx+ZJzvABmPVToUy34mE2zx7MDwqOIzOqnrbe9yaG/gdhieojHCbjGzMtjkxkBLBrsjkuAG1hCeE0/Pa1bPGE3iHvbtz4jcxNpRYUBueKb/37/ZW8ZeOFb+WsmcDDbzKhsdMpKPy8MZMsYDaNJH1f5P60IsSELUnTfCvEkvvYUmvOZWAbrjku2iLOFFgsbSDzC4kdXnYS0MI2Y/lR5I6k8AolPCqAWvEomeFJ2xsZTBAZCryh2DENWLgiec7cMh8tvxZcSa9VKi33KQo2J5wGmyP0A2fvq2n8w/ouRJer1VQ5aEvah2TIOTWcqKs0amzlH4KFgtfZQkXi4LRgAREQtegS0kTNRjxRNiUk41aEzKEvGBnMLlBsfr5Sh5xVC5m39kVO1oFnRk1aKTmYXXr5W9iEF5VLStfik/hn69pej3ACR9FOOMzCB1aN0y7PWi4SPAICJgTe0FC2rd89xZ6OUVvPr23wxpSkXxOc/CMZ3pynWo5SnBNiKMzR34emQ6N037ihTGRKBoBcpTFU3ygfYjPWUhYtgbelaGmRIE/+oh9ti8biyNcxyK3ZknPlf2NjDbtQCZZrhZMYg8P3vf4SfI1+M2sQBEJSviEXfosWyvaPDUV9bKLf+WzsDtIgC2lgGh9kykO0t+Xxu84yDm66veZGKjjP1dv7peRhfQI5QlKZ974trvQqzOabEXiBfT1f/7JfunmEY176OxjiovShjReGyja/ts8L015M0ZEPgeLQGQBA5m+TypVe9l26I1Rv6cHvT+DMmwSdxd/5sYSopPUMHP31GqurzFCmX4I+5710HydmBPVV7dmXHT0/H4NdKXsSLMTVcOQG18f1CGLjz4jCbzuwJG7HaholD5w6snbd8/8WUD5NDrzEg6gtSJZ/T+6xCwLL2gUzQV0zI5ZOzAz2MNLb3gfiUvWYoBTqqMMvwHsDithu6qlfoA7QOnXVozZu1HT3FGEyX/NN8mf8b7n2XOm2ZIrfey3OPJlGoeE0cFHP1RXujqSWucWj2SzCT4o9U6x6B5At+xNPGZr+aCyP4PW9VClQoCkwKqTBEEaKfXtRPRv9gdoLlfkdx96z3lqPYKTKeAyIQS7NNw2UXItG1hZ2HWfWHTx9fkB+EkaCsPMfd4KN8QoNCkTKoX42idfpw6xeHJdecDNZdmk9xNcwHYi2sR98zL86AhzYobuyXAug7G5CWZDqEKLvfkunsaRJhEdoFcN0pSEKpVYJURxUCDAIFbvR+atLcO1iqYhbWAq2t8m2juiw7llCiHOh3ynbt/3ZAUfdWdbIbWW3Spl4XM59WfkowTBrsBvdl1kA9jnAFO7GH7kXa4pmIeWkLt5NmAelqpyGfb6Fo2Cdw7VmbadIrfiSXmbqv0EviABOiPJNj00WOh2kjTiltzxFdvOp4yOhBbRUszdjmntsTegs/dvuJymDkwjYdTTGbcPX400JPIZ3dCrzyPfPn/v3jtMX+2qgqrQB9cOmrbsqptztShyh3kZxaAppgiv+V5YxtTwMkzDfX1HRSbsRgR275luTFFXs/Lu9TXohAh6Dgd3nJHAzAw0tQAfo6JWN5ysRsIq4aY0z75T44SOxYmp/2ueI8QuaJ6it1pO5aAJmMdbUwQMswcqYL0dzl+T0qhrxzCAtqmou7zbtiqyeHrilvEE7ofcu/2+JqhrUwHOEaWd7ZkUGvfN4ArSktIoUlm99TcEsFxCXZ7QEbcbcQfNJlEddAnJp8c3n2CZrsPXxpES05X+X3+qVcTXFARlYh59c6pnW15CqzgBonuFSVU1YT+JLb3T9RVujO+7Xqs1CAkLw/JUQ5P4biXxKdnuN10z08W1Fyx+uBHtNW2PTd1FzYxKYlSwDv31/o0K1C6xYm+46Vg8A9W2PIPydnybe5uJ6khsdPr05V6Xg9B9Aorzn5aMs8PSSuIHckZ4beZGKJpGFb3QWgUhU41Yg9Sb61g0qE8C1e8YUW7Lf4ruHuJ31b/W/q5QkCFHfpm498cJ5/DWipmfhg51Neo6BbM3JN1wuM3KN3BcQRY2h7YX9vRHxkhglrqiCTebIBhgbmaLulgaybp0SPb2Ojl70B2Wyw5iFeMK24LV3ibvdbVxsPQnJKjlgv2kJAIjL1YKp/VZN4LlSFDrGjMdFLxXKWdEkFZ3sd6F3Itn9Vj9Hm6d/5YgBYbMuDPMUlT7kduuT8E6ORODIhL3aF25M5gRLEjA9Ur4bPo59JsQqily+oI8CWBneSMw/7gBnlqlawEB7NlB0skcpFP9DzTjCWag7e2g+Ne7n1ITxZUCehv/ajQ6xEp5yJuyEFcCvJG3zmJ59mQ+o/jbx3fuoXvUoM1bb+bPJu3pIq5OYuqP7SSLpr9GvPhJhQWM0b63p2pDvZgxsU9YYKYE/3wryy9Z9MuM9kqoTCvB/bq8yG47qn3wwNVJv/iaB5WUUa2Rv9Oe052Z8H8Q/KCgOJBFoHs43P5biwX0qaCzIAR91ghrXCI9bsZyntyR4t5UoxsdaaayujzDsOOF0sJUEH7P9x+6n6AV4lSo6Qgbq3VqJ+YSfV7bUA8yYxygIvl+HRgJ0p5Zp9FWJzExA1E+NEuEen6sRsBgAO9skooqshQ==", 
		"answer": "25T1Od2z81S4u8UDH02+hdmyYSlSamX2STV3ViBon6vXe/GJ", 
		"explanation": "25T2KKL20gz48sUvQg791+nqO2LECmcC43mMQON8dXDvQK/bLun735J9KEyEiFVvsnnA46b4/l8Lna1V1YCjfg8CaohnzdTJwO3jzDEQaYZhl5B65YkWZvFTjDztd9vVJOttx3iFZ0D+cTCvC355kT/CynpZusO4/S63UMgyzlIh1oZ04YUuM8KR3eiX7Vu9igmS0X6fXPNYH3bX9f665E6TtId4sNyYsD6b/uHqjvHQ9Z4KbAwSr5RwdVK4kugP6i89EcSxbxNHseXZZRT5L2i3Lwtd6cTsxEhn+owEXH03/BpCwpRfdsgzhMKkmTwjKt9vBnOwtldUzpd5Hx6FNLy7023381w9eX9rcYUtvSE57U+OLVN/iG+QST9C1I9tvtUamgpscGZD3GX0gyuekyuzcrCtq7Duivz1o60j860jaUiNJU7XQIhccbvFZ2J83OCJAqhRNpFzW2L1PNMr+yz4MpLU2TYf1co0PDfm+i7ZhcT5PWmztZfFgOh4Ob4UNdnA7YuguUjPIXC7YUiBYc7nGRvkTmj9kw9moxEqxmEE5yLIGoxs8D8bmz6kQUEklyn2ZW6umLNZ5JbOfoA1k/fl0jYZjvFqjJLjzVMASSD1zVJKvI2SRk9KjV3YG9wSxQUnGL0EB9bY/C2fm3XfRnlBP93iALyS0GAI3OLyh210q5kLRsDOLRffytE22BijFeh3XHPkrZXFM8AbJ2U4+bp0zq22vt6zNaf+bFU4YBe4TepKs5RfKAdqBALJBCZDZfi9WZ4XRPRWkmLDgw8IQm5cBFaM9LgYUha+v8rBemPbcPEaAQyiYr8JXfL2ek/KJvTp7DnbA7yInFG7H3Q3RzSeKKAB4BSwfZn7IBbzh2BhudLxM0VeBJcYKybhcHj5sqaPDQcoemBlIp9Ubk7WTlxkhyvQM/hug6YCeRQkVbHrWVEYklFKjivTAlFRqQJWbaCrRUEiJKpAYFcQ1Tq8GqERXQiKpDUFhRu/ymLYIf8LFUAxfmeHhlrl26J0lvHqi56ND8eiIrtb4ZkCPLMbdJXaFlgF07Fkeox6YpWJKS+WugdQGCUB", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A-1, B-2, C-4, D-3", 
		"option_b": "A-2, B-1, C-3, D-4", 
		"option_c": "A-1, B-2, C-3, D-4", 
		"option_d": "A-4, B-1, C-3, D-2", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090111", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YNHwmNlCLk7Jr3U7wHfT47f19FwCgq1V7YubMDYLf58vydyFl/b+w3lVIIZXko9n6J5ffvEAxii+YN3YKf9swmu8KXn+NXeJDHU0nT/VhmlFoYy1tSi9FPwizhEzm4J2+ckwfOWW3qCH+w2xiEaW1H7RYbNgGFWX9e2n5VCIqZYtocSCv3LM9ee5k/bV/MsObAtXu8Z9ehuPnrpJ2gR4Y8mhLwEL4+HTblngJSanJhoU9sXw6npVyNFneWAm8RxSi5VTIvBh35bntSI8Ot4qGjX6kFBB05E8bxiafb6hkGn25RU1YGk/bIlkvS85pE+JJlB7iCuIRCkRvY5v99EX1Sdsc3xUlWL1ljaEjlmBQJ23pbP1l6jSjvlR87ZnIUCEdVLXFp8TabaALmkyyeiPCKFTIZZ9Hizhfccn+zHtM9ad0XkZ2NxgBnnj/SuX0u76N3auuobsmt15GoMOCt/y4cK0uBzIZ2P1KXjTZ8n7Tw2wXGj5xwtoshYx22ER+meYAYd8+j8fm32kFgb1T7YQT7y/OBaB2Q+4Ltg8", 
		"answer": "2+T0O9Hy3x2qo8e8LrcHZo7AbRbMPVvA7oZc", 
		"explanation": "24axetHR/1nY9pBgQBvxyvDyMGXUBmZRt3eCRuN1fH2jRq7FZvntiYR5KEmFiRt59zbMtrbk/lAGjqpX7LKRWSwAcZl9zdOdl9f+1jFjHYZ2m5Uy5ZkLafVMwCTtZtHYL/Njy2CEIkGwZDipAXd7hjjMg3JR6JGy8i+vR5o+zgE91o1t/tw1P96e26SWqAWekwiG3XaURqllHRSrvMmg/1DV4IM2sY2DvjyW/uHqjvHQ+d8Jbg0S96J2cV6/g6Ef/WoIQ8G6axtb/eHDIVvrYBu3JhoYufvs2n1q38tpT2Az/AtVvo1qbPR709jtsjE8Kt5jGj36rEIA4YFyWxabcbOs0WSk0lw4fW44JYNj/Dk9pE+1JlB3m2XcbyNfh5Ri6sUNnAttPXhBjzbpjDmHlWCBf5bnq4Llxdv5svlB3OMVKFTHJhzKU44TaL7FKWNz3uCUA7VgPbxoBTDjPsFu1DDqYISR3DYA3dwuK3bz/SWX0sHwPSWuvNLthtE2F74UM9bK+8KtsUjObi2hLnvTdMLzURzjD3X2xwElkQ0rzCAd7WzMCYU/xyQKlmqjBQRzmi7jZDyghLsc4Jeda4cy2vTu0Tdc2PV2m9vT3Q85RBCym3oDgpaWQV9G3VjTDY0IwkkdGLUVEdbh/WGflm+cC2sFds3+QamVxmxG1e28hHRuq5kNXI2MIBznhOIo7B6jBP5tXHHo6LbrNPIWA3Qg/6ExxevhhN66YfbkHGomZhmuGe5L9tVbfRFvGAjUBCZDZfi7WJkbU6Bb2nCKvglMTn5HRXnD9bscVBC/vs3HYFbQSr8fAQzwZrARU+rxXELMIfi/zXD5FLaSlk6uU0E2DjWbYYMZ5BP1Orz9KBqwiihl68SlPF5PBIkCLzP6d2K4p6+GR0Y3ei0rIYRAOlPdTglklSzGZ/domecMdR8sTaS+WVUYkB5dnDvTDFRA8E4HH6aiVUEzOelxKF4IjTanFOASUw7PxjYDhVPcxTflLf9HOEcmaCSVgF6gnJ1wmu3ng4CCD+jsEbMo259DCpgbdpvDX1MdnrPq4KHyHmA8RmR5bvvJSufWv13/GMH6pYPIzFtD3a1IP1F7MTGOybbX9DNsIeVsYH5ZqXoNud7bbQiW16FX1l96QlDv4QHXSHVhlD8zXJL+Ks3QK4Kg9BBeVjfOULdKnvV73CLwdc3eaB9/BnB1hQ+VNvHFySeXNLju1KQGCxmul7jPU4N+41o5z9K2g0RJuHtnin/tBnvfbOPs/BdbLG84XLGNHx1UiAQ2xy+82138PIPqjqhJmrhEmLYS9QnwrTN/lV+YRkXAI3zsnuSXsG7SrQcox+p3VGPjcn1pxw0qBNMk/Gp6STk0Xah7sv7HKbfBjGShLZn4wY0V6F9fR6nLO/2Zstr3aIDNb5Hk3MCnJmDk8odgEvDvFcwMLnXEdDEat/77ZMT3eQiHOSu03beRETLHZ7uppZjWHBOUciPGI4vJ9NI=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 and 2", 
		"option_b": "1,2 and 4", 
		"option_c": "2, 3 and 4", 
		"option_d": "1,3 and 4", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090112", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YNHwmNlVLk6Mjk9y5HOGk7f5+VAGn6Re+s6QdmIwaop7zZC52Oj+x2gBMtRB2opn944Wf/1BzjGoNMHVJPt8jnqIIgXZaT20BX40tz7YmWhfvJav/Ci1aNQLzkd8oo99rew1LtKczaGF7Q2IlA+M33KBRLh3UVWLsI6h5VeZroY9sY2ZvnLI8ebvn7jS454MdwFWuop2bV6v164G6mosWc30ewZK5eGQZUH/KSakZx4S9cLgzzRvyZAkSGU14BZJjL9YXs4gmKzsuXIzMNh4ASD6oEVOh5FyWRiEd7j49GH25VYrfGwuJbp/tSM2qB+QLUc+k2XcWCRU1JNq89VZggV6PXtImW+ghzGNj3eMedPF/o74hOX1rq1i/uMVIEaIIU/kWLESMf3kLnV3yf2SG6McA41uGSHvLdkr73n4KZvUyzZN0dooJnLx8WqKnc78OGn6spz9ztF1G7EPO9jGqc+yvVPEcyLiOD2aaIvdVwz5TkD27wBSvxEmwGEf7iLMAIw/9C8CiHvwWlBlhiLtaXK1hf5d+IfOfIEjwfDvyW1SzajrxSIKC5qQCmfTtGmqiA==", 
		"answer": "2+f4aZ/3kU2ou//Q2AbZiGVbdoMovrUDhg==", 
		"explanation": "25GxepTwxRD88sUQQBf8xvTvOW7DQ20X40yXU7dxMEHsWK7Bd63/25IxLUmamVJ4+3fEr6Cw4l0Lirob/YaaMAsNeoJuxpCq2Ork0HhVJtJNlY5O6qYRVfpDwy+/cdfPYNpn3GuDM0zmYnmNFnl6lzjGhnlF6IKp8Ge1W853ygAhgo575Mk+MNLTmaWW6UOxiAHCyHOUUf1nEFqXutro6UbcpYw+ut+OtDab9u25jvDWsN0EdxpGrLpxV1O514wA6i87RcGibVJ74+3eYl39LC2wZw8P/Ivq2GBsyIYsWSkg+19Vh5FAZ4ByxdjjqTs0OsFjGzap40JP1dRoVxLWZ6m5xG2k5EAtfHQsJZpisCQ2uE+aJ0Zzj2edWCVemrxlwt46mhZxeGxU3ELohybLgWabPJLwq4fpjOz5rr4j4rEuJ0KJJVDdRc0aaqGAM293iu6UG6NOPZJiGTamNNtu7Db1KZWNnz8CwtQ1I3bz/SWX0sz7PSW9vIT8nNp3GrwFCt/x4c73s1PSczfyYX6SaIvxVw7/XX/9kypspR0m3CgG7SLoGoBx9iQdknujCU1q0jPoaTyyl7NZqpWPZs4l2/D1nTcenvtqnJ638ggyQwW2iHFXs4jffVVIxUDFIsM7yiAgD7sTBpPS5i2inXOQSHMYbdrlQauGzSJHzqP0gGdyrZMLFaiHPhzYntcwzVeBE/R3Vm79pIPqff0GSnAk/6sxyeyv992yYfvkCnAkaxu6XOFN8pkRWgt8GR/ORQBGcr2tQpQIRKB/wHzElA5YS3paRVve/ugGUhDqpsHPb2bSevEZABjtcbAAEsz0S3vBEfi7zTPdD6mZ1XesVkomRyqRJKNN5A79Opj9ZBKwm2Fh78SlIV5YTYIbfCb9cCu8pqyNBAszfGwhLYdIeVXUSAlknTCDDvdjhKY8fiQjYqe1C1UVglF7lzuSD1FI8EMYH4GkUlYkPqBTJRsh3z67EqkPUBnZxjMZzkKTgif/PftJPUAwcySAgE/pmp4mnvHtwouCBdrtILQYkokGJblYVpvVBhdcn/33+vPpH2t5EWh7KPnaW6LXv122A8T46vHfw1lZzLALMx83JCGGgJTY/jt5b4dAYHsHnntZmMLXIiKjy41awVl+VRXc50jqQm4xuhRgLpztKu7IK4+gsGBQGi3ETvAB459xB1imORc4nqr0qhTDHw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "1 and 2", 
		"option_b": "2 and 4", 
		"option_c": "3 and 1", 
		"option_d": "2, 3 and 4", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090113", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YNHwmNlFL1nJi0l6/3PUsOX99lcKz4xS+4ucZCsVe8tf2tmH1O3nyHRSc8hLlM148YkLdfdJzT+hcZTPL75px3iFZ0j/dTz9FH9jkSOWnnMWvIu+tS2uUNM0yRQgj7t20cZucvKc1qac5US7xgqL0XKFSaltHlqK9c+8q1eUpcIsvMCI8T3dtN33nvHSt81LawZWupZ6bV+5masMuD09Q830aVJb4+XTdV3uISTjJAET6sLn02Zo0osmUyky+w0Gj4Jda850lrztrjczK8R8EHOKsU1OxJ1sUxKFNLO33iXu9UYrfHkiZIhhuRE7nQHPZmB2nyuaXi1ckZJ4vtkXgQFteWpE3HDvkH+viXeKf4fq/YW8tfr5rrpq4q8iOgGUOhzaU80QYLTBK2triuyVC6lOMJpmFS7jfdkn9zy5BoOa2zgA1dc0LnunxiOemtnmBWuGvca3utxzVLEPOJzP/NijuV/OYCHtJD2dZ9/hSw2wQHq49wd3shsxwTcVqFLKAYd8/D0Bm23wSEhonTDzLGipk/5b5ZSLbYA81vv4nTUCnfVsmom30hE5Xw25hHNKpp3fRlIPylvAG98JxQctCYgPKJj5/XrWmHfeUjwCeY7iCa3Hwi5HzOaxnXV8q5UDUIKaP1namNtmwRmyDu9rUGT598SpJF2B0qyban9A5zlHVwrn", 
		"answer": "27q2ZIizg1smflZICr57qZZO/eLK9Nqj", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH1wxjn8pczEhPzwfi/EWLCBmEFqmmGEpNmeX/gXbfOa/6+x5h/alacnk9y8X/Hoan1t0cAz69S/4vffS0Re8t/x8eMxaTjyzFVO8MEkJV27ZkWfeZZ8DORev3VI/F83GuDMwXEbzz9AmJ1mTTEmTxbqYe+tQOyRt801Bwkk8dI/8EyP96P1a2AqEO3iEuIyWiFQb5tEFaVsI685AObqZQ99cuBtCrS9v31k+zKsMoEIhxausZ4bE25haYE/SQsHYi6ZwYL5euQZFn9Lz+mNU4J8c6j3GFtz4EgXHstyBFjgYxYbc161djotT85K8x+HDy0sARB09RoVxLWYLS11Sjr5hUWe34iZM1+/CQ7pQqMLVp6n2WfSWxGkZJuvtFZhRZifntJn3fswjyEjnaGeJbx6pT1iuawprZxsq4mIkiOMhz8X58ZZqfJMWIy+vuSA6VVI5NiBGLoMttj9izqNJ+X1jgP3NwcIUvp1yWLgMj2LSWOu5e5iN14FbEDP9DJqci4vk/TcyLoL2mAJsTyGRz4Sjz21hlprlgsxiUV+GfWDIxx4W0Dn2q5RkoknybkaTyogv5V55Kcfo0l2vbt0XIEl7R1npDylDk1VQG4mXZVt8SvXVVBzl3GEsgUhAUrC7UNGI+R92OQmmTTTn0Pc8vKD5yPxmxOyOL8i3Nu/5kAQYmAKBzfytgp2leVCO98VnPkvoO5De4cBGcl6r502a21uIq5cLOoKWIrYxauGepX9ZpDawd6EwfYRShGa73ucIgQReFC13velgsIdXZODU7fx6Y0Uy2kqcvafG/dd/EoBhuiZaEEHsvqXQfGO+WsxiTACbGdmUunH0kkSj/dBbkf4ATkc5r3ZCOhmmZn8NHpN0IbSowZcS3mZ3+wpqqCCQo/PzgqaItLdkjCCxYrhn7ENfxmmaISMB4hRLCuG1kanwVW3zfcTl9KpkkMUaSjQ1ZnK6dBYEsewT62CO0SXRfDiD02gGKUx2LiJvQGO1wwb22Qhk3il5cmkf79l5yEStvkbZkSwIgAPL9NQdrmDVISmfr04+TzUW01CmJgPbjcVueRt0DgB9r6r8bU0RxM27sJIlopZT+HjIfQ8jNhJrFWL3lE/XQWus/AbAek2o1l22xmc1r+50TnVScVvhhgLpXnb8XVKJKp+URGViHJVrtPne84ySThddjech8tCW4wnxPQYt2K0DGKOqS71qwbDBe3xNnbV4tu+EF6z9DywENOuC9njnXsH2WaYOLr5wxRYnV1W7iaF1hTkh4s0nqh0V/hPoavlOYIgrlG1rAXoRv+tik2m1aJD27HcXbpyv+Isib2rE4vyqNzUGOwE0FoyAk2Qf4o9zliQTUsQKp1srfhbJPLkWriDZT4+YQIpXJdVKLJO7StuJXMN6rLLKz81YWQb33nsaB9BeGqZe4KLH/OfXRdUHPeZu1tgHwK3JqZsAmz8g==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "only1", 
		"option_b": "only 3", 
		"option_c": "Only 2", 
		"option_d": "All the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090114", 
		"question": "25aqYYX60gqq+IM0VxCy1/j5MHmQF21Rt3eGEod9YnTgQK7Ua63O255/JFWZgV5osnfV4+Lg/lwanOhk1rGgTx08QbRQ9++2kKT1wXJAJtVB2o90pI4Xef1SjDOiepnRNe16x22JJkf8YnmzBWRhhjSYyPPwKZrjoqyF3tEP7EZcJIM=", 
		"answer": "26ateJTh1xX//pEpVw2wwftlKw3xeks8CMZzItSLqQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHn1Avnt7liQhf90O6/Jn7ABnAXr2qKRqpxY02hFK7RLvjtzJMxM1PJjkly5n/Fqr/1t0cHiuh/4JyaczYKaI4v+MKA2ef+1H1EIIZAj4Uy8JVfaPxFxS/tetvVbfR73XqJJEzxZTW4RH51gCTEjzAWpYa6+y61U5ojyBAr1oR548YzKJed3Oif7Uq5igqbnH6fTrJ2ElGd9cemq0CTtZAspoPFgzfd8eb8lPvWsNIKegVbtIdxYk/8tacG82cbWYiAYBcL1e3CZFf5KT6mZz4P8MXg32Rlw5FpUm90xwtHloYWUs9/35v99XCAP0iji9gzKVMAs7CKvQOh", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "sup,erf,lui,ties", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090115", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq9sUjXRP/yvO/NnnZF2sSqmyOErF1eWLmUOfDaez3x4RlZ0iBiBtf+2TDoLH54VZPv7pS542WYC4GbctgzpC6w+XjwTFxPMpNmZk199oacvJP3j6oddbSLPd61yLAJkv0JzGyEzBwnTWWoTJi5sOI/SazFN8v0Ac3hZQ4+cA1L5ec1qaQ7V+22UQ4CJ7rjiCsdbDvMrb5nq/U", 
		"answer": "24GwbdH+0BDkt4YyWwr7xvTsOCvZECIFq3qKQON6f3+uXrLReuT9wJZzK1nJjlN64HfFt6DiuRFfyaPipdWhbbXsGSijgAeH", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9pcnRxuy0fX+ISvEC2dRrXCNH6lhY2XqV67DbOH7iZlwM0mbiBt09DbSq6Cw01odiqtP4JiaMBIRd4VswcCF0ve31nRPN8NWicBm7J8SPP1OyTurcdfPKehrgC6raXG+Jwq1BXg0mDjdj3JTrMOv/SK2FM44gFIin4ht/ogvKceay66f/USsjwORmzuQRrkkEluUpc+67kfctIo9uI2ZvnLatLP6kv3C5dtLbQYSvsZ9YlW32+gZ+TM5U8SxKB1F/f2QdlzoLmi3Lwtd687w2WF7xYc6HWYytAtOh8NUY854lojhrj85K4MtXQG/pUFSwpp/WleadaW12WPl7lQrNVgkaoEgnyV1lQeZaHB3iG6fWCVHkcBb7NkXlg1zcWpT3HnmwgyfgXGKPKPs54n/nKGytCVvCc4DZgc43cj3bmgNHg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Directive Principles are legally binding.", 
		"option_b": "K.T. Shah praised their practical enforceability.", 
		"option_c": "The main criticism is their non-justiciable character.", 
		"option_d": "K.T. Shah called them 'binding mandates.'", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090116", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0gvj44wxRxuyzO6/J2rZEGcV436BXbZgMGXrUefDfP//x5B0KlmHmRt09Dbiqrf19EcGma0b2ZyWfiEKbodq25zJ1urzhHlOJIZAk4Qy15MNPN1Wwy/tXtHVLvdgyX3AI0DjZCu0BnU0gDnfmTxfu5Cu8Hj5chUeDAnhlSmEvmYnIIXPKA==", 
		"answer": "25aqYYX60gqq8YwuVl7mzfi/NHnCAmwWpnKGXLc0f3ejcK7Qa+7qwIF0Z2ybhFV4+2bKpraw+1IMhKFV7s6WfmIPcYxmy5CI2eC3x35PIM9XjoV854NRPn7XY+yaY9JstV86b5flOag=", 
		"explanation": "25aqYYX60gqq9pcnRxuy0fX+ISvEC2dRh3aRV6BgeWfmFJfQZ+P9wId9Ik/JjEl+snjJt+Xx5UEOga9e7c6TfyUKfYpjxMnJ2Pa3xnBSNsIElY4y5docc/pTxS65cdrPYO5mx2KPNErgbyDzREN9hnH/nHNE6Km++ymyWt0kgBs9goJ8rdw0PcPfzaCW8Q21jx7CynKFSbEkFFeWu8Gl4kDcoYw89d6Csjva+LTwievG9c1LdQFGt8ZqbVKxh6cb7Cs2RYi5aQZf9PbDLRT/JS6vIg0J8MXklnUpyoMqVik78l9FjYtTcMV9wtj3qCAlPNl/Bzb063ZFwZFuWhmVcf200XDp6V4+e3s/JahisyZ4ggfcHFx72k+VXilSgIl9+5Aphw1tfmZQkHPzwjCNwFabfYfmq7DzieHzufAheu0OZFaWBZP8EeG2oBWdig==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Critics find the arrangement of Directive Principles lacking in logic and consistency.", 
		"option_b": "Directive Principles are arranged chronologically.", 
		"option_c": "Directive Principles follow a clear philosophical order.", 
		"option_d": "Directive Principles lack logical organization.", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090117", 
		"question": "2523f9H33hz5t7YpQF7b0/LtdUHVDWwYrXiQEqdxY3LxXaXHLvn2zNd9IluIgRt182LTsaCw+FVPm6BeqaqWYicAaoJ5zZC5xe35x3hRP8NX2ol8pI4XebRpwjmkddqbA/Fg3XqJM1DkbjazWzKVWBwvrDmu/npTShol+97/", 
		"answer": "25y8bZD/2Ar+/oZiewrlBziyR7EoUjPOoXzydw==", 
		"explanation": "24axetHaxxb4t68lXBD7y/rsdWjYAnAQoGuGQKpudWKjQK/HLuH7zpZ9Z1KImU5p9zbJpeXk/1ZPq6FJ7I2LeTQGPrt9wd6K3vT7wWIBOsgEjoh3pLMReP1Bwn2Oe9rINPd623qJKEuwZir9ODJ9kDTXhnVFvIq4uxv5FOY5/BsGno5rrdw5Ltrf3KWD4EyrjxyHzzuFQLxwUUCRsN2tq1OOqYw7vN2BtCGb5vHpiP3A9dAfIglBr49tYk+1mKYI9Go/Xsm4e1JK/+CQaFDoISSwZwgS64v33nEpwY0/WHs6+RpIlsNUd9Qz0peksj0kf8VrAzb6t0xFh5h5WBaaNLi21mf241A+d3MnbJ50/Dk9oBvcIUc+m3iPQy9YlZRu+pAOnBBrPWlVknLhjzqFlGSDPIHq7Ijolqawibcj97A0LE+DMBCYQoUZfPPTInVkz6maHuZbJpZjHizhfcU89Tf6KYaY2ipN1tYyb2fo+COai430N2H6tJ3vi8Z4FbEDM5HX6N+/tU6HdSvgLz2SdYv4XA/xQ3DhkwxsuRwsxiZQ52DUAY5+4SQCkG3+AXZhlCLyaXKik/5Q65qDdoUw3fT4nRAfl/81vJO34BU5ByCyn3pApo2JShx/313YHcQXyAw9TLsHVKXF83mT1UbfR3UOZoe0MVYfzoOADgqsQ1UiQttK4w==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Enforceable", 
		"option_b": "Idealistic", 
		"option_c": "Cheque", 
		"option_d": "Obligatory", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090118", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQ39+MUzRh/mwPD6O3/DQ2MSoGqRU7dxfGijUKLRbf/3y5IxM1SMzUl0/nOGrKOw01odiqtP4JiaMBIRd4VswcCF0ve3zX8BJ85B2ql84JMecrRjwzO+YN3PNepnwWDfG0vMaRjzRFR9hjTVnnVArcOL5y61V9MnzBAh1oZq6IgwOdCe1aSKqEi2gAmQ336QSrFhX2iXicCKpQO4qZA9ttmEpzebxObwlPva4NIOcUhBupRpZhu9hOgO7SM8WMazKAJZ+OrTaEThJTvjIQEPudvs2n1q38IoU2108xBQh5FYY85w09bYsg4+HIMqMTqopkdUzoJ5HyeEfbO72Xjo5UZ/cXVra4V5/D0npBmdIVg+lX2ZXmx3gY5v/90cmxBicS9ylXHolizFvGuzcretq6T1l+3ztLB19+MXO0iONlXIWogPJbvBMWIyxObbBKtMMpxzVy3ofcEm+Xn/NZiXyzAC3tAuKDfo8mqNmsi1PmqstoD3g9F4APFC0ZaneYwhYkncpwe1qiZojg==", 
		"answer": "25fxKJD91VnJvseVYlw5B/ZdtK/Y/em7IJgx", 
		"explanation": "25GxepTwxRD88sUQQBf8xvTvOW7DQ2MDpj+NXbc0fHTkVavOd637x5F+NV+MjFl39zqGobDkt0cHirEb6JyaMDEXd4djiNOG2ff+wHRTNsIEjo8y5p9feuFOyDygcdrPIfIux2DAM031Jz6yEnVmmjDYiXkWp4X74S++FNk41RsmhJ42reEofN6Mmbyb7Q28kxKbnHSXCKlsFBSKoc+87gOIr8I5pd2BqHLP/PHqn7jD4tcFYQFCs4NsI1Ky16UI8yM2Voi4aQVYvaTSdECtNCCmZw0S7Nn3xTRqx4wnUn108RFAjZFVZ4Bn3p3p8g4+A8MqMTqopkdUzoJ5HyeEfbO72Xjo5UZ/dGguJYthryJ1shqeJ0Z6k2WdWCkRgI8r2MUXkQVueGFUnXqgsDaMiHGcMNP044n/jaj9pbht4eMzIUCUdUjQU80PcbLUIidxy+eVArIcNpFmFDamMdQ573ntKJeAny8E39UhO3Kn0j+Xlsz4PGuusp65vN1xHKsTdtjLqcSltFnVITfuYXSedsfxVA3+Wzzc2hxgtAws3iRQ2HDRBop25SEIjTD4e0FilzXlYn+k1rJd8o+HdI8/0uGs/z0fk7lbl9vD3Bh8Yw2piHxXu5KaD2xdxFrVF90LwRpuA7JBJ4LQ5mjWpXncQn8UNozgqWc7nMm8KFETFgzIrcXI", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A) and C)", 
		"option_b": "B) and C)", 
		"option_c": "A) and B)", 
		"option_d": "C) and D)", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090119", 
		"question": "25SqepD91hyq440lEhj9yfHwImLeBCICt36XV65xfmXwFK7MLu7225h/KFCGilJ483qGrLf08kFVs6Zn56/RMBYLe8tMwNGEx+X8xXwBF8lWm4lg5ZAecrRDzS6oNMbOLPtqjnqIJlGwQSyzAHF5kT/Ci3AWmoq8/TOoFMolxQMzn4s44t45Lpe70LqW61mxkAPC7GmYRr5tAVicpoCU5X+Sgsx4gcWI8RXU+PXylPnH+J4IYxtX/4J6YFe9ha0NuD4wUNz0TgdF9eXdZFr5ISTjFQca8d/wlnV7w8JuTmg35hBVg41Vdo406pbYshF+f/liEHOKolZMzpVxWhmCNLi20Wvw5VF/YXIuJdg4qCV1gAKZJlBzn2WIDA1SgM5X8OwXsUojSWdF3EX1ki2OjWDPX5z2+ZS8ge3zrLhx96dnPUmFdU/dVYISYfPQNWhkw/qSAqgcPJknNjDyNNYi+XmqcbXU3ipNxdcjIHn04CONh9n8Nmu7v9y7nU5DkzjlJbpi3dwqjGzGiw==", 
		"answer": "25T1StzQnD2oOWeqfKptCZDaIpILhvP0Wg==", 
		"explanation": "25T2KKX71FnJ/4QtQh/5xPC/EWTCAmsDonWCXON3cWLmFO+TN7ivgNc8Z2iBhEg78XfVpuXi4l8Ki+hP4Y+LMAQWcI9uxdWHw+X7hENINM5QicBi9p8Jff1MjDK7ccabBPd8y22ULlP1JwmvDX53nSHaj28YlI2H+wX1FO4/xVUVmYt55sY9KN/f2qmA7Q3w11/UizLRBf1QGVHZhtu4+UaRpcIbutifpXLf8ff1m+rW9J4faglG/7Z+cVe1lqUM9j54Usm6Zh1fsefFc0DsKSTjJgAEucTllmBhw8IPSGcw9RJDjJdXboBB35/sqCFwNsMqATu/42dPyYdoVgODYLS33ijl7lF/cX8oaYt/uSl1tQeZJRR/iSvbXy1Sho94/94agUMtQWF8klWuwguDhSW/fYHv4oHxgObk4Lxt86AzLEXAIVTdFt9JcbuABmp3xO2WCKhIc75kA2KubIx5rXC5bdag1zAekNgtKnnj+S+XhoG1OGi1vZW5gcB+Ea1AItnM58yk/BzObzfzLnmGZc7wGSniW3X73wsl5EkGhGEH4GvbAMl+/CAImj6kRgRjmzHlLFiohLtf/ouYes4Bwfzi3jsAlPFr34vl0R45QwG1jnoDvZKaXRxMyEbCH8QJhC87ArAAGZPf5mya1UTZTHQZbIDKD5SJ52II7uv0zlJor4ILWInODxbOmMpmzBKyDfxrUGOtvI78fe8QCWsi/vJh2OK3vtmyev3kI2NqTgijUOxV9tUCOSE7EBidECpMb7a9QpQKVPRG3XvLm0cAFiYeVhOMtug8VQ256szJfnrbbbQYThfsI6cNFo7TS1TOI/CnyT7NB/++nUasXlAsDjmcMrVBpRD4f573ZAe7lihX7NH3N1xeBKAYKTXnNH6praaPD0YudyllLoNVaVOVWxE2gH7MIblGn7MJcxQoAfv2OhAUgwUPmzvRAllXtUheS62oAEAiKaZLJBsBzCWhXeAIVBXJjnoPllWQ1ybpLbpBJE0qeG2SgwzynoRvmuilwo+SSsHsLrIVwZkKPKNPTZXYHldS0sHh6eTyFGI6Ay17L+DFV+nQvk7iQur7rciX5lQL/bYNdnsyNzyInZbP9XpdPaxBbHlasXYK7MXUIjW+2JxclWBnXFzv7AimMB1phyZYxPa7oWAwI96MpQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "B-A-C-D", 
		"option_b": "A-B-C-D", 
		"option_c": "C-D-A-B", 
		"option_d": "D-C-B-A", 
		"quiz_type": "order", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090120", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQr+9pElXxv80e6/PHifAnAU4z+CUaBhYnD3UavbLu72yIVwJEiMn1Jh92WGt631t3QAg6lQ54+LeGIAf5hqiN+Pl7WukiYeD8h4lKE8pK4XebRwzS+hfdXWJfB6jm2BKQXxajyzADBSgT/Si3FTppe6+WeJXd0/1AZykIhqrcExLNua1K2d/ES2gUam1WmUS6ltB1HZhdyh5UCVsI49poOxvw7V1rq5vO3d9N8GZwZGvoo/UVK7n7wauCsqVIjzexNI4+vDYFruNG/jJgAZucji2Hpm0sIrWCk1+RpIhoZSIsZ8xNjAtSA1PNljAzb6k1ZJyZd1TxuTZ/OE3lTqwxt/UXM5YIl5tTsw4T+OIVp9k3uQST8RhJJu6NEQmURsa2pS3FD1jDuKjWCBaJLvq7L1guDks/df/J8pDQ/AAVTdFqoTabLLKWZmwqmYDLVZc5ZpAzDpOcAt+T25NJ6RnzoC3tolP2On+yzZmNjxMGazsp65nNFgHboXeJOYrCQ1FrFCmSaKc1GN0p5w", 
		"answer": "25q2ZIiz81Co9LI8UZwywfIoiMdh7FFpMQ==", 
		"explanation": "25T2XJn6wln544Q0VxP3y+m/PHiQDW0F436AUbZmcWXmFK7MLvn2zNdyKFKdiENvsnnA47H48hMogKRa4oCeZCpDfYp8zZ7J4+zyhHtUN8FJn45mpJMRPOBIyX2Ke9jaK/Bv2mbAJETjYnm5AXN4lSPTjjxCoIKvtRe6RtY+wRg3mJM46cc5L5eR1rzT4Eyug0aW1H7RWLJzFEbZocHo6k6ZroZ4k9iDtTPW8frtm/STwtcMahxB/5JwI1Kxh6QM9S82RYiQYQBO8vDZd1GtEDqqKQ0U6cfmxTpVyL4nfycA/BZVwpBCY9R2253qqHI5LI1rFjCvsUVUwto8ax+TNJq33Gnv7lQrfTooZJlo/CUwrQvcPFx/jiu6WSJVlY1u8MQYmURRdGhIiGWggy2OwCKcfZDx5JP9i+vk5/li/KdnKkCOO1PMFo8ZJafBLGJ8iuiMDL8cPI0nFiD0NNEp+T25Io/U3nkO39czO37z4T6QncP0NSW7vpf3itlzGqtOCt/55+j5hFTOcmPyNXyHY8bxVxywRm+43QFx9xkmyzQC6XbdSIBxtTkFmz6zRkpwlz/0LHOn1qpU78KpcIIw2PvtyTpQm/VrmtW34BU5BxaugXZNtcSKX1RKwVCWCsUChBk8BbkAF4+R/WvWs2PeT30AesDiAKTH8SVP0vfizm5ruoJOcYWcKRrPg8gjiCejCPN6XHfhrZW3AfIpBEBizrp42a2yo8uvcP6hInFqZgn3V+BNs5RSaxdpEB/YS2R7aL3uVZIQQuVfxjXFkUdCUntABlPN9+gaWBKjr9OIeWvNI7gSBhvwZr0RU8f2DlPHMLGKxz7aEraIgFO3UEplSCiSLPAE8RSwc4LxIQOnmmdqt4HROlQbY4wbPSz9dX+x5aCCGAN6aC02aJlOfUncTRknlTDXZ/9on+cJZAttSKazHEIGhBRbnirbAVYFokkZXrepSV0gar1NJRsQwDK7FakRW1zaiS0PnBaTxGLcKOhHOEgufmqHwwzijoYmluuphoeFStrtOf0S3JkRJ7JOR5+WC1MZ2vDr4eLlAXh5CWs3JO3MV+HYsUO2EM3iq8bNixR5zLgNJFo1JjzLhZ7B/TNmLqtOezBosnwS4enaIjKi3Mh93EJtU0Hl40SkcXUouBJ6fp/ueZ3TLNuW5FFLE2T3WLVKm+Uxn05y9NamD4RRQlYxzl3tufg=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Only A)", 
		"option_b": "B) and C)", 
		"option_c": "Only B)", 
		"option_d": "C) and D)", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090121", 
		"question": "25a3ZoL61Rz4t5EoV170yvHzOnzZDWVRsGuCRqZ5dX/3R/3+YNHwmN5QJF+Gn19y/HGGt6qw00FBz4oV28DfUS8Be49kycLFl/T4yHhVOsVFlsB24ZcQf+ZBzyTtfcebM+toyGeDLkD+c3m7C2I0gDnTymlavIq29DO+FN04wRlymYE4xMY4NdaRmbic5ESsn0i+0kefGvRAAxrZl4CapQO9rYA9scaMo3LZ8fjwn+7W9J4faglG/4N8bFWzmqEKuC49XMe3ehNI6KTZchToMzumKRoU+MejwnspxY0kTWUx+RpIlsNGbcx6wpHnvT5wO8hnGjCookdZiahyYxnFPZmqnijGrmdxNVsmZ49ptywn4RydPxRqkm7cWSBFnY1q6tVZkgticS9PmjbJjDuCgWvPbJzv4pTlxenj4Lhg+qoiP0iOMhzLWY4VZL+AI2J/xeqJDKVFfaNpKyyydPQt/zbrJJ+a2HkZ35kEPTmn1mSr3I3UNGe/t5n4nJg2EbwPON7I4Mj3tFnKbiDzIH6KJsLnGQHiXXn01hhkuQxl3C5Q/GrdSI5w9CFNkXjwYEpgmybuLGyumrdI88yycbI/xP3l3jpQl/I4i5PylA4oRhC2iHFX8qeQXU5KzkCJXHkTqFdH0J54cueR9I+cbJw=", 
		"answer": "2+f4aZ/3kUqoTRikMfo2huO6iLkTw9A3OA==", 
		"explanation": "2+TxXJn6wln544Q0VxP3y+m/PHiQCmwSrG2RV6BgPjHHRumCT+D8zJN6Jk7Jj153+3PQpqGw41sOm+hL5oKWZCsAf4cvzNWE2OflxXJYc8dIlY53pI0eb7ROwyntZ8HdJvdtx2uOMwuwTzz9AX1knDDFg2ZTrMOv/SavFMo4zBwmn4R54Yg4OdqQ2rqS61T4ixORyDuTTf1nHlmJucul7k2IpYZ4t9TNoj3Y/fX12vnd9J4OYQdcsIt2YBu4kqUG+zg5UtH0bh1Zse3EIUDiYCqmZwMY+MXq2HNv045nYWcI+k0PtotfcYBgwpnwuT81MdkqHCD6oEtS1ZF/S1nWUK/2kEnp4lA7fns5JYJkuyU5qAiUPFF62n+UTTgRg4l/9t8MgURieWtSmWXzizGMwHGHedPw5IP1iqX1o7Zt/a4uKgGJO1nJQ4wQbKfJInQ+ivmUAa9IOpxmG2LiONgh/yv4I4/UyDYY3N1gLXKn9T7ZgMTmMiv6m5e5jNF6HboWM9WF4MX3pFTCITPzKHOQb9v4XEj/STzEkQFrslgoyS9cqG3WDclp9CEYm0LyCUprhmfvYnC41rdSqpaGes4h3PnlyTsTmfg4jIv/0Q85BwaumT9CvpeQD1VBjUDeG40UywonDbhBFZjVsmiVmnjfRnUOP93mCa2Vxj8G5u3NgDI0i5gHRsydOBjPj9MjxgPxCO45Vmj/uoP6KbJVI2ps8rtiiuugusWuZrO3PGAvbBL3VuEZocBFYEJVHh3YCCZKcvj/D8lHDaBY2nzGkkdJQ3tbAEnf8qYPHRCir4TrYWTNd7gIGxvsd/MkAN39Q0XDLL3p7CKHRp6Rl0K6VEU3DimJIKQI4Ufkco3mZAe7lihx9dXsP1BPQcMWNSqzY2qq5beMSwc5dyUgPo8HaUjWQhEo1DrGKvZkn6YDaVRtVqCuGlhWmxROkS2SDxhSsVVeUKPtTFohL+lRKFoFjSWwEq8YUhXQgylKgl+exzD4MLYLNFg2emiam1Ws25Nom7/vkI+VD8bsJKkCnLENFLgPDa7eFkhciefl++TtFGItRmRkbvHGXe3Dokr1Foa0g9CayFlF3bcHOFo/ZTyKm5PQ9Sghb4FdITBrsHEcqMHTcEao3IRQ0EZtVBXl+wHwSWJhvxxjYYH/a9PfL9uq9hBaFSvJWLRKm7x82CHrNs3QZwN/E2x1kgidZt7PyjGNKezrz6EAERGh1pWLQY9g40trz9+ri35FrT5ninLhDjbWY//g4RVVLH1sC5aQFVYQpR9i4TK0nnfhL4qpk68fi/Bxyrwd4gXnriRlz1GKD3naYmfvnsaRu2/Fpw5jheAHmceA2F36OvAnSaXJng==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "1 and 3", 
		"option_b": "2 and 3", 
		"option_c": "3 and 4", 
		"option_d": "2 and 4", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090122", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzwxbm8sUkXV7WzO/6Nn/ZFWdRk22KXKB9YH3mR+fSYuzniZ5/Z06MgVpv+3nI47H/t0cHiuhY5puNZDFDf4VriMSB0u3lhGFOJMNW2o90pJAKeP1DxTyhNMbeNvdr2THCNxru5sA4UkdDnnhej5rAQQ==", 
		"answer": "25GxepTwxRD88sUQQBf8xvTvOW7DQ3EUsWmGEqJnMHb2XaPLYOq+2YV4KV+AnVd+4TbArLew9FwanbxIqYeRMCcbe5lswcOA2eO3zmRFOsVNm4wy9p8JdfFXgn+7gGfQ6CwfwknuP0tr4tRP", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHX2Avv9JEpRBuy9e/2O2jZE24UsD+MVONHZHD3UefyYeH3yo4xb3i5vmsyqErIn6vX4loLjqZY7M6ZfzBDXYR62sSajaTWyGVJPNNDksB865RSduFT2DSufdXZLPsijkqwFHXjJymvC2Z9kDSWizxQuoK28DC0RtF3xhog1pNw6Ig2KdOW2qGS+lT4kgnCyXWVTa93BVWXsY6840bcg402ptmEpSfP/fv33euT/9wBZwtGtpB6cBX8o6AM4Wo5WMz0YRwL+OrEZEb9Mi23LgAaucfiwWcpz4xpUWA68V9Ri5deItR704vh/D0yNchpATqsplcO+5pAUT6YcrGt1Wbn5RUwezoNcIRpvSAwrxudJBRMk2yUWD8L1KNk68INhkRrfHlF3HP4kj6FhGCLPIfr7sDvhufgpfls9OM0JkyFdXrNWIkdaLbOM2Z+ituSCq5IIN9yBCvoOpUKzArJM9aVzHkMkMslKXL18SSal4G1PGuppoDwgNM2GL4XJZHE5cKwvhzQaDfpYWmbY4vXVgbjW3XsxhpsuBZi22EG4XHRB4cxySMxkFaxW0lrnC7veW/hv7BI75CebYsl0uHl0jxK2MNwmpW31xIyQQiyjmtQ8oWNRk9KjVbTCtoCwQduKIQyJIWR82OS1VDFRXgMcsv4FamLgx5B3evlnS09vJ8bR5idbBjSh54yx1e4D+l8R3f/rZK5KfQQByQk+6B8xeOouN+oeerobGIjeRO5Xq9O9pxWYBZ6Fg6dESsPYre6XtMiT9xB/3rYlgsIdXpEDFTI/rpSHTOio8jNLmnRdqMIHV7hYr1CB479QEHAJ/KsiBT5NY+P2QeqV0E8DjWbNbUDpRX1d4X8IFOnm20k/s7zN0NVSYYZKGf8ciutraaQDkYqbSUrK4NXdkLGCxE31D3MKepzhLMVZBEiT6mrWVEFhhhdnirbAVZW/gQsWqOoUlYpKawFLFoJwD6+EK4eSFzoiTUBw3WUghbkLLpvOFsmeHCamUmgq4BvkfzgkoKEGZTtK/0oxowXLfZrS5bfHEJV2CX1BVnNYxFQCQ76GGKe1PI=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Directive Principles limit the power of judicial review.", 
		"option_b": "Directive Principles have no influence on judicial decisions.", 
		"option_c": "Directive Principles serve as guiding principles for courts in exercising judicial review.", 
		"option_d": "Directive Principles are legally enforceable by courts.", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090123", 
		"question": "2523f9H33lnO/pclUQr70/i/BXnZDWEYs3OGQeNnZWHzWKLPa+PqiYN5IhyPmFV/83vDrbHx+xMdhq9T/Z3ffyRDfYJ7wcqM2feohusF8eVkRY/PZjW39diudoY=", 
		"answer": "24GwbYizwQvl4YwkV170yu+/JmTTCmMd436NVuNxc37tW6rLba3swJB5M0/FzV1y/nrPraKw9hMIjrgb4IDfZCoGPo16xtSI2uH50HBNc9RNnYhm99RdQ3GH5A4aeL1RJJgRL8Z/yg==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHX2Avv9JEpRBuy9e/2O2jZE24UsD+MVONHZHD3UefyYeH3yo4xb3i5vmsysnXJrrX88l4Kgbwb/YaaMCQWcI9uxdWHw+X7hGNINM5QicBw/doeePBSyS6+fdrcYO1hzWeBKwXxaT39AXN7mj7bg38WqZCr8CSvR5R3/BsOmLBw5MQ5fNGK16yS5Ui2kgeOnGmYT7VwAhScu929+UbcsI00vNmEsjPXtPX3nrjQ+cgCbkhetoR6cU+1krtFuA4IYvinKBVe+ODVIUDlJWiwMw8J/Ivq2DR51I0kUn09+hgGgJFZY8R2xNj3szE5MIBvFjy0rElJxNRrWhuQda+9nCjh7kYqZ3MlYsps/C46rB+OLVx7lHiVWikRhols9sQK1QJxfGJFi3nyiX+Nj3fPf5r34pr5i/u+6Itm9KY1LE+DMBzUV5URbLjBKWZmisuUAq0REJcnIyrjffEn7jz6NJ+C2nk9wtAuLH73+C+K0sLzeVausob8zuR5GLYDL5iHcjO08sckrXg1Dmc8VHV0sw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "They provide for social and economic rights, filling a gap in the fundamental rights.", 
		"option_b": "Directive Principles replace fundamental rights.", 
		"option_c": "Directive Principles focus solely on political rights.", 
		"option_d": "Directive Principles are unrelated to citizens' rights.", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090124", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV17B0O3tMGbVQ0Eetm2XErFhfHSjXamCeuX7ibR5JlGZjFB6/zbirLfx/kEOhalVqY2eYydDNto2nYHAl/byw3BTN89KncBx65QZcP1D2C7tdtHPN/trwC6mMkv0ZjS4CmR1mHHkg3tevJD79Cm/FP4+0hAxgo5u6IgMLt6R2qGD5Eir2USXQ5x7bYLpKSTiOjQuUTS5", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHVxBfu9oglXArzyb3NPGzYF3FRtHCWXqc0YGPmQqbLYq3x35JjZ0iBiBtf+2TDoLH54VZPv7pS542WYC4GbcUtHn1i91Y5DGi0hRQqszcnSQ==", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIX71FnJ/4QtQh/5xPC/EWTCAmsDonWCXON3cWLmFO+TN7ivgNsxM1SMzWhu4mTDrqCw1Fwanbwb+5uTdSZDaoNu3JCe3+H5hGVJNtRB3ZMy5docc/pGwDSuYJTZJep5y2uOZ2PlaT28CXV6gDDayk5fr4uv5me6Wt535Bwgk4Rs5N45fOeN0KaQ4V20gxXOnG+ZTf1CBFqdtMOt5VedrMIKvMqFpSGb4/vslvyT5N8AZ0hCrYN8Zl+5masMtmoEX/S6XBpC4qTUZFfkMyGsKU4Y9Nvr12dg3IctHX088V9DjIVZcMN215rouXI+Ptl/Bzb6rEIA4YFyWxabcbOs0WSk0lw4fW44JYV7uT91tQeZaFpxlCaZQipehoNu/9IVkERHdH1Fn2LplDrLsHeGcpDq+4z5lqa4krxl97EiJ0KFdVDZToAVbrLOJnMy6OaUBut/O99THyemGdw8+TrtKYCRnwkf2dcjJmfr8TnZncu1CnG7p5e5vtt6HbwZf5OWaPvRX3zjtGaINUiYla9v", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "The Fundamental Rights would prevail over the Directive Principles.", 
		"option_b": "The Court held both rights as equally valid.", 
		"option_c": "Both rights would be amended to resolve conflicts.", 
		"option_d": "Neither rights would be enforced.", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090125", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRjn8oskXxv80b3+Nn/DQ3UUsXrDV611c2XmUOfAd63qwZIxF12bgVJ6/3PIt+X5+RMdirtL5oCMdWIXcct7wNXJ5PHn1nRMNoZnlZVg8N0MPP5VyDqoedHVNL5nwC6UL0CwQDaxBXt6lSXeyn9Xu4b7vXbiAo1+n1dN2dAti2iMOtTVPVITQkw7", 
		"answer": "2+fsfJmz8BTv+YEtVxDmhdz8ISuYUjtG8jbDU61wMCO2QK+CT+D7x5N8IlKdzXp45jaO8vynphpNPr04g8/qkWWs+XTkmBucVA==", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIP2wgnl+ZYlEgr9hen3MCvjFnIDpnKGEoB7ZWP3E7SCZPj6zpp0KUjJhFU75n7D44L/+1IEgalP4c6ccTEGPsM+kYbenqi30HlEc/ZFiIx75ZcacuAAyTOsd8DeJL5swXqIZ1H4YnnvUGR81BDbj3JSpYa14WeaV853zxNyx94vvIg9MtPfzaCWqB/tkg7C/XaURrlpFFqN9e+r/wOTpsJp7Jrc/w7VyPrNkv2TooofakhzsoNxZ1a5mbxJ2SksEcu4aQBC9+3VZRT5KC3jFw8P9cLi23Fn0sU6HWgh4BdJkIpCe4Bn2djlsTc+O41rGyr6s0VS09RzWVeCfLj482fq80E2YW8/bIVj8G08rwyQPVB3lGzcWCRU1KZ+8NQYmAFtaW5M3ETphTefkyuzcq/t34j5xbqltLEj064iJ0WNMFLMFqwfcfPJKXNgxe2ODqNYc5xvFizhOMZu/zb3I5OG0TAD15k0J3Kn5iOemtm1LWr6o4D2ntFkAKZAN9/Bqcqko1nVdSblYWmbZ9+0VQnnXDz10gpg9wwqiCYZ/meYDY958C4Z3mq/CVBsl2fEZW6klapV/IfOT5w43fblzT4Vi7RvkI770F0ySBD7j3oDtoGaQllLjULZF8lHywduGLwEVJHD/XiYkWWQRHpNdsDwE6GJxClF3+3lzm57/5MLR5iPJRebrMsozBa8BPNtVGutmo/+NegGRCQF7vJwxv6u98O1YeGrKHApah73eP1N+pZdbUIoQCidESsPZ7G4U906SPJK0WHDgQIId21AC1nF66QNTkTiudTNbWPYarIdAhL7I5IXB8f7QkLcdaLwgDKARr6SkQftBgwmB3PdMaII5gL0f4LxIVO8hW12ueD3JlhYSIYEfHanOCvo/O/DCgg+P390aINJOlTFThMtkjfAZ/pog7MFaAw+CZqiH1UEkx9Mmn7eD0BIuUcfUaS5AHEoJaIIA1NR+T+wUYQWThnJkjMcixas0CviKvNbPUwwO2uVz3/0moZj38/mjoeCE52gRuAsM1vg9G6kJIh4D53H0w==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "21st Amendment Act (1967) and 22nd Amendment Act (1968)", 
		"option_b": "23rd Amendment Act (1970) and 26th Amendment Act (1972)", 
		"option_c": "24th Amendment Act (1971) and 25th Amendment Act (1971)", 
		"option_d": "28th Amendment Act (1974) and 29th Amendment Act (1975)", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090126", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV17B0O3tMGbVQ0Eetm2XErFhfHSjXamCeuX7ibB+K12Cg1pv+jbForb1txte1v4MoM6NdSUCbI9mxtfJ1unyynVIPcEEvJV84JsSefpUzTHtRt3cKOp9jmiPNQXkbzz9DX1kmDTbj3JCqZey+in7W9x35Bwgk4Rs5N45fOeN0KaQ4V20gxXd4HWtRuwqJVyc9f29+1GZrYd4lsKYoyab5uH1n/yT5NYKdkh0qoh7Yla5mbwI9GoKWM+8fAEL8uXeb1v5YCqmZw8Q/MXn03ApwI07HX088V9Pj5NaZ8122IzlqDs/MY1lE3OeqlZFxIB1SRLWRK+x3mvt8Fk6ZjQXa7Zj7mMBqQrcG0FuiG6RSWxym5V56pALgAhmeS9UlHf0whmejmGOcZbt/4Hwxdr5p7F34eMkKE/AN1mYV4AZa7fFIyd0xfvbDKhFc49yBTLpLtBgwDfFLsXa6zEIkOo1P2Xi+S/ZscLgK3H6poLxi9hyVKsIM5HG5sanvFnTZGPgLHidYsbxVxywQHq49RtrsxkozS8E6W6YOoB4/Tke0EK+dUow3BPoaTySg65O74+LP60+xuf4nTMclPtvmp+3xwk9UwGozWtM8oWSSlJLjXLDEMkGyQwgGLUNVKTY9WWChjbRWDwDesvyBKy7zRBG7ev4jWk9jIQPQYmDKRfPytc1iDS+E+98VnOy6sWWV2lklkyCuIsWC3MckxY=", 
		"answer": "2+T4R5//yFugbe4EOCR8fhxQZY5K8wpU", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIX71FnN+IkhWRDz0fW/NmrDBiJZ8ibVBeo4MGXrUefxe/3szJp0Z3+GmElvsn7Dr6Gw41sOm+hr6JyTeSMOe4V7iNSG0ve3yn5Vc85FjIUy8JIaPORP2zi/NMDUYP9jy2CEZ2PlaT28CXV6gDDayk5fr4uv5me9W8h3yRgimoJ16MYoNdmYmYya+ki7kg+U2TuhWrRqEl2Jucu7pQOoqId4tsKYoyab8fnpkvnA+cQOZkhGt4M/alWqnqcF+SgxXcGgcVJE96T2dFrpISWmKRoc9YvR33Nh0pFlHW0x9xNHkIpYZYBn3p3p/A5yLMxpBzypokpD09pAHVeqeoG2+Xyk8kAzcH5rcYJsqG00rxbcKUBqn2aMWGxFm8Bo68INlA1vPWBS3HfthzGPwEOacpfi5oXyken84Itq9aszOgGXOknUUs0eYPPVKWR9xPqPBLJJJ5ZoGSPqcZU69DzrJZSNnzgew9wyO37p82qNmsi1KXezvpP6l5R5Ev8mI9/B6MayvkjGbWPTKHqbcti0Vh71XTzc2hxgtAws3iRQ2HDRBop25SEIjTaCTEJhgCLub3nhmr9E54uFfoAwx7XO0j0b1ddw36//0V0YTha+jmtKpIHff05Gw1ffDsEC10khCvQyAJfF9y2mmnrZSGVEPeP3dWCTMv3e30YRhOmI1lU=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "2 Only", 
		"option_b": "3 Only", 
		"option_c": "1 Only", 
		"option_d": "4 Only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090127", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV16gken3dUrdBmwVrnqNRuNVc2WjHPabOby3iZN0JFCIn1474HPBorf0/l0Iz7xT7M6PfzUGbMtgzpCd3+G39HBTP89Fl4V88MUjcshOnXOZfNGbEP98wmeBKkD+c3m1BWM0gDnTymxZv4aptTO0FNs10hw2kYI44tp8KNaU3OiS/0yhxiCX0n+QRbhqBVWV9fyh7EuIs8Isvd+CpDXTtNf2lOvH+coedgFdsYdzI3qxkqYN9S82RYiVawZYv9jeXVq/bhyrIk4t+Nnv33Vkw4w9HWo1+l9JjI9PIsF+05bg/BY5LchpATqspgRw1Z1yXB6GeLirkHzs8loqcnJrRoVjrzk8tRqIIVtwm2fcbSFUmoRm+94N1SVgaXwOoHjcjGzFtG2KPKPi+Yz1hOX1rq0j8aIpaU6OOUWYV4AZa7eAAXJ8zuiWCKhIMpMnJSvhNcE9vDvgYJuV1TYf2c05b2Ho4C/XrsPJNzH0h5r8zuR3BrMJN9zA59/3s13JISzvLWTTZ8bxVwywaWn21w9oshYxyS1Q2mvfAJ1stToEinbwQ1FgmyTpbXDhlbFS+YeAa8AN3cni6joZm/w4rI/2wBgxQgqvzVZNsYuNXVlM2RTEG8oG1g0nArNBA5/F+i2CnXfEC20Yet3iCKeJnG5Kc3cGak57m+fAZ1ugjSsJ", 
		"answer": "2+f0O9Hy3x2qo8dmrWEHpJcs4tKMsPG24sAJ", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGhhQ3it6QtVxD2yPjxISvxAHZRpG2CXLdxdDH3XKKCXuzsxZ5wKlmHmRtv+nOGorDk/1wdhrxCqZqQMCMOe4VriN+bl/bywGRCNoZij4525ZcacuBBwH2ffdPTNO0uzHfAIkvxZC20Cnc0tz7YmWhfvJav/Ci1VdZ34Rg3mIN16MYofPaczbvdoH+9gAOQ2XWSTf1oEEyUvMWp5UKI4KA3usbAkjqbwPz82tza4tsIdgFEusZPcVKylKEZ9C8rEceyKCFf8PDVIWTiLCGgPkdfVDF7UnzM7es3n29C4Hpktg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "3 and 4", 
		"option_b": "2,3 and 4", 
		"option_c": "1 and 3", 
		"option_d": "All the above", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090128", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV16gkOn3dUrdBmwVrnqNRuNVc2WjHPabOby3iZ5/M06GiU549zbSq7f/4lQHz6kb54uIMAMRaoJsxNXJhLXUm01PD8gV1Kxz84lfdflQwDigcdrPKfBpjkqJNUDzczCrATBEhjjYiXVGpIaotSapUZo+zgMzmo58rdo5O9aN3aSW+174iQDC+m6fTLxpFFqNtMLo2UqbqJYr+/GDjTyJutj4jeuT+dMbbg1fuohralW714wA6i87RcGibVJ74+3eYl39LC2wZw8P/Iv113hgwsImU2UttBZAwoJGctJ8wJ3g/DApf9liEHOKsUFTzpB5UQPYSLOE3juqzFQoZjoiaJphuSAwrxuVJlM+mW6OWC1YmsB48dMQlAhqbntJnzbEiy2Og3GGapaj25L1i+v5sLVm4eMkKE+OOkiYVIhcc7zJIyd9xKmcH6lJPZt0Vy3gfdYh8i3rIYCR0S0E39dgIHGn5zqckcTzMGb6lYf3itV7EbEUN92F28KwuEjULx/vHXPHKOf1ThuwRnHo3wtoshYxwS8XqEbRGox84SQbmz6AW01qkS7wYHmy1r9O78KYcIc1k/zqnSYYne04iZL42BwoQkS6g2YDlJGRS11CyFrCH8FH9gApBKASWqrfzmOhnX/TQzw+a8/iBKWCzTgI0/CxrW5vrZUNQdPMoRYnsO9/XbwtcpSWTUdJAg==", 
		"answer": "2+b4R5//yFuNb3X7RDU0i2QvbL3u+3HN", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGhhA3it6QtVxD2yPjxISvxAHZRrHnDA/ojITHqWrPQYenrypJ1Z32bmVJ4/nOG8PTTt0cAz6lf7ZyaYzFDaoNqiN+H0Ov+ynYBJ9NXiYx3pJgaaONFyTPtUsHVJP9jy2CUJkmwVTC6DGRn1DDYjjxyoZG+9jOyQt938Ac7mIRx/cQ5L5nf5aav5nmwjxXC3WmFQb5oFBSKpcur4kWVo4M0udTNsDvW8fC5jveT4MwCbRpbq49lZhu/krod+SM2Eey9ehdI5e3GZBTdMiGtJAcN9c7wlmZsyoM9WG104BAGlotTIsR6xYz2tTAlK8RlG3O1pQRSwodzSgWVca740WbgoEI6dHY/bcprsz91tQeZaFdxl2aTQmxWm49vvpg4hxBqfmNFjzaz23eJySWOcpejuNm0hqG57vlf/J8pCFOUPF/UU81PNJCAN3V93OCfCKIcJ5dmA2LnM8xu8DjuYJuV2zxNxNZgJnr3+C+Ul8PheXGytoH8zsdmEbwJMNjGqe++olnEdSr3JD2jdML6WgHgQ3nrkxlqohQhiC8f/CLaDcl78C4Bn2y1TQRynS7kLHm3k7Ac44TOdppx0PriySARjvF2mp+39Q8oTge3iGwD49DTDw0WgRTZDI1UlUkhCvQVHJOR0WKYhmLZX2kZdsH4T+i7zRBG//Dii29ptpECWZXCbBDPys0uwRK9Bfh9FWToupL4NPJVGWsv8708z+6uucW2fPDkPmAsYAi6Sq9f4ZpcKAB+GAXaRSdHYbSiU5MZROQP3XuKgw9NB3hbCk/C/7tIUgLqvM3HYmvKar8bTg3yZrAMFcf7DmHaO/WoxTXHEr6Q1XW3WEwxXXTVE7UL4BX1dI/3ZB+yi2Vt8sDrM0UbZowYN2rQfCuNrabDLw8oei8xIZxCOnfHQh4nnS7PIuongqFAQwwsVa3nKV8anxJW1nyAPNSzSY7JwXnlHgq3IJc8", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "2 Only", 
		"option_b": "1 and 3", 
		"option_c": "2 and 4", 
		"option_d": "3 Only", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090129", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV17B0O3tMGbVQ0Eetm2XEqdxc33iRqKCe+P9xpliM1WdmE9y/XjHr+Xx+VdPhqZN6IKWdGIKcMt7wNXJ/OHkxWdAPcdKnoEyxpIebvVUxX2udcfeYLY/lznTbhqy16hOgRcsqfLwoTXe0UZH1w==", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHg1Brl+YFgQgz90/TsPGTeQ20X416RRqp3fHSjB/bhLKU3XDziE8fOFPEaj4q96Pg=", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIX71FnB8pYhRB/8xPP7NCvyC2MDomuKEqB1Y3SjHPabOb63hddlL1nJvk5r4HPLpuXT+EYdm+hS55qNfyYWfY5riMSB0qTzy3JVIc9Kn8B94toLdPEA8H+PdcfSI75d2nyVJFHldTyBRjB7knHCgnkWi4y15jOyQM8jyRo82MdM5c18P9iKy7zT4Ei0gkaW1HqFCKpsGFic9f6p+U+VoY89u9nNuTPItOPwnv2T8dMObAxbsYE/c1SrkroatGoxRYiwZxdYserfdRTlIT6mZxoV/Iv22Hhgy4s9WG105BBRh5EWds8z15TwuSBwMN8qETapt1ZP3tRoVxLWSP+60Xvt4xUsYWg+Zp54rigJ40+TOhR4iGqRSTtehosr8dZZgQxmPUxPkmX0iyuelGyAct2j34j5xev/tat3sqcuLQGOOkiYRp8Tc7rEIidzxKmeFa5dJoxzHjTjfdkn7y25L5DUyDEMxJkjIHn04CONh9nwKiWuu5e5spZ0FawJNZHW/dmis0jScyatHT/TZN7gGQHkD3X20AJwsx02iCcV6XbNGoxstSEElXvwWkFnhyvhfnWym/Ic7oeDcI0j0vb1kXIRlvA4lY7z3R41Rgj7n3pVu4GIAWBB8VrlDsgEzQ8nD7UNGI+dsmSY1WTVR30ZdsH4QbyIgzhA36Oj23V1/7EDUIKKIRzVnp4HywP9QelxUCfevZbrOPEQSkcj76Blivixv8+3cbOwJGBqeRu7UOtQ54wRZwQ7BQPYRSJGcqu6Fo0fU/QP3XOKthVcTnxFABqfqotIFROio8fALm3fdbRcDRvwd7IMHY7cR1XKNuWg3jWJNq2Vm0S3T0ggXXqNM7UO4AP1dI/3ZByllnok2NPxO1JXQZBXbXOzdWW95fLaQkh6VyMyLZxCaAuVQgRkkDvAK/h1iKNAZBAoAbuiGl8YklFfnizGTldD8G0MS6yuTFZnefhmbBsGxT62GeAeVRHPgnoegRaZ2iHgPP5OcUM2f22Qhk3s24Bjifbslc6ODJTuLKoIkoACLLMbUJWWGFIKn7Ph6eflEnh5EmI3D+rcV+HdtVy2UZG8oIqaxFJPie1RflxyaXmKmt/M/jliIbZbZmRfqXoWosveIgek3chQ20ZpXFzovXPhR2Izsx9wa9Pna8XRI5Ck/lFLVgbIWLIOu/Q46SThdfvYdh88E2ojlEegZNvExD2TManogKIPRSu21o3OBbpi4EF615Xwleq/BQRBFiH0mXcYgmnj8Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "The second provision of Article 31C", 
		"option_b": "The entire Fundamental Rights section", 
		"option_c": "The first provision of Article 31C", 
		"option_d": "The concept of judicial review", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090130", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTjn8oskXxv80b3eNn+QBnoFpnGHV6c0ZHnmFLTBYf37iZh3Z0ybgk9+8WLPrKuw8Vwdz6Ra/p3feS8Tco5izd6d3urwhFVIIcNHjolk4dovbv1OzzS9eNHIYPxr12GOIwXRdS20B3xx1GKPwn4f6IK18WfzV5NogsF4suiTKwjjHHW6WatbRaI=", 
		"answer": "2+HqZpWz8BTv+YEtVxDmhdz8ISuYUjtG9TbBjR4TeShykqLL+E93o9uAkQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHS3Bzk84glXAqy5P7rdX/YAnZRpmeXV61wdXWjQK/HLv79xod0Z1OPzUtp/WLDoLH5+F1PiadJqYKeZzFDd4Z/xNWE0urjzX9Gc+JNiIVx8JMJebRw3jSjd93LLPt9jmyFPkr+Y3mcFmR9lz3TmTwF8cu5vGe6Wt53k0x6lc445Nt8KN+amfzB5kn4pwuH0n+cTbNwUXWaoY6n7QPN+dVu+425uTvItPX0n/bX/dsFdkhBsJN4a0/8g6dJ/yMuVIikehdI9ODVb1foYDysZw8R9YvH32ZsxZYgS2x0xA1PjIBfcsx2xdjrqjcif9liEHOctkpExpl5UQOXeP2K2W/s9EZ/cHQ4bZhksigx4QaSaHVsjmKfQClC1NE/spBIzEgjfGFE3CWxzH+3jlmBVJz07pb5l6SwtLFq4eMwIEWFdVnAQogSdrrPKSdly/rbHrNeIJp2AifoKdk3vDrsMoKV1jUI1JkiNjfz/C/ZxpnhMSWbvpf3itlzGqtAF9LRqcSx8A2eNnutYWqbb8j8GRr1XGj3wQth9wwtzWEA53HRHIBw+20ZkT6kQUEknTXpa3Wvl7Ic+pCBa4syx/zj03Iflvhh3534xl0dVRCyjnNGocTMFhRNhBTXEMlHl1BmD/1PXKTU9GiEkHjTTjwBftb7CKOGzS1cmsH+gWownJhOYYSLbD3SmNsl3B6nBL1JR27jq4/pMfkGSmsquoFly/mk9/q0efqnNSxodTN21ZQE499fFx1JosstHQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "42nd Amendment Act (1976)", 
		"option_b": "43rd Amendment Act (1977)", 
		"option_c": "44th Amendment Act (1978)", 
		"option_d": "45th Amendment Act (1979)", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090131", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV17fzPP6J33RQ08Yr3OQEqB1Y3SjHPabNr23iZN0JFCIn1474HPBorf0/l0Iz7xT7M6TdSUCcst/2tmE1ufuhH5Hc+JNiIVx8JMJebRw3jSjd93LLPt9jmGWIlewQSyzAHF5kT/Ci3AWmoq8/TOoC5hR9jSay07ERlUs9fxr/pEP", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHX2Avv9JEpRBuy9e/2O2jZE24UsD+UV7FxMH7tV6KCb+r/wJkxKl2NiBto53TJsaH5+VIbiuhP5s6LeCdDWJ5hzNGE0urjxX0BAc9DkpRhqtgjuvkJyOgJWXTUv0s7Pl7/", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIX71FnH/oslQAjzhdD2OWfDQ2EQsHrDGvItKCGqGOfWZui++oJhNVmEiBtY/WPUt+X08lADjrpe7c6LeCMXPp9nzZCB1vb6y39Yc8dKnsBw5ZYecvdFjD+oYMPeJfAu6HuOI0T9YjepBXw0pjjRgmhF6IK18WefXcgywwE7gII43do1MtSWyaSW+w2xlUaHz2iURqltEFjZocHo/0uZ4IA5psSO8SHP5uH6ju3B9Z4EZEhGt4M/QFSyhLwA7D8sWMe6JlJ3/9jeVVzoYAusMhwJucTz33pswsI9VWggtAtOh8NCdc8z2433qHIzMMhyHCCu40xB1ZlzUR6ZYa60ySSk4Vs7NW4jcJkh/Dk9pE+4IUZ7mX+VWikRpJJi8NMQhQhmbi9DnXjujSvLgmDPe5r17o68hOrjr7V25qZnOVOJOF3bT80Tc7bSZ0FnxO2aAKNSJ55rVxDvOt0673e5HJio0Q0F1ZkjJ3bp8y+K0sD0PWD6sYu5mtxzVOtSONWFyMayvljKZC31YVyQcov7X0ihFiuun05yvxEmwGER/HbdBZlr8ClNinHwTk1yl2fzeX+p1q5O44+PfJd9k+LpzzdQi+Bqipj8lBkzUAr7jGwDp4qcQFJc2V3CC9kOywcvAPpBPZiR92uQkHXEBzwZd8u2JaGVxi9c0/X0zlFvtp4NXJyCKQqbnds0zVe+D/58FWbqqY/3ffEUDmFs6adzxf+lvsS6YfbkOGpqexKyGclM/ZFQZQd1BQrRRRZGZ7C6RdNWc+VJ12fPmQRNB3NIHVfF8KkGXBDqiMvHZSf9a/EoBhuiR7oXFs3sR1HKdcG7wT7KD6+QkFT+UEJlfS6cNbVN1Qj8c4/rbVF8ajxKswARzoQ5eG775IWK", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "The Directive Principles would enjoy permanent legal primacy.", 
		"option_b": "The Directive Principles were once again made subordinate to the Fundamental Rights.", 
		"option_c": "Fundamental Rights and Directive Principles would be merged.", 
		"option_d": "Directive Principles would be entirely abolished.", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090132", 
		"question": "2523f9H32B2q440lEi3n1e/6OG6QIG0EsWvDVqZnc2PqVqKCeuX7iYV0K12dhFR14X7Ps+Xy8kcYiq1VqaiKfiYCc45h3NGFl9b+w3lVIIZFlIQywJMNefdUxSuoNOTJKfBtx36MIlawbjf9EHhx1BzfhHlEvoL72C63WMl3wxQhk8cwvJFkbJ7Am1dg+2TrfgI5Jt3EloM1Tss=", 
		"answer": "24GwbYiz0Avvt4kpWRuy0erwdXzYBmcdsD+MVON1MHLrVbXLYfmyiZV+M1TJiEho93jSqqT8t1IBi+hZ6IKefiEGesUtEFotHjiA9RF13XJ02Nb35g==", 
		"explanation": "25y2KIX71FnH/oslQAjzhdD2OWfDQ2EQsHrDGvItKCGqGOfWZui++oJhNVmEiBtY/WPUt+Xl5FYLz7xT7M6efiMPcYx2iMSGl+Dy13JTOsRB2pR64doNefhB2DSiesfTKe4uzGuUMED1aXmbEX5wlTzThGhXpMOJ/CCzQMl3wRs21qNx/80/KN6J3Oij+kS2hQ+S0H6CBv1YH2iXgcatq0CTtZAs9d6ZsCbe8LTtkvnHsMoDZ0h0qoh7Yla5mbwI9GoKWM+8fAEL8OrUIXDkMi2gMwcL/IvTxH1nxYs5UWwntB5Uh8Naa8t2lozsuXIMfdl9GnOtq0FFy4c8UBHWdf272Gn26VorOUZpJY9grCU0sgaGIVp52n+UTTgRlo9/9pAYhwEjeHxTmXj0iz6HwGOAbtP344W8luX/r61rsqUyJ0KUPFPWX4MbJbzGZ3N6z6mfCKtTMI1mFDumONs49SrwL5iR23kPyZk0J3Kn1yWXgdn8LXCuup33wJRKGoMOGd/Aqci2vlLIdWPjJD2AZ8jmUA75THn8kwhqpVgxwCRQ53bQDZsktTkFm2fwRFF3hmfiaTyjl7Jd5IGLe84w3fGs1TMClft2loHy0F06SBb7mXdG8oeXTk5GwkCWVsRJwUdiTKAJEdbf83mfmniZC2gCP8P5F63HxSNazeLjiiF4uZYLVpiHOhzXk5Bu+hK3BO98W2To6Ir4JfEcAWUi+6Yx6OKuvIeYfbOQJGBqSxOlXOxN+oNUKDJpGAXeDDRDZavuWZtecvROxnCKpwhETnxQTBhI/pxigN/368AXrkv5OYhp", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Fundamental Rights always take precedence over Directive Principles.", 
		"option_b": "Directive Principles are more significant than Fundamental Rights.", 
		"option_c": "They are like two wheels of a chariot, both essential and balanced.", 
		"option_d": "Fundamental Rights depend on the Directive Principles.", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090133", 
		"question": "24KwaYWzxhj5t4QiXRL71vX6MSvSGiIFq3rDBvdgeDHCWaLMauD7x4MxBl+dzRMqqyGe6uX5+RMdiqRa/YeQfmIXcctJ3d6N1unyymVAP4Z2k4d68IlAPk2gHAycV6n+jYQ93JjPdZ4=", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNRgGgz7wvXrdX/fQ3IDrG+GQLdtOTOJm4GssjJZR1LAovjFBDy4", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGnhQ3it6QtVxD2yPjxISvxAHZR6y7aBfs9MHDhW6vLfeX7zddlL1nJsRlJ+3HOt+Xk+BM/nadL7JyLaR5BPop8iNHJ8fH5wHBMNshQm4wy1pMYdOAOjAGjSNroMPttx2iJJET8ayDxRHlg1CPTh3NArYf71DWvXdk7xVVjz88ppIA6dZvfzqCa60X4gRODznqfXLhhFRSQu8qh/UqYtYM0po2ZuTeb5v3+kuyT5NFLYwtDqo9tZhf8n6cF/GZ4UMawKBZC4vTfclGtLy7jNxwS6c7xwm0nhqMtWWAg/RBIg49ae4wz34ykvT4jMI14ECO/okhFw9RdTQOfd7G9kDu1rBUofXMobcppuSw5tU+LIUB22miTQTxEmJNk7MlZlAdyaGZTlWLpjTHLj2PPbIHs+4XukfG+4IVtzq0OJ1KUMF3cFoIaJbHFLml1iujbK7NSN55qEizyPNluzjD+KILYny0F1ZkyJnDv4GqNnY3lK2qqtoDtl5RhFaxAO9DB7Iu28FDCZiLtYW+aYcPgFUjxQXi40k5rsg9l2DMf/mvLAYZxuW0sjGq5Skhh0nSwPF3t1qld+cKPe4o017X40nIEkPE4vJT5xwk1UxGvhHBN/sSIR1VMxRTFCswTwRpuGLwAANbf/S2GkGTDRHJNbMb3DaTHwSkI3ubhnGhrupROWorOJBDIys40xwe0E+lgFXTsvoO5P+VVHmwpurNk3uWupcOvbLOrKiUmbg35Ed1c9ZBDbQx4FEvRBDxCabOvWJwKAcJA3X6HtA8Ic3dMRX7F6a0LSQ28r4T4fGPQYLgMAhvxI7wDU/3sT1PKdcGmxDnKH/be/5sxClopAshX/pqc+i143A==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Article 14 (equality before law)", 
		"option_b": "Article 19 (protection of six rights)", 
		"option_c": "Article 31 (right to property)", 
		"option_d": "Non of these", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090134", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRvl85xgQBviyfz8MG+QF2oU40+PU616eX/kFITNY+D32oR4KFLJhFU7oCaX9uX2+EFPn6Ra54CadGIHe51qxN+Z2uH50DFIPYZtlIR75cVd7Un8dTsXpKzBjhYl3V6R/w==", 
		"answer": "25uRXLiz8Bjz+IJgGjDz0fTwO2rcQ0sfsGuKRrZgeX7tFKHNfK3K25Z/NFqGn1Zy/HGGiqv0/lJGzSXt7p8VVzMCZsLE2To9Rc0=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHx3h3zt5EoUwqy1/jvOWrTBmZRt3eGEpN4cX/tXanFLs7xxJp4NE+AglU7+3iG8fWhohMJgLob+YKefiwGestrzcaM2+vnyXRPJ4ZNlMBb6p4WfbRJ3325fNGbDtda5y6hJlz/YHn1KnFgnT7Yi3AWgY2o4S6vQc4+zxtykIhqrfwuPdmM36eB5US2gUar0n+YSfQsI1GfsNyt5UCZ4I45rcCEujPV9eC5uPfc+5Moakhmt4M/R1Kukqsd8Tw9EfimYRxI+PTcZEetLy7jFBoc7c6j5ntlz4EwFCs1K9rvQWwb5PC225294Gdv", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Central Economic Planning Committee", 
		"option_b": "NITI Aayog (National Institution for Transforming India)", 
		"option_c": "Economic Development Authority", 
		"option_d": "Socio-Economic Advisory Board", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090135", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEhPzzPO/JX7CE20Cpj+MVON4cX/nFLXHaOLsxNd9JkuazUt64WXDp+Xy7hMcm6lP7J3AMtVTazaFSJczuEBb0/rldEI=", 
		"answer": "24G3KJPh2Bftt4YoUxD1wO6/PGWQF2oU436EQKJmeXDtFLTNbeT73Y4xJlKNzVJ24mTJtaCw5UYdjqQb6oGRdCsXd4Rh25Je1pYLw8+X0ZBnyeZoEwWu", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdH+0BDkt5U1QA791vi/Om2QD2Mfpz+RV6V7YnyjWKbVfa3uyIRiIljJj0I74WLHt6Djt1ocz7xUqYyNeSwEPohnyd6O0ve3zX8BJ85B2oF19psNdfVOjC6id93eNOcuz2CEZ0z9dyuyEnU0hiTEi3AWq4y18S6vXdU501Uwj8d56cwuOcSM0KaUqESrlROHzzudQbZhUViYu8ro70qPtJAxt9iZuD3VuLTtn/bS/t0SIhpbuI5rcBf8lqYNuD4wVIi1ah1H+PDZblqtLy7jIQsI/crvlnhoyIYhUmUw/RFBwpBPcdR224uq/A4+A8NeHTappgRSwpJzTRqFNLyx3Sjw7xU6e2k+d48tryI2qA6QaF5riX+VTykd1IV669kNlAZveC9MnXjkwjuCk3GddZH2/4nzi6SwobdnsqYpIUCONlncFowbd7rDMmtm3/uaAeZMIZBjAiHyNMMn6CC1YIOYyzAA0c0lI26n+C+YlsT7PiWuvNL2mNFkFbMMdtPA/d+yolHCbzehKHPTdN7mWASwQ3Xu1gJsvxcqzDJQ6WzcSJpw9iQC03uzRkprny7jLH+umLpV/ouBcZ1/m8fp2zcCnfp7mtv71QUxTg+6g35X8qaQQFcC7lyWKsUChC0nHrECAJ/H9y2mh3/eSHUdc8vlQaeBgx9c2/f0zlFys5kNTMXMcTT1bAg+yHiC1MqN+KgjCQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "To bring changes in the agrarian society and improve rural conditions", 
		"option_b": "To increase agricultural exports", 
		"option_c": "To distribute land to industries", 
		"option_d": "To establish large commercial farms", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090136", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRjp48U3Uw2ywPP+Nn/VByIFrD+TQKxgdXL3FLPKa633x4N0NVmamUg7/XCGr6Ty+EFPnK1Y/YeQfjFcPDCcd/M09btDew7LWm4hSJU=", 
		"answer": "24GwbdHQ3hf+5YQjRl7exP/wIHmQMWcWtnOCRqp7fjHiWqOCT+/xxZ5lLlOHzXp45jaO8vynpxpNgyqNNy9DPNVoQQ41uqVe6A==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQ3hf+5YQjRl7exP/wIHmQS1AUpGqPU7d9f3+jVanGLsz8xpt4M1WGgxI703XS7+WhrgRfz79a+s6MYCcAd41my9GF2/23wX9AMNJBnsBm69oPbvtUyT65NMDTJb5nwHqFNUDjcyr9C3Y0lz7Ynm5Xq5f7+Sa5W8gy0gZ81rNw6IgdP8Pf2KGe+w2siVy+0kefGfNWFFOMuc+87gOIqId4sMCdvT3C+fH3jrjc9p4IbQZGrYd8dxuwlqoG6moxX4i3bQBf8O3eIVH+NCmhKwcO8cbm2GB6hoMnWSk9+htTkZdEa8VgmKTqgDxicexoGj+zsEwAzoA8VhnWd7iqxGnt7hU8fGgocId+qCw7ogqPaEN2n3mZDCVF1Il4vtYWgApnPXtP3HTlwj7LlmCGcNPl5JK8le3isLx356IzIE+HdVjdRoETd7LCK2Iy3eaJBq9SNN9kGCziNMEn8zfqbqqa4zdenvwuPGL18WqOl8HzOHe/84LrgcJ/B7YPOMKJqdiis1SHYDChInydcs7xVxu8D279wBp3uBco221Q6WzcSIZr/Sgf3nyxWk1n0ibtaXKogrdZ+cKIcJxx0PriySARm+A4k5r12w9yewqHgysNn4WRS11byBTCFshHyAAtCboSHZjWsmKQ1XXfRWgffs3iDrqUgy1G3qP0nXV8vZwHRoSDKRfPmZ4ywBalQfh0RWviscb6MvIBGGUv7vJ9y++upYTzR/aiKXcvYRmyGeNY65hYYwN1EB+dJytAa/WNXt0qSeUP9nzYkgRcTmlMRWre8qYLVBSmr9eIYWyeUKUdGhuiU7wJGs3hBwWUGW2BA9nOCfiTOPZRhoeR", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "The National Development and Labor Act", 
		"option_b": "The Industrial Protection Act", 
		"option_c": "The Contract Labour Regulation and Abolition Act (1970)", 
		"option_d": "The Employment Rights Act", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090137", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kQn4+IIyUxOyxPTyMG+QAnZRsX6KQap6dzH3XKKCffn/x5NwNVjJgl07/n/Qqqv3t1wJz7he5p6TdWIKcMt93cKI26T21nRAIJkGzKHYUtkr3k7WZx0TPNLVew==", 
		"answer": "25y2fJT0wxj+8oFgYAvgxPG/EW7GBm4es3KGXLc0QGPsU7XDY+D7id8gfgvRxBlE5NsU1ENxW6h2JKrAL4nw", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjwxbt5YQtEgr6xOm/NGLdBmZRomvDQKJ9Y3jtU+fWZui+2oNwKViIn187/XCGr6zm/l0Iz6ddqZ6afzIPe8tmxpCbwvb2yDFAIcNFicB799oLdPEA5TO5cdPJIepryi6yMlfxa3mZAWZxmD7Gh3lYvMOL5yi8Rts6zRBy3q5Kyfh1cpej15SdxEytiAWK2X/RQbMkQA3O7YLownG4kMIrutiKuSab4Pu5iurc5tcPZ0hbsYVwbl7xkK0H/Tg5RcG6b1JK4vfVdUetNCfjMwYYudvs2WZs1ZZpUm904BdDwpFDcMF/lojrsyB8f9pjATv6okoAwplsVxaFfa7432ak7VQtcnMlZIZkpigx4QiOJ0FuiSfcWCMRnIVn7pAVnAJ3PXtImXugjSqfwGqJPIPs/YXukfGwobdnsqoqOVOPI1mYQoUZbKGAKHF32OiXAeZPJ55pEyP0OZUh+nn1KYCd0T5DmOslKXL18SSal435OH23upn4gNViVJ0POdqIysP3hFTCIQfoM3iQcsLiXEjAXXX20Ad1ux02iC4WqFHMCZ16tR0CknezUA0myQXnLwC6T8DOsBlhsTyO8g==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Integrated Rural Development Programme (1978)", 
		"option_b": "National Poverty Eradication Program (1990)", 
		"option_c": "Rural Employment Guarantee Scheme (2002)", 
		"option_d": "Agriculture Modernization Plan (1982)", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090138", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7n1+3wJm6QDGRRt3eGErd8YnTmGbPLa/++2ZZ/JFSIlFpv+zbUoq+w5Eocm61WqYeRZDAMep5szdTJ3uq37X9FOscb2KbSZRX2c6kL0kPaA5FCyFk=", 
		"answer": "24G3KIXh0Bf5+4Q0V17VxPP7PWLaChsC43uRV6J5MH7lFKLUa//niYF4K1CIil478HPPraKw9hMdirhO64KWc2IKcJ9giMKM1uj+0GgDSMp40+2caPAnZYs+hbZXqQ==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjxAv6+JYlEhH0hen3MCvEC3AUpjKXW6ZmMEHiWqTKb/T/3Z4xFV2DzUhi4WLDruX5+UcdgKxO6oubMCsNPqJhzNmIl+3khGVOc9RBm4x7/p9faPxFjCukZ93ULr5hyC6EIkb1aS2vBXx9jjTSyntZvoap+ya1V993wRs21pN3rcouNdmYmamR51isxhKK2TuYTLhlUVuf9cm66lCPso03od7NtTfW+/frm/vKvJ4OcRtXsZJ2Ylewjugd6is2QsS1fBtF9qT3YFrpKCGpLncOuc/x03Vkho0vHWwi8Q1fwpVfbsxy0Z2kvjc5McoqFHOppkhGiodpWRGfd7S93nyk8lAvYHgnbIkttSMhrk+OLVVyk3+FAmxtmrxlytgc1Rd6bntFkTbhizKYwHGAPJTq/YW8lefnpasj5qxnPUmFdVDXVYwQJaPFKHd+z6XbCKhPJo1uGSWmOdAj8zrrIYKd3Hkd0cs0JnTu5CuNm8L7eWS0t9L9i9d/B7YPOJzI6MC+vluHYDehNXWWJt39VQTxSHm0kwxpuBsuhGER5maYDIBs4T8EnWrwRUFylyvzIjydmIJS3oqLP5o5wfDpnSYZneZr3++38w89SkSLjHFAuoWGTkgPhULfEsEGwwxuALEXEZqYvi2mlHjTQ30Uftq2MqmKyjhBmqvzgm5+tNACUJqLIFCXyt8ozFeLCPF4FVfsuo/qNf0RSiwo86Fl2OSio4q3cOWhICxqG1q2S+oZ95BCYQV1FA+dESsPZba9Q48bAexA0XTG1xRNS3kEAlXa/roGXAqpr4TJYG6eZrcaCx32aqUAU8f1XkvKOPSn3DHdD7CS1Ui4H1YwXDuRYbQI8wL8dZz/IR2n03tn8cToN0IVDLESOiLhcWW6oOOPCh43dickJotTOmXaRBtptzaDE/FizYMJYh0uVaGxHBAmhBhBnDfCAl1W8EMYH5a5QUciaplKLFIS1H73kX4Mj7V7dc6iw5b5kzSzIg==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "To establish urban self-governing bodies", 
		"option_b": "To promote industrialization", 
		"option_c": "To centralize political power", 
		"option_d": "To translate Gandhiji’s dream of every village being a republic into reality", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090139", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7n1+3wJm6QDGRRt3eGEo11ZHjsWqbOLs7xxJp4NE+AglU79HnU45bz/1YLmqRe7c68cTEXe5gvyd6Nl9f0zHRFJspBnsBG9pMdeecfjrdeuiFwfo2Kpb4FLQSKpE0=", 
		"answer": "24G3KIHh3g3v9JFgRhb3hfTxIW7CBnEFsD+MVONHU2KjVanGLt7K2tURdw0HYQs3PL1PnXeCHN4g", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHjxAv6+JYlEhH0hen3MCv+AnYYrHGCXuNXf3zuXbTRZ+LwiZF+NRy6jlN+9mPKpqGw1FIcm61IqcaxUxEgN8tuxtTJw+zyhF9AJ89LlIF+pLkQcflJ3y6ke9qbJvF8jl2DL0D0cjW4ADBAhjjUj28W4K2YxhPyFNMkgAE91pdq4tw5P8Pf2KaXqF2qiQuNyH7RXLVhUUaQssa8+AOdroZ4vMOZtCDe5+Dq2vfVsMoDZ0hhvI56Z06wkqxJ2ysrRc2nKFp40veZIVXjJGiQJAYY/d7v03Ap8pAgX2wntFd1tpAfItJ2xYjhvyY5KchmDH36l0xFzoY8UhaYcLys1Xuk6Vs8eW8vYNBRshE78EG1JkJ7iX+VSy1FnY5svtEXkURucmFJiHnyizGMwGycb4bm+MDugOTxtLxnsrcoaVWIMBzLV4sZYqbBNWNhivmJArBVN5pjVyTpL5Ud3yq5IZiQnwo5w5ccIUvppmSwnNzgMHezvZW5h9piG/8TJtTG4M2+sxzEbi7xLXyaaN/nGRr1SH3q1wdrsFgxwCRQ7GfIGoBp9DkEkXDwRkIkgC7nZGiy1r9S7sKdfog01ODtzzYD1sh2o5Wkmjw4UQ2ohHFE8oWRSxxCzF/fEMpH1gwtA7kMEZjV83mfmnjDC2gCP9r+BOiAzDpNyO38i29p/58AFZyBIBDYg9s1iBa/Bb10UGb+vZT8LrwTBXZs7rp0iuinsc+4YfqyKSUjYgq7XOJc/YFQfAt0H0vSA2RcYb6rUYgfU+RcknTEk0dfQnNPBEjJu7gaUgO4q8nbIFbQX79IQC7jcacMEMfoT1PGO/bpyT7NRr6Yg06tVkoiDjWTYaQF4Efgdo38Khq9lCh0687mN0JIBIUYLmfge2iwqu6GCAk0cCEsK8pDf1HQRx80mTvNM7loi+czUwttQKajWWMihV9zkQLcWxZ2pU4TVrG5SV0gartAMFQD2ST1Ba9fSBTPxgoYi0WVxifiPbpKP0c2emiflgzhlZYmnuupjZqJD8aiObQW155DKaUbVp/HClIOn/ek4O+gBWQ8RmByL+vdTOfC8Fv3Cc364sLUwRxfwbtIJk00IiuOmoyZ8TllJqBZanQE9UEcqs/AZwip3MhV1EhlWV7t+0DwAUUuuRo+TZurXtXZar+s4lVcAi3RUvlzivV23iX0OdrCJBU5R1AhkBOVNuLFyz2AJOW5R/QQRNy/PZLJbCS3rX7B1A==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "To protect the interests of SCs and STs", 
		"option_b": "To monitor urban development", 
		"option_c": "To oversee educational institutions", 
		"option_d": "To regulate media content", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090140", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV16jla7tMSvxDmcfp3KGXLc0UXL3FKjELr+umM4xIV2KhFdy5nfSpvqyow4iBwzrJttNtLW+QfMFMQ==", 
		"answer": "2+ToLdHh1Arv5ZMhRhf9y735OnmQJmEerXCOW6B1fH36FJDHb+b729dCIl+dhFR14TaOhpLD5BpNbc7Q63W15WdfKTrWCeqO3w==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdGigUr488UBXxv8wfD6O3+QImEF43CFEvEkISijUqbBZ+H33ZZlIljJmVN+smbUrLP55FoAgehU786KYGIXccs+mJXJxeHkwWNXMtJNlY4y4pUNPNFDwzOied3YIfJi1y63IkT7Yiv9N3V3gDjZhG8W4KaMxjTyFNM5gBI9gIJq48U5MsPf06eR+w25iALC2X+ES7xwGFuXtMLo4k2PtIssoNmEvjzIurTFlMTdxNYCcUhAupV6cU29g6EG9moxQoi7fhdZseXeZRTsIie1Ik4J8c6j02xg1ZYgU2505hpVh5FAY9R62Zb3/DQ/LY1ZFju/p1FMwpA8fBaFYLirnCjX4106cW8nYI4tiD88owqPZBR/lG/cYzhZkZIr3NEanhNib2sAv3rhkSyOkyvPSJvmq4H1iKj/pvl3+qo0aUCNMFLcW4gScfPXJnQy3ubbCL5INpFjVzbuOJUs+Tf8Jp+AzHkC1pkyKmTi5jyYhsT6NyWuvNLthttlEf8XPt6Jqc+yo0zOdSahL3KHJsnxVQf+SHX21E5xuFgkxjhQ+mfLDZtp8ClNnX+kTENrgD6sLHqglbsc74GBcYE82vas1TMCnOdwlovkmlUOQgK+n3pNsYHfQ11XwF3dH8MG0EkMA7sKWbXZslmekDb0Qm4IfNr/F63H8z5B1OD4nm14rNABU8y9OBjPj54Wxxu4AuQwF0rlbzGY+/e2DEbpz6VmRIw=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Expansion of the scope of Scheduled Castes", 
		"option_b": "10% reservation for Economically Weaker Sections (EWSs)", 
		"option_c": "Introduction of international relations programs", 
		"option_d": "Implementation of women's empowerment initiatives", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090141", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1RDut5EoV17R1/TyPGXRDyIhsXCAV6dhYnSjd6jGa622mM4mdBXJiVQ7+3iGsaD89kcGgKYb/YHfZCoGPoF6zNmK3uXl3S4D5/a9IsjKukYLjvU3KsNRSA==", 
		"answer": "24a9eJDh0A3v88U0Whuyz+j7PGjZAnAI43mRXa40ZHnmFKLaa+7r3Z5nIhyAgxtr53TKqqaw5FYdmaFY7J3dBxUwJTTJfc+S6zJn1wZekw==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHQwxDn/oshXl7C1/L8MG/FEWdRgHCHV+M8U2PTd+6CYeu+mM4mdByZgVpi93KGouXj/lQBhq5S6o+RZGIRcYdqiNmHl/D/wTFSNtZFiIFm7ZURPPtGjCmlcZTRNfpnzWeBNVywYSuyCTBgnDSWj2RTq5av/DG+FNM5gAE6k8d56cU1Mt6MzbqS/ES3iEaN2juBXb9oGFfZpsu6/UqfpZF09cieoTfY/fX1luGT8cpLdgBX/4J2cE+unqsduCY9R824KBNF9aTSZFjiN2bjGwAh9//r32cp0YM6HWA6tBNPjIYWdcln3tjwtDdwG8R4EDCuqlJFh6RuVhmVfa201Xuk71N/Rm4qcY8tjCI5qAyFZBRtim6fRSpYl4Fn8slZtBZ3dGxMmTa10nPLl22Gf5uj7o3sjenjqaNm4eMzIUTAJlnIV58dcbrPKSd9zKmPBaMcOYpjHiHvPMc3vD/rL5vUyzEIkNw4KnTy4COPl4O1BWuGvabxi5R/GqsFOMWF686/uVLDITfpKG7Tdc7kWBrxW3X33U5ytgtl3C5Q7WzLHZt6tTkFmz65R0BhgiLuaHmvlbsc5YTOa4Y0k//52TsTkfVqhtv22hl8Uwv7gH5KvJCeRlIPxEDFXsQK1Ag8GL0AGJ/F6y2fmzbEQ3lNe8flEa2J0C1c0+z/zm57/5obRpiHLxyVwuwjzhKjBPN6UCfhqZ70NPcUBGU4upB+xebslML7QfuhbEEjfR+0TeZP9tVhegt1EgLNCSFcILeoFq4KQPRKkkXFmw5LXjYL6pViVxzG38LnzgyZorX2kQ==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Combined the roles of judiciary and executive", 
		"option_b": "Separated the judiciary from the executive in public services", 
		"option_c": "Created executive courts", 
		"option_d": "Abolished judicial authority", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090142", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTjp48U3Uw2ywPP+Nn/VByIFrD+TQKxgdXL3FKbMbeT7x4MxKlOHmFZ+/GLV7+Xj/kcKnOQb6ICbMDAGc4pmxsPWlf2ds+/JJnofvAVIwGRoEuA=", 
		"answer": "25S2a5j23w2q9oskEjb71unwJ2LTAm5RjnCNR65xfmWjVanGLszsyp9wIlOFglxy8XfK45b541Ycz6lV7c6tdS8Cd4V8iPGKw6S/lSgUYo8GlGgRLx/EWGS+uJPmDYPukA==", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHy0g2q8oshUQr3wb3rOivAEW0FpnyXEqJ6c3jmWrOCY+Lw3Jp0KUiawRto+2LDsOmw9l0Lz7pe5I+WfjFDd5gv3NiMl8X5x3hEPdIEt4988ZcacuBTjDyjcJT6Mv1mz2uPK0r3bjq8CDBHnSXTmTxXpof7xyK2VdM501UTlZM44s58bY7KgebT1EOEiC6Ny36HTa8oUV2N8t3o/EyOtIp4u8KZuDzctODxm+yT5NYOIgtdrZR6YE/8makE/WoxQoigYBcLzabxb1fkJSa3ZyMS997u03p91cIoU2101Q1FioJTbcx80ZHnvT5wDMR+ECD6okpEh6Z5Uhafeq748WvwrBVuLC9zWcgtvSMx4QGTPBQvwz7NAmxtmrxlytgQhkRifnsAjGTvlDaPhXbPepzxq5T0gKjgsrxw97ExKFWJOlKUFp0OaqfFJHN7xefXTadSN99qFivoKdAg/Tf6Jdab2XkM3topKnnztCuXlo39MHauvIDwjdV6VLIPOMTI7MWjoxzGbyehIG+QbsrxVgT/SHX70gIlpBExzTJQ6WzcSJt6+CwEkG3wRkIknCb0ZXOvl7Ic44+ecJwl0vvv2HxQseA4npfk210uQgOugX5Xt5ffTk5MxVXTEcEIwwAtDbhBEY7S83uXgX/fRW9NfsDyQbiVzCRB2OrlnSF+uoIaVIWAbBjYntcwwQO4BO45XGmtqYj9ff0HBXEi/vJh2OK1ssmvcPfkLXcvbgn5Ed1c9ZBDbQx4FEvRBDxCabOvWJwKAcJA3X6HtA8Ic3dMRX7F6a0LSQ28r4T4fGPQYLgMAhvxI7wDU/3sT1PKdcGmxDnKH/beDUr6/UbFsniOJP5RMZiaxw==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "3", 
		"option_a": "Ancient and Historical Monument and Archaeological Sites and Remains Act (1951)", 
		"option_b": "Monumental Sites and Relics Protection Act (1960)", 
		"option_c": "Archaeological Treasures and Sites Act (1963)", 
		"option_d": "Heritage and Antiquities Conservation Act (1967)", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090143", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz0Avvt5YvXxuy1/j+JmTeECIXrG3DRqtxMHjtV6jPfuH73ZIxLlGZgV5293jSorH5+F1PgK4bzYeNdSEXd51qiOCb3ur0zWFNNtUb2E84oWc1cmS8HLBy3rxFpF8=", 
		"answer": "25y2aZX2wAzr44BgVBf8xPP8PGrcQ3AUsHCWQKBxYz2jQanEb/vx3IVwJVCMzUh08X/J7qDz+F0AgqFYqY2QfiYKaoJgxsPFl/T41GRNMtJNlY4y4YIPcPtTxTKjOJTINOxvx2CFIwXTYjepFnU5hyXXnnkWuoa39DOyW9QkjFUzmIM44McuOZndRfaK6vY8HZ3PIfkYlIynBA==", 
		"explanation": "24O5epj8xAqq8YQjRhHg1r38OmXEEWsTtmuGErd7MGXrUefLYO7xxId9IkiMzVJ24nrDrqD+41IbhqdVqYGZMAYKbI5s3Nmf0qTH1nhPMM9UloVhqNoWcvdM2TmketObKfBvymuRMkTkYnmvAWN7gSPVj28WqY2/tTS0V9M4jRAxmYl34ME/fNSX2KSf7UO/gxXMlEmUTrh2FFqasI6k6luRqYk5u8yZ8RDU+/+0ufCTxNYOIixbrYN8d1Kqkug56iM2UsGkZBdYsevWIWf5ITymZz4S9cLgzz0re5ucwjlt07j90Hl9ssIbzA==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Lack of government interest", 
		"option_b": "High public disapproval", 
		"option_c": "Inadequate financial resources, unfavourable socio-economic conditions, population explosion, strained Centre-state relations, and more.", 
		"option_d": "Overwhelming success of other programs", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090144", 
		"question": "25i5fJL7kRzr9I1gRhvgyL3oPH/YQ2sFsD+AXbFmdWLzW6nGZ+P5iZN0NF+bhEtv+3nI7eWwtxNPz+gbqc7fMGJDPssviJDJl6S3hDEBc4YE2sAypNpfPLQAjH3tNJSbYL4uji7AZwWwJ3n9RDA01HGWyjwW6MP7tWf7FJp3gFVy1sc4rYh8fJffmejTqA34xkbCnDvRCP0kURTZ9Y7oqwPc4MJ49Y3N8XKbtLS52riTsJ5LIkgS/8Y/Ixv81+hJuGp4EYj0KFILsaSQIRStYGjjZ05duYujljQphsJpHSl0tF8GwsMWIoAzltik/HJwf40qVXP64wQAh9Q8H1fWNP34kCikoBV/NTprJcot/G114U/caBQ+2ivcDGwR1MArvpBZ1UQjPS8A3Dagwn/LwCXPPNOjq8C8xaiw4PkjsuNnaQHAdRyYFs1cJfOAZycyiqnbTeYcc98nV2KmfZVuvHm5YNbUn3lNkJlgbzentGrZ0o21eSX689K5zpQ2VP9AdpGFqYv38ByHIWOhYT3TJou0GUiwDzy4k04l91hliGFQqCKYSMk/tW1N3j7wCQQk0megLDzh1v4cqsLOP85xk7WsnXJQ2LQ439u3lF18B0T7zT8D8sTfDxwPjRSWXo1HhEluTPRBVNaRsi3W1TaQCzxNP462QejHg2wImqOxziE9/9BOFczObFmbyp5miFfxQb05FSet6Ma5fbxVSiRsuvIxiq3h94r7NbPkbCVqL1r3Ga8Zs9URKEI7UUudRWQPIPjuFt1eAaAPkjWK10cIBz8JRRqMu+hIHUTq6oSILiqeI/FcTl6iI/NFU464DgePdbHpiHCJRv/c1Qf+HwRlDnrdYfBNpUewOsyyZFPz0ygkuYGlchEbBMNXfGezNCv55ePDS0Z6P2xlaMoHOgeVC1Bk1H6DZ7knzedAMFhtAejnWRBW1lEP336SThgF8AxeH+XtABNnaukFYBtRjXf1UeBfHFyKxnpKzhbcgmKsaboLcQljOyTTzwyg29Im37+pws7BSpSibf1bks1DaPYbBNqWXxtc2rOkr6GgUSx5Ri03briIHqKR8A+2Qoi04oOahRwLif5Idh97ZXnLyd+ZsHotb+UPLzAK/TNZ7IqSIkbqmcgZlRAoEBWstQGkASdh9lEzLtOrKp2catvlsBAfVmSHF/kD2Lw4nWykdZ+RJFp/RyN10UfQNpKKh3TDfey7gO1JRVjil9mLBcotrAg5jpzygwwA63s1zzyiSzaaIqetqF4UYjw4C/TfWh0dxldilXrxnhOofc/qx+ZJzvABmPVToUy34mE2zx7MDwqOIzOqnrbe9yaG/gdhieojHCbjGzMtjkxkBLBrsjkuAG1hCeE0/Pa1bPGE3iHvbtz4jcxNpRYUBueKb/37/ZW8ZeOFb+WsmcDDbzKhsdMpRLXvZZ5FYDaNJH1f5P60IsSELUnTfCvEkvvYUmvOZWAbrjku2iLOFFgsbSDzC4kdXnYS0MI2Y/lR5I6k8AolPCqAWvEomeFJ2xsZTBAZCryh2DENWLgiec7cMh8tvxZcSa9VKi33KQo2J5wGmyP0A2fvq2n8w/ouRJer1VQ5aEvah2TIOTWcqKs0amzlH4KFgtfZQkXi4LRgAREQtegS0kTNRjxRNiUk41aEzKEvGBnMLlBsfr5Sh5xVC5m39kVO1oFnRk1aKTmYXXr5W9iEF5VLStfik/hn69pej3ACR9FOOMzCB1aN0y7PWi4SPAICJgTe0FC2rd89xZ6OUVvPr23wxpSkXxOc/CMZ3pynWo5SnBNiKMzR34emQ6N037ihTGRKBoBcpTFU3ygfYjPWUhYtgbelaGmRIE/+oh9ti8biyNcxyK3ZknPlf2NjDbtQCZZrhZMYg8P3vf4SfI1+M2sQBEJSviEXfosWyvaPDUV9bKLf+WzsDtIgC2lgGh9kykO0t+Xxu84yDm66veZGKjjPuZKo8ekIZwJQDwK0vPMbpeM+yurUECi8dy5Y/65TvUyPUVC8BAajpP+pjwTO8Hm2vtAdzFhT0qgPt+yfM0FN6iaNy4FU6mz0DRs4yu/uYaGYs02W3cftsISVsOEdBr7RWb6ZxjT4DaAp+rxjUShgGLA35NKVGjhrXqtafVMTLJCdNeRWmIindCyAwYiyPXTkYS2TaltrS5xz/yaPvKlTUGoFS7yBzf5kGtkxAqv/Xw7LiUR1BBpmYsQKzEq5YpeIilTiE7vcoEOj5IdjiT1G9pYK5Kky6UCZdzyG5jYnmjGmQSB+FqcEtzT8Jvf2Faf1K8eady2daNgS9LI4cBeOllyix/Df/Jav2W2MC4pyA/w1VcR4tVobUN+taCyP4PW9VCks7ikwKqTBEEaKfXtRPRv9gdoLlfkdx96z3lqPYKTKeAyIQS7NNw2UXItG1hZ2HWfWHTx9fkB+EkaCsPMfd4KN8QoNCkTKoX42idfpw6xeHJdecDNZdmk9xNcwHYi2sR98zL86AhzYobuyXAug7G5CWZDqEKLvfkunsaRJhEdoFcN0pSEKpVYJURxUCDAIFbvR+atLcO1iqYhbWAq2t8m2juiw7llCiHOh3ynbt/3ZAUfdWdbIbWW3Spl4XM59WfkowTBrsBvdl1kA9jnAFO7GH7kXa4pmIeWkLt5NmAelqpyGfb6Fo2Cdw7VmbcsB/qyfNw/wvzF62lAB27ce8wMHNB3U33fx8n8RP7zn42znBfgV8XgxmjIiGa1+uIi6dFXNgQbYAWaHI5CRrB9EfdI+O2Tzh7HP3rylz4FeuiSg+ftCvIby9MdktdLtOk7uigMyPEMmzCuxEZZm+nFJ3TCIEAOaDOlChh3yqA/WRhC/qOjBA24vAm3MwpSoKTVwTENiDU6r6NHIsW5d/7a8f5dqhq20oG3/KyQ42LTueu3vCVKxVIPVxUFpzJM=", 
		"answer": "25T1PN2z81S4u8UDH0++hdmyZim+f6qNNIP4NPxTCwNMN2hd", 
		"explanation": "25T2KKH/0Bfk/osnEj39yPD2JnjZDGxL41qQRqJ2fHjwXKLGLvnxiZF+NVGcgVpv9zbHraGw+EUKnbte7M62fiYKf8x8iNSMweH7y2FMNshQ2pB+5ZQMMLRFwi64Zt3VJ759wW2JKAj1ZDazC319l3HRmHNBvIv1ySmHWvh5gDkzmIM4/806M8WSmaSS/17ixi+MyGmeTKhnFFDZocHo+UaPtJAtttmYozeb4Pz82vnU4t8Zawlc/4p+bV+vlKkZ/WZ4Q82wfRFC/+OQbVXjJGigKAAe/MX3xHV9z40nHWg68F9DjJBDcMl90djhrSc5K8xoGTb6p01T04Z1XQKCfbK2nlTq3FscOzoGbIRksTg44TidL1Ft2kqfWHYRpJJk6tUagRcjcW5Ck2SggCbLk2CbaJrt7MD9xf/xp7wj9K8oJlPMdVnWRZgObL3HZ3B92OKeH7UcIZpkEivwOJUo/TDrYJWb0ikI3sohO37o+mSlnPH7HSv6npPti8Z4HasZdvPA586xuUiHQCD1ez2gZ83xXh3xXXjrkxptslg3wSYY/HGYB48/4iIflXe+TgRznSrlYjylg6xV5IXOco8l1ufi1CYJ1LR9kYjixhQyQESvhXpa8paaTFlG21GWHMgJwQ8nGKdBFZjVsmeZlzbDTn8YbcfiGObP8SlO3/H0gGJ4/5wPTYGHJxjVi8pm6hi+CrBaXSfZoIO5GfUHD2c486R0it2zvsS4fOOoKXZqYBz3avtY55ARWA13GAjETGa2JWkbGsJf6HntCSOP2ZSH", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "A-4, B-2, C-1, D-3", 
		"option_b": "A-1, B-4, C-2, D-3", 
		"option_c": "A-3, B-4, C-2, D-1", 
		"option_d": "A-2, B-3, C-1, D-4", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090145", 
		"question": "25y2bJjykRHr5MUiVxv8hfvwOWffFGsfpD+XWqY0YH7vXaTbLuL4iahOGGO2smREzUn5nJrx+VdPn6lV6oaMeCcGcst7x5CZxev6y2VEc89KjoVg6psLdftOzTHtZNHaI/suz2CEZ1b1ZCyvDWRd2nNHOx5IncC0haEXi3b1D7P0", 
		"answer": "25u3Ztzy3RDt+YglXAqwXMynIchrfENjMo091iO9JQ==", 
		"explanation": "25y2bJjykRHr5MUiVxv8hfvwOWffFGsfpD+XWqY0YH7vXaTbLuL4iZl+KRGIgVJ8/HvDrbGw9l0Lz7ha542XYyoGe4cv3N/Jx/b4yX5VNoZNlJR39pQeaP1PwjyhNMTeIf1rjm+OIwXjYjqoFnlgjX+euHlQrZG++yS+FNY22Bg7nYZ27Nx8HtiQ0uWw4A2MjgPC+HKDTb5wGEKc9f664k2fqZI0sN7NvjSbx+D4jv2TwNEHawtL9sRTx2/emijNjSEq4AzVQG0S", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "No,n-a,li,gn,me,nt", 
		"option_b": "", 
		"option_c": "", 
		"option_d": "", 
		"quiz_type": "fillup", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090146", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kTj444wjXhuyyvu/IWPVQ0EerWyXW7dhZHjsWufHY/32yIR4PVmazU9z9zbWsar9+EcGgKYb5ojfdSYWfYp7wd+H1ui3xX9Fc8NHlY596ZMcPP1O2Di/ccfPM75hyC6zJE31YyyxAXQ0tzDFnnlF5MOI9i++UM87xRFyopVx780vcJee16zT51mwgxTCy36QQ7h2UUecttqh5E2P/8CUc0UkvvZZnxCkCMDc9miP", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3Ryqo9NiCVw6GBKfUr+CQkjgUitiaQ==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3Ryqo9NgVBHx0O76JivfDSIBsXCOXbd9fnajUaPXbezqwJh/JlDJjFV/snPFrKv/+loMz6FV/YuNdTEXbctgzpC61OzywGRNNsIEuYFh8J8MMLRzzzWocMHXJfou+nyJJUDjK3m8CnQ0gzTXgXlE6JC+9jOyW9Qkjl0Ak4F9/80yP9Lf1amL5USzhwiDyDuzR7JvXHeR9fqg7gO4qZA9ttmEpzebxObwlPva4NIOcUhducZMd1qokug59yYxUtH9Kqyta4SywLYSYoYDJDzTLYc=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Article 44", 
		"option_b": "Article 46", 
		"option_c": "Article 48", 
		"option_d": "Article 51", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090147", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz1Rbv5MUBQAr7xvH6dT6AQ20X42uLV+NXf3/wQK7We/n3xpkxNVmFjE9+smLJ/OdJEmuA/7pH56fx2TRf+fog", 
		"answer": "24a9eJDh0A3j+ItgXRiy0fX6dWHFB2sSqn6RS+NyYn7uFLPKa6370ZJyMkiAm141sDHX+UXaVcMZYuo/O9gCs14=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqotVgQhvg0fz2O3iQF21Rt3eGErBxYHDxVbPLYeO+xpExM1SMzVFu9n/FqqTi7hMJnadWqZqXdWIGZo5s3cSAweG5jENENcNWn45x4doTfexNxTasetXPYNxhwWXNBE2wUzG4RFR9hjTVnnVArcOL5y61V9MnzBAh1oh+rfsoPcOamZic5ES7n0/ATYdVqdsMoqDedsDbsLNr9Q==", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "2", 
		"option_a": "Promotion of international peace and security.", 
		"option_b": "Separation of the judiciary from the executive.", 
		"option_c": "Protection of monuments and places of national importance.", 
		"option_d": "Right to work, education, and public assistance.", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090148", 
		"question": "24GwbdHX2Avv9JEpRBvhhfTxNmfFB2cV43aNEpN1YmWjfZGCYeu+3Z90Z3+Gg0hv+2LTt6z/+RMOna0BqxQhC4ZxI2HanuRlCRhE8AY=", 
		"answer": "25u3Ztz5xAr+/oYpUxz+wL32OyveAnYEsXrNEF8qkOZicl5UkfGIF6FNJK0=", 
		"explanation": "24GwbdHX2Avv9JEpRBvhhfTxNmfFB2cV43aNEpN1YmWjfZGCb//7iZl+KRGDmEhv+3XPoqf88h9Pgq1a54eRd2IXdo52iNGb0qT5y2UBNshClZJx4ZsdcPEA2DW/e8HcKL56xmvAJErldS2uSjhGkTfTmHlYq4b7+SajWdM8wRszgsda4sc3cfSXmZyb7Q2cjxSH32+YXrgkIUaQu82h+0+Zs8I3s42+pTPP8bTJlfTa88dCIFj4bXeNu3oaat9/buOClrk=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Justiciable in nature.", 
		"option_b": "Enforceable through the judiciary.", 
		"option_c": "Non-justiciable in nature.", 
		"option_d": "Applied only to linguistic minority groups.", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090149", 
		"question": "24KwaYWz2Aqq440lEg7n1+3wJm6QDGRRgm2XW6B4dTGwB/KCZ+O++ZZjMxyxu3I7/XCGt631t3AAgbtP4JqKZCsMcNQtE2rWCyv0hWlEguTvXp7SlQ==", 
		"answer": "24G3KJT9wgz48sUlVBj7xvT6O3+QAmYcqnGKQbdmcWXqW6mCZ+O+yIdhKFWHmVZ+/GLV47H/t0AKnb5S6ouMMCMNest/x8OdxKq17ZRLzDV75j/KKXiDTWUUFg==", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNZ1Ehr3xPHsdXzZF2pRt3eGEqB7fmLqUKLQb/n3xpkxKFrJjld6+3vV46r2t2AsnOha54rfQxYQPoJhiNGZx+v+ymVMNshQicBm69oMeeZWxT6oZ5TMKPdiyy6NJkz+czi0Cnl6k3HXjnFfpoqo4TW6QNMhxVU3kIFx7sE5MtSGl+Ch7Uu9lAOM337RRLx8HF2StMCp/wO+r40z+O6F8QbT8bTdk+rW88oCdA0Sj5R2bVi1h6QM62o3V4iHfBNf9KTgbljkIzHqZSA/dg/A84vuWSS8+gdMZk4=", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "To define the rights of linguistic minority groups.", 
		"option_b": "To ensure efficient administration in appointments to services and posts.", 
		"option_c": "To provide equal justice and free legal aid.", 
		"option_d": "To promote co-operative societies.", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	},
	{
		"unique_id": "090150", 
		"question": "24KwYZL7kRj444wjXhuyyvu/IWPVQ0EerWyXW7dhZHjsWufSfOLzxoN0NBydhV474WbUpqT0t1wJz7xT7M63eSwHd8tjyd6OwuXwwTFAIIZF2o134JMKcbRPyn2obMTJJe19x2GOZ0P/dXmUCnR9lXbFyn9ZpZO05i6vUZo01Rkmg5V9soqeq1ye1tZzZsHQFuFRkn5L", 
		"answer": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNBxEH8oE772ZdR/EDG9oYxUxas=", 
		"explanation": "25SqfJjw3RyqpNBxEhv/1fX+JmLKBnFRt3eGEpZ6eX7tE7SCavjq0NdlKByZn1R2/WLD47H48hMcn7pe6IrffyRDVoJhzNnJ1ve3xTFMNsJNj40y65xfeexQ3ji+Z93ULr5owXzADkv0bjj6FzB3mzzGhW9fvIb79jK3QM8lxVt6pIJ+6No5MtSamaSS8ECxjQeM3W/RarJrGhm6vY6c40bchIsqsM6ZuCTetMTrk/bQ+c4HZxsSsIA/UE+9g61JyCU0WMutIVBuBaLNfrWZsOp1N3gIIq2G", 
		"topic_name": "Constitution & Political System >> Constitutional Framework >> Directive Principles of State Policy", 
		"difficulty_level": "1", 
		"option_a": "Article 350-A", 
		"option_b": "Article 39A", 
		"option_c": "Article 351", 
		"option_d": "Article 42", 
		"quiz_type": "mcq", 
		"syllabus_update": "null"
	}
]